(Episode 21)
(Born Again)
Shall I kill him now?
There were three people who went in,
but only two came out.
Kim Su Hyuk.
I knew this day would come.
Sung Ha,
I'll take your revenge
and bring Ma Chul back.
You won't die.
Not yet.
You still have things left to do.
- It's a cardiac arrest.
- 120 joules!
Shot!
Charging to 160 joules.
Make it 200.
It's ready, doctor.
Shot!
(January 25, 1988)
Come quickly.
I know that he is alive.
He'll be back in his time.
Sometimes, I meet people
who have seen Gong Ji Chul.
The prison officer in charge
of Gong Ji Chul...
kept the secret that he possessed
a fountain pen.
("Don't tell me that you know me.
I don't know you.")
("You, thou, happiness.
You, thou, love.")
("The fact that I'm alive is no more
than a rumor forever.")
Being an evil painter,
Gong Ji Chul...
did not regret his murder...
and was confident
at the execution ground.
The murder was...
his work of art.
(May 31, 1988)
Let's go visit your wife
at the hospital after this.
She will deliver a healthy baby.
Yes, she will.
Is this...
Lawyer Jang Hye Mi's house?
If you tell anyone that I'm alive...
you...
as well your family will die.
Do you believe Gong Ji Chul is
still alive somewhere?
Well.
I did write this book
but Gong Ji Chul is...
an evil being created by society.
All of it could be real...
or a fictitious novel
I have written.
People prefer to settle for a lie...
rather than see
the uncomfortable truth.
Should I read the next passage?
A woman helped Gong Ji Chul
to escape.
The woman supported Gong Ji Chul
who killed...
her stepfather who has raped her.
She was the woman of Gong Ji Chul.
Inside her,
Gong Ji Chul's baby was growing.
There's cash inside the book.
You will need it.
But must you go?
It'll be better for you to hide
for the time being.
You asked me to find out
where Jung Ha Eun is.
Open the last page in the book.
You can go to the place
that's written in the book.
It's the address of the hospital
in Samcheok.
(Won Nam Hospital, Jichul-dong
2090-11, Samcheok, Gangwon-do)
Then he went to fulfill
his last wish...
with the time he had left.
That last wish was revenge.
The detective who tormented him...
and his lover who testified
against him.
Gong Ji Chul thought...
the two should pay for their sins.
It's me, Jang Hye Mi.
You're being too cold
considering I'm your past lover.
By the way,
I saw Gong Ji Chul today...
whom you have executed.
You saw...
Gong Ji Chul?
April 7, 1979, was...
the day Gong Ji Chul committed
his first murder. Do you remember?
He hurt his back after falling...
while working
at a construction site.
He hovered between life and death
for two days in Suncheon hospital.
As I remember it,
the yellow umbrella case
that day was...
near Changsin-dong, Seoul.
It's funny.
I wonder how Gong Ji Chul who was
in bed in Suncheon Hospital...
went all the way to Seoul
to kill someone?
Didn't you even check
his hospital records?
What is it...
you want to say?
You should kill him properly
this time without mistake.
Once it's found Gong Ji Chul is not
the real culprit...
I will be in trouble too.
Just like you.
There is a large hospital
at the pier in Samcheok.
The name of the hospital is
Won Nam Hospital.
You can find him there.
I will keep...
my mouth shut forever.
Prosecutor.
You may go.
(Prosecutor Chun Seok Tae)
- Hello?
- Yes.
That thing. Your drug smuggling.
I'll take care of that,
but you owe me a favor.
- I need you to take care of him.
- How should I do it?
He's already executed.
He's already dead!
You're asking me how to take care
of a dead man?
(Won Nam Hospital, Jichul-dong
2090-11, Samcheok, Gangwon-do)
(Won Nam Hosptial)
Hey, remove that hood from him.
Organs aside, we'll have to see his
eyes to give them a grade.
Hey, what's the use of surviving?
Don't kill him. we need to take out
the heart while he's still alive.
(Cabin)
I stabbed a critical point.
No one saw how Gong Ji Chul died.
If he is still alive,
he will return...
to us at his time.
- It's a cardiac arrest.
- 120 joules!
- Shot!
- Charging to 164.
Make it 200.
It's ready, doctor.
Shot!
We have a pulse.
Get him ready for surgery.
I have to get into surgery
right away.
Are you his guardian?
What's his name?
His name...
I called his parents
so they'll be here any minute.
Wait.
I'll sign it.
I'm his mother.
I thought his heart stopped
just a while ago.
His brain won't deteriorate...
as aftermath, will it?
There's a bullet in his head.
We need to get it out through
operation before it hits the brain.
Are you saying his brain is
already messed up?
We can only see
how much damage was done...
after we open his skull.
If you can't guarantee that
the brain is not damaged...
I won't agree to the operation.
If you can't save him
without an operation...
I will move him to another hospital.
What are you doing?
- Who are you?
- Me?
I'm the one who saved your son.
I saved him once,
I'll save him again.
Why aren't you getting ready?
If he dies, all of you will too.
Let's move him.
(The Center Operating Room)
(Nice to meet you.)
The bullet was closer to the brain
than was shown on the CT scan...
so we couldn't take the bullet out.
We will just have to wait...
until the bullet moves away
from the brain.
- What about brain damage?
- Well,
the bullet is in the temporal lobe,
what we call the hippocampus.
We'll see after he wakes up...
but he may suffer
from light amnesia...
where he doesn't recognize
his friends and family.
Worst case scenario, he may show
signs of dementia or delirium.
What did you say?
Delirium?
Is his hippocampus damaged?
Wait.
If...
Jong Bum wakes up...
give him this.
Please.
Your son is in no shape
to go to America.
They don't know if he'll live.
Did you not see him hit
with a bullet?
Even a thug won't do this
to his family.
(Jong Woo)
Listen, son.
You should start drinking
the harp seal juice...
your brother was having.
You can only have nuts
as your snack.
You know I had you on the plane
on purpose, right?
You're an American citizen.
You don't need to compete
with beggars in this tiny land.
You know...
you'll be lonely if you don't do
extracurricular activities, right?
Let's start learning the cello.
Start to learn football.
So you can make friends in America.
(One year later)
Professor.
I think Jong Bum came back
from America.
What?
I saw him in Insa-dong yesterday.
That can't be.
I talked with his parents, he's
an exchange student in America.
I'm sure it was him.
But he seemed...
a bit changed.
He gave me the chills.
He looked kind of sick.
Jong Bum...
I love you.
Should we...
- be a family?
- Since I'm a criminal...
I guess we are family.
You kick the floor with one foot
when you're flustered.
You close your mouth and talk
with your eyes.
That's when you're worried.
(Did you really go to America?
I can't believe your family.)
(It's all my fault. Why aren't you
returning my calls?)
Jong Bum, are you in Korea?
Are you busy or are you sick?
Who is this?
Dad, why do you sound like that?
Didn't the pretty therapist
visit you today?
I'll be over there. We should
grab a drink.
(There is no signal.)
(Jung Sa Bin)
- Move it to this side...
- Look who it is.
It's Detective Rambo who got
suspended after the gun accident.
Start briefing.
A hiker found this early this dawn.
Her name is Kim Yi Su, aged 33.
This was found in a pile of dirt
under the tree...
where the body was found.
Forensics say it looks like
it came out from the body.
It's a heart transplant patient.
We'll have to undergo
a precise autopsy,
but from the dent in the skull
and the thyroid cartilage fracture,
it seems like this person was hit
with a dull object...
and strangled with something similar
to nylon wire.
Start the precision autopsy.
Yes, sir.
Let's see the umbrella.
The details are too vivid
to be called a copycat crime.
He's back, isn't he?
(Jung Sa Bin)
The victim's name is Kim Yi Su,
but why's it written as Jung Sa Bin?
Wait a minute.
The reason he didn't write
the date is...
maybe he's going to kill
Jung Sa Bin soon.
Dad,
why do you look so down today?
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
Who are you?
Hello,
I'm Han Hee Ji,
the new art therapist...
for Mr. Jung Sung Eun
since last month.
Are you his daughter?
Yes.
(The Magic of Color Psychology)
Don't you think your father's...
color yellow is a bit compulsive?
Other patients give off...
the energetic and positive
energy from yellow.
But your father is feeling
extreme anxiety and fear...
of the color yellow.
He has no other choice
but to feel that way.
He'll get better soon.
Don't worry too much.
Let's end our class here.
Let's have a meal sometime.
I'm so thankful that you're giving
my dad a private lesson.
Sure.
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
Aren't you going to check it?
It could be an urgent message.
I'm at the NFS
because of some remains we found.
Please call me.
Excuse me.
Good job, mister.
You'll have to do as I say
to save your daughter's life.
Did you get that?
Until when will you not answer
my calls?
Did you say you found some remains?
Let's meet and talk.
Okay.
I'll be back around seven.
(Chun Jong Bum)
Chun Jong Bum?
Who...
are you?
You said
Chun Jong Bum was dead.
He's dead for sure.
He was shot in the head.
He shed a lot of blood.
Who is this then?
Only Chun Jong Bum knows
this number.
If he's really dead,
bring me his corpse right now.
Weren't you...
dead yet?
She's about 167 cm tall,
weighing about 49 kg.
There's a fracture
on the right part.
I can see a microfracture
in a radial shape.
I think this person was hit
by something like a baseball bat.
The fracture was not
the immediate cause of death.
The cause of death is a fracture
on the thyroid cartilage.
Both tongue bones were fractured.
This was strangulation.
Sa Bin,
- what happened a year ago...
- I do not wish...
to talk about it.
It's a difficult memory
for me,
just like it is for you.
But your name was on the umbrella...
that was found next to the body.
My name?
Sa Bin,
you need to be protected.
I'll call the police
if I need protection.
If the suspect of the yellow
umbrella murder case is...
Chun Jong Bum,
why is this happening again?
Are you going to say
it's another copycat crime?
I don't hate you...
because you shot Chun Jong Bum
in the head.
It's because you insisted
it was Chun Jong Bum...
even when you knew
it wasn't him.
It's because you don't regret
the fact you shot a person.
I've been tracking
Chun Jong Bum's whereabouts...
while I was suspended for a year.
It was rumored
that he went to the States,
but after checking
his departure records,
there wasn't any record...
on him leaving the country.
I have nothing to say.
I told you.
I'm not going to lose
anyone close to me.
I don't care if you hate...
or avoid me.
I only need you...
to be alive,
just like you are now.
Can you turn up the lights?
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, we have a lot of lights.
Wait a minute. Turn it off again.
- Pardon?
- Turn it off again.
Yes, sir.
(Episode 22)
I will issue a warrant, so search
and confiscate Yuhon gallery.
Gang Du Chul has an accomplice.
Trail him and look for clues.
Gang Du Chul will need cash
before running away.
Wait at the ATM in front of Yuhon
and start following him.
That pervert is going inside
the bank before me now.
Yes, Kim Su Hyuk found out it's me.
Chun Jong Bum.
Why do you judge people and
give them a tag?
I don't think Jong Bum did that
to Detective Ju.
Are you going to say
it's a copycat crime again?
Lim Hwa Young murder case?
She confessed to me
while she was drunk...
that she killed her child.
He earnestly wants to change.
I'll try to be a normal person.
Is he really not the one?
(Jung Sa Bin)
The number you have dialed is
currently unavailable...
(The location cannot be found.)
Professor, it's Kim Su Hyuk.
is Sa Bin at the NFS right now?
Look at my hard work drawing
200 cuts in a frame.
Come on. Hurry up.
I will breathe into the dead
and he will resurrect.
Mr. John Doe. Show yourself
the way you were 30 years ago.
Make him resurrect holding
a walkie-talkie.
This is Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
They must look alike.
(Autopsy Room)
Put the book inside if you want
to give a memorial service...
to that detective.
In his next life, he can be born
like Gong Ji Chul.
Gong Ji Chul cherished that book
as if it was his life.
He was murdered
on the happiest day of his life.
That's why he did not decay.
He bought a ring he'll place
in his lover's fingers...
and was on his way to see her...
but died even before he met her.
It's 830403?
Is it the date of the wedding?
April 3, 1983.
It could be the first day he met
his bride.
Or a special anniversary.
(Old Future)
It's a keepsake found at the site
of the murder of Jung's parents.
So don't make a confession
on the first night.
It's not like he'll forgive you
if you did.
If Tess didn't confess her past
to Angel on the first night,
Angel would not have left Tess.
Then Tess would not have been
a murderer.
They didn't have to end up unhappy.
Doesn't it take courage
to confess your sin?
("Wuthering Heights"
by Emily Brontë)
Giving pressure to forgive
to someone who is hurt...
is making things harder
for him or her.
I would not confess if it were me.
So you're going to live on
carrying your sin?
No, the confession can be kept.
He can protect her by her side...
and risk his life once for her.
(Old Future)
It's snow.
April 3, 1983...
is the day it snowed in Spring.
I wanted to see the snow with you
for the rest of my life.
I, Cha Hyung Bin, will risk
my life...
and protect my bride,
Jung Ha Eun, until the end.
I've been meaning to ask you
why you look at me in that way.
How am I looking at you?
It's the way you'd see a lover
you broke up with.
To be honest, I trembled
from the first time I saw you.
Are you okay?
I was worried about you.
What happened? Where are you hurt?
- Ha Eun.
- Ha Eun?
Ha Eun, why am I lying here?
You're the one who's sick.
Prosecutor Kim, you are really sick
right now.
You can't even recognize me.
What are you talking about?
Of course I recognize you.
Which part of the holographic image
was so shocking?
You can't even remember my name,
Jung Sa Bin.
Jung Sa Bin?
Who's Ha Eun?
Who is she?
Are you really...
Wait here. I'll bring the doctor.
(Gu Hyul Ki)
Sir.
Hello?
Did you hear
about Detective Ju waking up?
They say it's a miracle.
Detective Ju In Do?
- Where is he?
- What?
Do you not remember?
He's in room 407 at Insung Hospital.
(Patient: Ju In Do.)
In Do, what happened?
Prosecutor Kim?
It's me, Hyung Bin.
Cha Hyung Bin.
Is this the underworld?
Or is he a ghost?
Is that what this is?
Sir, I'm in no mood to joke around.
- In Do.
- Just stop it.
What happened to
the Hwasung serial murder case?
That culprit was caught.
Then what about Gong Ji Chul?
What happened to him?
Gong Ji Chul?
He was executed a long time ago.
Stop joking around!
The year 2021.
In Do,
you know what happened to me, right?
Detective Cha, you died...
Wait.
What's the name of the bookstore
where Ha Eun worked?
What is it?
"Old Future."
In Do, do you have the cab fee?
What are you?
Who are you?
Where are you headed?
Let's go to Chunggyecheon.
Please put on your seat belt.
Just a moment, doctor.
(The NFS Jung Sa Bin)
(Old Future)
Open it.
Read it.
Who's Sung Ha?
Seo Sung Ha.
He's my only brother.
You reminded me of him when
we first met at the school.
He was killed by Su Hyuk as well.
That letter was...
sent to me a week before
he killed himself in prison.
Try to count...
how many times he wrote that
he wants to live again.
It's 332 times.
Kim Su Hyuk that son of gun.
My brother never killed anyone.
But he got locked up
for manslaughter because of Su Hyuk.
I don't need to tell you about
Su Hyuk anymore, right?
You've heard enough
over the past year.
If you get in this house today,
he won't be able to touch you.
The man who shot you in the head...
as long as we are alive,
he's done for.
Also,
that's the only reason I saved you.
So...
what do I need to do?
Just stay put...
in that house.
It's not revenge just to stab him
with a knife.
Stab him with your words,
it hurts more.
You're not their family.
You're my family who shares food.
Remember that.
You have everything.
Nice house, money,
brain, talent, and looks.
You need to have everything.
Get it all.
You're the owner of this house,
got that?
Also, I picked me up a reporter.
Chun Seok Tae won't treat you
badly anymore.
Pick up, not pick me up.
The doctor said...
that your unconscious mind
remembers everything.
If you don't remember anything...
just follow your instincts.
(Mobile phone)
- Hello?
- Is this Chief Prosecutor Chun?
Who is this?
How did you find my number?
I'm reporter Na Eun Sung with
the Jeil Newspaper.
We've got some information.
I heard that your son is on death
bed after being shot by thugs.
Is this true?
We already have a headline for that.
"A heartless father
and his lowly son."
"Chun Seok Tae who faces a promotion
as public prosecutor general."
If you want to continue
being a reporter...
stop making up rumors...
and start learning
how to check facts.
Where on earth is he?
Mom.
He's here.
Didn't you say he was in the States?
Your unconscious mind remembers
everything.
If you don't remember anything...
just follow your instincts.
Jong Bum.
How did you get here?
You didn't go to the States.
Where were you staying?
How have you been?
I'm healthy now.
You lived in a wealthy family
for 23 years.
Has your appetite changed?
Jong Bum,
you didn't like the smell
of cucumber.
What happened to Jong Bum's school?
We processed it as if he went
for an exchange program.
You can attend lectures
starting next week.
I almost forgot, Jong Bum.
Do you remember
that your dad will be appointed...
as the public prosecutor general
next week?
Since Jong Bum is here,
we should take a family photo
this weekend.
We're a perfect family now.
At least pretend to play the part
if you don't want to.
There will be a family interview.
Yes, father.
Make a credit card for Jong Bum.
Don't make him work
any part-time jobs.
We need to be alert...
for a month from now.
Be polite...
to your brother, Jong Woo.
You don't need to go abroad,
Jong Woo.
It's too hard for you to pass
the TOEFL test.
Is it that difficult
to get a score above 80?
I can learn English from Jong Bum.
Is that okay,
- Jong Bum?
- You might be...
better than me.
Let's get you a car, Jong Bum.
Stop riding motorbikes.
I never liked it.
Okay, I'll do that.
Jong Bum,
you and I should have a talk.
Tell me...
where you have been and with whom.
I don't remember.
Even after
Detective Kim Su Hyuk got...
suspended
after the gunfire accident,
he still went looking for you.
Your mom said
you went to the States,
but there wasn't any record
of departure.
Where were you with whom?
I wouldn't want to tell you
even if I remember it...
because it's scary
when you shout like that.
Do you remember this?
You can leave now.
I have somewhere I need to go.
Why, you...
Okay.
I'll let the driver know.
You can go now.
Where should I take you?
"Old Future."
Pardon?
Please go to the old book store...
in Cheonggyecheon.
I'll go to Cheonggyecheon.
Please stop the car.
(Born Again)
The connecting link between 1987
and the present is the painting.
Did you come back to life?
It's been a while, Gong Ji Chul.
I apologize.
It seems like everything happened
because of me.
- Oh, my!
- How did you survive?
It's because I didn't get
to tell her I love her.
Are you still doubting him
as the suspect?
Cha Hyung Bin,
why can't you recognize me?
We'll be together from now on.
It's not over yet.
I'm going to make him
confess his crimes on his own.
Today's the day you die
for the second time.