(Episode 23)
If everything in this world
disappeared but you,
I'm going to keep on living.
Whatever our souls are made of...
Your soul is the same as mine.
I'll be your lover forever.
You can get married to someone else.
I don't want you
to embrace this body.
I want you to embrace my soul.
That's not how I feel.
Just watching you makes me happy.
This place is
as if time has stopped.
Why don't you pick a book,
Prosecutor?
I'll buy you one today.
Can I also do an experiment?
Sa Bin.
Jung Sa Bin.
Ha Eun.
Please save Ha Eun.
I haven't...
kept my promise yet.
Please stop the car.
(We buy and sell old books.)
Don't die.
I'll get you a heart.
My promise is not...
over yet.
(An unfinished promise)
Could you tell me
where Kim Su Hyuk went?
Mr. Kim just asked me
where Mr. Ju In Do's room is.
Everyone knows Detective Ju
as he is a long-stay patient.
I see. In which ward is
Detective Ju staying?
Excuse me. Detective Ju?
It can't be.
Did you also come back to life?
Do you remember the owner
of this bookstore 30 years ago?
Yes.
Can you take a look at this?
Yes, this is her.
She's my friend's daughter.
Her name was Ha Eun.
You said you went
to Ha Eun's funeral.
Could you tell me
where she was buried?
It was a natural burial site.
My wife would know well about this.
Please call me when you remember.
Do you know the man
who just left the bookstore?
Right now? Do you know him?
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
010-1730-3033)
Thank you.
Is the name of the man
who shot Chun Jong Bum...
Kim Su Hyuk?
Where are you?
I'll tell you in person.
I'll be at the old bookstore
at Cheonggyecheon.
(The NFS Jung Sa Bin)
You had me worried.
Why did you leave
without telling me?
Your voice is the same.
Sorry?
It's nothing.
You won't have any money since
you left your jacket and wallet.
Wait for me. I'm going
to the bookstore to meet you.
How do you know
I'm at the bookstore?
I heard it from Detective Ju.
He said you went to "Old Future."
Did a suspect go there?
It never hurt this bad
since I had a heart transplant.
What's wrong with me?
- Are you okay?
- That's what I want to ask you.
Are you okay?
Take a good look
at Kim Su Hyuk.
He's my enemy and also yours.
The reason I saved you is
because of him.
The bullet in your head...
will prove that he is a prosecutor
who tried to kill a man.
Jung Ha Eun.
Jung Ha Eun?
Are the hearts of lovers connected?
At the same time
that I feel pain in my heart,
he will feel pain too.
It's not his mind that hurts, but
like a knife is stuck in his chest.
That's where he feels pain.
Ji Chul.
Gong Ji Chul.
(One year ago)
Let me ask you again.
What's your name?
Gong Ji Chul.
When were you born?
1961.
I was born in 1961.
On June 14th.
What year is it now?
1987.
And I died...
next year.
I think his sense of time
is disrupted due to the bullet.
He lost all his recent memory...
and only his old memories remain.
But...
his name isn't Gong Ji Chul.
It's Chun Jong Bum.
Also, he was born in 1998,
so why would he talk about 1987?
Do you remember anyone?
Someone I remember...
Let's do a different test
on him today.
What are you doing?
We're checking his brain signal.
He seems to have a strong memory
related to a snowfield.
Snowfield?
The reason I was born again is...
Jung Ha Eun.
("Secrets of a murderer")
(The serial killer Gong Ji Chul's
last victim was a detective.)
You need to come back right away,
if you feel nausea...
or have problems
with your sense of space.
If the bullet in your brain moves,
you can die any minute.
The tenth victim...
of the yellow umbrella serial
murder case who was killed in 1987.
Her name was Cho Yoon Hee.
One of them killed her
and the other gave her a funeral.
No.
One of them killed...
and the other one drew.
Gong Ji Chul's last target was
Ha Eun.
If that's the case again...
She must be
a heart transfer patient.
The details are too accurate
for this to be a copycat crime.
(Yoon Jung Hee, 1987
Kim Hee Soo, ?)
(Jung Sa Bin)
The third victim of the recent
yellow umbrella case, Kim Hee Soo.
The one who killed her...
and the one who drew her.
The one who killed her is
now after Jung Sa Bin.
The link between 1987...
and now is the painting.
If I follow the painting...
I'll find the culprit.
Let's go.
Why won't this come out?
I told you to take care
of this sooner.
What is that?
Take a look.
Isn't that the bones of
the dead man?
Oh, my.
What is it?
Find out where Doo Chul stores
his paintings.
I'll issue a search warrant.
(Morning Sea Burial Forest, 68-3,
Euiyin-dong, Namseo-gu, Gyeonggi-do)
(Old Future)
(The NFS Jung Sa Bin)
The caller cannot be reached
at the moment.
(Autopsy for the remain
discovered...)
(in nearby East Sea will
be conducted.)
The skeleton believed to belong...
to an adult was found
hanging in a net...
at a fishing warehouse
near Gangwon-do this morning.
While working on the net
to go fishing,
fishermen found the remains
and reported them to the police.
The police have searched the area
and other nets...
and collected belongings
and 130 pieces of skeleton.
But the cause of death and the man's
identity will take days to find out.
The police will request an autopsy
to the NFS...
and they will also look for
any connections to a criminal case.
I'll be going to school.
Wait.
I have something for you.
I can't drive.
What are you saying?
You got your license as soon
as you graduated high school.
This card has no limits.
You can use this
to maintain your class.
I'm...
so happy that you came back,
Jong Bum.
Why?
Do you not like the car?
No way. I love it.
If you don't remember anything,
just follow your instincts.
Chun Jong Bum.
Have you really ignored...
my messages even when you
came back to Korea?
Why are you making me upset?
I'm so relieved.
I really am.
Why, you...
How are you feeling?
Why aren't you answering?
I asked if you were okay.
Were you...
really worried...
about me?
Your first class is my lecture,
isn't it? Let's go.
All the remains of 137 children
found in Peru were found...
with their hearts cut out.
The children had been offered
as religious sacrifices...
of the Indian Chimu tribe
in northern Peru in 1450.
It was popular
to extract the hearts then...
so they won't come back to life.
In ancient times
where they believed in resurrection,
they believed that people wouldn't
come back to life without the heart.
("Resurrection" by Katyusha)
Resurrection may seem
like nonsense these days,
but there are cases of resurrection
in the present time.
Shall we end today's lesson here?
Remember to submit your reports
by next week.
I look forward to your reports
on the virtual autopsy.
You need to also submit
what you've been up to.
Hello?
There was a request for the autopsy
of some remains...
found in the East Sea.
- Did you get the message?
- Yes. I'll be on my way right now.
Wait a minute.
Do you have time today?
You still have one more
observation practice left.
Let's consider today
as your final one.
Today is the autopsy
of a death-row convict.
A death-row convict?
What's an observation practice?
You can stop that if you're joking.
It's not funny.
Do you want to have lunch
after the autopsy?
Sounds good.
It's my treat.
What would you like to have?
The older person has
to buy a meal.
Did you buy a car?
What happened to your motorbike?
I don't normally...
ride motorbikes.
Get in.
Jong Bum.
How's your head?
Are there any problems?
I'm fine.
Jong Bum,
I've been worried about you.
I couldn't sleep or eat well.
- Why not?
- I would like...
to apologize on behalf
of Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk...
about what happened...
that day.
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk?
Why are you apologizing
instead of him?
I just...
wanted to.
I feel like everything happened
all because of me.
The person is a male
with a frame of an adult.
His bone density is lower
than that of an average person.
His teeth show
he had a nutritional deficiency.
The right tibia, the left, and right
hip bones seem irregular.
This is the prisoner's number
found with the bones.
The ink has just been restored.
The number has already been passed
to the prosecutor for review.
We'll find his identity soon.
Okay.
Ribs.
Clavicle.
There is also an irregularity
on the lower jaw bone.
It seems they were all fractured
during his youth,
but he has never received
a single treatment.
It seems he had been abused.
He has a diagonal scar
on his orbital bone.
Was he stabbed with a knife?
It wasn't a knife.
- It's probably scissors.
- How do you know that?
I just know it.
The attacker probably didn't
mean to kill him.
If it was meant to kill him,
the attacker would've stabbed
his vital points.
It was meant to give him pain.
I said stop crying!
Die!
If he was a death-row convict,
why did he die...
by the sea?
It's because he had to meet...
the person he loved.
If he could only meet the woman,
he would've risked his life...
no matter what.
That death-row convict...
must've struggled to live...
even while he was dying.
It's because he never got...
to tell her he loved her.
You talk as if it's about you.
Did you find a way
to connect with the bones?
I'll show you...
that I'm not an animal,
including who the real murderer was.
(PRosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
I'll finish up the autopsy.
Can you wait for me outside?
All right, professor.
But why don't you call me
by my name anymore?
Your name?
Right. Sa Bin.
The caller is not available
at the moment.
(The NFS Jung Sa Bin)
(Morning Sea Burial Forest, 68-3,
Euiyin-dong, Namseo-gu, Gyeonggi-do)
(Episode 24)
Chun Jong Bum.
Kim Su Hyuk.
He's the one who shot
the bullet in your head.
How come...
How did you make it alive?
You look like you're not happy
I'm alive.
Can I ask you...
- why you shot me?
- Why?
Right.
It's because you tried
to kill Sa Bin.
You think I'd kill Sa Bin?
You still treat me
like I'm a murderer.
Aren't you?
The only one I killed is...
Yoon Jeong Yi.
Yoon Jeong Yi?
December 14, 1987.
Yoon Jeong Yi.
She's the 11th victim.
Cha Hyung Bin.
Look straight in my eyes.
I recognize you...
so why can't you?
The killer 32 years ago was...
Gong In Woo.
If you want to find out the truth,
get Gong In Woo.
Gong In Woo?
How do you know about him?
Stop right there.
Who are you?
Do you still think Jong Bum is
the culprit?
This has nothing to do with you,
Sa Bin.
Let's talk later, Prosecutor Kim.
Wait a minute.
Do you have something left
to say to Jong Bum?
I found the place where Gang Du Chul
keeps the paintings.
But someone is here.
Why did you come here
when you haven't recovered yet?
Are you really Detective Cha?
Tell me the name of the criminal
we first arrested.
It's Park Sang Moon, a serial killer
who raped women.
My gosh.
What was the name of the rice soup
place in front of our station?
Let's go in.
See? You're not Detective Cha.
It's "Grandmother's Rice Soup."
You dated the second daughter
of that restaurant.
Goodness.
Were you a detective
before you were a prosecutor?
When was this?
It's way before you were born.
Wait a minute.
Then take this.
Here.
You can eat this, each of you.
We used to always eat this
before arresting the criminal.
A total of 30 pieces from Yuhon
gallery are being stored here.
And 11 of them are a private
collection of Gang Du Chul.
From here all the way to there...
are the pieces from Yuhon gallery.
Please take your time
to look around.
I brought the blue flashlight
with me.
How come we're not getting anything,
Detective Cha?
Let me see.
These paintings...
were disposed of after Ji Chul was
executed.
How is it they're here?
Why does Gang Du Chul have
Gong Ji Chul's paintings?
By the way, I always wondered...
how Gong Ji Chul could
paint these...
when he was a middle school dropout.
The killer 32 years ago was
Gong In Woo.
If you want to find out the truth,
get Gong In Woo.
- Go and trail Gang Du Chul.
- Yes, sir.
Detective Cha.
There's something
I need to tell you.
The person who stabbed me
with an umbrella in the gallery...
is a woman.
- A woman?
- Yes.
It wasn't a man, but a woman.
Do you have something left
to say to Jong Bum?
Where would you like to go?
Do you want to go to the place
where we first met?
The place where we first met?
It's where you tried to sell
your book at a secondhand price.
Where is that?
I can't remember it well.
You'll remember when you get there.
You scribbled on the book
with a fountain pen.
I'm only telling you now,
but you were very memorable.
You were quite dashing.
("The eye...")
("The eye shall see
for the last time.")
I guess I like to scribble
with a fountain pen.
So where is this place?
Well, it's...
Go straight for now.
I'd like to ask you something.
When I was shot in the head,
why were you in that place?
I want to hear
about what happened that day.
I want to hear it from you,
not anyone else, Sa Bin.
I got a text message.
It said you might commit murder.
Did I try to kill you?
No.
You tried to save me.
(This month's best-seller)
This book is about Gong Ji Chul
as a serial killer.
Gong Ji Chul is the first person
my dad executed as a prison officer.
A prison officer?
What is the name of your father?
My dad?
It's Jung Sung Eun.
Jung Sung Eun?
I sometimes wonder...
whether Gong Ji Chul could
get redemption.
He'd want to.
Gong Ji Chul is also a human being.
But do you think Gong Ji Chul
in this book...
is who he really is?
Sorry?
He could've been a death-row convict
who was falsely accused.
The dead can't talk about it...
just like the remains
of that death-row convict.
You're right.
There might be death-row convicts
who were falsely accused...
but Gong Ji Chul is not one of them.
He's an evil one my dad witnessed
with his own eyes.
An evil?
The remains of the death-row convict
can't be identified by the police.
Hold on.
Jae Yi, can we restore a face?
Who is it this time?
It's an unidentified
death-row convict.
A death-row convict? Okay.
- Let's meet at the autopsy lab.
- I'll be there.
It seems like I have to go back
to the NFS.
I'll give you a ride.
Do you know the address
of Jang Hye Mi?
The author of
"Secrets of a murderer".
Of course, but why do you need it?
I have something to tell her
that I've held for 30 years.
It's 28-1, Jangan-ro,
Jung-Gu, Seoul.
("Secrets of a murderer")
You're amazing.
People will think...
you lost weight
after going through so much...
with my engagement falling apart.
Will my going through your hardship
with you...
change your engagement?
Maybe you should use this chance
to lose a few kilos.
What brings you here without notice?
I heard you went to America.
Were you in Korea?
Sang Ah, go to your room.
He's my guest.
Have a seat.
Do you want some tea?
Why did you lie to me?
Your tone got rough.
The one who killed
all the women...
was Gong In Woo.
Gong In Woo...
You can't ever know that name,
Jong Bum.
Where did you hear that from?
Tell me. Why did you lie to me?
I don't know.
A piece of writing is always between
reality and fiction.
Could you tell me?
From where to where...
do you think is a lie?
That address you gave me
32 years ago.
The hospital that Ha Eun
was supposed to be in.
That wasn't where Ha Eun was.
That was where I was going to die.
Your eyes...
are not Jong Bum's.
His eyes are closed.
I can't read any emotion from them.
But your eyes are...
like those of an untamed animal.
I tend to...
believe in those that the human
intellect cannot understand.
And the person in front of me is...
quite interesting.
Long time no see, Ji Chul.
You wouldn't have met her anyway.
The one you were trying to see,
Jung Ha Eun.
She was already dead back then.
What?
She was dead?
Do you know where
your stepfather is buried?
Because I do.
I was there.
I was there when In Woo killed
your stepfather.
Do you want his body to come out?
Then the world would know
that it was...
Jang Hye Mi who helped
Gong In Woo commit a murder.
Then your book will be...
used as proof of your sin.
It was a woman who helped
Ji Chul escape.
That woman...
worshipped Ji Chul who killed
her stepfather,
who had been raping her.
Why...
did you come to me?
Bring Gong In Woo to me.
Right now.
If you ignore me...
you'll see your stepfather...
on the news.
Who will believe...
that a 23-year-old medical student
is a witness to a murder...
that happened 32 years ago?
What do you think I found...
where your stepfather was buried?
Bring Gong In Woo to me.
("Secrets of a murderer")
That woman was Ji Chul's woman.
In her stomach...
the child of Ji Chul was growing.
Then the world would know
that it was...
Jang Hye Mi who helped
Gong In Woo commit a murder.
Then your book will be...
used as proof of your sin.
Sir.
There's someone you have to meet.
You'll have to come in.
Yes, I'll meet you there.
Tomorrow, 10 p.m. Yuhon Gallery.
You'll meet Gong In Woo there.
You have a twisted destiny too.
(Tomorrow, 10 p.m. Yuhon Gallery.
You'll meet Gong In Woo there.)
Even though he was a death-row
convict, I'm sure he had a family.
No, this man was...
abused as a child.
There might not be anyone
looking for him.
Do we have to restore his face?
When there's no one looking for him.
I want to at least put his face
on his urn.
At least I could remember him.
This death-row convict.
I found the owner of
the Donggang mummy's ring.
A natural burial site?
It would've been better if they
had met when they were alive.
I'll bring the ring.
It's the day that Donggang mummy
gets married.
It's his wedding date,
and I hope the weather will be nice.
(Please bury Hyung Bin here with me
when his body is found.)
(Jung Ha Eun)
Please bury Hyung Bin here with me
when his body is found.
Ha Eun.
I came here too late, didn't I?
I'm so sorry it took a while.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It looks like
you're the one getting married.
Prosecutor Kim,
what's the matter?
Did you bring the ring?
Yes.
April 3, 1983 was the date...
when they first met.
Pardon?
How do you know that?
They found...
each other at last, didn't they?
They'll be together from now on.
They won't be separated.
He must've wanted to keep
his promise to his loved one.
That's why his body didn't rot
as he was waiting...
for her to reach out to him.
Sir,
the pervert Gang Du Chul is
finally on the move.
He's picking someone up
from the Incheon Port.
Stick close to him. I'm on my way.
He's on his way.
I've got something to ask.
What are you planning to do...
when you meet your father?
I'm going to wash away my sins.
How?
I'll make him...
confess his own sins.
Gong Ji Chul.
Today is the day you're dying
for the second time.
I'm chasing after him,
but this is the way
to the Yuhon Gallery.
How does the fellow passenger
look like?
I can't see it
because it's dark inside the car.
Stick close to them.
(Chun Jong Bum)
I don't have any time
to deal with you right now.
Come see Gong In Woo for yourself...
at 11 o'clock in Yuhon Gallery.
I lost Gang Du Chul.
I found him.
(Born Again)
What's your relationship
with Gong In Woo?
Just be evil by yourself.
Why are you bringing me
into this?
Am I the next target
after Gong In Woo?
What's the secret of the real killer
that you missed in your book?
Remember that I'm the only one
who can reveal...
that you're not the killer.
I restored the death-row convict's
remains. Don't they look alike?
I only realized it today
that the deity gave me a chance.
I'll say it one by one,
but only to Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
I had a nightmare
that you were shot again.
My head is hurting so much.
Can you come?