(Episode 19)
Mr. John Doe came from the earth,
so the earth will give us an answer,
wouldn't it?
That's right.
Let's get started.
Scalpel.
The eyelids should be deeper.
- Deeper.
- Wait a minute.
The skin should be thinner
on this side.
Deeper.
Sa Bin, I'm going to
start mapping now.
It's really tough to map someone
who I've never seen before.
It's not just about the genes,
I have to use all my senses.
Do you think we've never seen...
this face before?
Eyes that match those nose
and skin white as snow.
How about his pupils?
The iris that draws you in like
a black hole, right?
- Okay.
- And...
as for the hair,
- we won't wear it back like this...
- Okay.
but put it down like this.
- Put the hair down?
- Yes.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
Put the hair down.
I think this man...
would've worn a uniform.
A uniform?
What are you talking about?
He'd look so good...
holding a walkie-talkie.
I feel like...
I've seen him somewhere before.
(Revenge: Getting even
with what you have suffered)
What is difficult for you...
will be too easy...
for someone.
Please go inside.
I'll be going now. Drive safe.
Wait a minute.
I can't send you
a wedding invitation...
since I...
called the marriage off.
His marriage is off?
Why?
Could it possibly be...
because of me?
- It's because of me?
- What is?
I saw you guys on the way home.
What's that weird vibe...
- between you and Prosecutor Kim?
- He is not...
getting married.
He had a girlfriend?
If you say it's because of you,
does it mean he likes you?
Is it because of the experiment?
So that experiment was...
the problem.
Hey, take your medicine.
Come on. Drink your water.
Oh, gosh. What is this?
Oh, my gosh! It's blood.
It's blood everywhere!
It's specially made.
It's an arrowhead made
with titanium alloy.
It's practically
a well-sharpened dagger.
Since he survived after being
stabbed 11 times with this,
Detective Ju's lifeline must
be long indeed.
Did you get Detective Ju's phone?
The memory chip has been shattered
so it'll take time to restore it.
What about the CCTV near the post?
There was no CCTV
since it's a residential area.
There was video footage taken
by a car that's always parked there.
Look at that perverted scumbag.
Does he want to be found?
Who entered the gallery before
and after the murder?
A man was caught on camera
in front of Yuhon.
Chun Jong Bum.
His motorbike was caught on camera
from the street nearby.
But he's also the one
who reported it.
Then he's a strong suspect.
He really likes going alone,
doesn't he?
(Yuhon Gallery)
Yes.
We got a written statement from a
witness in Chief Prosecutor's order.
We looked into a car that chased
after Chun Jong Bum's bike.
It is owned by Gang Du Chul.
The funny thing is that the owner
of Yuhon is also Gang Du Chul.
The statement says Jong Bum is
a fan of Gang Du Chul's paintings.
It's fishy, isn't it?
He offered a place to kill a man
and change the painting.
I can see they are accomplices.
Look into Gang Du Chul.
Detective Ju arrived at the gallery
at 9:20 p.m.
Chun Jong Bum entered the gallery
at 9:27 p.m.
Detective texted me at 9:38 p.m.
Chun Jong Bum reported it
outside the gallery...
at 9:45 p.m.
The painting Gong Ji Chul drew is
hung here.
It's the painting he drew
after killing a woman.
Do you think you're the only one
in danger?
Isn't there anyone that you want
to protect?
(Chief Prosecutor Chun Seok Tae)
You're slow to summon Baek In Seo
for the investigation.
So why would you dig
into something useless?
Hand over the case of Detective Ju
over to Prosecutor Shin Hyeong Jin.
You'll no longer be in charge.
It's a revenge killing
of the detective who suspected him.
He confirmed that he is
the criminal through the camera.
I think you'd know
who the suspect is.
Revenge killing?
Be careful of your words.
Who killed who?
No one's dead.
I'll stick with this case
until the end.
Hey.
Do you want to go
to the Criminal Trial Department?
Do you want to see the trash
that you put in jail...
be released through a petition
before your eyes?
You should swing your sword
carefully while you have it.
You need the power to set things up,
which you like so much.
And you can set it up
within your ground.
Who do you think you're talking to?
So you're going to slip away again?
Hello, uncle.
Forget fried chicken, the only way
to cook it properly is to boil it.
I was also healed after eating
chicken soup after being stabbed.
Hurry over here.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
I knew it. You couldn't
find that bookstore.
- I did go there.
- You were there?
- Why didn't you...
- You were with him.
Su Hyuk.
Did you see us yesterday?
- At the Old Future...
- I saw you kissing him.
You always kick the ground with one
foot pointed up when flustered.
You close your mouth and speak
with your eyes.
That look is when you're worried.
Your muscles above your eyebrows
show strong movements,
your pupils are dilated and you
shake your head a few times firmly.
- That's when you're angry.
- Me?
I always wondered what face you
made in front of someone you liked.
Jong Bum, I have something
to tell you.
I like Su Hyuk.
I've never liked a man this much.
Also, just as you don't change...
my emotions won't change either.
Do you think he'll be
able to protect you?
We'll see who can protect you.
I have reports to submit,
I'll be going now.
I also like chicken soup.
He was blocking me
from entering your heart.
I needed to kill him.
This is the first time I wanted
to kill someone for love.
Do you want to go
on a date with me?
Where are you?
Here.
That was the face.
Will I be able to have her?
This is a date, right?
You can only go on dates
if you're alive.
When you shoot a gun,
stand at shoulder width,
grab the gun not at the bottom,
make sure you grab the handle.
Keep your eyes fixed at the front.
Try holding it.
- These aren't real, are they?
- They're real bullets.
Now, try shooting the gun.
You should move.
I've shot plenty
of toy guns in my past.
That surprised me.
- Try it again.
- Okay, here I go.
Again.
I'll do it again.
My fights are usually done
with these in hand,
I don't fight with parking tickets.
Just by holding these,
someone can get hurt.
If I don't use them right,
either I...
or the person next to me will die.
Did you always like shooting?
I've never seen you more focused.
When I shoot 10 bullets,
I always miss the last 2.
I miss the first bullet because it
reminds me of my father's last look,
and I miss the second...
because it reminds me of my face
when I couldn't protect my father.
Did your father pass away?
He looked a lot like you.
That face, the trusting face.
That's why looking at you makes me
both worried and angry.
So I have to protect you
no matter what.
I...
won't be a scar to you...
like your father was.
I promise you.
My mom told me...
only death is a perfect possession.
You won't change, will you?
That's the only reason
I'm not killing you.
I took care of it.
The photos on his phone...
will be sent to your laptop.
You got the laptop, right?
Look what we have here.
We keep bumping into each other.
Why are you laughing?
(Power off)
What are you doing?
Come out quickly.
It's getting cold.
Handsome men like Jong Bum don't...
have any dating techniques.
Do you know why?
It's because the girls just line up
and wait for their turn.
So that makes me think...
that you've never had
any real relationships, have you?
Men should not be naive.
They need to be a little spicy
to make the girls cry.
He only talks about women
every time he opens his mouth.
Your relationships are not real.
You only took advantage of them.
He's too old now
for girls to notice.
You're making fun of me
when you look like a fish.
Jong Bum,
you should never date
someone who is...
well aware of their good appearance.
Wounds on the body may disappear,
but wounds in the heart...
cannot be erased even with a laser.
You got that?
Look at these uncles.
You only gave me the rice crush,
and you gave Jong Bum chicken.
You can only see Jong Bum
and not me.
It's been two days since you got out
of the hospital. You can't drink.
Let me have just one drink.
It's healthy if you drink happily.
My superior
from my baseball club is coming.
I'm sorry,
but I think I'll have to go.
You're the chef,
yet you've become a heavy drinker.
Go and work.
Geez.
By the way, Jong Bum,
don't let Sa Bin fall asleep.
She knows it's not good,
but she drinks little by little...
and falls asleep flat on her face.
That's our lifelong problem.
You looked happy.
That was the happiest look
I've seen...
ever since I've met Jung Sa Bin
as a person.
She had gotten a heart transplant.
Her uncles are ex-convicts,
and her father is sick.
She didn't have a mother
since she was born.
That means...
you too can become happy.
You only need to see
what you have right now.
What I have...
Unhappy people only wish
for things that cannot come true.
Do I look unhappy?
You wish to forget your past,
but you're not removing it
from yourself.
If you have nowhere to throw it out,
throw it at me.
What do you mean?
Can you tell me what happened...
when you were 15?
Jong Bum.
They say those people infected
with evil...
have their first moments.
I only thought you didn't like me.
But I realized it
after observing you.
You just can't feel any emotion.
Your emotionless face was not
apathy,
but you just didn't feel it at all.
My heart is hurting so much,
but you couldn't feel anything.
You fool.
You're stupid.
That was when I realized...
that I was different
from other people.
I believed in the world after death.
During those three days,
I thought she might be able...
to live again miraculously.
After a while,
I started to paint unconsciously.
Why did you
admit to that murder?
It's because I knew...
murder gave me freedom.
No one is born a murderer
in this world.
Freedom?
You were scared back then.
You probably didn't have anyone
to talk about your fear.
There was probably no one...
to scold you for doing wrong.
Your brother tried to
make you eat detergent.
Your father didn't believe
that you weren't a murderer.
How about your mother?
Was she different?
No one in your family...
came looking for you,
except your brother...
who tried to feed you detergent.
Do you want to become a family?
A family?
A family that will take your side
and scold you when you're wrong.
If I'm your family,
all my uncles are your family too.
I'm an ex-convict too,
so I guess we are family.
Then let's have a drink
to celebrate becoming a family.
Have a seat.
Here.
I've watched "Romeo and Juliet"
countless times.
I realized the reason
why Romeo killed himself...
after Juliet, whom he loved, died,
and why Juliet committed suicide...
after seeing Romeo,
who died because of her.
I only realized it by the time
I could memorize the book.
That I will never...
be able to feel that.
People call this love.
Your eyes feel hot,
your mouth begins to dry,
you become breathless,
and you become vulnerable.
We're so close,
yet I'm scared you'll disappear.
Don't be my family...
but my woman.
(Episode 20)
What is he doing out here
in the cold?
Jong Bum.
- Take responsibility.
- Sorry?
- I...
- You?
got a cold. You're responsible.
My gosh.
It's so cold.
Did Prosecutor Kim buy
that watch for you?
This one?
I'll take care of the rest.
Will you take the pots to uncles?
I'll do that.
You shouldn't soak this in water.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It won't go out of order
since it's a high-tech.
The memory chip of Detective Ju's
phone is severely damaged,
so we're trying
a partial restoration now.
Here. Can you hear this?
It's Detective Ju's voice.
- Yes.
- How about that of the culprit?
We need to do more analysis
of the voice.
This analysis system can track down
the component of the voice...
and figure out the age, gender,
and height of its owner.
It's like a composite sketch
of a voice.
We can contrast it with the voice
of the suspect.
- Give me a call when it's over.
- Yes, sir.
You look so familiar.
Could you put your hair down?
Won't you do it?
You are a friend of Jung Sa Bin.
Let me introduce myself. I'm Jae Yi.
I'm a 3D graphic designer...
- and restore through hologram...
- I'll see you next time.
Do you like Sa Bin?
If you do, I have something
to tell you.
What is it?
Sa Bin is being followed
by a stalker.
The way I see it, he's 90 percent
a psychopath.
He downloaded a tracking app
on her phone and stole her diary.
He watches over every move
Sa Bin makes.
Thank you. I'll return it as soon as
this lecture is over.
- Thank you.
Broken heart syndrome.
This is...
one of the syndromes...
that take place when you lose
the one you love.
A healthy heart will be
damaged drastically.
A heart has memory function,
which means the neurons
of a heart can remember.
There are many cells in the heart.
I can kill Jung Sa Bin,
and you can kill me.
But which one will happen first?
A heart has short-term
and long-term memory.
The neurons in the brain...
Jong Bum.
Chun Jong Bum.
What's with this flower?
And what about this card?
(Purple tulip. Eternal love
completed by death. Jong Bum.)
Do you have feelings for...
What's happening?
Jong Bum, help us.
Your body is too cold.
Chun Jong Bum!
It had a cardiac stimulant in it.
The component that is extracted
from a certain flower...
was found from the coffee.
A small amount can be critical
for people with heart disease.
They can get a heart attack.
But who sent it, if you didn't?
Someone brought the flower and card
while I wasn't here.
I don't know who it is,
but that person was after you.
If you finished your lecture,
I can take you home,
Sa Bin.
Sa Bin?
Anyway, you can go first.
I'll take Bo Hye to her house
when she wakes up.
I'll wait. I need to talk to you.
This is a watch.
It was broken because of me.
It's okay. I can get it repaired.
I don't think that's possible
because it's sensitive.
- Or I'll send you the repair costs.
- It's okay.
- I'll pick you up in the morning.
- That's not necessary.
I warned you to learn to feel...
- sorry for the one hurt by you.
- I told you too.
I'm not the type you can teach.
House, the hospital,
the NFS, and Body Heat.
Where are you going
to follow her next?
I need to tell Sa Bin...
what can be really dangerous.
You killed someone at 15 and became
a murder suspect at 23.
And you stand by the woman I like.
What could be more dangerous
than that?
I'll take care of my body.
Would you two go home now?
I need to get a rest.
- Please go in.
- You and I?
I have to check
whether no one's lurking around...
before I go.
But what is that?
Could I go in for a minute?
Would you give me a minute
to clean up?
I only need a place to sit.
I see.
Open it.
What did I have in my mind?
I'll tell you how to use each one.
This is a tear gas gun. Take it.
Please take it.
Well.
Tear gas gun, pepper spray,
self-defense rod, and a stun gun.
Do you want me to carry
those around?
A detective who's been investigating
Lim Hwa Young's case...
was stabbed wildly at a gallery.
And Chun Jong Bum was caught
on the camera in the gallery.
You never listen to me,
and he's always by your side.
I don't think Jong Bum did that...
- to Detective Ju In Do.
- What did you say?
I...
can even commune with a corpse.
I've seen what Jong Bum is like.
I was able to commune with him.
He goes between good and evil
numerous times in a day,
but he earnestly wants to change.
- I wouldn't believe he would...
- Even if he agonized for ten hours,
he only needs three seconds to cut
someone's carotid.
Regret and repent...
will not bring back the dead
over three seconds.
Chun Jong Bum killed someone
when he was 15.
Let's say he repented it.
But painting it means he is
ruminating murder.
He drew a picture
of the girl he killed.
He did that to remember.
Like a trophy.
It makes me shudder...
to think about him drawing you.
If you keep driving him
as a murderer,
he might end up like that one day.
If there's a moment that can stop
his memory of the murder,
it's now.
I'll make that happen.
My father trusted the words
of a murderer.
Just like you now.
Do you know the first thing he did
after his release?
It's murder.
Sa Bin, why...
If Jong Bum is a dangerous man,
the one in danger now is you,
not me.
I'll protect you.
And in order to do that,
I won't make him a murderer.
That's right. You'll watch her
through the night.
That's what a stalker does.
Why? Do you want to call it a crush?
You won't get a reduced sentence
for being a stalker.
Don't you think it's better to be
a stalker who protects his girl,
than a man who has no idea
who is putting her in danger?
His girl?
Who is your girl?
You just want to possess her.
What if she doesn't have feelings
for you?
Would you kill her?
I don't kill the one I love.
Is this what you call love?
You'll ruin a girl you love...
to have her to by your side forever.
Won't you?
Did you see it for yourself?
There's no way
Sa Bin will choose you.
She's my woman now. Got that?
Don't even look at her.
It's disgusting.
Why? You can't hold back?
Do you feel like you need
to kill someone today?
I told you my principle.
- Stay away from Sa Bin.
- Want to know my principle?
Once I decide to kill someone...
I won't stop...
until that person is dead.
You're finally showing
your true colors.
Fine, start by killing me.
Never forget that order
even if you really want...
to kill someone else.
I have something to ask you.
Would you say the same thing
if it wasn't me...
who was in love with her?
If a normal person watches over her
and can't give her up,
would you say the exact same
words you just said?
Normal people don't stalk
people they like.
You can try again if you're reborn.
As a normal person.
So I'm going to start trying
to be just that.
A normal person.
Want to know my principle?
Once I decide to kill someone...
I won't stop...
until that person is dead.
Once Detective Ju's
memory chip is restored,
compare it with the voice file
I send you.
What's happening? Jong Bum, help us.
It had a cardiac stimulant in it.
I changed the watch but do I still
get witness protection?
010 1237 9916.
That's the number for my new watch.
Please protect me until I get
used to protect myself.
There are five more USBs aside
from this one which includes...
the photos from your gallery.
Don't worry, I won't report
them to anyone.
I'm going to try to be
friends with you.
What changed?
I found out you were
dumped by Su Hyuk.
That triggered my interest, for you.
I have a question.
Are you trying to kill Sa Bin
because of Su Hyuk?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
I wouldn't want to kill her quickly
if it was because of Su Hyuk.
She needs to be hurt...
just as much, no, a bit more
than I was.
But if it was because of you...
I'd want to kill her right now.
It excites me.
How about this?
Let me invite you this time.
Don't you want to see
my first murder?
Are you serious?
Tonight at ten. I'll text you
the location.
Chun Jong Bum.
Jung Sa Bin.
(Songin Elementary School,
Kyunginbaek-ro 19-38, Jungsu-gu)
If you want to kill someone
in your head...
paint my face on top of the person
you want to kill.
If you still want to kill
that person...
imagine the bloody hands
that stabbed me as your own.
If Jong Bum kills someone, who will
be his first target?
Come to Songin Elementary
School in Seoul.
(A purple tulip. Eternal love
completed by death. Jong Bum.)
Darn it.
Take me to Songin Elementary School.
Your phones are all in
silent mode, right?
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
Wasn't this the invitation?
This is the only voice recovered
from Detective Ju's phone.
I compared it with the voice file
you sent me.
Once I decide to kill someone...
I won't stop...
until that person is dead.
The vocal spectrum match exactly.
They're the same person.
Should we go get him?
No, we can't make it official.
The person you have dialed...
You have a new message.
Su Hyuk, you're not at Songin
Elementary School, are you?
If not, that's great. Make sure
you never go there tonight.
Songin Elementary School.
He killed a female student and then
left her in an abandoned building.
What are you going to do
by yourself?
He'll escape us anyway.
People will die if he does that.
Do you want to see that?
Stay on standby until I call you.
Keep this a secret.
You're always up against the world
alone, who are you to keep a secret?
Let's go together.
It's me, Jong Bum.
- What is it?
- I caught the real culprit, Father.
You said you'd trust me...
if I caught the real culprit
behind the Lim Hwa Young case.
You caught the real culprit?
Yes.
I also have evidence.
I didn't kill her.
Then what about Detective Ju In Do?
Did you do it?
Are we starting...
a new misunderstanding?
Let's hang up.
(Where are you?)
Is that you, Jong Bum?
Don't kill anyone...
but only Jung Sa Bin.
I warned you.
I told you not to touch
my woman.
(Your last moment is not revenge
but sacrifice.)
What about me?
No!
Hyung Bin.
I once...
told you...
that souls will be resurrected.
Gong Ji Chul.
You'll never...
be resurrected.
I swear to the lord and to Ha Eun's
parents in up above.
I, Cha Hyung Bin, will risk
my life...
and protect my bride,
Jung Ha Eun,
until the end.
(Born Again)
There were 3 people who went in,
but only 2 came out.
If you can't guarantee
that there isn't any brain damage,
I won't agree to this surgery.
I know he's alive.
I saw Chun Jong Bum in Insa-dong.
I'm sure it was him.
It's me, Cha Hyung Bin.
Su Hyuk found out about it.
What's the name of the book store
of your wife?
Ha Eun.
You said Chun Jong Bum was dead.
Don't die yet.
We still have a lot to do.