(Episode 17)
The difference
between something real and fake...
is this blood.
A family?
How can you be part of his family
when you're not related?
Doing everything he wants...
is no different from a part-time job
running errands.
A real family does whatever it takes
for someone's happiness...
whether you want or not.
Sometimes I miss someone,
feel sorry, and sad...
all at the same time.
Regret is...
an emotion that a person can feel
only for the one he or she loves.
(Old Future)
(Emergency Center)
In one, two!
We'll stitch up her injury
right away.
As the knife was caught
in the shoulder blade,
it didn't lead to damage
in pleura or organs.
You don't have to be too concerned.
Could you sign
the surgery consent form?
(Representative: Kim Su Hyuk)
(Relationship with the patient:
Colleague)
I thought you were her husband.
Why did this happen?
(Sang Ah)
(Gu Hyul Ki)
I'm interrogating Jang Ma Chul now,
but this scumbag is saying
something weird.
(Operating room status)
(Surgery is in progress)
He says Chun Jong Bum told him
to kill you.
What is this about?
You two have visited this hospital
so many times.
I'll leave Ms. Jung with you.
Give me a call when she wakes up.
Don't you have...
many tasks to take care of with me,
Prosecutor?
You saved Sa Bin...
and Sa Bin saved you.
You two are acting like you have
multiple lives.
I understand Sa Bin,
but that's not the kind of person
you are.
The type to risk his life
for someone else.
Isn't this ill-fated?
Whenever you two meet,
one of you gets hurt.
Please stay away from each other!
Until Hyung Bin...
comes to find me,
I cannot...
die.
If Hyung Bin is dead,
please let me find...
his corpse...
at least.
"You didn't kill anyone."
"It's a relief that you didn't."
"I'm happy that you won't have
to regret."
Is that what you're going
to tell me?
I'm scared now...
but I can't tell anyone that I am.
You should ask me
what I'm scared of.
I'm so scared
that you would not give me...
a chance to talk to you.
The patient in room 505 is not
breathing well.
Sorry?
The doctor is here.
That doesn't make sense.
Who would do something for the one
who stabbed him?
That can't be true no matter
how stupid Jang Ma Chul is.
Don't try to understand it.
How would you understand someone
who aids murder after stabbing?
But why does Chun Jong Bum aim
to kill you?
He must detest me
for not being able to kill me.
Why do you...
deal with this vampire, sir?
When you have me.
What is this old man?
He looks like he could
be stabbed by a gang.
What do you mean stabbing?
Do you know what it's like to be
a goose father?
A goose father has to survive
to the end.
They can't die that easily.
(Chief Prosecutor Chun)
- Yes, sir.
- A familiar name came up...
while investigating congressman
Cho Hyun Gook's slush fund.
Baek In Seo of In Sung Foundation.
Your father in law...
must have been busy.
I'm adding reinforcements to the
investigation team. You should join.
You know better than anyone...
- about him and his family.
- I'll be right there.
What did Chief Prosecutor Chun say?
Lim Hwa Young's body will be put
under the second autopsy today.
I'll meet you at the lab.
Okay. I guess you're going...
alone.
You know I can't investigate a case
with a conflict of interest.
Just make sure not to seem
like you're working for him.
If you can tell me to go after
my son...
you can investigate this case.
Baek In Seo.
His foundations, both scholastic
and medical, will explode easily.
Investigating illegal sperm trades
from his hospital...
will make the news.
I'll decide on the direction
of the investigation.
Go hinder...
your future father in law properly.
You can go now.
I heard that Lim Hwa Young will be
going through autopsy again.
The first autopsy results didn't
match Do Jin's confession at all.
The way he held the knife, the
place, and the number of times...
he said he stabbed the victim didn't
match the wounds on the body.
I'll catch the real culprit
behind the case.
All you have to do is
take the reward.
You seem fixated on her tattoo.
What's this ink?
It's not tattoo ink, it's henna.
It's only temporary.
But this one is natural henna
mixed with oxidants.
Usually, people only use natural
henna due to side effects.
Oxidants...
- What do they do?
- It makes the color more vibrant.
The color of the tattoo
and henna stands out more...
only if macrophages are alive.
So the oxidants were added...
because the tattoo won't show
on a dead body.
I see. The tattoo was applied
after she was murdered.
Prosecutor, the tattooist is
the perpetrator!
The tattoo is too shabby for that,
don't you think so?
This must be an art form for him,
but it looks like a child's work.
One other peculiarity is that
phosphorous was found in the ink.
I'll look more into it
and report back to you.
I think we should call it a day.
I need to go visit Sa Bin
in the hospital.
I have a lantern too.
What kind of a detective doesn't
recognize a UV lantern?
It's not a regular flashlight.
You'll need it to take fingerprints
and blood samples on site.
Keep it.
I see.
So that's what this is.
Are you done checking?
- Yes.
- I'll put her back in.
Why isn't it moving?
Wait a minute.
Is something stuck?
I don't see it though.
Okay.
That's it.
What is it?
Is it luminous paint?
I don't know.
We'll need to find that out now.
Whose is this?
- A book?
- It must be Jong Bum's.
The cover is a medical book,
but the inside is...
Why?
That's giving me goosebumps.
Is your pupil a psychopath?
You know, in the movies...
psychopaths analyze people's faces
and try to mimic them.
When was he in the hospital?
How did he know you were here?
He must have heard it from my uncle.
He lives in the rooftop house
of my uncle's building.
Wait. Wait a minute.
When you lost your phone...
didn't someone named Jong Bum
find it for you?
Where's your phone?
Hand it over to me. Hurry.
I knew it.
You've been seriously stalked.
Did you know about the tracking
app on your phone?
What? No way.
Do you think it's a coincidence
that your diary disappeared too?
Stop it, you're scaring me.
Is there anyone who shows up
wherever you are?
Was there really no one
around you...
that knew everything about you,
without you telling them?
Do you live here? One of my
regulars lives here too.
What?
Do you come here often?
You wanted to come with me
to the arcades?
Actually, I wanted to ride
a rollercoaster with you.
Article 250 and 254
of the criminal law.
A person guilty
of manslaughter will...
be executed,
imprisoned for life,
or be sentenced to less
than five years.
Article 31 of criminal law.
The aider or abettor will be
punished equally with the offender.
If the culprit attempts to murder
the prosecutor investigating him...
he will have additional punishments
under vindictive manslaughter.
Let me correct it.
I guess it's for when you instigate
a thug to murder a prosecutor.
Instigated murder?
You visited Jang Ma Chul
on April 10th, 4 p.m.
and he showed up with a knife
exactly eight hours later.
Were you into instigating homeless
thugs to swing knives at people?
Is there anything I offered
to Ma Chul to murder you?
I was just there to apologize.
Since he was hurt badly
because of me.
You gave him the motive to kill.
The motive to kill?
But you must have it
in your heart too.
People you hate so much
that you want to kill them.
A kill list.
Aren't you going to kill them all
once you have the chance?
The kill list itself is
the motive to kill.
Thus, the motive to kill is...
not given to you by others.
Why are you in the hospital?
Are you here to apologize again?
A woman I have feelings for is hurt.
Obviously, I'm worried.
A woman you like?
- Who?
- Jung Sa Bin.
So you have feelings for her.
Yes.
I like her. I like Sa Bin.
This is why I despise
people like you.
Your head is only filled with love
and no apologies.
If the person who was stabbed
because of you was the person...
you liked, a regular human being
would have never...
shown up here.
You animal.
I guess you have
one more reason to kill me.
I will tell her about you...
instigating murder to Jang Ma Chul.
I'll tell Sa Bin.
Do we still have a business
left between us?
I'm sure you caught
the real criminal.
Didn't you want to kill me?
The Lim Hwa Young case isn't
closed for me.
You're still a culprit.
One more thing.
My motive to kill is my principle.
My principle is...
to get rid of the scumbags
who harm my people.
Is Jung Sa Bin one of your people?
Go and protect the woman
you'll marry.
Hello, professor. You can go ahead.
It's called UV ink. It was popular
overseas a while back.
The fluorescent material reacts to
the UV light to glow.
The material is known to cause skin
cancer, so it's not used anymore.
Then...
if I raid all the tattoo shops here,
I'll be able to find the buyer.
How did you know...
- I liked these?
- I didn't.
I like these too.
The purple tulip is...
- something you like too?
- They looked pretty on my way here.
How did you know...
riding roller coaster was one
of the impossible things...
in my bucket list?
I read your heart disease
through a medical article.
Patients with heart disease can't...
ride roller coasters
even if they wanted to.
Do you mean that?
Yes.
Can you leave me now?
I'd like to get some rest.
I almost forgot.
You left your bag.
Can you give...
my diary back?
Give it back.
Since when were you there?
Your father almost got hurt
because of me.
This time, you almost died
That's why I'm telling you
not to make enemies.
People around you will get hurt.
- How do you feel?
- I'm fine.
I'll be going home soon
because I feel frustrated here.
I'm tired of giving
warnings and advice.
I'll give you a gift instead.
A gift?
Why are you giving this...
But,
I won't be able to use this
because I'm bad with gadgets.
It's a smartwatch from the police
for protection uses.
If you press a button
during an emergency,
it will reach
the closest police station.
That's strange.
Why is the station number
a mobile phone number?
I guess it's a policeman's number.
What's the name of the policeman?
Can I ask...
when you're getting married?
I'll get going now.
The watch has a tracking feature.
Turn it off if you don't want that.
Is my location being sent
to the police station?
You know what that means.
You should stop crossing lines
if you don't want to be observed.
I heard from Detective Ju.
I heard the person
who instigated on you was...
an intern in NFS.
It's Chun Jong Bum, isn't it?
It was a medical student.
Are you trying to prove
that you're different from me?
Can you please leave now?
I'd like to get some rest.
I'm going to throw this away.
Goodbye.
(I can kill that woman
if you want me to.)
What's wrong?
Did Manson find something again?
Apathy.
Whether underground or underwater,
Manson always finds
the scent of his owner.
Let's go.
What's next?
This is the 137th time.
Walk one more block
and turn on the corner.
There's a tattoo shop
on the first floor...
of the glass building called
"Their world Drawn Out of Needles."
No, that's not it. It's a place
where perverts would visit.
Don't you know any place
that smells musty?
Hold on.
(Tattoo promises eternity.)
Are you getting a tattoo?
I'm the police.
Has anyone ever purchased...
the UV tattoo ink recently
by any chance?
Wait.
It's a butterfly tattoo...
on her neck.
She's been here a couple of times.
I remember her
because her skin was...
white as snow.
That skin is a fantasy
for tattoo artists.
I've always wanted to paint
on the skin like that.
Were you asking about UV?
Is this what people call
the UV tattoo?
That's...
a blacklight.
It's a tattoo that can only be seen
under the UV rays.
I'm investigating a murder case,
so please cooperate.
Is there anyone who purchased
the UV ink recently?
If I disclose any information
about my clients,
they'll stop coming here.
You've got nice skin.
Do you want some tattoo?
Policemen can't get tattoos.
I've never done it
in my 50 years of life.
(Product Order Form)
Hello?
You got a tattoo
from Idion Tattoo Shop, didn't you?
You have a butterfly on your neck.
I do.
I'm Detective Ju In Do
from Seobu Police Station.
I'm investigating a murder case...
and I found out...
that this number had purchased
a UV tattoo ink.
I'd like to meet and talk with you.
Can we meet?
I'm just checking on some things.
I'd like your cooperation
in this investigation.
- Are you alone, Detective?
- Of course.
Please come to Yuon.
It's a small gallery
in Gangseong-ro.
Sure.
(Episode 18)
This is...
How could this be here?
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
The number you have dialed is
currently unavailable...
The painting by Gong Ji Chul is
hung here.
It's a painting he drew
after killing a woman.
Bring in the accounting documents
from In Sung Foundation.
(Detective Ju)
Why is he not checking my message?
Isn't this painting beautiful?
You were not even invited.
Yet you're here.
Wasn't this the invitation?
Report me if you want to.
The CCTV at the entrance must've
recorded you.
Even if I were recorded,
you'd still be the suspect.
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
Is this the police station?
Someone is dying here.
I'm in front of Yuhon gallery
at the intersection in Gangseong-ro.
(Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk)
The number you have dialed is
currently unavailable...
(Gu Hyul Ki)
- Hello?
- Prosecutor Kim.
Detective Ju was stabbed
several times in his body.
He was found at a gallery
at the intersection in Gangseong-ro.
(Operation Room)
The wound in his chest
and abdomen is too severe.
Also, he had a shock
during the surgery.
As of now, I can't tell you for sure
when he'll be conscious again.
- Are you his family?
- No, I'm not.
Please inform his family.
It seems that they will need
to be prepared.
What do you mean stabbing?
Do you know what it's like to be
a goose father?
A goose father has to survive
to the end.
They can't die that easily.
The painting by Gong Ji Chul is
hung here.
It's a painting he drew
after killing a woman.
I'm sending the address. Analyze the
CCTV near the gallery and streets.
Is Jung Sa Bin one of your people,
Prosecutor?
Why didn't you pick up my call?
You've never been like this before.
Well, it's been such a long day.
Same here.
Do you want to drink
something strong?
Don't drink
since you'll need to drive.
I'm spending the night here.
Sang Ah,
let's call this marriage off.
What?
Is it because of my hysteria?
Because I'm not like other women?
I found someone
I want to protect now.
But because I belong to a side,
I can't protect her...
- if I'm not on her side.
- Who is this woman?
Is it that woman for whom
you risked your life twice?
Do you...
like this woman?
Tell me.
I want to know how you feel.
Whenever I'm with her, I keep
looking at her face.
I never failed to control myself...
but I can't do that
when I'm with her.
I think about her all day.
About what she's doing,
whether she's getting hurt...
if something happened to her.
So I want to run out even while
I'm working.
I recall what mom told me.
Frida Kahlo's lover Diego was...
her son, her blood,
her lover, her husband,
her father, her sun,
her sky, and her fiery pit.
Is she like that to you?
Do you love her that much?
Tell me!
I don't know yet, but...
I found this out thanks to
my feelings toward her.
I never...
loved you.
I finally know...
why I imagined horrible things
while I was in love with you.
It'll change.
Just like your love for me changed.
Your love for her will change too.
Sang Ah.
I saw her...
when I proposed to you.
That proposal was...
for her.
What?
I'll take you home.
Why...
can't it be me?
Oh, no. I forgot to say goodbye
to the nurse.
She's not just pretty...
she's Nightingale herself.
Wait here.
Wait.
I'm glad you look fine.
Was it really you who tried
to kill Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk?
I'm asking you.
Yes.
Why?
Did you want to
kill him because he tracked you...
and suspected you?
Because I love you.
- What?
- I wanted to kill him...
because he gave you a hard time.
He was blocking me
from entering your heart.
I needed to kill him.
What...
Even if you ask
for an explanation...
I can't give you one.
This is the first time...
I wanted to kill someone for love.
I'll be going now.
Next time...
ask yourself if you want to know
something instead of peeping.
Ask her what food she likes
and what she's scared of.
Don't ever lie in front
of someone you like.
If you're curious where she is,
just ask her.
Next time...
don't force a smile on you.
Stop living as someone you're not
in front of other people.
If you want to kill someone
in your head...
place me in your head next time.
You can paint really well.
Paint my face on top of the person
you want to kill.
If you still want to kill
that person...
Imagine the bloody hands
that stabbed me as yours.
Imagine what it must have felt like
to stab me as well.
If you can still kill someone
with all that...
I regretted it.
I thought I lost you forever.
- Take good care of her.
- Of course.
You are such a cool guy, Jong Bum.
That's her.
That woman keeps stealing
what's your master's.
What should we do?
(Gong Ji Chul)
Isn't it time we meet?
(I'll go where you are.)
I knew we wouldn't be friends.
Even I would have said no.
We are too alike.
You agree now, don't you?
How come you're not here
with Su Hyuk today?
Are you enjoying some time alone
before the wedding?
- I have a question to ask.
- Anything for you.
Why did you send me
Gong Ji Chul's message?
One more thing.
Why did you falsely charge me
with the murder?
You should be asking my mom,
I mean, Writer Jang Hye Mi.
Jang Hye Mi has known you
even before I knew you.
Maybe it's right to say...
she's been watching you
before you were born.
Me?
Why?
You'll go to the police
if I tell you everything, won't you?
Figure it out yourself...
why Writer Jang Hye Mi was
interested in you.
Then I'll ask you something
you can answer.
Why did you put a camera
in my room?
Don't you do it too?
You watch people secretly
when you want to befriend them.
You want to know their deep secrets.
That's why you want her...
- completely.
- A friend?
You might need a friend too.
A very special friend.
Aren't you lonely?
I'm grateful...
that you made me realize how awful
and filthy it is to have...
someone sneak a look at me.
Your murder video will be sent
to the police soon.
Before that, get back to me...
to my question
with an answer from Writer Jang.
I think you'll need some time
to talk with your mother.
I'll give you a day.
Also,
you become friends
when you're interested.
I'm not interested in you.
I can kill the woman you like
even now.
What are you going to do?
I know who the girl is...
in your painting.
You won't be able to do that.
You're afraid to die...
in my hands.
(Location cannot be found.)
If you're curious where she is,
just ask her.
Where are you?
Me? I'm on my way to the book store.
I'll join you. I have a book
I'd like to buy.
Don't ever lie in front
of someone you like.
I miss you.
I'll be on my way.
Hey, you must be bored.
You're coming here?
It's quite difficult
to find this place.
Okay, I'll send you the address.
They've got a lot
of interesting books.
Bring some snacks on your way here.
What would you like?
I'd like a dalgona flavor today.
(Gong Ji Chul's
First Yellow Umbrella Case)
(The first Chungsan-dong murder)
(Gong Ji Chul's
Second Yellow Umbrella Case)
Third Yellow Umbrella Case)
(Seoul Jong-gu Police Station)
(Detective: Chun Seok Tae)
I like you.
That's why you should never
get hurt.
Is anyone here?
Where did he go?
You're early.
How did you get here?
I didn't make a call.
I don't know if this is
because of the debt I have to you...
or because...
of the protective instincts
I got from saving your life.
Pardon?
Can I also do an experiment?
What experiment is it?
Subtitle by Kocowa
Resynced by IG @mad.yudi.subs
(Born Again)
Are you saying
Prosecutor Kim likes you?
I was curious about...
what face you'd make in front
of the person you liked.
I need to protect you.
I'm planning to become your friend.
- You're planning to escape again.
- She's my girl now.
It's my first time to ever like
a man like this.
Take responsibility.
Will I be able to have that woman?
There's a stalker following Sa Bin.
You're going after your superior.
I heard death is the only way
for ultimate possession.
I never give up when I decide...
on killing someone.