[ Episode 3 ]
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Maybe I should have bought
the chocolate earlier.
Speak of the devil.
How much is...
Sorry?
How much is what?
I thought you left.
Why...
Would you like to have dinner with me?
[ Restaurants ]
What should we eat? What could we get?
What should we eat?
All the restaurants I know are closed.
I'll look up restaurants that are open.
A lot of restaurants in Jeju Island
open 24 hours.
Places with scheduled
working hours are better.
The owner, chef, and staff
must be well-rested
to cook delicious food.
You sounded like Baek Jong-won just now.
There are two restaurants.
One restaurant serves grilled sea bream.
- And
- What?
the other one serves abalone stew.
Well, that one is closer.
Can you forgive me?
Pardon?
Gosh. What are you doing?
I'm sorry, but look over there.
What?
Wait.
Hold on.
Don't tell me you want to eat there.
Can't you tell they'd serve great food?
I don't know about that.
But let's go to an indoor restaurant.
When it comes to picking restaurants,
I'm pretty good.
Can you trust me just this once?
If we drive just 1.8km more...
I'm really starving.
My stomach is in big pain.
Excuse me!
Set up the table. Set it up again!
- No, don't do that.
- Give me some food!
- Welcome.
- We're open. Hello.
Welcome to our truck. A table for two?
Ma'am.
Wait, he's not her mom.
My goodness. Welcome to our truck.
You're from the city.
What should I get?
Wait. Do you really want to eat here?
This place doesn't look that hygienic.
Let's go somewhere else.
- I won't serve you food.
- Hold on.
My apologies.
Sir, don't you know that the better
a restaurant is, the shabbier it looks?
It's like a good stew restaurant that's
been around for 50 years is shabby.
- That's the vibe.
- That's our vibe.
- That's the vibe? That's great.
- Okay.
How long have you been running the truck?
[ Two Guys' Food Truck ]
Five years?
It's been five days.
- That was original.
- We're like newborn babies.
Let's go. Okay? Let's go.
So the problem is that I have to choose
between black pork or sea urchins.
Both of them look good.
Let me tell you about the rice bowl
with Jeju black pork.
These pigs were raised
in the clean area of Jeju Island.
When you bite into it,
you'll taste how chewy it is.
And the juice from the meat
will explode in your mouth.
Right.
Let me tell you about the rice bowl
with sea urchins.
The savory flavor and soft texture
of sea urchins will wrap your tongue.
Once you have a bite, you won't know
- The road.
- if you're on the road
or you are on top of
- The island.
- the island by the beach.
- That's how beautiful...
- We're already on one.
- I said no to him. It's embarrassing.
- Wait.
I want the rice bowl with sea urchins.
Right. Good choice.
The island is famous for that.
Give me the rice bowl with the pork belly.
All right. 1 rice bowl with pork belly
and 1 bibimbap with sea urchins.
Excellent choices.
All right. You can sit over there.
Gosh, I have a headache.
It's so good.
The savory flavor and soft texture
of sea urchins wrap my tongue.
I can literally taste the ocean with this.
Good.
It's just a rice bowl.
They're all the same.
How's yours?
What?
- Can I try some?
- Yes.
Thank you.
This is good too.
[ But why isn't she asking me
why I came back? ]
[ Isn't it normal to ask that first
as soon as I came back? ]
I can see you thinking,
"Why isn't she asking me why I came back?"
That's what it looks like.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking that at all.
I didn't ask because it's pointless.
It's probably because
I looked so pathetic.
That's not it.
I can tell that you are
very educated and respectable.
And you seem to be well-off.
I understand. If you are emotionally
and financially comfortable,
you will feel sympathy for others.
That's natural.
Given the way you treat me and talk to me,
I don't think
you're considering me romantically.
So the chance of hitting on me
will be extremely low.
To be honest, I don't feel as awkward
around you
because I don't consider you
romantically either.
You sound like a psychiatrist.
My goodness, I hate psychiatrists.
When I listen to them,
they all sound like frauds.
Pardon?
Have you ever been scammed
by a psychiatrist?
Well, not really.
You're groundlessly criticizing
a profession.
That's an awful behavior.
Has a psychiatrist ever co-signed
a loan for you? You're covering for them.
That's not what I'm doing.
Let's just eat. Please eat.
Anyway,
today is a very special day.
And it should have been an awful day too.
Well, thanks to you,
it became a strange day.
By the way,
let's clarify one thing.
I didn't come back
because I felt bad for you.
I came back to have dinner with you.
Now that I'm full, I'm sleepy.
I should find a place to sleep.
If you don't have a reservation,
why don't you come with me?
When I'm here, I usually...
- Do you need a place?
- Goodness!
- You startled me. What is this?
- What?
Listen. A vacation house is
five minutes away from this place.
The moment you see it, you'll be
confused if it's a house or a palace.
This place comes with the most
luxurious interior design.
On top of that,
the linens are of the best quality.
There's a swimming pool
as big as a water park.
And the couple who owns the place
is so kind.
The whole town knows how nice they are.
Would you like to check it out?
Should we check it out
since it's close and nice?
- No.
- Write down the address.
- All right.
- You made the right decision.
I thought you were here for dinner.
Now, you need a place to stay?
Aren't they kind of weird?
- Hello.
- My goodness. There's a granny.
Welcome.
My goodness, your outfit...
So tell me.
Do you want a room with a bed
or without the bed?
Pardon?
It looks like the lady isn't from here.
But you... Wait. Are you from Hamdeok?
I'm from Seoul.
I'm here on a business trip.
Welcome. Let's see.
The room you two can stay in...
How about a room with a hot tub?
No, we want two rooms.
We'll be sleeping separately.
Well, that's what everyone says at first.
No, he means it. Please give us two rooms.
Once you book two rooms,
you can't change your mind.
You can't change it.
All right. Do I pay first?
Yes.
We're having special rates this month.
We'll only charge you 180 dollars.
Do you want another discount?
- Can I pay with my card?
- I'll give you a 20-dollar discount.
[ Then, ]
what about when you have to eat dinner
with a stranger?
I don't know.
I don't want to have meals with people
whom I'm not close with.
And if I'm eating with a stranger,
it means I probably want to be
on that person's side.
It's the most selfless act
I can do for others.
Then, why don't you
do the best selfless act you can do
for the woman you love?
"Congratulations, Do-hee"
"on quickly finding out that he's a jerk."
This would be a line from
the unnecessarily positive
main character of a soap opera.
Congratulations, my foot.
There's nothing to celebrate.
If there's anyone who congratulates me
for what happened today,
I'll smack that person.
What a jerk.
Am I really such a loser?
Why do I still miss him?
[ "Ms. Woo Do-hee, go!" ]
This feels so nice.
She's exhausting.
This time, it's the butterfly stroke.
"Ms. Woo is very fast."
Butterfly.
What are you doing?
Hey.
You're out.
Do you want to swim?
Since there are two of us,
should we do synchronized swimming?
Come out of there now.
First, I need to lift my leg like this.
Darn it. Should I use my arms?
She has one dynamic drinking habit.
You're not going to come out of there? No?
I asked you to come in.
Let's do it together.
This is really fun, you know. Turn.
Suit yourself.
The water here is warm.
Hey, what are you doing?
My goodness, she's so exhausting.
Hey. It's cold out here.
Why don't you go inside?
Hey.
Are you okay? Hello?
You know what?
If I stayed
on the bottom of the pool like this
when it was filled with water,
I would probably be dead, right?
The thing is,
there's no water here.
But why do I feel suffocated
as if I'm going to die?
It feels like I'm drowning.
Then,
force yourself to breathe.
That's how you'll feel your pain
and it will heal quickly.
When you keep trying,
your wound will wither away
and turn into a gill.
It will help you breathe comfortably.
[ Heights Mountain Cabin ]
Oh, my gosh.
You are unbelievable.
It hurts so much.
Did you go somewhere?
[ Digestive Drink ]
I stepped out to buy something for myself
and got you these.
Thank you.
I can drive you to the airport.
No, it's okay. I called a taxi.
Besides, your flight is later than mine.
Yes, that's true,
but I owe you a lot.
I'd like to buy you dinner
when we go back to Seoul.
I see. It's all right.
I want to apologize and thank you
for your help.
I want to buy you a meal for your help,
so please spare me some of your time.
Gosh. There's no need to.
Right. Please don't get
the wrong idea here.
I'm not trying to feel you out
or cling onto you.
Given the situation we're in,
you understand, right?
Yes.
With that said, I don't think
you should turn down my offer.
To make you feel less bothered by this,
I won't ask for your name, job,
home address,
and any personal information.
I'll treat you to a meal
and end our business
without any small talk. Good, right?
[ Hello, Mr. Tae Jin-ah. ]
[ Yes, hello. I'm Tae Jin-ah. ]
[ You're going to premiere
your new song on our show, right? ]
[ That's right. ]
[ I poured out my soul on this new song. ]
[ It's "She Comes and Goes". ]
What would you like to do?
- Sure, why not.
- Thank you.
- Did you call a taxi?
- Yes.
When should we meet and where?
I'll see you then.
- I'll see you then.
- Sorry?
The day Tae Jin-ah's new song
tops the music chart.
8 p.m. at Daedong Fish Market.
[ Tae Jin-ah topping the chart? ]
On the day Tae Jin-ah tops
the music chart?
What a creative way to say,
"I don't want to see you again."
How offensive.
You're being honest with me
100 percent, right?
Yes.
You didn't make up that story
because you felt guilty of having
a hidden lover, right?
No.
It's like the movie "Before Sunrise",
you know?
This is what really matters
in this Jeju Island version
of "Before Sunrise".
- What is it?
- Is she pretty?
Gosh, zip it.
Come on, feel free to share it with me.
Is she pretty?
In my opinion...
She's definitely pretty.
- What?
- Dr. Kim.
You don't know this, don't you?
When you describe a pretty woman,
you always go like this.
Is this right?
Can you do that for me?
1, 2, 3.
When you describe a pretty woman,
you start your sentence
with "In my opinion".
You seem to feel too prideful
to admit it at once
when someone's actually pretty.
Aren't I right?
You're going to see her again, won't you?
- What?
I bet you are.
♫ I can't tell her heart ♫
♫ My heart trembles going back and forth ♫
♫ We can't just pass by like this ♫
This song is marvelous.
This is real music.
I can't stand listening to those songs
just for youngsters.
Those won't do. This is real music.
I'm sorry,
but can you turn down the music?
Why? Don't you think it's fantastic?
Sing along.
I won't sing along.
Can you please turn it down?
Okay, I will.
[ When Tae Jin-ah tops the music chart? ]
That's like having
a cat-grooming documentary
top the box office.
I know, I'm not dumb.
Yet you had to say that?
You should've just given her a flat "no".
Hey, that would be rude.
I was trying to be as witty as I could be.
"Witty"?
What kind of wit did that come from?
New York? Copenhagen?
Rio de Janeiro?
That's being the worst scumbag...
It was very impolite of you to do so.
"Worst scumbag"?
Hey. I was being very considerate.
And I don't think she was offended
that much. Probably not.
Dr. Kim. You're a psychiatrist.
Not Mr. Elated who loves joking around.
Hey, you're overthinking this issue.
By the way, why did you say no
to a casual meal?
You're wearing me out.
Byeong-jin. Byeong-jin!
Get here. Listen to me.
According to what happened yesterday,
she would've unconsciously developed
an extreme case of dependency on me.
The more we meet,
the messier the relationship will be
because more of those issues will surface.
Understand?
Then you shouldn't have gone back
in the first place.
I do volunteer service regularly.
It was a very social
and altruistic act of kindness.
Next time,
you should never do charity work
to a woman you meet in an island.
Okay, fine. I won't do it.
It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
- Get lost. I'm going to bed.
- I'm going to leave.
But you completely disregarded
her approach out of full respect.
Leave. Get out.
You totally toyed with her.
You're the worst human being.
- Get out.
- The worst human being ever!
Get out, will you?
I'm going to bed.
Gosh, he's so talkative.
[ "Sophie's World" ]
I've never seen you before.
You must have just moved in.
Excuse me?
That waste bag tells me
that you live around here.
You must like drinking.
You got the strongest dose of soju.
You must pay...
I'm sorry if I made you
feel uncomfortable.
I just wanted to say hi.
Go home safely.
I'm going to have dinner now.
Kimchi!
Is he a lunatic? Goodness, me.
[ This Jeju trip is a bundle ]
[ - of blessings over blessings. ]
- Look at you all pumped up.
[ Awesome possum.
This is amazing, blazing. ]
[ Ms. Bride-to-be... ]
[ My apologies. I'll do it again. ]
[ - Congratulations to... ]
- Now taking a closer look,
- she's evil-looking.
[ - and your upcoming wedding. ]
- I can tell
[ - Don't forget to travel... ]
she's the type who can't be
satisfied with one man.
Fine.
I wish all the best for you turtledoves.
I'm going to delete all of this.
[ Delete Files ]
What good will deleting these files do?
Everything's already vividly ingrained
in my head.
[ - I'd like to ask a favor.
- I can't do it. ]
You rascal.
Only if you ended things like a gentleman.
Cheers.
[ 2N BOX ]
Are you watching Jin No-eul's
pilates videos again?
You're here.
You're watching it as if it's porn.
Can you not talk to me?
Where is it?
Is it here? Where is it?
What's wrong with you?
Where is it? Is it here?
Stop it.
Come here.
Goodness.
How could he do that to you?
Right, I never told you this
because it might offend you.
But Yeong-dong, no, I mean that punk.
I hated the way his eyes looked like.
His pupils were filled with butter and...
You should've told me that earlier.
That his pupils were filled with butter.
Why bring it up now?
Anyway, congratulations, Do-hee.
On witnessing his true colors soon.
So-ra.
Yes, Do-hee?
I want to hit you so hard.
What did I do?
[ In position. ]
[ You completely disregarded her approach ]
[ out of full respect. ]
[ You totally toyed with her. ]
[ You're the worst human being.
The worst human being ever! ]
I mean,
I didn't do anything majorly wrong.
What's up with all the fuss?
Gosh.
I will
take full responsibility.
"Full responsibility"? My foot!
Have you ever carried out
your responsibilities? Forget it!
I don't need you to be responsible.
You just shut it
and do as I tell you from now on.
But... Okay, I know I did you wrong,
but limiting a producer's creativity is...
Quit if you don't want to follow.
But you have to pay the monthly rent.
You're being so cheap. The monthly rent?
If you can't stand it, forget it.
Come on, let's get to it.
Are you going to follow my orders?
Fine.
What? I didn't hear you.
Fine. Fine!
Okay.
I need you to do something right away.
What is it?
Find a hero
and create something with great quality.
"A hero"?
[ Episode 4 ]
[ "Hakju-dong Hero". ]
All right. Here.
- Hey!
- Is he a policeman? A bodyguard?
You want to open a martial arts class?
He's a psychiatrist.
What? A psychiatrist?
[ "Food Psychology, Healing Food",
Written by Kim Hae-kyong ]
He's the most wanted psychiatrist
all the writers want,
from the public to cable channels.
It's Dr. Kim Hae-kyong,
a psychiatry specialist.
Not only is he famous for his
general counseling sessions,
but he's also known for treating
his patients by eating together.
I know him.
Wait, are you...
He's the Hakju-dong Hero.
It's him.
You can feel
it's going to be a hit, right?
Plus, his looks are...
I can't see his face well.
Do you have any photos or videos of him?
He's strict
when it comes to revealing himself.
There's nothing online.
No photos on his book either.
Maybe it's a lie.
If he's that handsome,
his face would be everywhere.
It's true.
And
he has also done some podcasts before.
[ The act of eating itself ]
[ can be analyzed and interpreted
in many ways. ]
- His voice.
[ - A psychiatrist like me needs to think, ]
He's golden.
[ but it's most ideal to eat
without anything on your mind. ]
[ What I tell my patients the most is ]
[ nothing surprising,
but to enjoy their food. ]
[ They could be enjoying their food
because it's really good. ]
[ Or they could be enjoying it
because of good company. ]
[ I hope all my listeners
enjoy their meals today too. ]
He's hot.
- Piping hot, for real.
- Goodness.
I heard he's such a smooth talker.
Then why wouldn't he go on shows?
Who knows? Everyone wants him,
but I guess he refuses all the offers.
Is he
a pervert or psycho by any chance?
So what? We just need a hit with him.
Let me get this straight. You want
to birth a new trend of sapiosexuals?
Right, Jeong-hwan contacted him for now,
so make sure you get Dr. Kim.
You know what?
This project requires a lot of tough work.
I wonder if there are any bonuses.
Your monthly rent.
Monthly rent is nothing
compared to the work this requires.
Look at you getting down to business.
What do you want?
If I succeed in casting him
and make it a hit,
I get to design a project I want to do.
- You!
- You're also giving me this job
because you know I'm fit to do it.
Goodness, you sneaky fox.
I'll get him sitting
right there inside our studio.
How does that sound?
Fine.
What did you say?
I can't hear you.
What is it that you said?
Fine!
I'll get him sitting right there.
Do it again.
I got you.
Catch him like this, okay?
- Get him.
- Okay. Let go of me!
- Can you check this?
- Yes, sir.
What happened to Patient Ko Ji-hwan?
Oh, he's on his way back
after getting caught
at the bus terminal.
Is that right?
He's run away so many times already.
What are you watching?
- What?
- You're watching something skanky.
No, I'm not.
There's an MCN company called 2N BOX,
and they wanted to cast you.
I said no for now,
and I'm now checking
the contents they make.
Take a look at this.
Gosh, his hair...
[ - My goodness.
- I'll pluck all of your hair. ]
[ - Hey, it's my hair.
- I'll pluck every single strand. ]
It's a terribly poor MCN company.
- Both look like psychos.
[ - I'll pluck all of your hair. ]
[ Hey, it's my hair. You started first. ]
I think the people who designed
this program are the ones insane.
That obsession
that they have to be different.
Lack of altruism
and a tendency of violence.
Those types of people are more dangerous
than psychopaths.
They are kind of like you.
Like me?
These people are ruining this planet,
- and I'm like them?
[ - Good work. ]
- I'm sorry.
[ - He rejected us ]
at once.
At once?
He treated me as if I was a spam call
selling insurance.
Did you talk to Dr. Kim himself?
No. It was his assistant
who's also a nurse.
Give me his number.
Oh, yes. Hello.
You're the producer of the show?
[ Why don't you at least listen to... ]
No, thanks.
I've already said no.
We make different contents
apart from any public, cable,
and subscription network.
[ I am sure Dr. Kim will be
deeply interested... ]
We're not interested.
Dr. Kim will not make an appearance
on that kind of show.
I will hang up in three.
- Three.
- Darn you!
You didn't count from one!
I told you.
What?
"That kind of show"?
How dare you test my grit, you punk.
You don't know Dr. Kim's number, right?
No. But I do have his email address.
Email address...
- I'm off.
- Goodness.
Are you heading to your dinner counseling?
Yes. What are you doing?
We got a wrong package here.
You shopped again, didn't you?
No.
What do you buy online all the time?
- Let me see what it is.
- It's not ours.
- It's a misdelivery.
- What do you shop all-day?
[ Written by Lee Mun-jeong ]
Did you order these?
- No.
- Then who did?
Did you give the hospital address
to Writer Lee Mun-jeong?
Who told you to do so?
Well, she said
she would like to send me these, so...
Throw them away.
But there are 20 of them. How can I...
Then sell them online or something!
Why is he mad at me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
[ New mail has arrived. ]
[ Hello, Doctor. ]
[ This is Woo Do-hee,
a producer of 2N BOX. ]
[ Inbox ]
He opened it.
Hello?
[ You got a parcel.
Are you at home right now? ]
No, I'm not.
Please put it in the parcel drop box.
Well, I don't think it will fit in.
May I ask who sent the parcel?
[ Mr. Lee Yeong-dong, it says. ]
Okay.
I went to department stores and
supermarkets and did what you said.
With earphones on,
I listened to music loudly
and walked in the stores
while looking at my shopping list.
Then I found myself
buying only the things I need.
It was a fascinating experience.
I guess then you can now
pay more attention to your son.
Because you couldn't during the therapy.
I guess that's true.
But I would like to care less
about my son for the time being.
Not only because of the therapy
but also because of my work.
Work?
I see.
Not all women
have the maternal instinct after all.
Excuse me?
Never mind.
So how do you shop online these days?
[ Let's give the things back to each other
that we exchanged. ]
[ Seeing those things will break my heart. ]
[ Although we broke up like that, ]
[ let's not forget the good times we had ]
[ and make this a beautiful end. ]
[ I'm not sure if you can ever find
a man as nice as I am though. ]
What a sentimental prick.
This trash gave me trash.
Why couldn't he just
throw them away himself?
[ Now I feel less suffocated. ]
[ I can start breathing now. ]
[ Now I feel like I have gills. ]
Gills?
It sounds familiar.
How strange. I wonder why.
Mom, when will you come back
from your writing trip?
Until I find my name, Lee Mun-jeong,
I might not come back.
[ Today at 10:00 a.m.,
there will be a disaster upon Korea. ]
[ Listen. Watch out, government officers, ]
[ those in the media and entertainment
and even in finances! ]
[ I don't know where I'll start this. ]
What kind of name is Big Johnson? Gross.
10:00 a.m?
- It's almost 10 a.m. now.
[ - I hate K-pop. ]
Are they that scary?
Those guys can hack the CIA and NASA.
His mask and outfit look a bit tight.
This looks really lousy,
but I guess they're pretty good.
I wonder whom they will hack this time.
NIS? FSS?
What if we get the virus as well?
What if we lose all the data?
We should probably back up the data
we haven't backed up yet.
Hey, Jeong-hwan.
We don't have any important data.
Don't speak like that.
Do you want to lose
everything we have done?
If we lose it, we can do it again.
You made a mistake.
- Oh, no.
- Did someone wash a rag in the office?
- Goodness.
- It smells horrible.
- Gross.
- It stinks.
I don't smell anything.
Okay. The original price is 17 dollars,
and they're now 10 dollars each.
Okay.
Doctor. I posted the books online.
- What book?
- The books.
- "The books"?
- Yes.
You told me to sell the books.
- What?
- You told me to sell them online.
So I posted all of them
except for one for myself.
Byeong-jin.
I know you were stupid,
but how could you sell those books?
"Stupid"? I just did what you told me to...
I know that's what I said,
but you should have thought it through.
Gosh, you're one tactless man.
Donate some of them to the library.
I can't believe him.
I think I'm having a stroke.
[ Creator Im So-ra ]
Did you hear from Dr. Kim Hae-kyong?
He checked the email,
but he hasn't replied yet.
Don't be just waiting like this.
Just push it through. You're good at that.
Start.
[ Inbox ]
[ I'm pretty disappointed. ]
[ I heard you were a well-mannered person, ]
[ but I guess it was just a rumor. ]
[ I kindly explained through email
why we'd like to invite you ]
[ and asked for confirmation. ]
[ Don't you think ]
[ we deserve at least a simple yes or no? ]
[ I find it unfortunate
that a reasonable man like you ]
[ showed such disrespect. ]
[ I guess I have to take this as a no. ]
[ P.S. Manners maketh man. ]
"Manners"?
[ Dear Producer Woo Do-hee. ]
[ This is Kim Hae-kyong. ]
"Dear"? That doesn't sound bad.
[ I wished I was wrong about
my preconception about you. ]
[ But sadly, ]
[ you seem to be exactly
the kind of person I imagined. ]
[ You don't seem to show
any respect to others. ]
[ And your professional attitude is ]
[ definitely subpar. ]
[ You seem to be a complete mess. ]
[ Just like the lame program you made. ]
Hey!
Does this jerk think
I'm potato salad or something?
He's making a complete fool of me.
Hey, I got a heart attack because of you.
What's wrong, Ms. Woo?
What?
[ "Si bel homme". ]
[ Oh, it's not a curse word. ]
[ It means a handsome man in French. ]
[ Everyone is talking about
how handsome you are. ]
[ I will stop writing to you. ]
[ I wish you a happy life. "Si bel Homme". ]
My goodness!
[ Dear Producer Woo Do-hee. ]
Dear, my foot.
[ I made a brief analysis
of your mental health. ]
Why would you?
[ As a result, a visit to a psychiatrist ]
[ is highly recommended. ]
"A visit to a psychiatrist"?
[ You show symptoms
of obsessive-compulsive disorder, ]
[ intermittent explosive disorder, ]
[ dysautonomia,
and borderline personality disorder. ]
[ I highly recommend you ]
[ to visit a psychiatrist
or a therapist nearby. ]
[ Your mail has been successfully sent. ]
[ I wish you realize
the significance of mental health ]
[ - and seriously consider it. Bye. ]
- Goodness.
Gosh, now he made me a crazy woman.
Not army base or police station nearby
but nearby psychiatrist?
Guys.
I'm now a crazy woman. Ms. Crazy Woo.
Let me give you flowers.
Here. Take them.
Maybe she's stuck.
Right? It seems that something
isn't going right.
She would probably be able to break
the keyboard with anger.
And she's already stressed out
because of her boyfriend.
Why? Do they have a problem?
- Tell me.
- My stomach hurts.
Hey!
[ Come on out. ]
[ Give me your number.
Let's talk on the phone and meet. ]
[ "Si bel homme"! ]
I don't think she's using the word
for what it means.
"Si bel homme".
[ "Si bel homme"! ]
I can't accept this.
[ Contact us ]
Do you know
where Dr. Kim Hae-kyong's office is?
- Why do you ask?
- I asked him to talk in person,
but he wouldn't reply.
This is why I hate psychiatrists.
Here you are.
I'll be right back.
- Doctor, I found something interesting...
- Later.
Where is he going with such an angry face?
He should see this.
This is amazing.
Look at how high it ranked.
[ "She Comes and Goes"
by Tae Jin-ah ]
What a coward.
Wait there.
Woo Do-hee is coming.
Look at that.
How does that feel, coward?
You're so dead.
How may I help you?
I'm here to see the CEO here
and Producer Woo Do-hee.
I'm the CEO. Who are you?
I'm Kim Hae-kyong.
Excuse me?
Hello, Doctor.
What brings you here?
Do you even have
work ethic in this company?
What do you mean?
Vocational ethics.
- What?
- Are the employees here
taught to curse to their clients?
- Curse?
- That's right.
She called me "si bel homme".
Who? Producer Woo?
What did you say?
Did you not hear me?
- "Si".
- "Bel".
"Homme".
This has got to be a joke.
Why don't you get inside first?
- Would you like a cup of tea?
- I'm good.
You're very handsome, by the way.
You're one good-looking man.
Please come in.
I'm a huge fan.
Where's Dr. Kim Hae-kyong?
How may I help you?
I'm Producer Woo Do-hee, from 2N BOX.
We said we were not interested.
You can't just visit us like this.
I'm not here to cast him.
I'm here to ask him something personally.
What kind of a psychiatrist
has such a horrible personality?
I'm not sure where this is coming from.
Just because I said something
he didn't want to hear,
he told me to see a psychiatrist.
What kind of a psychiatrist says that?
You've got a point.
[ Assistant Producer Kim Jeong-hwan ]
No way!
I can't believe this.
Do you know
"She Comes and Goes" by Tae Jin-ah?
That song topped the music chart.
Unbelievable!
What?
[ "She Comes and Goes"
by Tae Jin-ah ]
8:00 p.m.
At Daedong Fish Market.
Wait...
What on earth?
She came and then went away.
She's pretty.
Please come back!
[ Relax Psychiatric Clinic ]
[ "Live Entertainment News" ]
Here you are.
She doesn't answer.
What's she doing at this crucial moment?
[ Gosh, he's really handsome. ]
I got you.
Where's Producer Woo right now?
Are you hiding her or something?
No way.
She seems to be out of office
because of work.
- Right?
- Yes.
Fine.
I request your compelling explanation
and Producer Woo's
sincere and respectful apology.
I'm so sorry. Please calm down.
There seems to have been
a misunderstanding
- during the scouting process...
- There was no misunderstanding.
- I'm here to hear a sincere apology...
[ - Some interesting news just got in. ]
[ "She Comes and Goes" by Tae Jin-ah ]
[ just topped the music chart. ]
What?
[ This is a truly impressive achievement. ]
[ He beat all the popular idol groups
and topped the chart. ]
[ Let's check out the details right now. ]
So you like Tae Jin-ah.
You like trot, don't you?
The man who stole Big Johnson's girlfriend
is a K-pop fan.
And he planted virus
in all K-pop related websites in Korea.
Unbelievable. I'm a psychiatrist,
but there are
so many weird people in this world.
Seriously.
So this song topped the chart
because of the virus. Am I right?
That's right.
Still, you have to go.
What? Go where?
You promised you would see her
if Tae Jin-ah's song tops the chart.
What?
Why would I do that?
Why did I come out?
As if I'm actually going to meet him.
I must have gone out of my mind.
His song topped the chart
because if the virus. It doesn't count.
But you didn't mention
that it has to be done without virus.
This is crazy.
Are you kidding me?
He didn't really top the chart.
You didn't mention
he has to really top the chart either.
I don't care. I'm not going.
Hey. Think about it.
Like you said, I hurt her feelings
with my stateless sense of humor.
Would you come out if you were her?
You never know.
Maybe she's not angry anymore or bored.
Stop. Let's stop talking about this.
Gosh. Seeing you gives me a headache.
Please leave me alone now.
Goodness.
Doctor, it's 7:30 p.m.
You only have 30 minutes left.
You should go now.
I said you have 30 minutes left.
Gosh, he really doesn't know
how to date girls.
If I don't do anything about him,
- he's going to mess up everything.
- Gosh, this is nice.
Are you still there?
Gosh, this is confusing.
What should I do?
Is he really psychic?
What do you mean by the person next to me?
What on earth? Are you a psychic?
How did he know
the song was going to top the chart?
I'm not fascinated.
That prick just got it by luck.
If I end up being the only one
showing up, I will look like a fool.
And even if we both show up,
I'll look like an idiot who came anyway
after being humiliated like that.
All right. Let's just go home.
I should make some kimchi stew for dinner.
What was that?
What happened?
Hey, I was parked.
Why did you run into my car?
Why isn't he getting off?
Hey, come on out.
What kind of person drives like...
Goodness, I'm so sorry.
I'm on my way to a live show.
I'm terribly sorry.
Are you okay, young lady?
Yes, I guess.
That's great.
I'm in a rush.
Fix everything you have to fix
and get all the tests you have to take
in the hospital.
Here's my contact.
I will pay all the bills.
[ Tae Jin-ah ]
Okay.
Oh, right.
Please listen to "She Comes and Goes".
And please congratulate me
for topping the chart.
Right. Congratulations...
I'll get going then.
That's
a fish.
[ Daedong Fish Market ]
Hey.
Oh, no!
[ Dinner Mate ]