[ Episode 16 ]
[ Just now, the shocking deeds
of Chairman Lim Chul-yong of Donghan ]
[ have been broadcasted live
on the internet, ]
[ putting the whole country in shock. ]
[ Here is a clip from the live. ]
[ Do you know why they died? ]
[ Because they underestimated me. ]
[ Had they just listened to me, ]
[ they wouldn't have died so painfully. ]
[ Dad, ]
[ I'm not Bella. ]
[ Stop all of this! ]
Hyun-a...
[ I'm not Bella. ]
[ For the past few months, ]
[ - under the orders of Chairman Lim ]
- Hyun-a...
[ of Donghan Group... ]
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon Show ]
Moon Seung-mo...
Bella...
[ Inspection in session ]
All right.
What?
They've tracked the suspect's location
with his phone.
Is that right? Let's get going! Hurry!
What is it?
Where did he go?
[ They'll get him soon, right? ]
Don't worry.
There's nothing Lim Chul-yong can do now.
It's all over.
Are you all right, Yu-jin?
I'm all right.
I guess I've been too tense.
Come on, this isn't the right time.
- It wasn't me. It was you.
- No, it wasn't.
Should we eat something?
I'm good.
All I can do is just cook for you.
It's not just cooking.
You're the best chef in the world,
and it's the best food in the world.
Whatever.
Your food always smells great.
It's to cheer you up.
I love it.
It's warm and soft.
Don't have such a hard time anymore.
And please don't cry.
You too.
I really don't know!
They found a phone inside the car
Lim Chul-yong left behind.
[ We can't track him anymore. ]
[ It won't be an easy search. ]
Do you think he already got away
from Nonyang?
I don't know.
But it won't be easy to be on the run
without a car at night.
We blocked all the roads
to and from Nonyang,
and we're inspecting everyone,
so don't worry.
I hope you get him soon.
Oh, and how is Hyun-a doing?
We're investigating her
[ based on what she said earlier, ]
so it's going to take a while.
You're going through so much.
Then I'll leave it to you and wait.
Get some sleep tonight.
I told you, no!
[ We need to bring him down ]
at this meeting,
for our company's reputation.
They haven't even investigated him yet.
We can't jump to conclusions.
How long are we supposed to wait?
Everyone's talking about it online!
Lim Chul-yong said it himself.
What else do we need?
And if the prosecutors drop the charges?
[ Or if he is proved innocent? ]
Will you take responsibility?
[ I will take responsibility. ]
What brings you here, Ms. Han?
The chairman is away,
so this is obviously
my place.
What will you do?
I will bring up an emergency agenda
at the board meeting.
I will suspend Lim Chul-yong's position
as chairman
and appoint someone else
to act in his place in the meantime.
Who do you have in mind?
Mr. Kang.
- Mr. Kang?
- Mother...
Then, shall we proceed
and take a vote regarding Mr. Kang
taking the place as acting chairman?
- Mr. Kang will do a good job.
- I agree.
[ - He will do well.
- Sure. ]
[ - What a relief.
- Goodness. ]
- You're here?
[ - Yes. ]
Isn't this a bit too early in the morning?
I'm sure you're all tired,
but the fashion show is this afternoon.
Let's do a final rehearsal.
In your positions, please.
- In position!
[ - In position. ]
- Let's go.
- Okay.
By the way, do I have to do it too?
You should since you got clothes too.
Okay. Please strut down the runway
as you learned yesterday, one by one.
- Starting with Hyo-sook.
[ - Sure. ]
[ - Goodness, am I next? ]
- Okay.
[ - Like this and that.
- Gosh, here? ]
Hyo-sook, you're the best!
Squeeze in your butt.
Straighten your back.
Come on, Da-hoon. Quit joking around.
Goodness, that goofball.
[ Oh, gosh. ]
- Am I doing it right?
- Yes, you're doing great.
[ Okay. ]
Hello?
I'm sorry, but we're closed for the day.
[ It's good to see you all happy. ]
[ I'm dying to mess everything up. ]
Lim Chul-yong...
[ I can't go down like this alone. ]
[ Wait to see what happens. ]
Darn it!
Officer Cho, Lim Chul-yong just called me.
[ - What? ]
- He said he's going to mess things up.
He'll do something at the fashion show
when everyone's there.
I'll go to Seoha Farm,
where the fashion show will take place,
and search every corner.
The show must go on no matter what.
[ Of course. ]
Then shouldn't we tell
the village people too?
I don't want to make them anxious.
Let's keep it a secret for now.
Okay.
Good.
Bella, I'm hosting the event.
Do I still need to do this?
You should do your clothes proud.
[ We're getting better at it now. ]
Of course, we're doing great.
[ How do I look? ]
[ You're doing great. ]
Hello, Chef Moon. Look at us!
Chef Moon.
Are you all done?
- Not yet.
- Then why did you come so early?
To keep an eye on you
and check if you're doing okay.
We're doing great.
Chef Moon, you should be nervous.
Why?
Because I'm going to do
a better job than you.
There's your smile.
What?
Let's smile.
Everything's okay now.
You're right.
Hey, be careful with that.
Right, careful with the flowers.
- I'll put it in the center.
- Sure, in the center.
- Right.
- Here are the chairs.
- Goodness.
[ - Hey, hurry up with that. ]
We've finished already.
What are you doing?
There are three of you.
- Come on and hurry up.
- Gosh.
Oh, you're here.
Can you help me unpack the ingredients
if you're done?
[ Sure. ]
Dad, I'll bring the last one left
- in the car.
- Okay.
I love the colors.
Goodness, beautiful.
[ CHTV ]
- Hello.
[ - Hello, sir. ]
Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- This way, please.
[ Over here. ]
You're here.
Where's Hyun-a?
She has to deal with a lot of issues,
and it's taking much longer than expected.
By the way, what can I help with?
- Goodness, this is unbelievable.
- What is?
How come there are so many people already?
- What?
I'm so nervous.
[ All of Nonyang can't be that... ]
There are so many people.
This is... This is not a stage
[ for amateurs. ]
[ There are too many people and cameras! ]
[ What should we do? ]
Come on, this is manageable.
- What?
- Just do it like we did the rehearsals.
Goodness.
Seol-a's the boss here.
She's the man!
- Gosh.
- Come here.
Wait, everyone.
Is our gift for Bella all prepared?
- Yes.
- Are you okay?
- Ta-da.
[ - Goodness. ]
We can show it right away
if we connect this to that laptop.
Take good care of that.
That's our treasure.
No doubt.
Bella can't know about this.
- Yes.
[ - Over here. ]
- Goodness, you're here.
- Hello.
We should do their makeup first.
What's "makeup"?
Oh, Seol-a. Do you remember the last time
I did a makeover for you?
No!
Never!
My mom did a terrible makeover on her
and it traumatized her.
- Hey!
[ - Oh, I see. ]
How cute.
Sweetheart, your name is Seol-a, right?
- Yes.
- If I do your makeup, you'll be surprised.
You can look forward to it.
I did Bella's makeup
when she was young as well.
Madam Jang, start with Seol-a.
I'll take over the rest.
Okay. Let's go, princess.
- Okay, now.
- Let me look at you.
- Come here, Yoon-ja.
- Your lips are too red.
[ It's pretty, right? ]
What's this?
Oh, that?
This is...
[ If you use it like this,
it covers the light ]
and you can sleep tight at night.
May I borrow this real quick?
- What?
- Please, wait a moment.
Bella.
Hey, Seol-a. What's up?
[ Come here and sit for a second. ]
You don't like flashlights from cameras.
[ Dad said so. ]
You should keep this on
since they will probably be taking
a lot of photos today.
Seol-a, how are you so kind?
It's all thanks to my dad.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Chef Moon?
Officer Cho.
How are things going?
Any suspicious-looking people?
I haven't noticed
anything in particular yet.
We have some detectives
in the audience as well.
If there's a hint of something wrong,
they'll jump right at it.
Good.
Mr. Choi. Mr. Kang.
You came all the way here?
We're not too late, right?
We wouldn't miss a show
held by you and Yu-jin.
Oh, and Chef Moon.
He's no longer "Mr. Kang".
Call him "Chairman Kang" now.
Come on, Gun-woo.
Forget about that Chef Moon.
I'm just the acting chairman.
Congratulations.
We can't let our guards down yet.
Lim Chul-yong's whereabouts are unknown.
We should stay alert until we find him.
The Nonyang Police Station is
actively helping us out
so we'll get him soon.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
[ Thank you for your patience. ]
[ We will now begin ]
[ 2020's spring and summer collection ]
[ of Designer Yoo Byeol-na ]
and Chef Moon's collaborative
fashion and food show.
[ Now taking place
at Nonyang's Seoha Village, ]
this is the Eccentric Chef Moon Show!
- Goodness.
- Congratulations.
She looks beautiful.
It's beautiful.
My goodness.
[ Please give her a round of applause. ]
They look really beautiful.
They are just like models.
[ My goodness. ]
[ They are mother and daughter. ]
[ They look so beautiful. ]
Oh, my goodness!
[ That's so sweet. ]
[ You guys look great together. ]
[ Please give them
another round of applause! ]
[ Here comes the head of Seoha Village! ]
- Oh, my.
- So beautiful.
[ - Gon-sook! ]
- You look so beautiful!
- Gon-sook!
- You look beautiful.
[ And her husband, Mr. Hwang! ]
Gosh, he looks great.
[ Aren't they a lovely couple? ]
[ Stop fighting. ]
[ Mr. Cho Chul-nam is coming! ]
[ The Iron Man of Seoha Village,
Cho Chul-nam! ]
[ - He looks great. ]
- He could be a model.
You look awesome!
[ - He looks adorable.
- He looks really nice. ]
[ - I love his outfit.
- This is awesome. ]
- Goodness.
- He looks great.
[ Now, here comes
the most beautiful princess in the world! ]
You look beautiful!
[ My goodness. ]
- Oh, my.
- She's so cute.
You look beautiful.
- My gosh.
- You look so pretty.
[ She's so adorable. ]
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- How adorable.
- You look so pretty.
[ She's so cute. ]
[ Please give her a round of applause! ]
Seol-a!
Who are you? Who sent you?
Wait. He's a detective.
I'm sure you're surprised.
[ Well, the thing is,
she's a very special person. ]
That's why she made
a very special appearance.
[ She's the designer who made
those awesome clothes for the villagers. ]
[ Meet Designer Yoo Yu-jin! ]
Byeol-na, close your eyes.
I'm fine.
Yu-jin.
Let's go.
[ Please give them
a big round of applause! ]
- Yu-jin, are you all right?
- Yu-jin.
My heart was pounding so much
it almost jumped out of my mouth.
Would you like to take some rest now?
No.
This is fun.
- Yu-jin.
- Chef Moon.
Thank you.
- Are you okay? The flash.
- Yes.
I'm okay.
It's not over yet.
Please stay focused until the end.
It's time for our Chef Moon
to show off his skills.
No. It's time for us
to show off our skills.
Turn this on. Chairs.
- Let's go.
- This is exciting.
[ - Here.
- Thank you. ]
This way.
[ Yes, here it comes. ]
[ Goodness. ]
Gosh. It looks great.
[ Chef Moon. ]
Are you leaving already?
I'm afraid I have to. I have work to do.
Why don't you have some food
before you go?
I wish I could.
I don't get to eat your food often.
What a shame.
But there's nothing we can do about it.
He's the chairman now. He's busy.
Come on, Gun-woo.
I will come back some other time.
Okay.
I heard Hyun-a was released
from the police station.
So I think I should go.
- Chef Moon, sorry I have to leave early.
- Don't worry.
- Keep me updated.
- I will. Let's go.
Okay. We will get going then.
- The soup smells great.
- Come on.
Bye.
Guys, I think we should get started.
- Okay.
- When should we start?
Two dishes after this,
we're getting desserts.
When we get the desserts,
we will introduce Chef Moon and Byeol-na.
- Then boom!
- Exactly.
That's the moment of tears.
- Right.
Now, let's start getting ready.
Gosh, this is exciting.
What's wrong?
We are in trouble.
The flash drive is gone.
- What?
- Hey!
Did you search everywhere?
- It's gone.
[ - What do we do now? ]
Does that mean we can't play it now?
But now is the perfect time to play it.
I have the file at home.
I will quickly go and get it.
Da-hoon, let me come with you.
No, you're too slow.
But I can't trust you!
What if you drop it somewhere
on your way back?
- Hurry up.
- Just go already. We don't have time.
- Make sure to come back in 10.
- Now go.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes.
This is why I said I can't trust you.
Seol-a, I don't think I can do this.
Go and bring the laptop on my desk.
Okay. You can count on me!
Who are you?
- What do we do?
- What's taking them so long?
The dinner is almost over.
Why aren't they coming?
Call him.
Hold on.
He left his phone here.
When they get back,
no one will be left here.
What should we do?
- I guess it's time for me to step up.
- What?
I, Bong-doo, am the master of stalling.
Ladies and gentlemen.
- Well...
- Fire!
- What?
- Pungcheonok!
- There's a fire at Pungcheonok!
- What?
- But Da-hoon and Seol-a are there!
- What happened?
Did Seol-a and Da-hoon go to Pungcheonok?
- Yes.
- They went there to bring something.
My goodness.
Chef Moon.
- Hurry!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
What's taking her so long?
Da-hoon!
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for Seol-a.
I got tired, so I asked her
to bring my laptop.
Hey!
You sent her home alone?
Yes.
What's the matter?
You idiot.
Seung-mo!
Darn it.
Seol-a.
Dad!
Seol-a, are you all right?
Dad, the house is...
I'm glad you're all right. Let's go.
Oh, my.
If it isn't Chef Moon Seung-mo?
[ Seung-mo! ]
Da-hoon.
Take Seol-a and go.
Seung-mo.
Go.
How does it feel
to see your precious things burn?
Do you now understand how I felt?
Tell me how you feel.
I don't feel anything.
Why can't you feel anything?
Why?
You're only pretending you're fine.
I can tell by looking at your eyes.
I know you want to kill me right now.
This reminds you of how your parents
were burnt to death, doesn't it?
This is more like it.
Hit me.
Hit me again.
You and I are the same.
All humans are the same.
Revenge, fury, and selfishness.
Am I wrong?
Yes, you are.
I hit you so you come to your senses.
Because I'm really fine.
I have something more precious than this.
[ Chef Moon! ]
[ - Chef Moon! ]
[ - Are you okay? ]
Chef Moon! What happened?
Are you all right?
Chef Moon!
Oh, my goodness!
My gosh.
Hurry up!
[ I hate fire so much. ]
[ But the villagers ]
[ looked after me and my dad. ]
[ That, I liked. ]
[ So I wasn't scared at all. ]
[ And the bad man... ]
[ Here's today's first news. ]
[ The former chairman
of Donghan International, Lim Chul-yong, ]
[ was caught red-handed
for committing arson ]
[ in an old house
in Seoha Village, Nonyang. ]
[ Crimes he committed in the past
are also being uncovered, ]
[ which is shocking the nation. ]
[ - Would you like to say a word? ]
[ - A word please? ]
[ Please hang on. ]
[ He got caught. ]
[ And as for my first love,
the handsome guy... ]
Donghan International will do away
with the conventional management system,
and adopt a new management system
with management specialists.
I would like to make the new Donghan
together with you.
[ He's become even cooler. ]
[ And as for Byeol-na,
who used to say she would leave... ]
Seol-a.
[ She didn't leave and she's staying here,
which is great. ]
What are you doing?
I'm writing in my diary.
Hey, you can even write now.
Yes. I learned it all while you were gone.
I'm really smart.
Yu-jin.
Would you like to go for a short walk?
Right now?
Why are we taking a walk so suddenly?
Just because it's nice outside
and I wanted to walk with you.
We met in the fall,
and it's already spring.
You're right.
I changed so much after meeting you.
I'm no longer anorexic,
and I'm no longer afraid
of cameras flashing.
And you're now a designer with a face.
You changed a lot too.
How?
You're now Chef Moon and a dad.
You're right.
Before I met you,
I was just a wandering chef.
But now, I'm rooted in Seoha Village,
am a father of a child,
have represented the village,
own a restaurant
where everyone works together,
and Yoo Byeol-na's love, Chef Moon.
You're right.
To be honest,
I never thought I'd become who I am now.
Even as a child,
I was more comfortable away from home.
Once I decided to become a chef,
I rarely came home
and traveled all across the country.
That's when I met great people
like Mr. Song.
After learning to cook Korean cuisine,
I went abroad.
I wanted to make Korean food for people
who don't even know where Korea is.
But isn't it weird
that all that time away from home,
I never thought I was lonely,
because I knew that my parents are
always here
and that there is Pungcheonok.
I realized this only recently.
The reason I could do whatever I wanted is
because I knew
that I had a home to come back to.
What are you saying?
Everyone is talking
about how the genius designer Bella is
reborn as Yoo Yu-jin.
They're all waiting for her next show.
- Chef Moon, I...
- I thought about it,
and this is
the only thing I can do for you.
Yu-jin,
don't worry and just leave.
Do whatever you want,
make whatever clothes you'd like,
and then come back
home.
The village people have prepared
something for you.
Let's go.
[ - Would you look at that?
- How adorable. ]
[ We told her to pick an object ]
[ and she's going right to her mom. ]
[ Right. ]
[ You look so happy
seeing your granddaughter. ]
[ That's right. ]
[ - Are you that happy?
- Yes. ]
[ Yu-jin, come here. ]
Grandfather...
[ Over there. ]
[ Look at that! ]
[ - Adorable.
- There you go. ]
[ She chose the thread!
She will have a long life. ]
[ No, she grabbed the thread
because her mom is a model. ]
[ She's going to make clothes for her! ]
[ - Is that right?
- Indeed. ]
[ How adorable. ]
[ Yu-jin, ]
[ are you going to make clothes for me?
That's so sweet! ]
[ Then become a designer, ]
[ so that you can make me
many pretty clothes, okay? ]
[ There you go. ]
[ This is so cute. ]
[ Just look at her. ]
[ She's beautiful. ]
[ Look here and smile! ]
[ Sir, you look so happy. ]
[ Bring some makgeolli! ]
[ Let's party all night long. ]
[ You're the best, sir. ]
Thank you, everyone.
Seol-a.
What's wrong?
Here, take this.
You're giving this to me?
You know
how much I love this necklace, right?
- Yes.
- Why then
would I give it to you?
I don't know.
Because I'm going to come back for it.
I love the necklace so much,
so I'm leaving it with you
to come back for it later.
I'm leaving.
You're leaving? Where to?
Don't leave!
Please don't leave.
Don't cry.
I'm not going to take this.
Seol-a...
Give it to me when you come back.
Promise me that you'll be back.
Here.
Da-hoon, here.
Hold on.
I've got some Nonyang garlic
that Bella loves so much.
Here are some dumplings too.
- Hey, there.
- This is some gochujang.
That's good.
Koreans can't live without gochujang.
That's right.
Should we pack her some more, then?
So, this is the end.
It won't be if you come back.
What's that?
Were you planning on
never seeing us again?
I don't do that.
If it's the end, it's the end.
If it's not, it's not.
Let's not make a promise.
That way,
we'll try our best.
I love you.
What?
How can I leave with you saying that?
We can't have
either of us regretting anything.
So, here I am, checking for the last time.
Me too.
Checking for one last time.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, everyone.
- Yes.
- Of course.
Seol-a, you too.
Bye, Seol-a.
Bye now.
Drive safe.
Bye.
- Bye now!
- Drive safe.
Hello!
You're back from school!
Yes, I am.
I hear that the kitchen renovation
at Pungcheonok is all done.
Yes.
All we need is the ssi-ganjang, then.
Let's start with the Hwangs.
I'll lead the way.
Do you really think there's something
so precious as the ssi-ganjang
in our village?
Exactly.
My heart was broken
when all of our ssi-ganjang dried out
from the kitchen fire at Pungcheonok.
That's why I'm going to try to look
for our own ssi-ganjang in the village.
That's meaningful, too.
Come on in first.
We have some old ganjang at home too.
Come and give it a try.
Let's go.
May I give it a try?
Of course.
We don't even need to try it.
This isn't it.
But you still have to give it a try.
Here.
Chef Moon, here.
Where's the next house?
Ms. Byung-chun's house.
Let's start over there
and make our way down.
Sure.
- This is not it.
- That's too bad.
Hello there.
You're here.
- What are you doing?
- Hey there.
I'm just getting my husband lessons.
What are you saying?
- You're looking for the ssi-ganjang?
- Yes.
Is this not it?
Come this way.
This family has good ganjang too.
Hyuk's mom!
Well, in that case, right this way.
Here.
Jang-su!
I'm here.
Hello there.
Thank you so much. Bye now!
You can stay for longer.
This way.
Bye now.
Goodness.
Bye!
This isn't it either?
Yoon-ja's home is the only one left.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
- Sure.
- When are we going to find it?
Let's go.
It's that way.
It smells good.
- What?
Dad, it smells very similar
to the old ssi-ganjang.
Really?
I think we've found it.
My grandmother made this ssi-ganjang,
and I've just been adding more to it
when I run out.
Is this really good?
The secret behind your amazing food was
this ganjang all along?
If you'd let me,
I'd like to use this
as Pungcheonok's ssi-ganjang.
Goodness!
Pungcheonok belongs to all of us.
If we can re-open the restaurant
with this ssi-ganjang,
I'd be more than happy to see that.
Does that mean that we can open
Pungcheonok once again?
- Awesome!
- Great!
We found it!
It was right here all along.
What a surprise!
Let's all try some.
Yes, Jang Madam?
I told you,
it's Madam Jang.
Who says Jang Madam?
That doesn't sound respectable at all.
Jang Madam, Madam Jang, same thing.
I'm busy designing some things. What's up?
Let's make this brief.
Why did you have to buy a winery
all the way in Australia?
There are so many wineries in France too.
You used to give me such a hard time
because you couldn't work anywhere else
other than at your studio,
[ but now, you're always there. ]
[ You're doing this on purpose,
aren't you? ]
This is so frustrating.
Stop beating around the bush.
Why did you call?
What?
Right.
When are you going to come back?
It takes over 24 hours
to get from the Gold Coast to Paris.
[ You should've prepared sooner! ]
Stop nagging!
I'm not a kid.
I can take care of it on my own.
I'm sick of your nagging.
You're sick of it, aren't you?
I'm mortified by it.
Had I picked up a rock from the ground
and gave it as much attention
as what I've given you,
the rock would've been flying in the air
by now.
Fine.
I'm going to start packing now.
By the way,
how is the other rock doing?
Is she good?
The other rock is quite a girl too.
She struggled at first,
but she's doing quite well now.
She's now used to working here.
We're going to take her with us
starting with the Rookie Designer Show.
[ If we find anyone with potential,
we'll have them as Hyun-a's apprentices. ]
At least that rock listens to me well.
Not all rocks are like you.
There's nobody in this world
that can make my blood boil like you do.
Come already!
I'm having a hard time putting up
with Madam Jang's anger.
She's hitting her menopause.
Just try to be good to her.
Right? I thought so.
Hey! Yoo Yu-jin! Lim Hyun-a!
I didn't say the menopause part.
It was Yu-jin, not me.
[ I have no idea why I'm here doing this
with you guys. ]
It's like the whole universe is forcing us
to stay together.
Exactly.
Let's be done with this relationship
in this life, okay?
That's my one and only wish.
Hey,
do you not keep in touch
with Chef Moon in Korea anymore?
Why ask?
[ We sent him an invitation
to your last show, ]
[ but he didn't respond. ]
He didn't respond?
Then he must be over me.
How can you be so ruthless
with your words?
Anyway, come quickly! Bye now.
All right.
How is it?
I think we've found the one.
[ Angle your knife diagonally
towards the body. ]
Right to the heart.
You have to stab deep right away.
My suitcase. Watch out!
- Why did you call me?
- Come and take this.
- Hey there.
- Yes?
- Come here.
- It looks amazing.
Let's put it here.
Chef Moon, I'm hungry. Give me some food!
Look at who it is!
- Yu-jin!
- Seol-a!
- Look who it is!
- It's Bella!
- Finally.
- You're here!
Bella is here, everyone.
What took you so long?
You're even prettier now.
Have you been staying healthy?
Yes, have you all been well?
- Of course.
Where's Chef Moon?
Yu-jin?
How have you been?
Byeol-na, you won't leave again, will you?
Then teach me how to make clothes.
Seol-a, do you want to become a designer?
Yes!
- What kind of clothes do you want to make?
- Dresses.
What kind of a dress?
You know, the ones that people wear
at weddings.
What for?
To make Byeol-na stay.
What about mine?
Don't worry. I'll make some for you too.
- Seol-a.
- Yes?
Here.
You're really giving it to me?
Of course. I promised.
[ Eccentric Chef Moon ]