(Episode 13)
You did well today.
You did very well yourself.
Oh, wait. Just a moment.
I bought this a while ago and wasn't able to give it to you.
Here.
Throw it away if you don't like it.
Put it on for me.
Go on home.
Thank you.
I...
Hey...
Thanks for the gift.
It's not exactly a gift.
How should I put it?
It's kind of like a Band-aid.
But don't think too much of it.
I kept noticing your scar, so I thought I'd give it to you.
Thank you so much for the Band-aid.
Right.
Gosh.
Why is he running?
He must be really embarrassed.
Maybe it's because I confessed everything like a loser.
But I feel so much better now.
Not me.
I never got to confess my biggest secret...
and become a sad loser.
What's that?
I never got to confess my feelings...
to the person I like.
So let me give you a word of advice.
Just confess how you feel if you don't want to be a loser.
I've become a good friend now, but that's not the case for you.
It's not too late.
Were you working out?
What's gotten into you? You rarely work out.
I love to exercise.
If I think about it, you really don't know much about me.
I heard Woo Joo started doing stage therapy again.
Good choice.
I didn't exactly do it for her.
I was the one who needed her help.
She's really good at making patients talk about their feelings.
You don't need to draw a line.
You guys would've ended up meeting each other again...
even if it weren't for stage therapy.
It just happened a lot faster than expected.
I think Woo Joo is...
experiencing transference with me.
(When a patient redirects their feelings for someone important)
It seems to have a very positive effect on her.
She must've relied on you a lot.
Do you think I should keep a distance?
Just treat her like you normally do.
Or you can start treating her right away.
Then she'll find out that her feelings aren't real.
Can you help me out a little?
I've encountered tons of borderline patients,
but why do you think I chose to introduce you to Woo Joo?
She's different from Se Yeon.
Don't avoid her or draw a line. Face her, for your own sake.
Wow, Young Won. You truly are my doctor.
I don't want to be your doctor.
A good friend is a good psychiatrist.
You listen and take my side.
I don't want to be a friend.
Then what?
Never mind.
It's just transference.
It's not real affection. It's transference.
I dreamt of the fire again.
Can you swap night duty with me?
- I can't. - Please, just once.
We swapped twice already.
Dr. Lee didn't come with you?
I doubt he has time to eat today. He's really busy.
- He can't even eat? - He can't.
- Enjoy your meal. - Thanks. I will.
- You too. - Thank you.
Will you stop it?
Dr. Noh, you like fried eggs, right?
Yes. How did you know that?
- Here. - Thank you.
Ji Sun, what should I stop doing?
I was talking to Woo Joo. You can eat.
Your doctors are really clueless.
Get up.
Are you that pleased?
Do you know what this bracelet is called?
My gosh. You named it already?
"Band-aid."
Darn you.
Get in there.
This is Assemblyman Ko Sang Moo. Say hello.
Hello. I'm Lee Si Joon.
Hello.
I'm Ko Sang Moo.
You must've seen many people like me,
so you're not surprised, are you?
When did the symptoms begin?
Last night.
It's the first time since his first outbreak when he was nine.
There had been signs of a few possible outbreaks.
When I was a lawyer before I joined the National Assembly.
Those signs disappeared shortly.
I believe you're stressed out over the upcoming hearing.
Can I be healed before the hearing?
- Not completely. - Dr. Lee.
I can reduce the symptoms with medication.
To see that this happened before the hearing,
I'm guessing the deities want me to realize my place.
Why would you say that?
You fought for laborers' rights your whole life.
You can't give up over something like this.
We will do our best...
and ensure you can attend the hearing.
Can you explain the situation right before the tics began?
Let's see...
You all did very well.
Thanks to you, the bill was passed.
Now let's work even harder on the upcoming project and bill.
- Yes, sir. - You all did so well.
Sir. Are you all right?
Mr. Ko Sang Moo.
He has a chronic motor tic disorder.
The first outbreak was when he was nine.
It occurred a few times in adulthood,
but the symptoms didn't last.
They stopped soon enough.
By Ko Sang Moo, do you mean...
Yes. The candidate for the Minister of Employment and Labor.
His hearing is coming up.
Then we must cure him before then.
That's not far off.
How should we treat him?
Of all neurotransmitters, tics are...
strongly connected to the dopamine system.
We should treat him with appropriate medication...
and carry out habit reversal training.
Although it's not common practice,
we could also carry out biofeedback therapy.
Prior to the hearing,
he must've been under great pressure.
We should quickly identify the cause with psychotherapy.
There's not much time.
I think we should do everything simultaneously.
I agree.
Woo Jung and Ji Hee,
focus on the patient's cranial nerve.
Noo Ri and Se Chan.
Carry out research for his psychotherapy.
Yes, doctor.
I can't work with Se Chan.
Do you enjoy scanning me?
What?
You've been eyeballing me up and down.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
You're mistaken.
It's disgusting.
Noo Ri.
What is wrong with her?
- Dr. In, check on her. - Sure thing.
What were you doing? Why did you take my photos?
I didn't.
Don't lie. I saw you.
Stop it. I didn't take photos of you.
Give me a break.
What is it, Noo Ri? What's the matter?
He took photos of me with his phone.
I saw you do it.
I didn't take any photos.
Take a look. I didn't photograph anything.
You must've hidden them!
You hid the photos so others can't find them!
What are you talking about?
I think I'm losing my mind.
I think the whole world saw my photo.
I think everyone's looking at me.
I keep looking for photos of me online in case they're there.
I keep regretting...
taking the subway and ending up getting my photo taken.
I should've splurged and taken a taxi.
Noo Ri, it wasn't your fault that your photo was taken.
It was just something like an accident.
I want revenge.
I want to hurt the man who took my photo.
He's paying the price.
He got criminal punishment for running around the park naked,
and he can't practice medicine anymore.
How about you take a few days off work?
I won't snap my neck doing this, will I?
My gosh. You don't have to worry.
It's your muscles that are twitching.
First of all, we'll begin by naming your tic.
We'll name it?
To become attached to it.
That's interesting.
What will you name it?
I think it's best we go with a term you're familiar with.
How about we call your tic "My fellow citizens"?
It's a phrase you people say a lot.
"My fellow citizens"?
Very well.
From now on, we'll call your tic symptom...
"My fellow citizens".
But before that symptom occurs,
I'm sure you experience something in advance.
For example, your neck might feel a bit heavy...
or a little stiff.
Right before my neck is about to move,
it tickles a little or sometimes feels a bit stiff.
I feel like I have to move it.
Then every time your symptom occurs,
try your best to move the opposite side of your neck...
although I know it's going to be hard.
But here's what's important.
Every time your symptom occurs, you must shout out its name.
"My fellow citizens!"
Just like this.
You're not joking, are you?
This is called HRT...
which is short for habit reversal training.
It's a very popular way to treat tic disorders.
By trying to move a muscle that is irrelevant to your tic,
it creates a competitive reaction and helps you stop your tic.
Let me show you one more time.
Okay. Right when you feel like your symptom is about to occur...
"My fellow citizens!"
Then you push your chin this way.
Okay, it's your turn now.
"My fellow citizens."
You need to be more confident. Say it out loud.
Let's try that one more time.
"My fellow citizens!"
That's exactly it! Great job!
Let's try one more time.
"My fellow citizens!"
The last one was better.
The key point to habit reverse training...
is to be aware of the signs that lead to the symptoms.
"My fellow citizens!"
In other words, it means the patient...
needs to become sensitive to their symptoms.
Let's try one last time.
When a patient has a tic disorder, you must distinguish them...
from patients who have Huntington's disease.
But Mr. Ko Sang Moo's neurological examination...
and brainwave tests all came out normal.
That means it got worse due to stress.
It was probably due to a psychological reason.
I wonder what it was that caused his tic disorder to reoccur.
(Han Woo Joo)
- The receiver cannot be reached. - Why isn't he picking up?
He was too busy to even eat lunch. He's probably too busy to pick up.
The only time I get to see Ji Hee is when she comes here for lunch.
It's normally hard to meet her.
Then I should go.
- Go where? - Today's my mom's birthday.
What mom?
Your adoptive mother who runs a chicken restaurant?
You still care about them?
When did I ever care so much?
Those people sent you back to the orphanage.
And not only that, but your adoptive father...
even took money from you.
Don't badmouth them.
They raised me for six years.
My adoptive father was the only person who gave me flowers...
when I graduated elementary school.
I should visit them often if I want them to forgive me.
I dreamt of the fire again.
That's because you still think of it.
What should I get for my mom's birthday?
Your mom's birthday?
You know what?
I'll give you a bag of trash. Why don't you give her that?
You're so mean.
You're an idiot.
(Luxury Chicken, Craft Beer)
They urgently put the place up for rent...
even though their contract period wasn't over yet.
It's been less than three weeks since I took over.
Do you really not know where they went?
How many times do I need to tell you?
I never even got to meet them.
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail...
- The receiver cannot be reached. - Darn it!
What do you want?
Mom!
Mom, why did you move your business without even telling me?
Did something happen?
It's your birthday today.
I'll leave as soon as I give you your gift.
You can't do this to me!
This was the only place I could come to see you!
You can't just leave without telling me!
Do you think I won't be able to find you?
I'm going to find you no matter what!
Mo... Mom.
Mom!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
His chief of staff told me that he rarely got much sleep...
because he was busy getting ready for the hearing.
On top of that, he's been helping laborers get reinstated...
and organized a support project for laborers.
He was also getting ready for an open forum for platform laborers.
And I heard Assemblyman Ko usually uses the subway.
- "The subway"? - Yes.
He once formed an organization to help improve...
the working conditions for subway conductors in Seoul.
And he even said assembly members still earn three times more...
than the average laborer in Korea even if their wage...
gets deducted by 50 percent.
So he gave out gifts to those who clean the National Assembly.
You must be a big fan of Assemblyman Ko.
Sir.
I think a man like him deserves to become...
the Minister of Employment and Labor.
I want to help him overcome his tic so he can attend the hearing.
He's receiving habit reversal training.
Make him do it 50 times a session.
Okay, I will.
(Han Woo Joo)
I guess you were really busy.
I called you a lot of times earlier.
Yes, I was busy today.
I guess this is why you don't have a girlfriend.
Why did you call me?
Dr. Lee.
Look up at the sky.
There's a full moon.
We might be apart.
But we're able to see the same moon.
I'm sorry, but I don't have time to look at the moon.
Can I meet you at the hospital?
Why? Is there something wrong?
Do I need a reason to meet you?
There's a chicken restaurant I used to enjoy going to,
but the owner suddenly changed.
The owner moved without even telling me.
How could this happen?
Are you crying?
I'm just so upset.
It's so upsetting.
You're crying because the chicken restaurant is gone?
It wasn't an ordinary chicken restaurant!
There are tons of chicken restaurants in Seoul.
I'm sure you'll find another place that suits your palate.
No, there's no other place like this one!
Let me tell you about this place in person.
- I'll go see you. - I don't have time for that.
I don't even like chicken.
Do you think I'm being like this because of chicken?
Then what's the issue?
Forget it.
I don't need your help.
What's her problem? She's being so ridiculous.
Is it not about chicken?
Where are you?
I guess you were waiting for someone to call.
Oh, Young Won, it's you.
What brings you all the way to the hospital?
I wanted to have coffee with you.
Thanks. This will have to do for dinner.
- You didn't eat dinner? - No.
You must have something to say to me.
You're good.
Is it because of Woo Joo?
What's wrong? Did something happen again?
I'm the problem.
I can't seem to be natural with her because of the transference.
I keep avoiding her calls, and every time she calls,
I find myself being cold to her.
I think I'm being more sensitive about it.
You also become a patient when you're with a borderline patient.
It's PTSD.
(PTSD: Post traumatic stress disorder)
Take your time. No one's rushing you.
What are you here to talk to me about?
To be honest,
eight years ago, I actually knew...
that Jeong Se Yeon might die.
I knew that, but I never told you anything.
The reason I'm telling you this...
isn't because I want to apologize and be forgiven.
It's because I want to tell you why didn't say anything back then.
Why are you laughing?
Gosh, you fool.
You must've been pretty hard on yourself because of that.
If you had told me,
do you think I would've been able...
to stop her from dying?
No.
She would've done everything she could...
to die in front of me.
After all, her goal was to torture me.
Don't you want to know why I didn't tell you?
No, I don't want to know.
Gosh, I'm starving. Let's go grab something to eat.
Why isn't she back yet? I can't even reach her.
She's not my friend. She's like a little baby.
She's like a seven-year-old girl.
Dr. Lee, are you here to eat?
- Do you have any food left? - Yes, have a seat.
Hello.
I've heard a lot about you from Woo Joo.
I'm Ji Young Won.
Hello.
Thank you.
- By the way, - Yes?
did Woo Joo have a bad day today?
No, not really.
She spent all day bragging about the bracelet you gave her.
That's nothing to brag about.
Dr. Lee, did she call you today?
Yes, she called earlier.
She was angry because the owner of a chicken restaurant...
- had changed. - What?
She must really like chicken.
Yes. Enjoy.
You gave Woo Joo a bracelet?
It wasn't exactly a gift. It was more like a Band-aid.
She has a scar on her wrist.
Young Won.
Make sure you never tell Woo Joo that you introduced her to me.
She'll think you abandoned her.
Don't worry.
I'm a doctor, too.
Eat up.
The bus will be arriving soon.
(We can help you get your money back!)
Hello, are you even able to find people?
You gave Woo Joo a bracelet?
It wasn't exactly a gift. It was more like a Band-aid.
She has a scar on her wrist.
Who's here at this hour?
What are you doing?
Didn't the doctor tell you about the precautions?
Do you think you're totally fine...
just because your tic symptoms have subdued a little?
I just wanted a nice, cold beer.
I won't drink it.
What are you doing? Get out.
What? I... Well...
You should go.
I had so much respect for you,
but I'm really disappointed.
This is so wrong.
How in the world...
could you think of drinking this alone?
This is better than your medicine, isn't it?
You're an interesting doctor.
- You're pretty interesting, too. - Me?
I heard you go to work by subway.
Why do you do that when you're a busy man?
I just do.
Sir.
It's hard, isn't it?
But you can't ever tell anyone how hard things are for you.
You always need to be careful...
of what you say and how you act when you're around others.
And you can't easily get angry at anyone either.
And it's not like you're free to enjoy a nice drink.
I bet it feels more comfortable to be here.
How do you know so well?
People tell me that I'm like a mind-reader.
I'm sure everyone struggles in life.
- But it's hard. - What gives you the hardest time?
The fact that I keep...
turning into a liar.
(Episode 14)
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to...
Is she upset?
Woo Joo.
You know you have stage therapy today, right?
What happened to the chicken yesterday?
(What happened to the chicken yesterday?)
My fellow citizens!
Assemblyman Ko, you have a great sense of humor.
You even named your symptom?
It was Dr. Lee's idea.
I love you!
That was my idea.
It'll be hard, but hang in there for a while.
Our staff are working their hardest to help you.
Sure.
Mr. Deputy Director. He can attend the hearing, right?
Of course he can.
Even our director's on your side.
You will make a full recovery.
That's just embarrassing.
- I'm a fan. - I'm honored.
Since you said you're my fan,
could I ask for a favor?
Yes. What can I do for you?
The director wants us to treat...
subway drivers who have panic disorders.
Why so suddenly?
Assemblyman Ko personally asked our director this favor.
- Personally? - Yes.
The panic disorder of subway drivers...
is probably about seven times worse than normal patients.
I'd like Dr. In to head this.
- Can you do it? - Of course.
Assemblyman Ko seems to have a lot of interest...
in the welfare of the subway drivers.
There's probably a personal reason we don't know about.
By the way, Dr. Lee,
the director emphasized that we must make sure Assemblyman Ko...
is discharged from this hospital feeling completely treated.
Our hospital's reputation is at stake, so give it your best.
No need to remind me. I'm trying my hardest to fix him.
There won't be a problem with him attending the hearing.
We can alleviate his condition with medication.
I'm continuing with the HRT session...
and today, I'm thinking of using stage therapy...
to find out the cause of his stress.
Okay.
Make sure you prepare plenty of material regarding panic disorder.
Yes, sir.
And check his counseling schedule...
- and confirm it. - Yes, sir.
All right, let's get to work.
(Ankang Supermarket)
Mom.
You're really creeping me out.
How did you find me?
I want to give you this.
Did you eat seaweed soup yesterday?
Yes. Since you came to give me this, I'll take it gratefully.
Mom, why did you close the chicken restaurant?
If you're done here, go.
Let me work.
I won't come often.
I'll just come sometimes during the holidays to say hi.
I should at least know where you are.
It makes me anxious if I don't.
I hate you! I don't even want to look at you!
Everything was a mess ever since I adopted you.
My husband's business went bankrupt, and my mom passed away.
And after you came last time, I ran out of customers.
Is running out of customers my fault too?
I don't want to be mean to you either.
So please, let's not see each other ever again.
You and I are ill-fated!
It's been ages since I sent you away.
Why do you still chase after me and call me your mom?
If you have time to find me, go find your real mom.
Can't you forgive me now?
I still...
have dreams about the fire.
I'm being tormented by guilt too.
I already forgave you for that.
But you were creepy since the first time I saw you.
I tried to understand since you were abandoned...
and wanted to raise you with love.
But I was wrong. I don't know why,
but you were a sick child.
I'm not doing this because you set that fire.
So please don't come to me anymore and look for your real mom.
Your misfortune is all because of your real mom.
Stop it!
- Don't touch me! - Stop!
Did you come here to do this?
To throw a fit in front of me?
I wanted to be forgiven.
I came here to be forgiven.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
You're out of your mind. You've totally lost it!
I'm so sick and tired of you.
I should've locked you up in a mental hospital.
I should've done it back then.
You're crazy.
You crazy brat!
The receiver cannot be reached. Please leave a message...
What on earth is she doing? I can't reach her.
Darn.
Dr. Lee, welcome.
Did you come to eat?
I can't get hold of Woo Joo.
She didn't come here either?
I can't reach her since last night.
- Really? - Dr. Lee, you said yesterday...
that she said the owner of the chicken restaurant...
changed, right?
Yes.
What does that chicken restaurant have to do with Woo Joo?
Woo Joo's adoptive mother owned that place.
Adoptive mother?
She raised Woo Joo for about six years.
Then...
If the owner changed,
that means she moved without Woo Joo knowing about it.
It was her adoptive mother's birthday yesterday,
so she probably went to see her with a gift.
She probably drank all night and fell asleep somewhere.
I'll go see if she's home.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
Here we go.
- Will it end here? - Okay, good.
- We did it! - Yes!
Nice shot!
The game's over. You should all leave.
- Good game. - That was fun.
- Good game. - Thank you.
Nurse Oh.
We have something to discuss with you.
Discuss? What is it?
You heard about Noo Ri, right?
I heard she took some time off. Is it serious?
She acted like it wasn't a big deal,
but I think she was just pretending to be okay.
She has a cranky personality, but she's so vulnerable mentally.
Speaking of which,
how can we help her in this type of situation?
Aren't you on bad terms with her?
My goodness, I knew it. She knows everything.
Our whole team knows about it.
In a situation like this,
there is one way to help Dr. Kang.
What is it?
The receiver cannot be reached. Please leave a message...
(Han Woo Joo)
The receiver cannot be reached.
- Hello? - Yes, what is it?
Where are you right now?
What is this about?
Regarding the stage therapy,
I think we should meet right now.
- I can't go today. - What?
Wait, but Woo Joo...
- Where are you right now? - I'm at home.
We'll stop at this rest area for 15 minutes.
- When you get off the bus, - It doesn't seem like home.
- please take all your belongings. - I'm on my way to meet my mom.
- Where to? - I'll call you later.
Woo Joo is on her way to see her mom.
Do you know where it is?
It sounded like she was on an express bus.
Thank you.
Do you know what you need the most right now?
A borderline patient.
I'm sick of borderline patients.
I never want to meet one again.
Until when do you think you can avoid it?
You must overcome it someday.
You know that...
a doctor grows once he meets a tough patient.
I already lost a patient who could've helped me grow.
I'll never receive another chance.
That person will appear in your life one day.
Someone who will make you into a better doctor.
I looked for you everywhere.
How did you get here?
How did you find me?
You invited me over for chicken.
I came for the chicken.
Wow, this is amazing! It's the sea!
How are you?
Was this it?
Where your mom carried you?
Yes.
That's why you said you left to see your mom.
This is all I remember about my birth mom.
She left me at an orphanage when I was six.
I don't remember anything else.
I deleted it all from my mind.
I met a good set of adoptive parents...
and lived happily until I was 12.
But they abandoned me.
The fried chicken place I mentioned yesterday.
My adoptive mother owned it.
She quit without so much as a word to me.
When a restaurant that you're a regular at closes,
it's the worst feeling.
You feel angry and betrayed.
Why won't you ask?
About what?
Why my adoptive parents abandoned me,
and why I keep looking for her after what she did.
Why would I make you bring up what must be sad memories?
Tell me about it when you want to, like just now.
I like how...
you won't ask.
You have more memories to come...
compared to the ones you already have.
How about...
we not have fried chicken?
I suddenly don't like it anymore.
It's so greasy and I worry about my cholesterol levels.
Okay, then.
- What's that on your hand? - What?
What happened?
It's nothing.
Do you know how you feel?
- What? - I don't know how I feel.
I miss my adoptive mother, but then I hate her.
I go from this to that a dozen times a day.
But...
are there people who are freaky and scary from birth?
How could there be such people?
The fact that you're born into this world is a blessing.
Even if we were abandoned?
In life,
how you were born isn't important at all.
How you live is much more important.
You don't believe me?
Then live a great life.
There will come a moment when you think of what I said.
I enjoyed the noodles. I'm so full.
What's wrong?
I can't find my car key.
Look carefully.
It's gone.
Wait here.
- Did you find it? - No.
I must've dropped it while running around looking for you.
What should I do? Should I call the police?
Let's look for it.
At this time of night?
Woo Joo.
Woo Joo?
Woo Joo!
Han Woo Joo!
I'm right here.
Where were you?
Didn't you hear me call you?
Are you trying to make me lose my mind?
Why did you take off your shoes?
I was looking for this.
Where did you find it?
You must've been really worried.
Did you think I was dead?
That I took off my shoes and jumped into the sea?
Put on your shoes. Let's go home.
It feels great...
to have someone worry about me.
- Put them on already. - This is great.
How did you find it?
I just noticed it.
Like a miracle.
This is all I have to offer you.
It's fine. Thank you.
- Please sit. - Okay.
Is this where and how you sleep?
Yes. We have no choice if we're to drive the first train.
We get up an hour before to check the carriages.
I heard from our union that...
you decided to help us.
Yes. I came to ask a few questions before that.
I heard there was an accident a month ago.
Was it caused by a panic disorder?
That accident?
He felt suffocated.
So he stopped the train...
and just jumped out.
Right in front of an oncoming train.
We work alone,
so if something like that happens,
there's nothing we can do.
- Then were you... - Yes.
I was diagnosed with a panic disorder.
It got worse these days,
so I have a convulsion whenever I board a train.
It's practically terminal.
Panic disorders can be cured.
We will help you.
Why would such a large hospital help people like us?
Because we're doctors. Do we need another reason?
- Thank you so much. - My pleasure.
I will leave, then.
Oh, okay. I'll take that for you.
Thank you.
The man in the middle.
Isn't this Assemblyman Ko Sang Moo?
That's him. Of all the assemblymen,
he's the one who cares the most about our work environment.
Is the man next to him a driver like you?
The man who died in the recent accident.
That's him.
Did you wait for a long time?
No. I just got home.
There's nothing to eat.
You don't cook and just drink alcohol?
I eat at Gongbap Restaurant.
You're in a good mood.
Didn't you fight with your adoptive mom?
I felt like I'd die,
but Dr. Lee made me feel better.
He's a good doctor.
He even went to the seaside.
He really worries about me a lot.
Why is he so good to me?
Obviously it's because he's a doctor and you're his patient.
Wrong. It's more than that.
- He has feelings for me. - I doubt that.
It's true.
Ji Hee told me that...
Dr. Lee doesn't...
see his patients just in his office.
- Right. - Wherever they go,
he goes with them.
It's like...
Was it Cha Dong Il? That fake cop.
He even patrolled with that guy.
Exactly.
And takes patients on walks.
Didn't he take you to a landfill...
to throw away your watch?
That is how Dr. Lee treats people.
I know that.
Today, I saw his true emotions.
To him,
I am special.
So...
People who see psychiatrists...
tend to get the wrong idea about...
their doctors' good intentions.
Because they listen so intently and are so kind and gentle.
I didn't get the wrong idea.
- Woo Joo. - Yes.
Did you know that...
Dr. Ji sent you to Dr. Lee?
What are you talking about?
Why would she do that?
- Said who? - I heard it myself.
When a doctor sends a patient to another doctor,
isn't it because there's only one reason?
If Dr. Lee really thinks you're special,
wouldn't it be that reason?
Here.
Assemblyman Ko and Seoul City...
set up a team to improve the drivers' working conditions.
The two-driver system...
was scrapped due to budget reasons.
Basically, someone died...
as a victim of the solo system.
Because of that, Assemblyman Ko must be plagued by guilt.
That would've caused acute stress.
If we get rid of Assemblyman Ko's guilt,
his tic will disappear too.
How can we eliminate his guilt?
A man's already dead.
If he were able to value his promise,
wouldn't that help?
It would,
but that's not something that can happen overnight.
HRT, was it?
I think that has been a great help.
The medication is only temporary relief.
Then my tic will come back when I go off the medication?
I think I figured out the cause of your tic.
Did you really?
Do you remember this man?
There's a subway line...
that the drivers call "Hades Line".
A dark, endless tunnel.
They can't take toilet breaks,
and some even wet themselves.
It broke my heart to hear that.
That's why you promised him that...
you'd ensure they could work in teams of two.
While you were unable to keep your promise,
that man lost his life.
It all felt like...
my fault.
Shall I give you an injection?
No. It's fine.
Thinking of that driver...
brought back my fellow citizens at a higher speed.
I'm not the one who can cure your illness.
You are.
Of course, we can reduce the symptoms with medication,
but that's only a temporary remedy.
The true treatment...
is something only you can do.
Isn't Ms. Han Woo Joo scheduled for 4 p.m.?
What do you want to confirm with me?
I heard that you...
referred me to Dr. Lee Si Joon.
No. I didn't refer you to...
What is it that I have?
What do I have...
that you had to send me off in secret?
Why did you send me to Lee Si Joon?
(Fix You)
You abandoned me!
She might be fixated on you even more out of her anger for me.
I think it's fate that we met.
He has a fit almost every day,
and you want him to drive?
Do you think that makes sense?
Are you turning into Lee Si Joon?
For panic disorders at least, I want to treat them Si Joon's way.
They walked with arms linked? In the hospital?
This is fate. It has to be fate.
Just because we feel anxious...
doesn't mean we must become timid.
The patient you put in charge of stage therapy.
Make her quit immediately.