(Episode 15)
Why did you send me to Lee Si Joon?
I asked you countless times...
to tell me the name of my condition.
But you never told me.
You frequently have conflicts with the people around you...
because you have trouble controlling your emotions.
And you keep having the same dream...
which are all symptoms of anxiety disorder.
Just tell me the name of my illness!
When a patient has a personality disorder,
we normally don't tell them the name of the illness.
Not only is it difficult to determine the illness,
but it's also bad for their treatment...
when patients are given the wrong information.
I personally don't think you have any problems living your daily life.
I know you often get angry...
and have a wide range of emotions,
and that may cause difficulties with your personal relationships.
But everyone lacks something and feels anxious sometimes.
If you know me so well,
why did you send me to another doctor?
That's because Dr. Lee is a better doctor than I am.
I see. Then I guess you're a bad doctor.
Why did you always pretend like you didn't know anything...
every time I mentioned Dr. Lee?
You practically made a fool out of me.
- Woo Joo. - You abandoned me!
Why are you angry?
Is it because I didn't tell you the name of your illness?
I just gave you an answer to that.
Then is it because I introduced you to Dr. Lee? Well, that's not true.
You two had already met before I even introduced you guys.
I only asked him to cooperate after I found out about that.
The reason I'm angry...
is because you abandoned me!
But it doesn't matter.
I'm used to getting abandoned.
You're just the same as my birth and adoptive moms who abandoned me.
I thought you'd be different.
Because you're a doctor.
I won't come here again.
Then the reason Lee Si Joon was nice to me...
was purely because I was his patient?
Woo Joo!
Han Woo Joo!
No. I saw it.
What I saw was real.
He was really worried about me.
Woo Joo's furious.
She thinks I abandoned her.
Don't worry too much.
Si Joon, what worries me is...
she might be fixated on you...
even more out of her anger for me.
This is transference.
What should we do?
You figured out the cause of Assemblyman Ko's tic?
Yes. I figured it out by chance when I visited the subway conductors...
to ask about their panic disorders.
Good job. You did great.
The director was very pleased.
You put him on medication.
Me?
Of course. You figured out the cause.
I'll deal with the rest.
I'm late, aren't I?
No, it's fine.
I just came over after waiting a bit.
Come inside.
Do we have to talk in your office?
We don't have to.
Shall we go for a walk?
I'll decide where we'll go.
Who was that?
A musical actor who helps with stage therapy.
Oh, her?
What's their relationship?
There is no relationship.
They're walking arm-in-arm and it's nothing?
Ms. Han is Dr. Lee's patient too.
His patient? What does she have?
I don't know.
Then what?
Si Joon gave his patient a part-time job?
I think she became a patient after starting her job.
Each time someone abandoned me,
I thought it only natural.
Because my birth mom abandoned me.
But then you said that...
I'm not someone who deserves to have...
a boyfriend who cheats on me.
You said that I changed other people's lives.
I think...
it's fate that we met.
What do you think?
I'm not sure.
Rather than say it's fate,
I think there's a reason we met.
- A reason? - Like...
Everything that happens to me,
whether it's good or bad,
happens for a reason. That's how I see it.
I met you...
for a certain reason. That's what I think.
That is fate.
I think it's slightly different from fate.
No. This is fate. It has to be fate.
If it's not, all the comfort you gave me is a lie.
- Woo Joo. - I have to go.
You're leaving? I barely even started.
There's always tomorrow.
Oh, dear. She just dropped a bomb.
"Fate"?
He must've been flustered.
- Why? - I told you.
If you mention fate when he thinks you're just a patient,
wouldn't that make him feel uncomfortable?
That's what I thought at first.
I denied what I felt too.
I'm bad at controlling my emotions,
so I thought I had fallen for a doctor again...
who happened to show up when I was feeling lonely.
But?
But I realized for sure after coming back from the beach.
We have something special.
What's that?
Are you thinking...
a doctor's way out of my league...
when I was abandoned by two moms?
Why would you say that?
I'm afraid you'll get hurt again.
I know what you're worried about.
But Dr. Lee's different.
Look at Ji Young Won.
She was so sweet, but she ditched me in the end.
Now Dr. Lee is all I have left.
He is different.
He'll be different.
My fellow citizens.
Then it's a matter of time before Assemblyman Ko's cured, right?
Yes.
If he fully recovers, attends his hearing,
and someone mentions the tic,
wouldn't he say that...
the Eun Kang staff cured him?
- You did very well. - Thank you.
(National Assembly, Republic of Korea)
As of this moment,
I stand down...
as a candidate for Minister of Employment and Labor.
The reason...
is not the tic...
that you clearly see I have.
For a long time, I worked hard to ensure the safety of...
Seoul's subway service,
by working to improve the conductors' working environment.
I even made them a promise.
"Make a correction."
- "Make a correction." - Working in teams of two.
Reduced work hours.
More safety personnel.
Improved working conditions.
But I couldn't keep any of those promises.
Because of the promises I couldn't keep,
not long ago,
another conductor...
lost his life.
The tic you see that I have...
is the price I'm paying for not keeping my word.
I'm not the one who can cure your illness.
You are.
Of course, we can reduce the symptoms with medication,
but that's only a temporary remedy.
The true treatment...
is something only you can do.
Thanks to him, I was able to look back.
Now I feel much at ease.
From now on, as an assemblyman,
I'll improve employee stability, abolish discrimination,
and improve working conditions by reforming existing laws.
So that those who work in the low places, behind the scenes...
can receive fair pay for their labor,
I will put in all my effort.
- Assemblyman. - I have a question.
- Can I ask something? - I have a question!
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
If you found the cause, you should've treated him.
You sent him away?
The tic was caused by...
acute stress due to guilt.
I believed he had to be free from that to be completely cured.
He's the only one who knows how to free himself.
Why do doctors exist?
If guilt is what caused his tic,
you're supposed to do everything you can to treat him.
Why would you make him overcome it on his own?
I came to a conclusion that it'd be way faster for him...
to overcome it on his own by actually keeping his promise...
rather than relying on medication and psychotherapy.
Are you saying you made him leave so he'd keep his promise?
Well, that wasn't my intention.
But I guess that's how he understood it.
You just had to use medication to ease his condition...
so he could attend the hearing. Was that so hard to do?
Everyone does that.
You pretty much neglected a patient.
You could've treated him, but you didn't.
I never neglected him.
And I never gave up on treating him either.
As his doctor,
I chose a different method rather than medication...
which would've only been a temporary solution.
And I don't think my method was wrong.
More importantly,
in order for him to fully recover...
"Fully recover"?
You talk as if this is some kind of surgery.
There's no full recovery in psychiatry.
It's a life-long journey.
You're so arrogant.
You are one incredible doctor.
How could you treat an illness without medication?
It's impossible.
How can we think of building a medical psychiatry center...
when we can't even treat a tic disorder?
Dr. Oh and Dr. Park. I want you guys to think this over.
Okay, ma'am.
My gosh.
Sir, do you really think I made the wrong choice?
Was that really your best choice?
Yes.
I'm on my way to do a lecture for the training. You should come.
"Training"?
Isn't that for 1st and 2nd-year residents?
So what?
Why is he so angry?
Okay, I'll go.
Now, we're going to practice how to deal with a crisis...
that sometimes occur to doctors during treatment.
The most frequent type of crisis...
is meeting a violent patient.
Dr. Lee, come here.
- Me? - Come on.
Let's think of Dr. Lee...
as a violent patient.
Okay. Now, come at me.
My gosh, I can't do that in front of the kids.
It's okay. Come on.
My goodness.
- Come on. - My gosh.
Did you see that?
This is how you oppress violent patients.
What was that for?
Take him back to his seat.
My gosh, my back hurts. I don't think I can move.
- Wait a minute. - Are you okay?
- It hurts so much. - You're being a crybaby.
Take him back to his seat. Go on.
Okay.
Stop exaggerating.
Things would be very simple if we could do what I just did,
but I'm sure not a lot of doctors know how to do that.
Right?
Young Seok, turn off the lights.
Okay.
When you encounter a violent patient,
- what's most important... - Gosh, my back.
- is to keep yourself safe. - This is killing me.
Dr. Lee.
Does it hurt that much?
Dr. Noh.
- I can't... - Woo Jung.
Yes, sir.
What do you need to do when a patient refuses medication?
First, you must ask them why they're worried, scared,
or feel reluctant to medication and hear them out.
You must remind them that the pros of taking medication...
are far greater than the possible side effects...
that may or may not occur.
I never asked you.
- Sir. - Yes?
Many patients experience transference during treatment.
How are we supposed to deal with that?
Dr. Lee, why don't you answer the question?
Well, when a patient experiences transference,
you must maintain a neutral attitude.
And it's important not to get swayed by how they treat you.
You must remember that you're a doctor...
and do your best to remain objective.
And most importantly,
it's crucial to treat your patient like you always have.
She's so happy.
Hello. Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
We're here.
My gosh, I'm starving.
Is it just the three of you?
Young Seok and Yoo Mi are going to eat at the hospital.
- Thank you. - No problem.
What should I eat today?
Excuse me.
I'm sick of getting spam calls.
Hey, what's the name of this song?
I don't know the name of the song.
I just downloaded it because I liked it.
It's "Vocalise" by Rachmaninoff.
Do you like classical music?
My sister majored in cello. She was in a symphony orchestra.
Stop talking nonsense and just eat your food.
- You'll get your meals soon. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Why is your sister no longer in a symphony orchestra?
She told me not to talk nonsense.
Just eat.
Dr. Lee, aren't you coming to eat dinner?
I need to go home.
I need to do a live podcast today.
I haven't recorded anything yet.
I see.
"Podcast"?
Did you get a call from the Social Welfare Team?
There's stage therapy tomorrow.
Yes, I got the call.
If we have time after the stage therapy,
- let's have our therapy session. - Okay.
(Doctor Lee Si Joon)
(Gongbap Restaurant)
- Here's your food. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Everyone feels anxious.
We look left and right before we cross the street.
We wear seatbelts.
We don't leave our homes when there's a storm.
We may not be able to acknowledge it,
but anxiety helps us get through all the difficult moments...
we often encounter in life.
The first place that perceives anxiety...
is our amygdala which is located deep down the limbic system.
And in order to calm the anxiety we feel,
we need certain types of neurotransmitters such as serotonin,
GABA, and norepinephrine.
Neurotransmitters are created...
by a certain person or a thing.
It could be someone you know...
or your favorite activity.
Anxiety can be divided into normal and pathological anxiety.
And it's the latter one that causes problems.
Pathological anxiety...
is when you try to avoid certain things or situations...
that aren't normally considered as threats.
For example, I'm talking about people with panic disorders,
social anxiety, or social phobia...
which is when people have difficulties forming relationships.
I just got a message.
"I get anxious every time I become close with someone."
"I get scared that they might abandon me."
"And I fear that they might become miserable because of me."
To be honest, I also have a psychological illness.
I get extremely scared...
when I'm faced with a certain situation.
I have an offer to the person who sent me this message.
Why don't we overcome our illnesses together?
- Sure. - We can't live in fear forever...
just because we have anxiety disorders.
Let's be confident and try our best to overcome this.
Okay.
To be frank, we're all sick in some ways.
We just haven't gotten diagnosed yet.
A psychical disorder...
isn't a characteristic. It is a person's condition.
Therefore,
it can always change depending on the situation I'm in.
In other words,
your illness will go away once your condition gets better.
And that is why the best medicine is to have a peaceful mind.
This is the Soul Repairman.
Hey, you're here.
I can hardly recognize you outside.
How do you feel?
I feel a lot better now.
I can come outside now.
Why are you sitting so far away?
I still feel uncomfortable around men.
You're a guy, too.
Okay then. You can listen from there.
Everyone's worried about you.
I was surprised to get a call from Ji Hee.
I don't think you'd want to get treated by a male doctor.
So I'll introduce you to a female doctor. Is that okay?
I've actually been looking for one.
Thank you.
Lots of fun things are happening at the hospital.
You should quickly come back if you don't want to be a loner.
I already agreed to have a meal with the others.
Six conductors will be getting treated for their panic disorders.
I'm going to do counseling with them first.
And once that's over,
Woo Jung will give them exposure therapy.
Okay, sir.
I also requested for stage therapy to the Social Welfare Team.
- Se Chan, you give me the updates. - Okay.
How many people do you plan to treat in total?
The labor union gave me a list of 15 people for now.
I'm also ready to take photos.
- Photos for what? - The deputy director told us...
that today is going to be a historical day for our hospital.
So he wants me to take photos and send them to the PR Team.
He also wants us to take a group photo.
Is he nuts?
Does he want to disclose our patients?
Sir, what do you mean you can't come?
I'm sorry. I know you're trying to help.
But if I go to the hospital,
there won't be anyone to replace me.
Sir, are you okay?
Sir, are you really okay?
Okay, I'll quickly call you back.
Okay, bye.
None of the conductors can make it today.
Why?
Dr. In.
- Where are you going? - Seoul Metro.
Are you going to complain?
We already settled everything with their superiors...
and even set an appointment. This is absurd.
Don't they know whom we're doing this for?
How could they tell a guy...
who gets panic attacks every single day...
to go to work instead of the hospital?
How did he sound over the phone just now?
He had trouble breathing. I'll see you when I get back.
Wait.
Why don't we just go to them?
What?
If they're short of hands and don't have time to come here,
we can go to them instead.
You can go to Seoul Metro and complain to their superiors,
but his condition seems urgent, so let's deal with that first.
What do you plan to do there?
Are you going to do therapy while they drive the subway?
That's not even necessary.
What they need to know...
is that they're not alone.
Dr. In, you're the doctor in charge, so it's up to you.
If you don't want me to go, I won't.
- Se Chan. - Yes, sir?
I want you to call the operation control center...
and ask them which subway station we need to go to at what time...
in order to get on the subway that's driven by Mr. Park Jong Woo.
Okay, sir.
Go and deal with what's urgent.
I'll take care of the rest.
My gosh, get going already.
We have an hour to get to the station.
Hello.
- You're here already? - I came a bit early, didn't I?
Oh, dear. Stage therapy got canceled today.
- Why? - I should've called beforehand.
I'm sorry.
What?
They went all the way there to treat the conductor?
Yes, I also wanted to go, but I didn't.
Sir, I'm very confident about treating panic disorder.
I've been doing a lot of research about drug treatment too.
Please help me so I can treat them, sir.
We already offered to treat them,
but they rejected it.
Is there a way to change their minds?
I might pack up some meds and visit them myself next time.
You're starting to sound like Si Joon.
I don't ever want to be like him.
But when it comes to treating panic disorder,
I'm more than willing to do it his way if necessary.
The director is upset about what happened with Assemblyman Ko.
But I guess we could talk to her.
Please help me, sir.
- Is this it? - Yes.
We need to get on the next train.
If we miss it, we need to go to another station.
- How much time do we have? - Two minutes.
The train is now approaching.
The inner circle line is now approaching.
The screen doors are opening.
The screen doors are closing.
Yes, how can I help you?
Hello, is this Mr. Park?
- Who is this? - I'm Dr. Lee Si Joon,
a psychiatrist at Eun Kang Medical Center.
You didn't come to the hospital today,
so we came instead.
How do you feel right now?
Is everything okay?
You... You came all the way here?
I'm right next to you, sir.
I'm right behind the door.
So don't worry and drive safely.
I'm going to stay with you until we reach the last station.
And nothing will happen during that time.
So don't worry and drive safely.
Okay.
I feel relieved to hear you cry.
I was worried that you might be out of breath.
But I guess that's not it.
Sir, you're not alone.
Don't worry.
Cheer up, sir.
Did you hear that?
You're not alone.
We're all right behind you.
- Cheer up. - Cheer up.
- We respect you. - Cheer up.
- Cheer up. - You're amazing.
You can do it, sir.
Every time we drive a subway, it lasts three hours.
But we're pretty much...
inside a tunnel during the whole time.
I really thought I might die earlier.
But you saved my life.
The fact that someone's next to me...
is more than enough to put me at ease.
I'm sure you already heard this from the doctor you previously met,
but let me remind you that your panic disorder can be cured...
by taking drugs and doing a few exercises.
You should come to the hospital and get it treated.
We can't always come here to treat you.
Okay, I'll go to the hospital with my colleagues.
(Episode 16)
Hello.
I'm the deputy director of this hospital.
Oh, I see.
You're the actor who helps our stage therapy sessions, right?
How did you know that?
Oh. I saw you last time.
- Walking with Dr. Lee. - I see.
I recognized you just now and came over to say hi.
What are you doing here? Are you waiting for someone?
I'm waiting for Dr. Lee.
Have you two known for a long time?
We met over a patient called Cha Dong Il.
Oh, that's right.
He gave you a hard time, didn't he?
Still, thanks to that incident, I met Dr. Lee.
I see.
The conductors didn't show up today?
I'm trying to sort that out now.
Is it so hard to come here?
Forget about that for now. Come with me.
Where are you going?
What?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Exactly.
It makes so little sense that I came straight over.
Dating a patient? Is he in his right mind?
Mr. Deputy Director. Dr. Lee isn't dating Ms. Han.
I just confirmed it myself!
I asked Ms. Han in person!
What is it you really want to say?
What do you mean?
A psychiatrist is dating one of his patients.
What if the word were to get out?
Our center will be humiliated.
Our image already hit rock bottom because of Assemblyman Ko.
Si Joon did mess up with his treatment of the assemblyman.
But even if we consider that, don't you think this is crass?
What? Crass? What's crass? How is this crass?
Do you think I'm making a fuss over nothing?
Dr. In, you tell me. You saw them walking with their arms linked.
Sir, that was...
Did you see it or not? Yes or no?
Is it true?
Yes.
- You did well today. - Thanks.
Woo Jung, check on the inpatients.
I will.
- Good job, doctor. - Good job.
Woo Joo.
When did you come over? I kept an eye out.
Were you waiting for me?
I just couldn't go home.
Why couldn't you go home?
My finger...
hurt so much.
How come?
When you ran past me,
your jacket brushed my hand.
It was just cloth,
but it hurt so much as if I'd been cut by a knife.
As if it were a real knife.
I couldn't take a step after that.
Have you ever experienced something like that before?
When was that?
When my adoptive mother gave me up,
she took me back to the orphanage.
She gave me a five-dollar bill...
and turned away.
The hem of...
the skirt she was wearing brushed by my fingers.
At that time as well, my fingers stung and hurt...
as if I'd been cut by a knife.
What are you doing?
Touch this. See if it cuts you.
That's just how it felt to me. I'm not saying I was really cut.
Happy now?
You felt that way...
because of...
your painful memories.
Dr. Lee.
Am I very sick?
Tell me honestly.
Dr. Ji Young Won sent me to you.
Dr. Ji said...
it was a collaboration between doctors.
Am I so badly broken somewhere that...
two doctors need to collaborate to treat me?
Woo Joo.
I'm sick myself.
How so?
My soul catches a cold often.
For no reason.
The people I go to for healing...
are my patients.
I gain comfort and solace by treating them.
The drum beats you played for me were a great help and comfort.
Whenever I feel down, I think of your performance,
and it makes me feel better.
I said this on my podcast yesterday,
but there's no person who isn't sick.
They just haven't been diagnosed yet.
While treating you,
I'm treating myself.
Just a moment.
(Drum Beats)
I just sent you the drum beat.
Listen to it whenever your soul catches a cold.
I read somewhere that this works really well.
When you listen to the drums, think of my performance too.
I'll share something else next time.
Okay.
Okay. Then...
how about we two patients...
do a high-five?
Okay.
Come on.
Once more.
1, 2.
I knew you'd do that.
- 1, 2. - 3!
- Gosh. - One last time.
1, 2, 3.
I think Dr. Lee's really amazing.
How could he think of visiting his patients?
He doesn't see his patients just in his office.
Whether it's their home or work, he follows them all over the place.
I wish I could join Dr. Lee's team.
Should I ask Dr. In to send me?
Se Chan. Dr. In might give you extra work.
I heard that patients are already comparing the two doctors.
I got dumped even before sharing my feelings to Si Joon.
Before I even said anything.
Dong Hyuk. I feel the worst ever.
What happened now?
A patient dumped me. Han Woo Joo.
She found out I sent her to Si Joon...
and blamed me for abandoning her.
She's borderline.
Isn't it natural for her to get angry over such things?
It's a complete and serious case of transference.
She relies on Si Joon a lot.
Does Si Joon know that too?
Of course.
It'll be hard on him too.
He can't do anything.
Then I don't have to worry.
About what? Is something wrong?
Our deputy director thinks they're dating.
And? Did he make a fuss of it?
Is there a scandal?
It could be bad if word gets out.
It seems to be okay so far.
If it becomes an issue, you should help him out.
Why should I do that?
I will stop standing in Si Joon's shadow.
What do you mean?
I'll send over a patient. She's one of our residents.
She has social phobia and anxiety issues.
Don't change the subject. What were you trying to say?
What kind of patient is Han Woo Joo?
A borderline.
What?
You let a borderline patient do stage therapy?
I found out after I asked her to do it.
Why does that matter?
She's doing so well on stage therapy.
We shouldn't be the ones discriminating patients...
when our goal is to stop them from being discriminated.
Is Han Woo Joo experiencing transference right now?
How did you know?
The deputy director said you two are going out.
You're not, right?
What are you talking about?
I know it too.
If I just wait patiently,
her condition will improve on its own,
so I'm just waiting.
Then why did you link arms with her?
That's because she acted so suddenly.
If I refused, she could've been embarrassed.
Then she could've been hurt again or something.
You better be careful.
The deputy director is waiting for you to make a mistake,
and the director is also sensitive because of Assemblyman Ko.
No good will come from this if the director finds out.
Okay.
Make sure you draw the line so she's not mistaken.
And never meet her personally besides in the hospital room.
Why aren't you answering me?
You sound like my dad who has dementia.
Do you think I'm saying this for no reason?
If this is because of what happened eight years ago, don't say it.
It's different from then.
What should I wear?
(Eun Kang Medical Center's Medical Team...)
(Cures a Conductor with Panic Disorder)
My gosh. How did you think of going there yourself?
Mr. Oh, wasn't Dr. In's idea so brilliant?
Dr. In is really unpredictable.
He visited the patient himself, which is rare lately.
You talked with the conductor through an emergency phone?
Ma'am, it wasn't me who went. It was Dr. Lee.
Dr. In asked him to go.
Whoever it was,
it's important that you came up with this brilliant idea.
I really lost face because of Assemblyman Ko's issue,
but thanks to you, I suddenly feel so much better.
Dr. Park, did you read the newspaper?
Dr. In did something truly amazing.
Yes, I just read it.
Dr. In took care of the total mess...
Dr. Lee made.
Dr. Park, did you check what I said to you yesterday?
He said it's not true.
- What's this about? - Well, it's...
It seems like Dr. Lee...
is in a personal relationship with a patient he's treating.
I told you it's not true.
The patient is just experiencing transference.
I checked myself.
"Transference"?
Then they shouldn't have linked arms inside the hospital.
They linked arms inside here?
Don't take it the wrong way, ma'am.
I'll ask him myself it's I'm mistaken or not then.
Did you sleep well?
In order to help Ms. Yang sleep better last night,
we gave her a drug with a stronger anxiolytic effect.
Since the effect of sleep improvement...
differs between each patient,
why don't we prescribe her an antianxiety drug as well?
That sounds good.
She's been sleeping ever since her guardian came last night.
I'll call you when she wakes up.
Okay.
Yes.
Did the deputy director tell her?
Explain what?
Okay.
Why didn't you ask me to come to your office?
I didn't want to waste your time when you're busy.
I heard something that made me feel uncomfortable.
You know what I mean, right?
No, I have no idea what you mean.
I heard you're in a personal relationship with a patient.
Is that true?
Did you just scoff?
You must be talking about Han Woo Joo.
She's just a patient to me.
Of course there's nothing going on between us.
Explaining this to you like this feels so ridiculous.
Is this because of what happened with Assemblyman Ko?
Dr. Lee, have you lost your mind?
Anyone would go nuts after hearing something absurd like this.
I don't regret my decision.
It was the best decision I could make as his doctor.
Are you trying to get emotional with me through this attitude?
Fine, then.
Mr. Oh, cut all funding for Dr. Lee's research as of today.
If he wants to go to another hospital, just let him.
Yes, ma'am.
If I hear another similar rumor, I won't tolerate it.
And that patient you put in charge of stage therapy.
Make her quit immediately.
- When did you come? - Just now.
I made this for you.
Thank you.
- I should get going then. - Wait, Woo Joo.
I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid I can't treat you today.
Something suddenly came up...
so I have to cancel all my appointments.
That's a relief. Gongbap Restaurant was so busy today,
so I was thinking of rescheduling anyway.
I'll call you about your new appointment.
Okay. Bye.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
I thought Lee Si Joon would be different...
but he wasn't.
He's the same as everyone else.
I...
I was abandoned again.
I guess I'm really...
a nuisance to everyone.
It's my fault Lee Si Joon became like that...
and I feel so sorry.
But I also hate him so much!
I'm sorry, Ji Sun.
I really didn't want to cry in front of you ever again.
I really didn't want to cry...
I'm sorry.
First of all, this treatment will use simple tools.
You'll practice being exposed to...
the similar emotional, physical changes you feel under fear...
when you have an episode.
First, we'll train for nausea and dizziness.
- Do you feel okay? - I guess.
You have one minute left.
That's enough. You can stop now.
Now take a deep breath.
When you have a seizure, you'll feel nauseated,
and you will also feel like you can't breathe, like now.
But you have to remember just one thing.
Like right now, however nauseous or suffocated you may feel,
you will never, ever die.
Remember that.
Until now,
I did what I could to get over it.
If I'm unable to do that,
I'll become a slave to that incident forever.
For a while, I prayed every day.
For those jerks to suffer the same way I did.
Did you feel better afterward?
No.
I just felt worse.
What angers you the most right now?
The fact that my photo was taken.
There must be something else you feel worse about.
What could that be?
I lost my first case.
I'd looked forward to having my own patient.
That's my real loss.
- And? - Financial distress.
Now I have to take a taxi because I can't take the subway.
What you should feel most upset about right now...
is that you went from being a doctor to a patient.
Because of those losers, you lost your first patient,
you're suffering from social phobia, and you are suffering financially.
Isn't that so unfair?
Even I feel vicariously traumatized.
(To feel one's pain as their own.)
You're really right.
You studied so hard to treat your first patient.
How can a doctor become a patient because of those jerks?
I'll guarantee you this.
If you overcome this well,
when you come across a similar patient,
you'll be able to treat them better than anyone.
I will get better.
I'll help you.
What are you doing?
I heard you're not eating well.
I just dropped by.
I had nowhere else to go.
Darn it. I want to fold a plane, but I can't.
My gosh.
Why fold a plane?
I have a 10-year-old son and he asked me to.
You fold one for me.
You have a son.
He's very smart.
Oh, goodness.
My son will love this.
Can you fold a boat too?
Whatever I say today,
you'll just forget.
How come you're so good at this?
My father taught me.
I see.
I'll make you a paper boat, tortoise,
rabbit, everything.
In return, will you hear my story?
Sure thing.
You see,
I think I got transference.
To a patient I'm treating.
Oh, dear.
Do you even know what that means?
It means you turned into a fish. How can you be a fish?
My gosh.
So?
Actually,
I knew it for a while,
but I denied it.
I didn't want history to repeat itself.
I tried to stop seeing her.
I tried to avoid her.
But in the end,
here I am.
Here I am as if it was fate.
Gosh. You're really good at this.
What should I do?
Should I...
keep on running?
Or change direction?
Life is short.
Keep going. Don't turn back.
You should always go straight ahead.
Right?
My son will grow up soon, won't he?
Yes.
When he's older,
I bet...
he will...
make things out of paper for you.
Goodness.
What is that there?
It's delicious.
It's good.
You should have some.
It's tasty.
Eat some more.
What's this?
Why is no one here?
We love you, Kang Noo Ri!
What's all this?
What's that?
Noo Ri. I heard that you love home-cooked food.
We prepared you this.
- Tada. - Tada.
It's amazing.
Noo Ri.
You've been through so much.
Don't look at me cry. It's annoying.
Don't cry.
- This is great. - Eat all you want.
Thank you.
- Said who? - Try this.
That's enough.
- We'll take turns feeding you. - What?
Can you give me some of that?
Come on.
- This too. - Do you want some?
I ate a lot earlier.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- It's delicious. - Seriously.
- It's so good. - Oh, what I meant is...
I'm correct, right?
Will you stop?
Can we please eat?
- Please. Let's eat. - Okay.
- Sorry. - I just wanted to ask.
- But... - What about this?
It's delicious.
- Well... - It's not true, right?
Come on.
- What was that about? - What?
(Fix You)
Why were you nice to me? You just confused me!
My brother was diagnosed with PTSD.
Si Joon's PTSD is just as bad.
There's a fire! Fire! It's burning!
Why do you keep smiling?
You shouldn't commit fraud with your friendly face.
What? Fraud?
We can't just kick people out like this.
Do you have special feelings for Woo Joo?
Woo Joo was different from other patients from the start.
Why do you make your life so hard?