(Episode 11)
When you suffer an illness due to a psychological scar,
you call it a psychogenic illness.
A psychogenic illness...
is developed through a mental...
or psychological issue.
When you're put in the same traumatic situation,
you feel the urge to avoid it or become hesitant.
When you run, your body lets out adrenaline...
which gets rid of your gloominess.
And just like that, some scientists say...
psychogenic illnesses can be treated...
by examining the neural circuits in our brain...
or the chemical compositions.
But that's not how the human mind works...
even if all the chemical reactions in our body are in a normal state.
We're not like computers.
What we feel in our hearts is a product...
of everything we experience in life...
such as love, pain, loss,
anger, violence, peace, and happiness.
In between a deep mountain valley
There is a small well that holds clear water
And among the beautiful flowers
Gosh, why are you singing facing the ground?
Come here.
What is it?
Isn't it so cool?
I can't believe a flower bloomed here.
I sang to it hoping it'll grow well.
I see.
My goodness, that's enough. Now, get up.
You need to come here early tomorrow.
Why?
You lost your job at the hospital.
Starting from tomorrow, I want you to work part-time.
- All of a sudden? - You got fired from the hospital.
You might get sick if you're suddenly free all day.
There's only one way to free yourself...
- Forget it if you don't want to. - from a psychogenic illness.
- Come on. - And that is...
to face your fears.
In order to escape from darkness,
you must walk into the darkness and face it.
And you start by saying goodbye...
to all the hurtful memories.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
I find myself constantly waiting for him.
"Is he not going to come for lunch?"
"I wonder if he'll drop by for a drink after work."
If you're so curious, why don't you just call?
It's not like you guys had a huge fight.
I'm scared he might notice.
Notice what?
My feelings for him.
I think...
I like him.
But I'm pretty sure I don't actually like him.
I have trouble controlling my feelings.
That's probably why I'm feeling this way.
What makes you think you like him?
It feels like...
losing love...
when I was never in love.
I haven't seen him for just a few days,
and I miss him so much.
I think of him all day.
I thought I just had anger management issues,
but I have this problem too.
Doctor.
What do you think is wrong with me?
Liking someone isn't a problem.
Don't try to deny it.
Look into yourself as if you're a mirror.
Do you really like him,
or is it just a feeling of abandonment...
because you relied on him and can't see him anymore?
"A feeling of abandonment"?
If you suddenly feel lost or discarded,
you look for someone to lean on.
Could that be it?
But...
what if this is real?
Then can I like him?
Does someone like me have the right to like someone?
Why does one need the right to like someone else?
Dr. Lee.
I can go home.
Are you happy about it?
Where is your mother?
Sorting out the paperwork.
She said she'd be back soon.
Did she?
Shall we go out for a short walk before she gets back?
Where are you taking Luo?
His mother will be back soon.
Exactly.
She'll be back soon, so we won't be long ourselves.
Dr. Lee. You know I'm responsible for everything that...
happens in this ward, don't you?
I just want to...
take him for a short walk to say goodbye.
- Say goodbye here. - I gave my permission.
Dr. Lee's taking him outside with my permission as Luo's doctor.
Must you be like this too?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
You never gave permission.
Did you think I couldn't tell?
You know his mother is...
just looking for an excuse to bring up the taser incident.
I will talk to Luo's mother.
My late mother was...
very interested in my education.
She wanted me...
to attend a famous after-school class in Daechi-dong.
So I could befriend rich kids...
and go to a good university.
But that was impossible for a kid like me...
from the outskirts of the city.
So my mother thought of...
getting an insurance payout.
My maternal grandmother had a grassy garden in Gimpo.
That afternoon, my mom mowed the lawn with a machine...
and cut off her toes.
She got treated right away,
but we couldn't find one toe.
You have no idea how much I cried all night...
as I looked for her toe.
I realized that day just how strong and sharp...
grass can be.
We moved to Daechi-dong with the insurance money.
Why...
are you telling me this?
I sometimes,
even now, have nightmares about looking for my mom's toe.
She's dead now,
but the nightmares still plague me.
I got the feeling that Luo...
might suffer from nightmares for the rest of his life, like me.
That's why I told you that.
Luo.
Do you hear the wind?
Yes. I do.
How does it sound?
It sounds warm.
You're right. It's a warm sound.
It's cozy.
Do you feel it surround you?
Yes. I feel it.
Do you hear the sound of leaves rustling?
I do.
What about the swaying grass?
I hear it.
Luo.
In this world, there are good sounds and bad sounds.
There are real sounds and fakes.
Remember that.
The sounds you heard just now are good sounds and real ones.
They are sounds that make you feel warm and cozy.
Sounds that torment and torture you...
are bad and fake sounds.
Like the voices I hear in my ear?
You know those voices are fake, don't you?
Now, listen only to true, real sounds.
Forget the fake ones.
- Will you remember that? - I promise.
A sound changed a life.
- Go home, returnee! - Go home, returnee!
That one phrase broke a boy's soul.
The wind caressed the broken soul.
Another sound woke up a depressed soul.
Luo.
This is my secret.
The truth is,
I also hear an endless sound in my ear.
Like a beating drum.
Is it a cozy sound? Is it warm?
Very much so.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
Come on!
- Ms. Gong. - What?
Buy me a beer.
- What? - Please! Please!
How much beer?
How do you think Si Joon feels right now?
I'm sure he has a lot on his mind.
He gave up on a patient.
Woo Joo said that she likes Si Joon.
- It's transference. - I think so too.
That is why he didn't want to take on a borderline patient.
What if it's not transference and she really likes him?
Are you afraid he'll fall for her?
He fell for his patient once.
Si Joon's not the kind to be so reckless.
Do you know what I've been thinking...
ever since Woo Joo confessed that to me?
"What if it happens again?"
I knew about it.
That Se Yeon was in a bad condition eight years ago.
But I didn't tell Si Joon out of jealousy.
Se Yeon relied on me so much.
I bet no one is as bad a loser as I am.
I knew that you knew that and didn't tell Si Joon.
I knew all along.
I'm even worse than you, aren't I?
These days,
I feel the urge to tell Si Joon how I feel about him.
It makes me wonder if I might be able to get a chance with him.
The inner-circle train for...
Seoul National University of Education is approaching.
What are you doing?
Were you secretly filming her legs?
- Excuse me. Hey. - Yes?
He secretly took a video of your legs...
- Move. Move it. - Oh my gosh!
He secretly took a video of you!
- Move! - My gosh!
He's a thief!
Thief! He's a thief!
My goodness.
He's a thief!
- Let me go! - Where do you think you're going?
- Stop him. - What's going on?
I'm not a thief! I'm not!
He's not a thief. He secretly recorded a video of a woman.
- What? - He secretly took a video?
Check his cell phone.
Give me your cell phone.
Take it out, sir.
My gosh, how shocking.
I can't believe the best heart surgeon in our country...
turned out to be a pervert.
This is crazy.
I was the one who caught him, so I was even more shocked.
I almost fainted.
I even took one of his classes.
He didn't look like a guy who'd do something like that.
Maybe there was a misunderstanding.
They found dozens of photos in his cell phone.
And he even uploaded them on a porn site for doctors.
The cardio department of that hospital is in a panic.
Gosh, this is going to destroy his career.
Do you think he'll lose his medical license?
Over 1,000 doctors apparently signed up for a membership...
on the porn site called "Doc SC".
"SC" stands for "secret camera."
And "Doc" stands for "doctor."
Unbelievable.
Why would they waste their brains on doing something like this?
But Doc SC is pretty famous among our colleagues.
- What? - What?
My gosh, what a bunch of perverts.
All the hospitals are in an emergency.
Aren't you best friends with Dr. Park in Cardiology?
You used to boast about him all the time.
My goodness, that's not true. We're not best friends.
He's just an acquaintance.
I heard there are over 1,000 members on that website.
So I looked into it.
And it turns out some of them even work at our hospital.
How many?
We found 22 so far.
What should we do?
I think it's best for the patients to have them fired...
before the cops start investigating.
We need a good enough reason to fire them.
So why don't we wait until the investigation begins?
This is irrelevant to whether or not they get punished by law.
I don't want people like them treating our patients.
Let's just have them dismissed.
Ma'am.
Paraphilia is a very serious psychological disorder.
We're even building a Medical Psychiatry Center.
We shouldn't approach this like other hospitals and fire people.
So what do you think we should do?
Even if we fire them, I personally think...
we should have them treated first.
That way, we'll be able to prevent future crimes.
It's true that paraphilia can eventually lead to serious problems.
We are going to carry out...
a group counseling session for those with paraphilia.
Among all the members of that illegal site,
22 of them turned out to be working at our hospital.
And among them, eight people seem to have voyeurism.
They are the ones we will be treating.
Sir, did they agree to get treated?
No, they don't know anything yet.
We need to approach them and convince them.
But this is such a sensitive issue. I don't think they'll get treated.
None of them are going to admit that they have voyeurism.
Do your best to convince them.
Blackmail them or lie to them if you need to.
You're good at that.
You talk as if I'm a gangster.
Plus, I haven't received any outpatients for a while.
So I have tons of patients waiting to get treated.
We need to be extra careful and make sure...
their information doesn't leak. You know that, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
- And Dr. Kang. - Yes?
You will get to have...
your first patient.
Really?
You're a real doctor now.
Congratulations. Good luck.
Noo Ri, you caught a pervert at the subway station.
And now, you even get to treat your first patient.
It's like you were destined for this.
It's like the skies are telling me to do a good job.
I won't take this chance for granted.
Okay.
We're psychiatrists.
I will be telling you the names of our patients.
Do not think of them as perverted colleagues.
You must think of them as patients who have voyeurism.
Please don't ever forget that.
Okay then. Here's the first patient.
When the patient got here,
I heard he was able to communicate by writing things down.
What did you do to cause a cardiac arrest in just one hour?
That means you guys didn't give him proper first aid.
He said he couldn't breathe properly.
So I did a tracheotomy and freed his airway.
His vitals were fine.
And he could even talk to us before you came.
But he had severely hurt his chest,
so I kept calling you for surgery.
But...
you came over an hour later.
So are you blaming it on me?
Is that what you're saying?
Tell me. Is it my fault?
No, sir.
The patient is brain dead.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You look really tired.
Here. Take it.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
I'm Dr. Lee Si Joon. I'm in Psychiatry.
Hello.
Do you have something to say to me?
Do you know Doc SC?
You're a member there, aren't you?
How did you know?
That doesn't matter.
I'll just cut to the chase.
People don't know this very well.
But voyeurism is a severe psychological disorder.
So I'd like to offer some help.
What are you trying to do?
I don't know who told you this.
But don't treat me like a pervert.
I only saw it a few times just for fun.
I already went to the police station this morning and got investigated.
I only did it...
I only did it out of curiosity.
But you have...
a gold membership.
Darn it.
That's because I shared my ID and password with my colleagues.
Do I really need to explain this to you?
You don't need to explain.
You'll end up getting sued anyway.
- What? - But even so,
I'm still willing to treat you.
I'll keep everything confidential, so don't worry.
(New Post Uploaded)
What are you doing?
My goodness, I got your face too.
I told you. Voyeurism is an illness.
You can try all you want, but it's an addiction.
You need more than a strong will to stop.
I'll treat you and keep things confidential.
So when should we start?
Voyeurism is a serious illness.
Just get treated before things get worse.
Come on.
You're talking to the wrong person.
What do you take me for?
Don't you get it?
Do you want to end your career?
I told you. You're mistaken.
You pathetic jerk.
Did you have nothing better to do?
I can't believe you're a member on that site.
Be grateful that the hospital is willing to treat you.
- Just get treated, okay? - I don't know why I did that.
What's going to happen to me?
Can you please help me get better? Please.
It can get treated. I promise.
Sang Joon.
Trust us and receive the treatment.
It's just a psychological disorder.
Mind your own business. Forget it.
- This is my life. - Sit down.
You must not understand what's going on.
Do you think you're a doctor just because you're wearing this?
That's not true.
Just get treated while we're offering to help.
Something must be bothering you...
seeing that you're at the chapel at this hour.
Where did I see her?
She looks so familiar.
I'm Kang Noo Ri, a resident in Psychiatry.
What do you need to talk to me about?
Do you know Doc SC?
All the hospitals are in a panic because of that site.
They're planning to fire...
all the doctors that signed up as a member on that site.
But our hospital decided to treat those who have voyeurism.
In other words,
you're my patient now.
I remember now. It's her.
Everything will be kept confidential.
You must be shocked.
Don't worry. You have a doctor now.
We finished talking to them individually.
Five people agreed to receive treatment.
I want you to take charge of what's going on.
It's a great chance to win the director's favor.
What happened to your friend, sir?
His life is over.
He always complained of stress.
So many people badmouthed him for performing heart surgery...
on the former president.
What a waste of great talent.
He won't ever get to do surgery again.
I can't believe he has voyeurism.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
My goodness.
I'm so happy today. I can't go without giving you this.
Here's your tip.
Go on and take it.
- Thank you. - See you again.
- I hope you come again. - See you.
Ji Sun!
He gave me a tip.
You can have it.
What's the matter?
- What's wrong? - This isn't a bar.
Why did you sit with them and pour drinks for them?
This is a restaurant.
I opened this restaurant...
so I could serve a nice meal...
to those who are too busy to cook for themselves.
What could I do? He asked me to do it.
He asked me to pour alcohol for him.
You hate doing that kind of stuff. Just be yourself.
Are you saying...
I should've yelled at him and thrown a fit?
That would've been better.
I didn't want to pour alcohol for him.
But I tried not to get angry for your sake.
You did it for me?
Why would you do something like that for me?
When did I ever tell you to stoop low for our customers?
Do you have no pride?
You should just go back to getting angry like before.
It's so frustrating to see you like this.
You're right.
I have no pride.
I even got fired from the hospital,
so why would I care about that?
Nothing about me is normal,
so why would I care about my pride?
What's so wrong with pleasing a customer?
What matters is how much you sell.
You idiot.
Yes, I'm an idiot.
You're all I have left, so I can do anything for you!
Woo Joo.
- I won! - He wins!
Great job.
Hello?
(Episode 12)
Dr. Lee.
I liked Woo Joo from the day we met.
She was honest, feisty,
never played coy, or ignored an injustice.
She put up with disadvantages even less.
But these days, she suddenly turned into a fool.
She bottles up her emotions.
She became timid and has no pride.
She never gets angry about things she should be angry about.
I'm worried now that the fiery girl never gets angry anymore.
One should live as you are. You can't try to change.
That will make you sick.
She didn't really want to quit stage therapy.
Doing that made her so happy.
Can't you just take her back as if you can't do without her?
I made a decision a long time ago.
But recently, I am losing my resolve...
because of Woo Joo.
I'm looking for a reason to persuade myself these days.
- Woo Joo. - Doctor.
What are you doing out here? Why didn't you come in?
I walked without knowing where I was going,
and ended up here.
Is something wrong?
I don't have a single friend now.
Thinking that...
no one in this world is on my side,
makes me feel so sad.
I suddenly felt...
so frustrated.
So I walked aimlessly.
You came to me, so I'll be your friend.
You will?
What shall two friends do now?
Let's go to the sea.
Let's go to the seaside.
You said the seaside.
Doctor.
Why do you think...
my emotions are so extreme?
I feel like I'll suffer and then die,
but then I feel fine as if nothing was wrong.
Then right away, I hit rock bottom again.
Look at me now.
I wanted to see the sea,
and I got distracted by those blinking lights...
and made you turn around.
What's the matter with that?
Live as your heart leads you.
It's fine.
Am I really okay?
I'll prescribe you something to do away with your gloom.
Go to him and tell him that...
you'll continue with stage therapy.
That last time, you said what you didn't mean out of anger.
That you really need to do it.
That you must do it in order to be treated.
You treat sick people probably because...
you hurt even more inside.
Song, who was on the run...
for running a site known as "Doc SC"...
was arrested today by the Seoul Cyber Investigation Team.
Song, who is a plastic surgeon,
created an internet cafe called "Doc SC"...
which only doctors could become members of.
He's being charged with uploading secretly taken pictures of women...
and spreading them online.
I'm really glad the administrator of that site...
wasn't someone from our hospital.
Whether it's the administrator or a member, they're all the same.
Since the administrator's been caught,
I guess all the members will be revealed, right?
Of course.
I'm just worried our hospital's name will be disclosed too.
It seems like all the doctors from our hospital...
watched it out of simple curiosity.
You know the saying,
"He who will steal an egg will steal an ox."
That's why we're taking measures to solve this first.
From now on, raise your O, X pickets...
to the questions I ask.
Have you visited a particular place or an internet site...
to see pornography?
Even during business hours,
did you visit an illegal site to see pornography?
Were you addicted to pornography before you became 18?
Did you ever forget work or miss something important...
because you had to watch that type of pornography,
and did that eventually affect your everyday life?
Do you feel anxious and humiliated right now?
Are you sweating, finding it hard to breathe,
and feeling frustrated?
If your impulse for voyeurism gets stronger, you can't control it.
You keep searching for stimulating content.
And in the end, it doesn't just end with secretly peeking.
It leads to exhibitionism where you show your private parts...
to other people.
Are you saying I'm a pervert?
Just now, when you heard the word "pornography",
everything you watched until now flashed in your head, right?
Stop treating me like some lowly scum.
His condition is worse than I thought.
Are you nervous?
You're not looking at me straight.
Is it because I'm a woman?
I'm not a woman, but a psychiatrist.
It's not that...
I can't do this anymore.
I'm really sorry.
What's wrong with him?
Did you check yourself?
The site has been closed down, so I couldn't check myself.
But the people who saw it captured the picture and shared it.
One of my friends even saw it.
And Noo Ri doesn't know at all?
She probably has no idea.
She'd throw a fit if she found out.
Those perverted jerks. Goodness.
Noo Ri doesn't even know that, and she's counseling.
What are you studying so hard?
He's my first patient.
I talked to him and discovered a lot of other problems too.
I really want to treat him.
But he's so timid.
He can't even look me in the eye.
I did some research,
and people who are timid,
have watched a shocking type of pornography when they were young,
or received the wrong type of sexual education...
have a high possibility of having voyeurism.
Noo Ri.
Why don't we change your first patient?
- What? - Leave that patient to me.
I think you shouldn't be a part of this paraphilia treatment case.
But why? Did I make a mistake?
- No, it's not that... - Then what's wrong?
It's because you are a victim.
What do you mean?
Let's begin the strategic seminar...
about drug treatment of osteoporotic fracture patients...
and prevention of falling accidents.
Who are you?
It's you, isn't it?
You posted my picture on Doc SC, didn't you?
No, I'm not.
- No. - Don't lie to me.
That's why you can't even look at me straight.
Hey. Did you like secretly looking at me?
Do you want to see more? Shall I show you?
My gosh.
All the professors and teachers in here,
this jerk secretly took my picture...
and uploaded it on the infamous Doc SC site.
I didn't even know that and studied all night in the library...
in order to fix his voyeurism.
Can you believe how messed up this is?
- What are you doing? - What?
He needs to suffer exactly like me.
He needs to feel what it's like...
to be stripped naked in front of the world!
It's not me!
I didn't upload it. All I did was watch!
I'm sorry.
Was it a mistake to entrust Noo Ri with a patient?
I'm afraid so.
From Noo Ri's point of view, it's understandable.
What are you talking about?
How could a doctor reveal her patient's information...
in front of all those people?
She had to differentiate from being a doctor and a victim.
Okay, I heard you.
But about those pictures. Are you sure he took them?
We've reported it to the police, so we'll find out soon.
Take Noo Ri out of this...
and Dr. In, you can treat her patient.
- Okay. - Sir.
I know we're focusing on treating the inflictor,
but shouldn't we treat the victim first?
Well, I've thought of that too.
But the victims of these types of cases usually don't step forward.
I'll discuss this with the director...
and find out what we can do.
That resident from the Emergency Medicine Center...
seemed like he was in critical condition.
If this gets worse, he might even quit his job this moment.
So stop agonizing over it and call Han Woo Joo.
You need her for the patients' sake.
Do you have feelings for her or something?
- What are you talking about? - You're hesitating so much.
What are you so afraid of?
This isn't for Ms. Han, but for the patients.
Noo Ri needs to be treated too now.
We can't have another victim like her.
Think about it carefully.
We meet often.
I heard what happened to the Orthopedics resident.
Is that how you psychiatrists treat patients?
By humiliating them in public?
You said you kept everything secret.
You just got someone all worked up.
"Worked up"?
Is this how you respond to goodwill?
You could lose your medical license,
and we're offering to treat you.
Don't you feel anything?
Did you not just look at photos and videos?
Did you take and upload photos too?
You did.
Did you think about the victims?
Do you think...
we offered to treat trash like you because we adore you?
We didn't.
It's because you'll just crave something worse and worse,
and end up creating even worse trash.
And that will create even more victims.
That's why we're treating you.
Not to save you but the future victims out there.
Do you think you're different from the perverts...
on the street because you wear a doctor's gown?
You're all the same.
Your symptoms are different, but it's all the same paraphilia.
I'm done being generous.
Accept our help and get treated,
or go on peeking at photos and end up being humiliated in the open.
It's your choice.
I'll...
- What? - What?
Don't you have something to say?
I don't.
- I'm off to see Lee Si Joon. - Did you call ahead?
I'll just barge in.
If I ask and he says no, I'll lie down and protest.
My gosh.
You're finally back.
You're such a nuisance.
I'd like you to come back to work at the hospital.
- What? - The Social Welfare Team...
tried very hard to find your replacement,
but they're protesting that they can't find someone with your talent.
I said it would be hard to ask you to come back,
but everyone insists they can't do without you.
They forced me to talk to you, so here I am.
Help me out.
Oh, I see.
Well, you asked so nicely and earnestly,
and it's hard to say no to you.
Please help me out.
I have a condition.
You want me to...
sing to these flowers?
I sang to them every day,
but I thought they'd grow even better...
if they heard a man's voice too.
Why should I sing to them?
- To flowers? - Just do it.
But... I can't sing.
Do you think flowers care about that?
Go on.
1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
Mom...
Mom.
Mom, don't you worry
Mom, your son is doing fine
If the repetitive days bring you down
Just let it out, yes
Let out a long sigh
Do it, yes
Count from 1 to 10
Do it
When the long day is over
Do it, yes
Why can't I forget you?
How embarrassing.
Why did you make me do that?
- That was amazing. - Goodness.
That was embarrassing.
My gosh.
(Treatment to overcome voyeuristic disorder)
I'll have to play many roles this time.
I understand why you wanted me.
That's why I begged of you.
Because we needed you.
If I must confess,
I was going to visit you first.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
So, Mr. Shin Jong Sik.
This session...
was arranged to hear your inner thoughts.
It will be unfamiliar,
but pretend this situation is real and keep up.
Okay.
She is a police officer.
You call yourself a doctor,
and take photos of women without them knowing,
and share it with friends. How can you even do that?
You.
When you saw the photos of the numerous women on the site,
did you think that they belonged to you?
Did you think that you ruled over them?
In real life, you can never say a word to a woman's face,
but you log onto such pornographic sites...
to feel superior, right?
Mr. Shin, don't you have anything to say?
Say it out loud.
It's not that.
Did you feel as if you dominated those women?
You ball of inferiority.
I said it's not that.
Then what was it?
Did your first-ever date humiliate you in some way?
It isn't like that.
No woman in your life...
ever acknowledged you, right?
No. It's not that!
As of this moment, Mr. Shin...
is a teenage boy of 15.
You got back from school and your mother is very angry.
Why is that?
What is this?
Why was this in your room?
You're reading this at your age?
You're so pathetic!
What did you think when you read this?
What evil things did you think about?
It's not like that. I just...
I asked what you did!
Shin Jong Sik. You have something to say.
Speak up.
I was just curious.
I didn't do anything bad.
If you have the time for this, memorize more English vocabulary!
Jong Sik, please.
We're barely getting by.
You're the hope of the whole family.
Mom and Dad are working so hard to support you.
Do you have the time to read such things?
I'm sorry.
A beating from your dad will teach you a lesson.
No, I'm sorry.
- I won't do it again. I... - Let go!
Now...
your younger sister is here.
Jong Sik.
In the subway...
someone took a photo of me.
Some scumbag...
put my photo on a site called "Doc SC".
Those jerks will be...
looking at it right now and getting all sorts of ideas!
Those animals are crushing me.
You're a doctor too.
How can doctors do something like that?
Is the world allowed to be such a crazy place?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
What are you sorry for?
I am...
trash.
I knew what I was doing was wrong,
but I couldn't stop.
Whenever I got stressed...
or was feeling tortured,
- I unwillingly... - You didn't just look.
You took and uploaded photos too, right?
Do you feel guilty?
Over what?
I did it.
That photo.
The photo of one of our doctors.
I took it.
I didn't know you worked here.
I'm truly sorry.
Mr. Shin.
I get that you were traumatized.
But that doesn't mean you can be forgiven for what you did.
Paraphilia...
is a terrible illness that harms other people.
We will treat you,
but for the crimes that you committed,
please take responsibility.
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry.
You know,
I like this place a lot.
Thank you for letting me...
come back to work.
When I was six,
I went to the seaside with my mom.
I was catching clams and crabs...
when I realized the tide was coming in.
The water reached higher and higher and I got so scared.
Just then, my mom...
put me on her back and walked through the water.
The smell from her back,
her hair that tickled my face.
The water that reached her thighs.
I still remember it all so clearly.
To me, that is happiness.
That was the happiest moment in my whole life.
When I come here,
I don't feel as happy as then,
but I feel as if I'm on my mom's back.
I didn't ask...
where that mother is now.
What happens to that patient now?
He turned himself in to the police,
so we think he's serious about being treated.
The problem is his addiction.
I didn't know this was so addictive too.
It's similar to drug or alcohol addiction.
They crave something more potent and exhilarating,
and it can lead to exhibitionism.
Eventually, they ruin themselves,
causing something unimaginable.
Their life is ruined in one fell swoop.
You did well today.
You did very well yourself.
Oh, wait. Just a moment.
I bought this a while ago and wasn't able to give it to you.
Here.
Throw it away if you don't like it.
Put it on for me.
Go on home.
(Fix You)
Guess what I named this bracelet?
"Band-aid".
Can I be healed before the hearing?
I heard there was an incident a month ago.
Was it because of the panic disorder?
You really don't know where she went?
Her foster mother?
She raised young Woo Joo for about six years.
Do you think I can't find you?
I will find you!
Doctor, do you know how you feel?
I don't know how I feel.
Woo Joo!
Han Woo Joo!