I never once thought that
I wanted to die.
I always wanted to live.
I got this because
I wanted to get noticed.
I didn't even use a knife.
I used a plastic ruler
in case it hurt.
That's not the issue right now!
Take some of my blood already!
Just hurry up and take my blood!
You're right.
I'm a patient.
(Episode 9)
There's someone...
There's someone I like.
My goodness, congratulations.
I want to ask her out.
But I don't want...
I don't want to shake
my head like this in front of her.
So I want to get better
as fast as I can.
How are you going to ask her out?
Well...
Do you want to hear it?
Sure. Go ahead.
I'm getting nervous.
I won't beat around the bush.
Will you go out with me?
That's it?
What do you think...
What do you think about it?
It's simple and honest.
I think it might work.
Oh, really?
Then...
Then it's your turn to answer.
Hurry.
Okay, fine. I'll give you some time.
- Go home safely.
- Okay, bye.
Si Joon.
Why did you ask me
to treat Han Woo Joo?
You knew from the start, didn't you?
Why did you do that?
Because I couldn't stand
seeing you live like this.
What's wrong with how I live?
You don't care about yourself.
You only care about your patients.
You always work so hard because of
what happened eight years ago.
I sent Woo Joo to you...
because I had
diagnosed you with PTSD,
and I thought she might be
your way to heal.
Who gave you the right
to give me a prescription?
I just want you to overcome
what happened as fast as possible.
But why...
Why would you do that?
Yes, you're right.
I have PTSD.
What happened eight years ago...
is still very traumatic to me.
Every time I see a patient with
a borderline personality disorder,
it reminds me of what happened
that day.
And it makes me want to avoid them.
You can't avoid them forever.
You're just punishing yourself.
You have no plans to treat yourself.
Han Woo Joo...
was your patient to begin with.
So take her back.
Now that I know she's borderline,
I can't treat her.
Are you a doctor?
Are you a psychiatrist?
A borderline patient...
stabbed me in the back.
One such incident...
is more than enough.
If you reject Woo Joo now,
you're not a doctor.
You're less than a human
and I won't see you again.
Am I pretty?
What? What did you say?
You witch.
You cruel witch.
You were the worst.
That day, you killed me as well.
And he just drove off.
I couldn't believe it.
Hey. How can someone
change so suddenly?
Dr. Lee should feel the worst today.
I think that's why.
Dr. Park punished him.
He can't see outpatients.
Does that mean
he can't treat anyone?
He's a total workaholic.
He'll feel like
the sky caved in on him.
Is it because of that?
The search and seizure?
Yes.
Who on earth
tipped off the prosecutors?
Woo Joo. Do you remember
the anorexia patient...
who was in stage therapy?
- Hwang Bo Young.
- Yes.
She gave up treatment.
Because of me?
- Because of what I said?
- It's not your fault.
But it's true that
it caused Dr. Lee some trouble.
Dr. Lee's suffering with
many things right now.
You need to understand.
It's my fault.
I was the problem.
I had no idea.
I feel so bad now.
My gosh.
Woo Joo.
How does it feel to dupe...
a naive doctor to get a drink?
I bet you feel great.
While we all are down in the dumps.
Lady. Why do you nag so much?
- Just get changed.
- I'm getting discharged.
Just like that?
Don't think of trying to
keep me here by force.
If you do that,
you'll get searched
and seized all over.
Fine.
If you want to get discharged,
then we'll have to let you go.
But only once you're sober.
You're not leaving today,
so get changed.
Darn it.
I can't change until you leave.
How dare you? I knew it.
Give it back. It's mine. It's mine.
It's mine! It's mine!
Give it back. Give it back!
- Give it back.
- Nurse Oh.
Give it back to me.
- Come here.
- Let go. Let go of me.
- Let go!
- What's wrong?
I'll report you to
the Human Rights Commission!
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be...
I can't reach Dr. Lee.
You can decide whether to
send Ms. Kim home or not.
- She's your patient.
- That is true, but...
Is it the right thing
to discharge her right now?
I'd like to hear
what Dr. Lee thinks.
She was his patient at first.
Like she said, she walked in...
and asked to be admitted.
If she wants to leave,
we have no choice but to let her.
We can't keep her a day longer.
She's threatening to report us...
to the Human Rights Commission.
Why are you so deep in thought?
Just call him.
He might not pick up.
He might not if he's too busy.
He seemed very angry.
With you? Really?
Hey. He's not that small-minded.
I really wanted
to get along with Dr. Lee.
Am I the type that
men get sick of easily?
He's not a man. He's a doctor.
Do you have an ulterior motive?
Like what?
I mean...
You do seem a bit too concerned.
He's not my type.
You fall for anyone so quickly.
Hey. Who's that woman?
What is she doing
outside my restaurant?
- She's one of the patients.
- What patient?
It's obvious she had a drink.
She's an alcoholic.
- One more?
- She said she knows...
who reported Dr. Lee
and bargained for a drink.
And Woo Joo took the bait.
She said she got discharged today.
Is she allowed to drink?
This is just unbelievable.
Take the bottle
away from her right now!
What got into Woo Joo as well?
This could cause a huge problem.
- Hey.
- What?
Do you really know
who reported Dr. Lee?
You said you'd tell after one drink,
and you had a lot.
The culprit...
is within the hospital.
- It was a patient.
- A doctor.
- Really?
- My glass is empty.
You should go now.
You can't do this
the day you got discharged.
- You stop as well.
- Hey.
A doctor tipped them off.
- Which doctor?
- Hey.
She put on a show
to get a free drink.
Where do you live?
I'll call you a taxi.
I don't live anywhere.
Will you go back to the hospital?
Shall I call them?
Are you belittling me?
Why would I go back there?
If you want to know the tipster,
bring me more alcohol.
No. You could get into trouble.
No more drinks
until you give me a name.
I'll get soju myself then.
I'll get it myself.
I'll go and get...
Hey.
You can't fall asleep here.
Who called the prosecutor? Tell me.
Get up.
Oh, no. What happened?
- Hey.
- Check her.
Oh, dear.
She's not breathing!
What?
Hey. Hey.
- Hello?
- Si Joon.
Cut.
It's a great day to save lives.
Hey, you're the new guy.
Are you getting ready for surgery?
You're very quick-witted.
Yes, I'll let you join this time.
I need to do a liver transplant
and a proctocolectomy.
It's going to be
the best surgery of the century.
I'm honored, sir.
When is the surgery?
Tomorrow.
The surgery will take place
at a hospital in Seoul.
Okay? My son works at that hospital.
Then...
I guess you'll get to meet your son.
Why would I meet that punk?
Why not?
You just said he works there.
I told you he's dumb.
We're like water and oil.
That's just like me and my dad.
My dad and I are also like
water and oil.
How did that happen?
I can't seem to talk to my dad.
He's very stubborn and audacious.
He thinks he's the smartest person
in the world.
I totally understand
why my mom ran away.
My dad didn't know how to smile.
All I remember...
is that he used to beat me.
Do you know what I did...
to ease the pain
every time I got beaten up by him?
I objectified him.
"Who is this person
that's hitting me right now?"
"What kind of life has he lived?"
"I wonder what's on his mind
as he beats up his own son."
All I got...
from my father...
was poverty.
I didn't want to pass that on
to my own son.
The biggest wealth
I could give him...
was my medical knowledge.
That's why I wanted you to become
a surgeon like me.
Do you...
remember everything?
You pathetic punk.
Why are you still
holding onto the past?
Dad.
Doctor.
My princess.
You've never met her before,
have you?
He's a resident.
What are you still doing here?
You're so slow-witted.
Get out of here.
Go. Go on.
Get going already. Go.
There you go.
Catch this.
Here you go.
I've never seen my dad
smile like that.
His affection for her
is helping a lot.
He doesn't shout
as much as he used to.
My dad wandered
numerous times today.
(Wandering: A common state
among patients with dementia)
It happens to him often these days.
As you already know,
people with dementia...
sometimes regain their memories
from time to time.
Here you go.
My goodness.
Thank you.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
You should go
and get ready for surgery.
I'll be right there, okay?
Okay, sir.
By the way, drive safely at night.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Is he doing okay?
- Who?
- The kid.
What?
Park Luo.
If you fail to answer me in the OR,
I'll have you kicked out.
You darn punk.
- Hello?
- Where are you, sir?
We urgently need you
at the hospital.
Why? Did something happen?
Ms. Kim, the alcoholic,
got discharged this afternoon.
But she just got brought in again
due to acute alcohol intoxication.
- How is her condition?
- The level of alcohol...
in her blood is 0.3 percent.
She's in a dangerous state.
What?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have let her leave.
Gosh, why did I give her alcohol?
What is wrong with me?
(Emergency Medical Center)
She binge drank
when she had alcoholic hepatitis,
and that's what caused
the acute alcohol intoxication.
We did a blood test
and took an abdominal ultrasound.
We injected her with dextrose
so her alcohol level will go down.
Is she conscious?
Yes.
I heard she didn't drink
for six months.
Gosh, she should've tried harder
not to drink.
Alcoholics need more than just
patience to treat their addiction.
Alcoholic hepatitis got worse,
so she got sent
to Internal Medicine for now.
Why did you let her get discharged?
I took her out for a while,
and that's when she drank.
I'm sorry, sir.
She got hospitalized
because she wanted to,
and she was eager to get discharged,
so we couldn't make her stay.
Have her hospitalized once she
comes back from Internal Medicine.
Okay, sir.
We'll detoxify her
and prescribe her medicine...
as soon as she gets hospitalized.
But I feel like she might not
want to get hospitalized.
Then call her guardian.
Dr. Lee.
Ms. Kim doesn't have a guardian.
She cut ties with her family
after she became an alcoholic.
I think...
we should just
let her get discharged...
and have her hospitalized
the next time she comes back.
Alcoholics drink until their bodies
completely get ruined.
How did she end up in the ER?
I thought her family brought her.
Ms. Han Woo Joo brought her here.
What? How?
They drank together,
and that's when she collapsed.
What?
Ms. Han is a huge troublemaker.
Ms. Hwang refused to get treated
because of her.
That's not true.
It's not Woo Joo's fault
that she refused to get treated.
Plus, Ms. Kim wouldn't have drunk
if I didn't take her outside.
She came here
due to acute alcohol intoxication...
because she drank alcohol
with Ms. Han.
It's not like
she forced her to drink.
What are you doing...
in front of Dr. Lee?
- I'm sorry.
Why did you stop them?
Go ahead. Keep fighting.
I'm sorry, sir.
Thanks for Luo's files.
They helped a lot.
There's no need to thank me.
I'm going to start
with counseling...
so that Luo doesn't feel
too uncomfortable.
Okay.
He's your patient,
so that's up to you.
I heard you met Young Won.
She's really worried about you.
Did you also know about Woo Joo?
Yes, I did.
So what? Are you
going to get angry at me again?
I can't believe you're my friend.
Do you not care at all
about Young Won?
Do you think I pretended not to know
for your sake?
I only did it for Young Won.
I should've stopped her.
You really should know
how much she cares.
Why do you think she chose
to do that to you?
(Han Woo Joo)
(You have 4 missed calls.)
He's ignoring
all my calls and texts.
He must be really angry.
Fine. I'll just ignore you, too.
Woo Joo.
He just...
called my name.
You knew Ms. Kim
was an alcoholic, right?
I met her
in the stage therapy class.
She could've died.
She had been clean for a while,
but she suddenly binge drank.
She collapsed
due to acute alcohol intoxication...
and could've died.
- My gosh...
- You knew she was an alcoholic.
So why did you drink with her?
Well...
She had gotten discharged.
And she was already drunk.
Is it my fault that she drank?
- I heard you drank with her.
- Well, yes.
But I didn't force her to drink.
I gave her a few shots
because she promised to tell me...
who the tipster is.
Why do you have to care so much?
Why do I have to care?
Yes, you're right. I'm very nosy.
You should've stopped her
from drinking if you knew...
she was hospitalized
for being an alcoholic.
You talk as if I poured alcohol
into her mouth!
You talk as if it's my fault
that she collapsed!
From now on,
I don't want you
to meet my patients.
Gosh, this is very upsetting.
You talk as if I only cause damage
to your patients.
I guess
that's what you really think.
Is that why you ignored my calls?
She would've gotten drunk
even if it weren't for me.
I just wanted to help you.
I just wanted to know
the tipster's name.
We should go.
I'll just quit stage therapy.
All I do is cause damage
to the patients,
so I have no right to do
stage therapy!
I'll quit!
That will solve everything!
Okay then.
I think that will be best
for both of us.
Darn you, you son of a gun!
How could he say that?
Does he not know
that I didn't mean it?
I only said that
because I felt sorry.
He could've just
patted me on the back...
and told me that it wasn't my fault.
Isn't that what a psychiatrist
should do?
He's not in his right mind, is he?
What do you think?
Do you agree with me?
It looks like you're not
in your right mind.
What should I do with him?
How can I get revenge?
Should I report him
to the Human Rights Commission?
Wouldn't they consider this
as mental abuse?
Do you think
I shouldn't have done that?
You did nothing wrong.
Stop being so hard on yourself.
You just did your job
as a doctor and a friend.
But Si Joon was pretty stern.
Young Won, stop worrying so much
about Si Joon.
Just give up on him.
Do you know what I said to him?
I told him that a bad doctor
is a doctor who gives up...
not someone who's incompetent.
I won't give up
either on Si Joon or Ms. Han.
Then I guess I shouldn't
give up on you either.
What?
It was a joke.
Eat up. It's delicious.
If there's someone you want
to cuss out, don't hold it in...
and scream into this bag.
Don't become a bad doctor
who gives up...
when it gets too hard to handle me.
(Episode 10)
Why are you here at this hour?
I have a favor to ask.
- Come in and have some tea.
- No.
It won't take long.
Woo Joo said
she'll quit stage therapy.
There was an altercation
with another patient.
I knew she didn't want to,
but I let her quit,
without even a moment's hesitation.
- What?
- She brought it up first,
and I felt so grateful.
You really are the worst.
It'll be hard on her.
She's a typical borderline case
who self-harms to get attention.
She wanted me to notice her,
so she jumped out
in front of my car.
Just like Jeong Se Yeon...
who jumped into the water
so I'd never forget her.
They're just the same.
I'm so afraid...
that it might happen again.
The only way for someone
who has almost drowned...
to overcome their fear of water
is to jump back in the water.
You should know well as a doctor.
I don't think I'm ready yet.
Young Won, you should go
and meet Woo Joo.
Don't wait until she comes to you.
Go meet her and treat her.
I promised her...
that I would never give up.
Please do me this favor.
I'll do it my way, as I please.
Can I?
Rage, go away.
According to the CCTV footage,
we've confirmed the patient
wasn't assaulted.
But the problem is, regarding
his emergency hospitalization,
you held him at the hospital against
his will for more than three days...
without his guardian's consent.
This is a violation
of the Mental Health Act.
I don't have to explain further,
do I?
I know.
I admit to everything
you've just said.
Once we forward our investigation
to the prosecution,
they will make a decision soon.
You will probably receive
an extenuation...
and this will end as
a summary order.
But you need to be cautious
from now on.
If this problem arises again,
it won't end with a summary order.
Yes, I understand.
But don't you want to know
who reported you?
Everyone asked that first.
It's probably someone who hates me.
According to that person,
you were the one who came clean
in the first place.
- Me?
- Yes.
Think carefully about
who you told the truth to.
Who did I tell the truth to?
Luo.
I know it might be awkward...
since this isn't the room
you always came to.
- Where is he?
- Who?
Oh, Dr. Lee?
From now on,
I'll be your doctor in charge.
I heard Dr. Lee explained
everything to you.
From now on,
your medication might
increase a little.
Will that be okay?
Dr. Lee told me about...
which medication
had side effects for you.
So don't worry...
and trust me.
Luo, is there anyone else in here
besides you and me?
No one can enter this office
without my permission.
That friend you're looking at
right now.
How did he come in here?
I didn't call him.
Go! Go!
- Luo.
- Go! Go!
- Go!
- Luo.
- Go! Go!
- Luo, wait.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Luo.
- Luo, no one is here.
- Go! Go!
- Luo, no, it's okay...
Luo. Park Luo!
Park Luo!
Luo!
Please call security.
It's an emergency.
Luo!
Dr. Lee! Dr. Lee! Dr. Lee!
Luo. Luo!
Luo. Luo. Luo!
Are you insane?
What have you done to a kid?
We just followed protocol...
I don't care about protocol.
Who told you to use this?
Was this patient holding a weapon?
Did he threaten you?
I'm sorry.
- Luo.
- What's going on?
I mean,
how could he do this to me
over one single mistake?
I've totally been abandoned.
Thank you for calling me today.
You can cry all you want
until you feel better.
Why is my life such a mess?
What's wrong with your life?
I can't get along with others.
Once I think I've become
close with them,
they all abandon me.
Just like throwing away trash
in a recycling bin.
I'm really nice to them though.
The more I think about it,
it enrages me.
What's the matter
with my darned life?
Do you know
what's even more annoying?
That I still don't hate Lee Si Joon
despite all of this.
That's what annoys me the most.
Why do you think that is?
Last time...
Woo Joo,
you aren't someone whose boyfriend
is allowed to cheat on you.
You changed someone else's life.
When I heard that,
it felt like I was coming alive.
Just like a withering flower...
blooming brightly again
under the sun.
Have you ever seen something
like this?
When you see a halo
behind someone's head?
I saw that halo
behind his head at that moment.
He was like my savior.
I always thought I was
a nuisance to others.
But I was...
actually someone
who could help someone.
I was someone who could make
someone happy.
He was the one who taught me that.
And I was so grateful.
I keep thinking of that moment...
You can't hate him since
he's the one who gave you courage.
So it annoys me even more.
I can't even cuss him out
because of that.
Shall we become honest
with each other?
What do you want to do?
I want to give back...
exactly what he gave me.
Dr. Lee.
Dr. Lee, Luo has been
in an accident.
What happened?
While receiving counseling
with Dr. In, he ran out suddenly.
And the security guards used
a taser gun on him...
while they were trying to stop him.
He wasn't hurt,
but I think he was shocked.
I think it would be better
if you go see him.
You must be very bored.
- Pardon?
- Luo is Dr. In's patient now.
Why do you care about
another team's patient?
No, it's not that.
I was told Luo ran off
to look for you.
You're a third-year resident.
Can't you tell what's important?
Take better care of
Ms. Kim Young Seon.
But...
What?
A taser?
Those foolish sons of...
How could they do such a thing?
What is the matter with you?
What is it?
Are you going somewhere?
I have a meeting.
Do you need to talk?
No. I heard you'd gotten hurt.
I wasn't hurt. I'm fine.
How did that happen?
I apologize. It's my fault.
Nurse Oh. Was that patient
usually this disruptive?
No. He took
a sudden change recently.
Was there an incident?
I think...
we missed the timing to treat him.
What do you mean by that?
I think you should ask
Dr. Lee Si Joon yourself.
Why Dr. Lee? Was there a problem?
It's not for me to share.
Mr. Deputy Director.
We're not here to discuss Dr. Lee.
A security guard used a taser,
making it look like
we assaulted a patient.
We must tell Luo's mother
of his condition.
What for?
Of course, she must know.
Something happened to her son.
Many people saw the security guard
use a taser on the boy.
If we hide it,
it could become a bigger problem.
Isn't it natural for
a security guard to have a taser?
The problem is that
it was excessive.
Dr. Park,
you tell the hospital director.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
What if someone else
sues us over this?
I'm more concerned Luo's mother
might want him discharged.
Dr. In.
If that's what she wants,
discharge the boy immediately.
Don't say a word.
Don't let anyone mention
involuntary admission.
What was Nurse Oh
talking about earlier?
Do you know anything?
The nurses have a lot of work to do.
I'm guessing
that's what she insinuated.
No. There's definitely
something else.
Find out what Nurse Oh meant by
missing the timing to treat Luo.
That was just her crossing the line
when she doesn't know much.
Shall I find out?
I understand.
Why is Si Joon so quiet?
He should've kicked up
a fuss already.
(Nursing home)
What's going on?
Why are you all out of it?
Music. Do we have any music?
Who are you?
What?
Who am I?
I think you're in
the wrong operation room.
What nonsense is that?
I'm Lee Taek Kyung.
Scalpel.
What took you so long?
Stand opposite.
- Come with me.
- Hey.
Let go of me.
I can't leave during an operation.
My gosh. Hey, are you crazy?
Let go of me, you fool. Let go!
That hurt.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you here?
I said I'm operating at
my son's hospital.
Why is it your son's hospital
of all the hospitals around?
What is it you want to prove to him?
You arrogant fool.
Is there still more
you want to force upon him?
What do you know to lecture me?
I know my son well.
He needs to change specialties.
He needs to see how great I am
in surgery if he's to wake up.
Psychiatry?
Why does he struggle with
weak-minded people?
Do you know why
I became a psychiatrist?
It was to understand you, Father.
You're my father
and I couldn't understand you,
so I became a psychiatrist
hoping to understand you!
Lee Si Joon.
- Dr. Park.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
But who is this man over here?
He's...
I need to scrub in.
He's new here.
I'll talk to him.
Wait right here.
Wait here.
I heard what happened.
Even so, what are you doing
out in the open to a sick man?
My father isn't a patient.
He's very normal.
He's normal enough...
to report his son to
the Human Rights Commission.
What?
He reported you?
Yes.
It was my father.
How would he know to do that?
Because...
I told him that
I had Luo admitted...
against his will.
That's what I wanted to say.
Sleep well.
I wanted to come clean to someone
about what I'd done,
but I knew it could
become a problem,
so I told my father
because he'd never remember.
But...
when I was there talking,
he was completely lucid and fine.
He understood what I'd said
and feigned ignorance then,
and then reported me.
Why?
Because he still hasn't given up.
He...
hates it so much that...
I'm a psychiatrist.
He still wants to
crush his son whenever he can.
Hey. Speak so that I understand.
What are you talking about?
Please, do just one thing.
What?
Be a father like oil and water,
or be a pitiful patient.
What was that about?
Why not come to my office
for some tea?
- Shall I?
- Yes.
You're the one who's suffering.
Let's go.
Don't just stand there. Let's go.
Come on. Come with me.
Let go of my arm.
By the way, Doctor.
Did you really report him?
Yes, I did.
Do you remember reporting him?
Do you take me for a fool?
Why wouldn't I remember what I said?
Why do you look so old?
What? Do you have any idea
how old I am?
Dye your hair.
One would think you're
a department head in your 50s.
Yes. In my 50s.
You're smiling? You need to grow up.
Fall in love, get married,
and have kids.
My gosh. How much longer
will you be so hard on others?
Aren't you exhausted?
It could ruin your health.
I have been thinking...
I might have dementia or something.
I get forgetful sometimes.
Don't you shed tears
for no reason too?
Depression usually
accompanies dementia.
Are you crazy?
Why would I cry? I'm a man.
You should cry every now and then.
Don't hold back your tears.
You can cry freely now.
You've been through a lot.
What? Did I offend you?
Will you scold me?
Who are you?
Where...
Where am I?
What is this place?
Whatever happens in this room,
no one will know.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night.
Do you know
what I looked up all night?
"How to turn back time."
Wouldn't it be nice
if I were able to...
reverse time by 24 hours?
But there's no way of doing that.
What happened yesterday
wasn't solely your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
The doctors are mostly responsible
for not managing the patients.
I know that.
But I'm the one that got fired.
None of the doctors got fired.
So are you here to complain?
Because you think it's unfair?
I do feel wronged and angry,
but for some odd reason,
I didn't hate you.
I should fly into a rage
and curse you out,
but I didn't feel like it.
I wondered why that was.
Then I realized that...
it's because...
I owe you so much.
Until I pay you back,
my life will stay twisted.
So I want to repay you
for what you did.
Can I do that?
Do whatever you want. I don't care.
Okay. Then sit down over there.
Listen to this.
I want to give back
exactly what he gave me.
What did he give you?
Comfort.
You know...
Guess what?
A person who notices
someone who is sick...
is someone who is even sicker.
You treat sick people...
probably because...
you hurt even more inside.
When you feel down,
listening to drums...
is supposed to help.
You comforted me,
and I wanted to comfort you.
Rather than how we meet,
how we part is more important.
There.
That's it.
(Fix You)
Before I realize it,
I'm waiting for him.
She's transitioning.
What if it's not a transition
and she really likes him?
Do you know
of the Secret Photo Gallery?
Did you post my photo
on the Secret Photo Gallery?
How could they have voyeurism?
Are you saying I'm a pervert?
I haven't seen you before.
Where's your pride?
Nothing in my life is normal.
Why would I have any pride?
Can't you just take her back
as if you can't do without her?
I made a decision a long time ago.
But recently, I am losing my resolve
because of you, Woo Joo.