(This drama is fictitious and all characters, events,
organizations, and settings are unrelated to real life.)
The person you have called...
It's over. I won.
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
(Caller ID restricted)
(You'd better pick up.)
(Don't you want to
see your daughter?)
(Caller ID restricted)
Hello?
Mom.
So Hui!
How did it go? Did you get it done?
Did you blow your cover?
She realized I'm an agent.
Did you see who chased you?
No, I didn't...
What's wrong? Hello?
Hey.
Darn you!
Hey. Hello?
Hello?
What's wrong with the call?
I'll deal with the rest.
Lie low until you hear from me.
Chief Seo. Where is he right now?
Chief Seo?
In his office. Why?
I'm sorry, sir.
Something urgent came up.
I must head to Seoul first.
(Mr. Byun)
I took care of it.
Okay. See you there.
So Hui.
Mom!
Mom, did that hurt a lot?
It didn't.
It didn't hurt. Mommy is okay.
Now keep your promise.
Just tell me what
your teammates are doing.
(Team Leader Dong Gwan Su)
Hello?
Ye Eun.
Ye Eun!
Why are you not saying anything?
(You'd better pick up.)
(Don't you want to
see your daughter?)
(Calm yourself
over a cup of tea first.)
(You can't live
in a safe house forever, right?)
Mom.
(Good Casting)
Is the third round of research
progressing without a problem?
To finish it before the deadline,
I haven't even been out
for fresh air...
and stuck in my office working
for several weeks.
If the drive doesn't go smoothly
all the way through,
it's not just the driver who dies.
Bear in mind that you're going to
take other passengers with you too.
Of course.
I'm doing my best...
as if it's a matter
of life and death.
Please don't worry.
- What's the matter?
- I'm sorry.
I told him not to,
but he won't stop calling.
Do you still have
something left to say?
If you didn't pick up my call,
I was going to visit you in person.
I was just getting ready
to head out.
You sure catch on quickly.
Did you arrive in Malaysia safely?
I just can't get used to their food,
so I couldn't go.
I thought I made myself clear.
If you take it easy at
the Malaysia branch for a few years,
I will bring you back
at the right moment.
Do you think I didn't see you...
getting rid of people like that?
What do you want?
Half of the money
you have stashed away.
I know everything about
your hidden accounts, anyway.
Give me your PIN.
Then I will leave quietly.
And I will clean up
these useless things for you.
You're asking too much
for a clean-up job though.
If Pi Cheol Woong talks and so do I,
it's you who will suffer
the most damage.
I'll think about it.
I can't wait long.
I'll give you a day.
Have a drink before we talk.
I will...
hear what discomforting things
you have to say before we drink.
I thought it would only leave
a small scar so I left it.
But there was pus inside.
What should I do?
Pus should be squeezed out...
so that it won't give off a stink.
It will hurt when you squeeze it,
but only then will it heal.
So you're asking me to
squeeze out the pus?
As I did three years ago?
If that's what you wanted to say,
you came to the wrong person.
You only got to where you are now
thanks to my help.
Climbing up might take long,
but it only takes a second to fall,
you know.
I can...
look after myself.
But it seems like you can't.
What if I tell you I know a way
to clean up the mess you have?
I'll hand you a broom.
All you need to do is sweep with it.
People wouldn't know how many
bugs you kill while sweeping.
(NIS Sheltered Ward)
Shift change!
Good work.
- Hello.
- How are you?
See you later.
(Authorized personnel only)
A fire has been detected.
What?
- Is there a fire? Go check it.
- A fire?
Okay, I will.
Fire emergency. Fire emergency.
Check the alarm in the closed ward.
What's this?
A fire has been detected.
Please don't push.
Hold on.
Requesting back up.
Suspect escaping to the basement.
The suspect is escaping
through the basement.
Block the underground parking lot,
all entrances,
and emergency exits.
- Call headquarters and 911.
- Yes, sir.
- Check the other floors quickly!
It's a blowfish. A blowfish!
So Hui.
Who did you meet earlier?
Dad.
What do you mean by "Dad"?
Dad bought this for me.
What are you talking about?
You don't have a dad!
I'm sorry.
Mommy was wrong. Sorry.
Yes, Mr. Dong.
Pi Cheol Woong is dead?
How did Pi Cheol Woong die?
Let's talk upstairs.
The killer got way too gutsy.
He got rid of two agents
to get upstairs.
Why isn't Chan Mi here?
Why isn't she here?
- I called her.
- He called her.
Why are you so late?
Goodness.
Dung is in the worst possible mood.
Don't get on his nerves.
Hey. Hey, the meeting...
Why are you going in there?
(NIS Chief Seo Gook Hwan)
Right there.
Rewind.
(Authorized personnel only)
Zoom in on his vest.
(White Collar)
"White Collar"?
It's a laundry service.
Go to Cheol Woong's room's camera...
at the time he got off the elevator.
After White Collar appeared
and the fire alarm went off,
Pi Cheol Woong was murdered.
Do you get the picture?
He activated the alarm
to cause a distraction,
to kill Pi Cheol Woong.
Mu Hyeok, check White Collar's van.
The rest of you, go through
the hospital's surveillance.
Figure out White Collar's route.
Get to it.
Mu Hyeok.
You said Chief Seo is in his office.
Come with me.
Why are you looking for Chief Seo?
He sent someone after me.
He was watching you?
- What for?
- I'd love to know too.
What this is about.
Let's find the killer first.
Chief Seo wanted to send
Pi Cheol Woong to the prosecutors.
I had him...
locked up in a closed ward
for a psych evaluation.
I might have to take the fall...
and lose my job over this.
Wait. He tried to send
Pi Cheol Woong to the prosecutors...
without a police investigation?
We can suspect him
after we catch the killer.
There's no time.
How far did you follow the killer?
To a laundry collection van.
The laundry collection van.
It disappeared in
the underground parking lot.
What do you mean?
We have it on camera
entering the parking lot.
But I just can't find it leaving.
Did it disappear into
thin air or what?
Even if it vanished into thin air,
it should've left a few crumbs.
What time was the police called?
11:43 p.m.
A police van...
coming and leaving the scene
even before the call?
That's impossible.
It must've left
pretending to be police.
A black van.
License plate number 16R 3419.
It left the hospital
at around 11:40 p.m.
Check nearby roads.
I found it. A black van,
number 3419.
Checking it's route.
Did you run the license plate?
(Car Registration, Theft Report)
Lee Gwang Hyeok, 58, male.
He reported the car stolen recently.
Have you found it yet?
It took the Incheon Airport
Expressway 3.5 hours ago.
Incheon?
Is he fleeing the country?
It looks like it.
He took the Yeongjong Bridge
three hours ago.
(16R 3419)
We're leaving now.
Regroup at the van.
Everyone, follow me.
We have pressing business.
Let's go.
Didn't you hear me?
As of this moment,
Dong Gwan Su is relieved from duty.
- What?
- Relieved from duty?
Then who will lead the team?
What good is a ship
without a captain?
Right after the emergency meeting,
Industry Security Team 3...
will be disbanded.
What are you talking about?
Is this what you wanted?
To break up our team?
How can you say that
when you wasted time...
and got our witness killed?
Pi Cheol Woong was murdered
and made to look like suicide!
We must catch the killer
before he gets away!
Yes.
The media will report
it was suicide,
but there was definitely a killer.
Chief Tak.
How did you find that out already?
He disappeared from the airport
instead of boarding his plane.
Where do you think he went?
Fingerprints and footprints
found at the scene,
and the knots used to tie the rope
all point to Chief Tak!
How can you be so decisive
without evidence...
The tools he used to
commit the crime...
were found on his yacht!
What's wrong? What happened?
Our team is being disbanded.
What do you mean?
We won't be fired, will we?
Chief Seo.
Where is he right now?
It's over already.
The chiefs will gather...
to discuss and vote on
breaking us up.
Chan Mi!
Industry Security Team 3...
Open the door!
Don't mind her.
I locked the door
knowing she'd do that.
Let's begin.
Look.
Are you crazy?
Did you just find out I'm crazy?
What's the problem?
You had me tailed!
Tell me.
Why did you have me followed?
Why send an agent after me?
Do you want to...
discuss that right now?
Why not?
The cause for spying on
a subordinate...
doesn't have to be a secret.
I sent a subordinate into the field
to carry out a mission,
and she reunited with a student...
she once tutored and got distracted!
Yes. I had you watched.
- That's...
- Wait.
Yoon Seok Ho.
You knew him?
The great Baek Chan Mi...
couldn't have forgotten the manual.
Did you...
act as a spy to betray your team?
Just like three years ago?
Is it true?
Did you break the rules...
and monitor someone
you knew personally?
Mi Soon.
Will we really be disbanded?
I don't know...
what's going on anymore.
What do you mean?
Chan Mi and Yoon Seok Ho.
People are saying they used to date.
What?
Hang up.
I'll say this just in case.
I didn't wait for you.
You just happened to show up.
You wanted to punch Chief Seo
but got punched twice instead.
That's why you should
control your temper.
You do 99 percent perfectly,
then mess up the rest because of it.
You can nag only after
you quit smoking.
This?
It's not mine. I quit long ago.
When?
Five years ago.
You quit smoking when you quit me.
That's how disgusted you were.
After we broke up,
I thought I'd really die
if I kept smoking at that rate.
That's why I quit.
You knew it would be a problem.
Why did you take on Yoon Seok Ho?
That's all that I was told.
So he worked for Director Myeong
and handled the secret ledgers?
You can't trust anyone.
He was persuaded by Director Myeong
that it's all for the company.
He felt so guilty that he confessed
to the Chairman for that reason.
The conclusion is that right before
Father passed away,
he found out about
Director Myeong's ledgers.
And right after he argued with
Director Myeong about those ledgers,
he got into a car accident.
Those ledgers
will definitely contain...
the reason behind this.
I...
will bring those ledgers for you.
You don't even know
where they are.
They must be in his office...
where even ants can't break in.
Don't. It's dangerous.
Don't worry.
It's dangerous for Director Myeong,
not for me.
You can't even kill an ant.
I can't kill an innocent ant,
but I will punish the guilty.
The Yoon Seok Ho that I know...
isn't a bad kid.
But if someone else watches him,
they would have had
a bias against him.
First, Yoon Seok Ho isn't a kid.
Second, you're the one who's biased.
The bias that Yoon Seok Ho
would never do anything bad.
On what grounds? With what proof?
If I were Chief Seo, I would've had
suspicions about you too.
And you're not suspicious of
Chief Seo?
He even put an agent on me.
If I were smart enough to insist
like a certain someone,
I would've stuck to my opinion.
But you know me.
I'm in no place to do so.
(Lim Jung Eun,
Advertising Department)
You must be looking for Ms. Lim.
Did she not come to work today?
That intern was gutsy enough
to take the day off.
I wonder who's
looking for her though.
Goodness.
You're CEO Yoon's secretary.
So what brings you by?
Why are you looking for Ms. Lim?
May I ask you that?
I had a work-related question.
I'll get going then.
Good morning, Mr. Yoon.
It's not a good morning for me.
I had a rough night...
because my secretary disappeared
at Busan Port.
I'm truly sorry about that.
I looked for you frantically...
since I thought
you might have been abducted.
Unbelievable.
No way.
Who would want to kidnap me?
You couldn't even bother to call.
All I received was a text...
saying you were heading home.
Well...
I had urgent business
to take care of.
You were urgent enough...
to abandon your own boss?
That's ridiculous.
I never abandoned you.
What would you call it then?
I just entrusted someone else...
and handed over my duties
to the hired driver for a while.
Is that so?
So you dumped me with him.
I understand that
my actions could be misinterpreted.
She handed me over. Seriously.
I should've escorted you
all the way back home.
I'll make sure that
it never happens again.
I'm glad
you weren't hurt in any way.
- Sorry?
- You see,
I was worried about your safety.
This is me getting back at you
for scaring me.
Anyway, let's make sure...
that Mr. Byun
never finds out what happened.
Anyway, wait 10 seconds
before coming in.
1, 2, 3...
Right, of course.
Good morning.
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks for the coffee.
I'll call you back later. Sure.
Gosh, that's good.
(Letter of Luck)
(This letter has brought
its recipients good luck...)
(but only if it leaves you
in 4 days.)
(Read the letter with good music)
This is to announce
the end of your mission.
At midnight tonight,
your mission will come to an end.
You are not to carry out
any more related operations.
If your identity
is exposed after midnight,
the agency
will deny your affiliation.
You have been advised...
to leave your post
before the mission ends.
This message will now delete itself.
What's putting a frown on your face?
It's spam.
Do people still send out
chain letters?
Doesn't it feel a bit weird
not to send them out though?
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
Sorry?
I once didn't send out
any chain letters...
after receiving them.
I got injured in a car accident...
which put me in a cast.
I don't believe in superstitions.
No one really does.
It's just to be on the safe side.
So Hui, here you go.
My gosh.
I'm still paying installments
on this laptop.
I haven't shown this
to Mr. Dong yet.
Why did Min Seok have...
Chan Mi's handkerchief?
What?
But I definitely wrote it down.
I wrote down
detailed instructions...
and stuck the note on the fridge.
Kang Woo Won...
(How to use a rice cooker)
"What a joke."
No, that's not the right tone.
"The handle of a millstone
is called an 'eoi' in Korean."
"So imagine trying
to turn a millstone..."
"without a handle."
"It's so ridiculous
that it has to be a joke."
I need a partner
to bounce my lines off.
Hold on.
She's the one who did wrong,
so why would I call her first?
No way. Never.
Are you here to apologize?
I have no intention
to forgive you...
I left something here.
- As in what?
- I'll take it and leave.
(How to use a rice cooker)
You're here for the note?
What happened to the note?
What a joke.
Hold on.
Are you going to just leave?
I'll text you the instructions...
on how to use the rice cooker.
It's mine.
I'll write down
the instructions for you again.
You can't take back
what you gave me.
But I'm the one who wrote it.
Taking things back is the worst.
I'll write you another one!
Why are you doing this to me?
Do you want this?
I can't give it to you for free.
Go ahead.
"If it weren't for you,"
"I wouldn't have known
what love is."
That's not the right tone!
Put some emotions behind the words.
Why can't I just read the lines?
I'm not an actor.
All I'm doing
is helping you study your lines.
That's the issue here.
How am I supposed
to get into character...
when I have a robot for a partner?
(How to use a rice cooker)
I'll give it another shot.
Okay, start.
"If it weren't for you..."
That's no good!
Hey, Ultra Fine Dust.
You haven't been in love, have you?
I'm not obliged to answer
such personal questions.
You're saying goodbye
for the first and last time...
to the person you love
before leaving him.
Of course.
I must be stupid to expect
anything more...
from a relationship virgin like you.
"If it weren't for you,"
"I wouldn't have known
what love is."
("The Love after Love")
"Thank you for teaching me
how it is to love someone..."
"and how it feels..."
"to be loved too."
Isn't it your turn?
"What a joke."
Darn it. That's not right.
(How to use a rice cooker)
Mr. Yoon must be staying late
to finish the employee evaluations.
I'll stay until he heads home,
so you can call it a night.
What has gotten into you today?
It's not like you
to work late voluntarily.
Is it perhaps your last day here?
You should head home.
With pleasure.
All right then.
Tell him I left if he asks.
Mr. Byun.
You've got to be kidding me.
Have you changed your mind already?
I apologize for always
getting off work on time.
I'm grateful for everything too.
What's going on?
Don't tell me...
I'll head in tomorrow
and see your desk cleaned out.
That's good then.
Anyway, I'm off. See you tomorrow.
This is definitely
how he ironed my shirts.
Darn you, Cheol Woong.
Couldn't you have at least
found a replacement before leaving?
Unbelievable.
(How to use a rice cooker)
Why does...
she even want this silly note back?
Was it that hard
to come up with an excuse?
Why couldn't she just apologize?
As if I'd believe...
she really wanted
this lousy note back.
I can't just give it back to her.
This is my ticket
to boss her around a bit more.
Mr. Pi, the manager
of actor Kang Woo Won,
was found dead.
Mr. Pi worked as...
Kang Woo Won's manager
for several years.
An acquaintance of the deceased...
stated that he was under
a lot of stress due to long hours...
and was devastated when Mr. Kang...
started to work
with another manager...
after becoming an A-lister.
The police announced
that they will focus on...
Mr. Pi's depression
and the possibility of a suicide.
- Such news...
- Pi Cheol Woong...
- Many send their condolences.
- is dead?
Anyone can tell
that it's Chan Mi and Mi Soon.
Hold on.
I smell something funky though.
You see,
my daughter spilled some soup on it.
Well,
I'll have an expert look into
the physiological aspect of this,
so keep me posted
on Kang Woo Won's condition.
How has he been lately?
He seems off.
Has he remembered anything more?
That's not it.
Before,
he used to glare at me like that.
But these days,
he looks at me like this...
and calls me whenever he wants to.
I'd go to him...
only to find out
he needed a silly favor.
He'd then come up with an excuse
to keep me around.
Ye Eun,
was So Hui's dad
the first man you dated?
Yes. Why do you ask?
The reason Kang Woo Won
is acting that way...
Forget it.
Telling you...
will only mess with your head.
I hope his condition
isn't getting worse.
If this was because
you didn't trust me,
I must say I'm offended.
You're offended?
You couldn't handle CEO Yoon,
so I had someone tail him.
Why you felt the need
to complain is beyond me.
You put me in charge of everything
related to Il Kwang Hitech,
so I would've...
Baek Chan Mi and Yoon Seok Ho
knew each other in the past.
Did you choose not to tell me
or did you not know about it?
The latter proves
your incompetence...
while the former...
disgusts me.
I was going to report it soon.
This is exactly why
I can't quit smoking.
How else can I relieve the stress
brought on by my subordinates?
What did you say to me again?
You're offended?
I apologize.
If this is how it'll be,
how am I supposed to trust you...
to do the job?
How could I possibly
back you up on your promotion?
Just how?
Answer me.
I'll...
do better.
You may leave.
Don't get caught on camera
taking the elevator...
and take the stairs instead.
I'm sure I didn't
have to tell you that.
You are the director
of the NIS after all.
How dare she talks like
I'm beneath her...
when she's way younger than me?
Oh, my knees.
Are you heading home?
I was here working late,
but my own secretary...
didn't bring me anything to eat.
I'm heading out to grab a bite.
I'm sorry, sir.
Should I make reservations
at a nearby restaurant?
Or I'll run out
and get some take-out.
Join me.
- Sorry?
- You haven't had dinner either.
Then...
please buy me something delicious.
Enjoy. I'm only buying
because I'm grateful.
I don't think
I've been of much help though.
You kept me company on November 17.
Anyone would've been
able to do that.
Keeping me company...
is a huge deal to me.
Everyone precious in my life
left me, you see.
All of them.
(15 years ago)
I won't stay for long.
I just want to see him.
You signed a contract...
that states once it expires,
you are no longer
permitted to see him in private.
I want to see him as a friend,
not as someone I once taught.
That's why we cannot allow it.
Please leave.
(Seok Ho)
You know how it is with people.
There are encounters
but also farewells.
My mother died in her sickbed...
and my father passed away
without a warning.
And...
the person I trusted the most...
also left me.
Ms. Baek,
I hope you never
disappear from my life.
But my contract is only temporary.
I hope you never leave me.
You're all doing
a good job as always.
Mr. Byun, you shouldn't have.
- Gosh.
- You're the only one...
who looks out for us.
Is that his sarcastic way
of telling me to visit often?
Well, you should.
It's not like we can
go to you upstairs.
You have to come down to us.
Sure thing. I'll come by...
when I receive my salary
next month too.
I love you.
- Let's eat then.
- Enjoy.
What do we have here?
Let's eat. My gosh.
Trotters, pizza,
fried chicken, and more.
(Director's Office)
Aren't you joining us?
Don't mind me. I already ate.
Then hand out the cups...
and pour the guys some soda...
instead of just standing there.
All right, fine.
- Please enjoy.
- Let's eat!
(Caller ID restricted)
Is it the spam call again?
I told you to block that number.
Hello?
I'll hang up the second you put
a trace on the call, so just listen.
Will you excuse me?
I can't believe how many
executives are working late.
What do you expect?
They're practically
temp workers, right?
They must work extra hours
just to keep their jobs.
- Right?
- Of course.
Director Myeong's office
is empty though.
That's how it is with him.
He comes to work
three hours earlier than others...
but gets off right on time.
His secretary must be exhausted...
to get to work before he does.
Why?
The man handles
his documents personally...
and his door
opens for him automatically.
Automatically?
Let me show you.
Look at the door to his office.
There's no security lock on it.
How do you open it then?
How should I know?
There must be a way.
A key or a keycard.
Let's see.
(Director's Office)
Look.
Open sesame!
That's fascinating.
No one will be able to go in there.
There's only one person who can.
And who's that?
Tak Sang Gi?
I know you work for the NIS,
so why do you think
I didn't tell Director Myeong?
Why's that?
I needed insurance
for a time like this.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but your insurance just expired.
I'm aware.
It's why I was hoping...
to suggest a deal
between two abandoned parties.
Show me your cards first...
and then I'll decide
whether or not I'm in.
You'll find it worth your while.
You see, I saw something juicy...
when I went to kill Pi Cheol Woong.
You weren't the one who killed him?
See for yourself
if you can't believe me.
Name your price.
Wait, how did she get in there?
She's an outside hire
who comes once a week.
Director Myeong
hired her in person.
Only she would know
how to get in there.
Why are you curious
about how to access his door though?
Well, I'm seriously considering...
installing the same system
for CEO Yoon.
I see.
Can I see her access the door
on another day?
Why? What for?
Well, I need to see if the system...
works properly.
- Just to check?
- Yes.
Sure, let's take a look.
(Director's Office)
Wait, the door isn't opening.
- Why not?
- It's not opening.
Was it out of order?
Freeze. Take it back a few frames.
Director Myeong's ledger.
His ledger?
The one he has in his safe.
Bring it to me.
My mission at Il Kwang Hitech
ends tonight,
so how am I supposed to get it?
That's for you to figure out.
Don't you want to catch Michael?
Michael?
Are you saying...
that Michael is the killer?
He said so
before he killed Pi Cheol Woong.
Do you know
what's more interesting though?
He's around you.
Somewhere close.
What do you mean...
he's someone around me?
Get me the ledger
if you wish to know.
I'll be in touch.
Hold on.
And here I thought...
you had run off like last time.
I received an urgent call.
You seem pale.
I'm all right.
The ramyeon has gotten
cold and mushy.
Let's enjoy it again
some other time.
First, Yoon Seok Ho isn't a kid.
Second, you're the one who's biased.
The bias that Yoon Seok Ho
would never do anything bad.
On what grounds? With what proof?
(Crazy Baek Chan Mi)
I'm outside your house.
Get down here.
If you don't, I'll barge right in.
Fine, I'm coming!
She's unbelievable!
Hold on.
Where is she going at this hour?
(Wash and Clean)
Are you insane?
You can't drop by where I live.
What?
What's going on?
Tak Sang Gi contacted me.
What did the jerk want?
A deal on his prison sentence?
Is he smuggling himself
out of the country?
Tak Sang Gi...
has a video of Michael
killing Pi Cheol Woong.
Are you saying that
Michael killed Pi Cheol Woong?
Tak Sang Gi suggested a deal.
It seems like
Director Myeong has a ledger.
If I bring it to him,
he'll hand over the video.
Come on.
Are you trusting
the words of a killer?
What if...
he's telling the truth?
What if
Michael killed Pi Cheol Woong...
and had our team dismantled?
Hold on.
Do you mean...
that we're the final target
of whoever's behind this?
Don't tell me you're
suspicious of Chief Seo.
What I have aren't suspicions.
I'm sure of it.
Agent Baek...
will steal...
the ledger tomorrow.
(Good Casting)
You'll steal
what's in Director Myeong's office?
We need to get our hands
on his sensor.
You must return all the equipment.
We have no choice
but to do it old-school.
- Okay.
- The target is en route.
If I knew you weren't
some ordinary secretary,
I would've gotten rid of you sooner.
We're just getting started.
Kang Woo Won is on
a downward spiral.
Mr. Kang!
- I'm on my way.
- That nutjob.
- You have three minutes.
- Start up the backup generators.
The security team is here.
Get out of there. Hurry!
My assistant stole from
Director Myeong's office?
(Epilogue)
(NIS Chief Seo Gook Hwan)
Who uses a flip phone these days?
(Agent Dossier)
(Baek Chan Mi)
(Hwang Mi Soon)
(Lim Ye Eun)
(Lim Ye Eun and Kwon Min Seok
were in a relationship.)
(Kwon Min Seok died
the day their daughter was born.)
Kwon Min Seok?