I have access to Ok Cheol's phone.
All I need to do
is find Michael's contact number.
(Michael)
What? It's on speed dial.
Michael. That's him, right?
The phone is turned on.
Trace its location.
(NIS Chief Seo Gook Hwan)
(This afternoon, 1 p.m.,
the cafe in Royal Hotel)
(Wash and Clean)
(NIS is on to you.
Will be in touch.)
(NIS Chief Seo Gook Hwan)
(Baek Chan Mi)
What do you mean
you lost the signal?
It's been 30 seconds
since I asked for a trace...
and you couldn't even get a signal?
- Transferring to voicemail.
- I don't need the cell tower!
Yes! Yes, I was a bit rude!
- What?
- Darn it.
- We almost had him.
- At least...
- we connected Ok Cheol to Michael.
- That's why we always fail!
That's why I'm so annoyed.
What?
He'll be watching us
from his hiding spot.
How old are you?
Where are you?
Yes, where is your location?
(Baek Chan Mi)
If I had gotten rid of her
three years ago,
it would've been clean-cut.
I want a report
on Baek Chan Mi's whereabouts.
Off the record.
(Il Kwang Hitech Research Center)
Gosh.
Do you think Ok Cheol
found out about the cameras?
You said he saw you in the vent...
and passed out.
Yes, and that's what I don't get.
Is this the kind of face
you'd pass out over?
I got a bigger scare.
You have no idea how much...
What's that?
Shoot. What happened?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
What is this?
But still, just in case,
I brought it with me.
No way.
How did you think of that?
You still have the touch.
That was nothing at all.
I was in the field for years.
Years and years.
(Good Casting)
We got a call from Taiwan.
They found him?
I think it's for sure this time.
Arrange a business trip.
I'll meet him right away.
You have other plans.
(Weekly Schedule)
I'll go alone this time.
Gosh. I searched for him
for three years.
Finally.
I must leave tomorrow afternoon.
Sir.
You'll have to take Ms. Baek
on your unofficial schedule.
Ms. Baek?
Look for all of Michael's aliases.
I checked all the old text messages,
but it's too clean.
I don't think
this is his main phone.
What's that? This.
It's all research data.
When a sneaky jerk
doesn't leave a trail,
it means they have
something huge hidden away.
My goodness...
Gosh.
Oh, dear.
Why is this so easy?
This is making things so boring.
If anyone tries to hack
your computer,
the hacking tool
will begin to operate...
and trace the other person's
IP address.
So it turns it the other way around
and hacks that person's computer?
That's right.
Gosh, if I ever get to use this,
it's going to be so fun.
Does it also work on cell phones?
I think I could make it work.
Let me see.
Why don't we ask Chief Tak for help?
He got discarded by Director Myeong,
so we could just ask him
to help us instead.
Chief Tak...
didn't tell anyone who I was
even though he knew.
Things might backfire on us
if we don't do it right.
Did you get anything else
from Mr. Ok's phone?
They're all just research materials.
It looks like all he ever does
is do research.
Mu Hyeok, find the guy
who registered the phone.
And Ye Eun, keep looking into
Mr. Ok's cell phone...
until you find anything
regarding Michael.
"Ye Eun"?
She looks pretty.
If you took one,
I should take two...
to make things even.
Right?
"It's okay. That was just a dream."
"Monsters do not exist."
"That's what her mom said to her
as she patted her on the back."
"She patted her on the back."
"A few days later,
So Hui had another dream."
"This time, a huge goblin
appeared in her dream."
"No, go away! Get away from me!"
Chan Mi!
Darn it.
It was that dream again.
Oh, my gosh.
"That's right."
"We create our own dreams."
(Contacts)
The fact that you keep
having nightmares...
means your suppressed
traumatic memories...
keep showing up in your dreams.
People who have
short-term memory loss...
tend to suffer
from repetitive flashbacks.
They repeatedly experience
the fears from their past.
Why don't you start a hobby...
so you can forget about your anxiety
by focusing on something else?
You can try puzzles,
play an instrument, read,
or even draw.
Perfect.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
Ms. Baek, do you have
a driver's license?
I used to.
Until my license got suspended.
Didn't you write in your resume
that you could drive?
The thing is...
What should we do?
I need someone to take Mr. Yoon
to the countryside.
(Informal schedule)
He never shares anything
that's informal.
I wonder what's up.
I'll take him.
But you don't have
a driver's license.
Well, I do.
As of this afternoon.
But how will you drive
with that arm?
I'm really good at driving
with just one hand.
I see.
Really?
(Calling Team Leader Dung)
Hey, it's me.
Can you make me a driver's license?
Why do you need a driver's license?
It's urgent.
When can Chan Mi
legally start driving again?
CEO Yoon needs someone to drive him
to an informal schedule.
I really need it.
We don't break the law.
Hey. Seriously? Team Leader Dong.
My gosh.
Ms. Baek doesn't have
a driver's license?
She can drive like
a professional F1 driver.
But her license got suspended.
Did you check where
Mr. Ok's cell phone got registered?
I'm still checking.
Wait a minute.
Her license got suspended?
Did she drive under the influence?
No, road rage.
With that temper of hers,
I can already imagine what happened.
A habitual DUI driver
committed a hit-and-run,
so she followed that person
and drove her car into his.
The car practically destroyed
and they had to scrap it.
I wonder if the driver was okay.
What?
Hey, isn't it time for lunch?
(Lunch time: 12 p.m. to 1 p.m.)
I need a temporary driver's license.
There's still a minute left
before the clock hits 12, right?
Why do you think I married
a fool like Yoon Seok Ho?
He always keeps his promises.
He never even held my hand
because of the prenup we signed.
(Record of transactions)
We agreed to live our own lives,
respect each other's privacy,
and stay out of
each other's bedrooms.
But why won't he wire my money?
He always kept his promises.
I wonder if he has suddenly
changed his mind.
Look into their relationship.
It'd be great if you find something.
If you don't, then it'd be a relief.
I'll sit in the passenger seat.
I feel bad that you have to drive
with an injured arm.
It's okay.
Please slow down.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Don't be too nervous.
Just take your time. It's okay.
It would've been more comfortable
for you to sit in the back.
I prefer the passenger seat.
But Mr. Byun always beats me to it.
Here.
The flight to Taipei
departing at 1:35 p.m., correct?
Yes.
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
Does this old man have dementia
or something?
How could he forget
that I have a big mouth?
(Flight to Kuala Lumpur, 1:35 p.m.)
Why couldn't he just take
what I offered?
Does he really need me
to explain everything?
My gosh.
Who's that jerk?
Darn it.
You're dead.
- Gosh.
- What are these punks up to?
What's wrong with you?
Hey, you!
Watch where you're going, won't you?
- What a pig.
- How dare you...
Hey, roll down your window!
You little punk!
This jerk...
What's up with them?
Why?
Is something wrong?
I think the drivers
got into a fight.
They shouldn't do that.
It seems dangerous.
Change lanes and avoid them.
I will do that.
I'm coming after you.
Seriously.
(54R 6103)
6103.
(19N 2362)
2362.
Sir.
Hold on tight.
What? Why?
I'd like to speed up.
Sure. Okay.
What are you up to?
You just wait.
What scumbags.
I'll stop by a service stop.
No problem.
The toilets are over there.
Run a license plate for me.
19N 2362. 21R 9318.
54R 6103.
(54R 6103)
Okay, I'm on it.
Mr. Dong. If you mess up
with a temporary license,
does that get suspended
or canceled too?
What do you mean?
I'm terribly worried about Chan Mi.
(Chinese Industrial Espionage)
Who should I go after first?
Eenie, meenie, minie, moe.
Bingo.
2362. It's your lucky day.
Why are you crying?
Where's your mom?
Why are you here crying on your own?
Nice.
Is she a ghost or what?
Hi.
Who are you?
Min Jae!
Thank you so much.
I was so scared.
Min Jae. You can stop crying now.
A man must protect his loved ones.
It's silly to cry once they're gone.
I want to thank you.
Can I at least buy you some coffee?
No, it's fine.
It's really okay.
You can't take that.
That hurt...
(CEO Sim Hwa Ran)
Hello. What can I get you?
- I'll take this.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Do you have a death wish,
you psycho?
Wrong. I am a psycho,
but the one with a death wish...
is you, Mr. 9318,
who drives so erratically...
when you're a criminal
out on probation.
Who are you? Who sent you?
Who sent you?
That's what I want to ask.
Do you want to...
get beaten to a pulp
on this gloomy day?
Why you...
You made the first move, didn't you?
No. Darn you.
What? Oh, no.
What... Why...
Why... Why...
No!
What's going on?
Are you crazy?
No. I'm not the crazy one. She is.
I dropped a plastic bottle
by mistake,
and he slipped on it and fell.
That made him angry.
Even so...
Do you think I got this
because I fell over?
Hey, you. Let's check
the surveillance cameras.
Check the surveillance cameras!
Gosh.
You lured me to a spot
with no cameras and...
Let's just go.
What if he follows and hurts us?
If I see you again,
you'd better be prepared.
- Watch your step.
- Go.
It's okay. You're safe now.
- Were you very scared?
- What are you?
- What happened to the cast?
- It's fine.
- How could you...
- Let's just go.
My gosh!
Okay.
I'm still on their tail.
I mean, what is his problem?
Baek Chan Mi
isn't your average agent.
Make sure you don't get caught.
If you do get caught...
What should I do then?
Deal with her quietly.
My gosh.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
(Death anniversary)
(Kang Woo Won)
If you don't pick up in 10 seconds,
I'll consider it
a breach of contract.
(Kang Woo Won)
Hello?
It's urgent,
so I want you here in an hour.
Hello, I know you're supposed
to start next week.
But if you're free,
can you babysit today?
What's so urgent?
What?
That over there.
What about the rice cooker?
I want to eat at home for a change,
but I don't know how to use it.
My manager always
did everything for me,
so I've never used it before.
Did you...
ask me to come all the way here
because of that rice cooker?
I'm an advertisement model
for that brand.
And you're the employee
of that company.
Did you forget that you have
to come running to me...
every time I call you?
Should I reset your memory?
Based on Article 4, Clause 5,
I only need to assist you...
when we're shooting an advertisement
at the studio...
as a means to promote the product.
"Promote"? Just wait a second.
I promoted the product
on my social media page...
that has a million followers.
So does that cover it?
Cook a few side dishes
along with the rice.
I don't expect you to cook
anything fancy.
But I'll be nice enough
to have a few bites.
By the way,
there's meat in the fridge.
- Hello?
- Nothing comes up for 6103,
no matter how hard I try.
I checked the VIN, make,
and where it was registered.
Is it under a fake name?
I don't think so.
There seems to be an owner
listed on file.
Text me who it is.
I've been getting
a lot of spam these days.
It's really annoying.
That's because
you keep letting them talk.
Block the number. Go ahead.
Sure.
The owner is a corporation,
but I think it's a paper company.
Should I dig some more?
Did they even send a text?
That's pretty relentless.
Here. Let me take care of it.
It's best to just ignore them.
Of course.
Anyway, why are we here?
This is my father.
Your father...
passed away?
(15 years ago)
Gosh, it's pouring.
What are you doing here?
I waited but you never came.
What can I do
when I wanted to see you?
We'll run on the count of three.
All right. 1, 2...
I came here to say goodbye.
You decided to study abroad?
I stayed in Korea for my mom,
so nothing's keeping me here now.
I'm sorry for not even
bringing you a bouquet.
I see you've already
had a change of heart.
Don't be silly.
My heart doesn't change that easily.
The funeral home
was filled with flowers,
so I think I want a break from them.
Just thinking about lilies
makes me want to throw up.
Seok Ho, that day, I...
Don't get caught in the rain.
You'll catch a cold.
Seok Ho, take the umbrella.
You're getting soaked.
Maybe some other day.
When we meet again someday,
I'll give this back to you.
You can give me the umbrella then.
This is why having sons
isn't worth it.
There was a vendor out front.
You were too embarrassed
to buy flowers, right?
Don't people...
usually buy lilies?
For some reason,
I'm not fond of lilies.
He suddenly passed away
three years ago.
Three days ago on this date?
That's when Min Seok died.
I still don't know why...
he went to Busan alone that day
without his driver.
He went to Busan?
What on earth happened that day?
Wherever I go,
wherever I run, I'm being followed.
They won't give up.
Who are these people?
Dad!
Get back inside right now.
They eliminated the chairman,
so killing me would be easy.
I heard that the chairman
was particularly fond of you.
Wait. Here you go.
This photo was on
the chairman's desk.
No...
This is all because of me.
I promise you this.
I won't...
tell a single soul.
The secret ledger.
A ledger?
This is all my fault.
Are you saying that
the chairman kept a secret ledger?
No, Chief Myeong has one.
Chief Myeong?
Do you mean
Director Myeong Gye Cheol?
(Director Myeong Gye Cheol)
(Chief Tak)
Greedy scumbags.
They won't leave you alone
when money can be sniffed.
They're never satisfied
with what they're given.
You might find something out...
if you talk to his driver.
Well, he...
passed away two years ago.
He died?
Get out.
- Sir?
- Get out of my house.
Leave this instant.
- But, sir...
- Get out.
- Sir!
- Leave!
- Get out.
- Sir, hold on a second.
Just a second. Wait.
Don't open the door. Don't open it!
Did someone die?
What on earth is this?
Is there something wrong?
Don't you know that
I need at least one meat dish?
The only...
pork dish I eat
is stir-fried spicy pork.
It's stir-fried spicy pork.
You've gotten better at this.
This drawing...
What's this?
That?
A sudden inspiration
motivated me to draw.
What do you think?
The strokes seem genius, right?
You know it's a work of art.
One's artistic ability...
just can't be suppressed I guess.
I see the image when I'm eating,
relieving myself,
and even when I'm sleeping.
So I decided to hold an exhibition.
Drawings like this
will be viewed as valuable.
I believe that
it'll be better to have your work...
be appraised by an expert...
who knows what true art is.
You're not wrong.
Not everyone will realize its value.
I know someone
who set a milestone...
in the world of contemporary art.
Who?
What's this? Was it drawn by a kid?
Was this drawn by Kang Woo Won?
Yes, Mr. Dong.
The master of contemporary art?
Okay, got it.
May I ask for your opinion on it?
Anyone can tell
it's Chan Mi and Mi Soon.
Right?
I completely agree with you.
Don't tell me that
Kang Woo Won's memories are back.
I don't know.
What if his memories
are slowly coming back?
Since I know there are no photos,
I won't sign the contract.
Guys!
You are to keep
your eyes on him from now on.
If he regains his memories...
and threatens to
sue Pi Cheol Woong...
Would that make things
harder for us?
Just like what happened last time,
the police could
take our only witness.
That'll be the end of our operation.
But Mr. Dong,
I might die before
Pi Cheol Woong does at this rate.
Can't someone else
watch Kang Woo Won instead?
What is it? What did he say?
What did he think of my drawing?
He can't say anything
before he sees it in person.
Wait. What did you say
that his name was again?
Why do you ask?
He's a famous artist
that'll be handling my work.
I should know who it is.
Well,
this artist works under a pseudonym.
What was it again?
What's his last name.
Dong. It's Dong something.
Dong?
Master of contemporary art,
surname Dong.
(Known quotes)
(Everyone has
a Picasso within them.)
I did it.
(Master of contemporary art,
surname Dong)
(Dong Casso)
Dong Casso?
Yes, I think that's it. Tonkatsu...
I mean Dong Casso.
Good job, So Hui.
Hello?
Yes. I see.
Yes, I've got the time.
There.
There you go.
Daddy?
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
Are you all right?
I heard a thump. Are you okay?
I guess we have no choice.
I'll drive us back.
You have a driver's license?
I'm even qualified
to drive a freight truck.
Mr. Yoon,
your shoulders seem too tense.
Please don't talk to me.
I'm trying to focus.
May I ask...
when you got your driver's license?
When I was 20.
Then you've been driving
for over 15 years.
Why can't you pick up
the pace though?
This is my first time
behind a wheel since then.
Pull over. Pull over right now.
We're clear...
Don't swerve!
Did you just talk down to me?
Don't look at me.
Keep your eyes on the road.
- Make a right.
- A right.
Make a right here.
Don't swerve like that.
You are off course.
Are you all right?
- Eyes on the road!
- Sure.
Please keep your eyes on the road.
We're in Busan?
(Busan)
Busan?
Exactly.
We're in Busan?
Busan is this way?
- Eyes on the road.
- Of course.
My gosh.
You're leaving already?
What do you mean? It's 9 p.m.
When did my phone go off?
You need to show me
how to use the rice cooker.
I thought you might need it...
for next time anyway,
so I wrote down
detailed instructions...
and stuck the note on the fridge.
Where?
Where is it? I don't see it.
I stuck it on the fridge.
It isn't here.
But I stuck it on there.
See for yourself.
There's nothing there.
Then read this instead.
I don't read due to
my compulsive reading disorder.
Shouldn't your condition
make you want to read?
I've been steering clear
from reading as a remedy.
How do you study your lines then?
I listen to the audio file
recorded by my manager.
Are you kidding me?
Hold on.
Did you just yell at me?
That's right. I'm angry at you.
You call me over whenever you want.
That's what today was about.
You were bored, so you called me...
and had me cook for you.
I'm not your manager,
your housekeeper,
or your girlfriend.
Why do you call me over
all the time...
and order me around?
I would've endured it
if it were any other day,
but today...
Not today.
This isn't what
I should have been doing today.
Understand?
I'm sorry, Min Seok.
I wanted to cook
a decent meal for you.
There's no one else who would've.
I should've
been there for you today.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Min Seok.
Gosh.
We ended up driving to Busan Port,
but it's nice, right?
Why did you offer to drive...
when you aren't good at it?
I wanted to let you rest.
Have you been here before?
I haven't since my last trip
three years ago.
Why?
Because it's too far from home?
No.
I wasn't brave enough
to come back here.
Please stay here.
I'll go and buy an umbrella.
No, you stay. I'll get it.
Find shelter already.
You'll catch a cold in this rain.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- I'll take this.
- Sure.
(54R 6103)
There were too many jerks
tailing me today...
that I almost forgot.
It's good to finally meet you, 6103.
Bring it!
You're an agent?
All I've heard are rumors about you.
I guess it's an honor
to finally meet you in person.
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
Who sent you?
We're both in a situation...
where we need
to maintain our covers, right?
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
It's over. I won.
The person you have called...
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
(Epilogue)
Goodness.
Hello.
So he's the master
of contemporary art?
- Yes, he's Dong Casso.
- Dong Casso.
I hear that you've been adamant...
about meeting me.
I'm well aware
of your achievements, sir.
You set a milestone...
in the world of modern art.
Well, it's really nothing.
However, I did change
how modern art is today.
I was hoping for
your honest opinion of my work.
Let me see. My gosh.
How should I put this?
This is more than
just post-modernism.
I can detect...
a major element of contemporary art.
The lines may be rough and simple,
but I can see an artist...
taking a bold move...
in trying to dismantle
the conventional structure of art.
Goodness. I'm impressed.
Thank you.
How about a photo
of you two together?
- Sure.
- Okay.
(Good Casting)
Pi Cheol Woong is dead?
Pi Cheol Woong was murdered...
while the fire alarm was ringing.
What if I told you that I had
a way to get rid of our problem?
Team three will be dismantled.
Is this what you wanted all along?
- What's your issue this time?
- You had me tailed!
Don't tell me
you're a double-agent.
Hello? Ye Eun? Say something.
I'm glad you weren't hurt.
I was worried, you know.
I forgot something.
- It's mine.
- But...
Why are you doing this to me?
Isn't it Michael you want?
He's right beside you.
What are you talking about?