(This drama is fictitious and all characters, events,
organizations, and settings are unrelated to real life.)
Be careful of the control system...
and disconnect the power by cutting
the third wire from the left.
- Step back.
- But...
It's you, isn't it?
You're Michael.
It's fine.
Good.
We checked the files.
Will someone else
make the third delivery?
No, no.
I'll make the third delivery myself.
Okay. Very well.
Good? Okay.
- Thank you.
- It's fine.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
It's over at last.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
What? Why is it ticking again?
There must be another bomb.
What?
Just kill me already, will you?
Get it off him.
I love you.
I won't let you leave alone.
Why didn't you untie me earlier?
You could've done this earlier.
Let's run.
Out of the way!
Move!
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
You will be charged after the beep.
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be directed to voicemail.
It's a welcome gift.
I'm bribing you so that
you'll stay with us for years.
(Good Casting)
(Episode 7)
Why are you out already?
You should've finished your IV drip.
Where is Ye Eun?
Why is she not here?
Ye Eun?
Did something happen?
You're in no place
to be worried about me.
I really thought...
you might die.
Do you know how scared I was?
Why are you so angry?
Don't ask.
From now on,
try not to get hurt so much.
I'm sorry.
Yes, you should be.
If you die during a mission,
our Team Leader Dung
will have to stay up all night...
to write up a report.
Your doctor says...
it's just a small fracture,
so you'll be fine in 2 to 3 weeks.
Hang in there until then.
(Congratulations on
returning to the field.)
What about Pi Cheol Woong?
(NIS Sheltered Ward)
Pi Cheol Woong had a seizure
the moment he woke up.
I'm not surprised.
He almost died wearing a bomb vest.
He's weaker than he looks.
He was given sedatives
and barely fell asleep.
Not only...
did those guys
try to use him as a parcel box,
but they even put a bomb on him.
They probably wanted
all of us dead.
Anyway, now that they stole
the chip,
what are we going to do?
What's there to ask?
We're going to do
exactly what they did to us.
What is your problem?
You told me you'll catch Michael...
and stop him
from leaking the technology.
You badgered me
as if it was extremely urgent,
so I gave you my approval!
But the culprit
came back as a corpse.
The only witness is half-crazy.
And you don't even know...
if the technology was leaked or not!
We didn't expect...
Chief Tak to suddenly
get in the way.
Don't use him as an excuse.
You should've thought of
all the possible options.
It was your job...
to have multiple plans ready...
prior to carrying out the mission!
Someone must've...
leaked inside information.
What did you just say?
We found out about
Pi Cheol Woong's departure...
two hours prior to his flight.
But Chief Tak...
was already on the plane.
We'll be able to find something...
if we take a look
at Chief Tak's whereabouts...
prior to his departure.
You're right.
I've been feeling uneasy
about this mission...
ever since Baek Chan Mi
joined the team.
What do you mean?
What?
You just said so yourself.
You said you think there's a mole.
That's just an assumption.
It can't be...
Agent Baek.
She already betrayed us once.
Who says she won't do it again?
It's all my fault.
I'll take...
full responsibility
for what happened.
Deal with the darn corpse first.
It's starting to stink.
Don't just stand there and get lost.
The chief must be really angry.
He normally
doesn't even talk that much.
And Team Manager Dung
is really boring.
I'm surprised they're still
talking to each other.
Yoon Seok Ho
could still be the culprit.
I know for a fact
that it's not him.
What do you know?
Yoon Seok Ho.
He would never do
something like that.
Now that I think about it,
you've been pretty strange lately.
Spill it.
Something's going on, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm a field agent,
and he's my target.
What more do you expect?
If Kang Woo Won is no longer
a possible suspect,
can I also stop tailing him
in the field?
Did you seduce him instead
of keeping an eye on him?
My gosh, are you kidding?
When did I ever do something
like that during a mission?
Give me that.
Your response tells me
there really is something going on.
Stop talking nonsense.
Pi Cheol Woong is all we have.
But he's not sane,
so we won't be able
to make him testify.
Have you ladies thought about
how we should convince...
Director Myeong and Mr. Ok?
I'd love to participate
until the very end.
But as you already know,
I have to go home...
and cook for my husband and child.
I'll be off now.
See you.
Hwang Mi Soon. Hey.
Just go home. Go ahead. Leave.
Ms. Baek, why are you still here?
If I go home,
I'll just be staring at the TV.
I'd rather stay here
and watch something productive.
I watched that for days,
but nothing came up.
Isn't that even weirder?
The fact that someone stole
the technology...
means someone leaked information
from inside the lab.
But isn't it even weirder
that Mr. Ok seems so fine...
when he's the key figure?
Ms. Baek, you should stop
being such a workaholic.
It's time to get yourself a guy.
I'm popular.
I still have tons of people...
trying to set me up on blind dates.
My gosh, why does he keep
moving his head?
Classical music
doesn't suit him at all.
They were supposed to take out
the recyclables yesterday.
I told them not to forget
so many times.
I told them again and again.
My gosh, I can't believe this.
This place will turn into a pigpen
if I'm not around.
They'd be better off living as pigs.
What's the use of being human
when they're this dirty?
(Good Dew, original flavor)
Why is there a soju pack?
Did you drink soju?
Don't you know I prefer beer?
Didn't you mix soju with beer?
You know that
I can't stomach mixed drinks.
Cigarette ash?
(Report Card)
I told her to study
and instead she's...
I shouldn't rip up
photos of other people's kids.
(Ointment)
What's all this?
Honey! You got a text!
You got a text!
Is that woman going deaf?
(Overseas roaming canceled.)
What? Roaming?
So, is your mother doing okay?
She's just the same.
She complains of the pain,
then a few days later...
My gosh. I told you
not to drink from the bottle.
It's gross.
I should give her a call then.
What for?
Why? Can't I call her?
Well,
if you call,
the old woman
will just act up even more.
Don't call her all the time.
Did Joo Yeon come home early?
I think she came straight back
from her after school lessons.
Did she?
(Il Kwang Hitech)
How did you hurt your arm?
I was taking care of personal
business over the weekend...
and hurt myself slightly.
That's not slight.
I'll make sure
it doesn't hinder my work.
What do you do on weekends?
Why do you ask?
Because you hurt yourself
each weekend.
Are you maybe into kickboxing?
As if.
Or are you into dangerous hobbies?
Hey!
I'm not the type to
risk my life just for a hobby.
You don't hang out with...
dangerous people, do you?
I'm surrounded by ordinary people.
It's almost boring.
Then I should've taken you with me.
- Pardon?
- The first few months...
at a new job is tough
because you're trying to settle in.
If I brought you along
on my business trips,
I was afraid you'd call me
a terrible boss,
so I left you behind to rest.
And you just get hurt.
I should've taken you with me.
Chief Secretary Byun
pushes his staff really hard,
and I'm concerned.
About what?
In case...
you end up resigning.
But then,
when I see you at your desk,
I'm relieved.
But not that you get hurt.
Don't get hurt again.
I get concerned.
(15 years ago)
Please leave.
I won't stay for long.
I just want to see him.
You signed a contract...
that states once it expires,
you are no longer
permitted to see him in private.
I want to see him as a friend,
not as someone I once taught.
That's why we cannot allow it.
Please leave.
(Seok Ho)
I'll leave you to your work.
Who's that?
You hired a woman?
Why are you here?
You don't let women in your office.
You prefer to meet them outside.
If you're here to be nosy,
just finish your tea and leave.
I'm busy.
Can't I even say that?
Between us?
I'll pretend I accepted your advice.
The tea tastes terrible.
It makes my mouth dry.
Does your secretary
not manage your pantry well?
Why? Does the tea
Director Myeong serves...
taste just amazing?
The day before yesterday,
he flew to Henan Province.
He must have bought
some expensive puer tea.
I'm a shareholder of this company.
Why act like it's odd for me to
spend time with the management?
You're the CEO.
You shouldn't be so closed-minded.
Mr. Byun.
He has a female guest.
It must be his wife.
His wife?
Why are you so shocked?
Because she's so beautiful.
Yes, she is beautiful.
Seok Ho was married?
But then, he is old enough...
to be married with 2 or 3 kids.
Should I call her his ex-wife?
They got divorced.
Why didn't I see that on his file?
Ms. Baek, put these in a vase...
and put them in the CEO's office.
CEO Yoon doesn't like these flowers.
Do you know his taste in flowers?
Exactly how well do you know him?
Do you know him
better than his ex-wife,
or better than me
who served him for eight years?
Do you?
Of course not.
I'll do as you said.
Do it.
My father will soon
announce his candidacy.
Why are you telling me that?
You know that...
I tend to be very well-prepared.
I do know that.
Before we even met,
you wrote a prenuptial agreement
for me to sign.
Isn't that much better than
the heir to a company...
who was forced by
his parents to marry,
and did so without a plan
as if he were eating a meal?
Stop beating around the bush
and get to the point.
It's too boring to listen to.
You'll need some time
to prepare a slush fund,
so I came to give you a heads up.
It's never a good thing for people
to be so consistent.
People should change at times
in order to become more mature.
What's wrong with that?
From the moment we got married,
I've loved no one else but you.
My heart stays consistent.
"Consistent"? Yes, you're right.
You care only about my money.
I really like
how consistently honest you are.
I also look forward to hearing
how much you can provide.
This is so awkward.
I've never seen a woman
in his office before.
(My dear niece, you didn't forget
our meeting on Saturday, right?)
You'd better keep your promise...
and leave me be until I'm done
with my project at work.
I swear this is the last time.
The ramyeon here tastes great.
Then I'll have
ramyeon with dumplings...
- Ramyeon with rice cakes, please.
- Okay.
- We'll take two.
Is your mother's condition
really bad?
She's getting better.
She seemed healthy
when I last met her.
She'll get better soon.
I'm sure she'll recover.
It's here.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Do you not like green onions?
No, they're too spicy
when they're not cooked.
There are so many.
I'll have them.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- Take your time.
My gosh.
The rice cakes are delicious.
Will you grant me a wish...
if I get better grades this time?
What's your wish?
Someone must've...
leaked inside information.
We found out about
Pi Cheol Woong's departure...
two hours prior to his flight.
But Chief Tak was
already on the plane.
We'll find something if we take
a look at Chief Tak's whereabouts...
prior to his departure.
Pi Cheol Woong will be...
on a flight
that departs in two hours.
(Michael: This afternoon, 1 p.m.,
the cafe in Royal Hotel)
Sir!
Micheal sent him a text.
Zoom in.
(Michael: This afternoon, 1 p.m.,
the cafe in Royal Hotel)
What are you waiting for?
Call everyone.
Yes, sir.
All right.
We now have a good chance.
Let's do this. Give me a grand slam.
Come on. You can do it.
What on earth are you doing?
Get this off me!
I saw a big piece of trash,
so I thought I'd clean up.
It's too big for the vacuum though.
Let go!
Wait, someone's calling.
That's what I call perfect timing.
You and your darn strong arms.
Hello?
Are you kidding me?
You want me to work on a weekend?
Are you drunk?
Extra pay?
It should be double on weekends.
Of course.
Mr. Dong,
I can't get a hold of Chan Mi.
She probably got wasted last night
and is now ghosting you.
Call her until
her phone battery dies.
(Congratulations on
returning to the field)
Where else would I be?
I'm in Nonhyeon-dong.
Exactly.
Why would I be here
on a weekend morning?
It's because Royal Hotel is here.
Auntie, I said I didn't have
the time for this.
What do you mean you want a photo?
Of course I'm in a skirt.
Yes, I'm wearing makeup too.
Did you think I came here
without washing my face?
Whatever. I'm hanging up.
Sure.
Look at you getting your hopes up.
This is how you get
a bomb blasted on your head.
(Congratulations on
returning to the field)
It's the weekend,
so finding a babysitter
won't be easy.
Don't spit it out.
I made this just for you, you know.
Right.
Which hotel in Nonhyeon-dong?
Royal Hotel?
Yes, I know the place.
(Wash and Clean)
Ok Cheol is here.
Il Kwang?
That's right.
Il Kwang...
is Korea's most prominent company.
It's admirable.
You're the one
who's more impressive.
One would have to be passionate...
to get injured in the line of work.
Here you go.
I see...
you're good with knives.
Well, this is nothing...
compared to my cooking skills.
I'd love to show you next time.
I'll make you a tender chop steak.
Next time?
Well,
Il Kwang has over 30 subsidiaries,
so I shouldn't worry.
So what is it
that you do for a living?
I...
work at a small company...
in overseas marketing...
I see.
You work in overseas transactions.
Yes, something like that.
(Team Leader Dong)
Excuse me.
The person you have reached
can't talk due to...
the business she's engaged in.
If you call again, she might
turn off her phone altogether.
Bye, see you tomorrow.
What? Hey!
Chan Mi!
Unbelievable.
That was JS.
JS?
The jerk-scumbag.
Mi Soon, where are you?
Get in there!
I'm on my way.
Let's greet my customer then.
What's wrong with this?
What on earth are you doing here?
I could ask you the same thing.
No way...
No way.
Why...
What is she doing there?
Chan Mi, how about
we go out for dessert?
Can I take a rain check?
I'm sorry,
but something urgent came up.
You scumbag!
Please don't go.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
Things are over between us.
You should leave.
We were together for seven years,
but here you are on a blind date...
days after we broke up.
I thought you loved me.
You said I was the one for you.
What a scumbag.
Do something.
See this?
I'm going to find another woman
and live a good life,
so get over it already. Just leave.
Don't put me in the middle of this.
Go. Get out of my life.
Is that Zo In Sung?
Zo In Sung?
What are you...
What just happened?
Zo In Sung?
What on earth? Where did he go?
Where is he?
I really hoped
to find someone decent this time,
but I guess I'm cursed
when it comes to men.
Sorry.
Where did he go?
What?
Under the table?
Sweetheart!
My gosh.
Are you all right?
Open your eyes!
You ignored my call, this operation,
and my orders.
What a proud moment for you.
Did you see everything?
A romantic thriller with a twist.
How was
the entertaining blockbuster?
It was more like a soap opera to me.
Didn't you know?
Soap operas have
been trending lately.
- Are you all right?
- I'm good.
It serves you right.
Ok Cheol isn't ordering
and is waiting for someone.
- Hey, newbie.
- Yes?
Want to try the new menu?
The new menu?
Sure. Why not?
This must be my lucky day. Awesome.
Gosh, it's very good.
(Michael: NIS is on to you.
Will be in touch.)
Ok Cheol is heading out.
Seriously? Darn it.
Goodness.
- It's to die for.
- Mi Soon, get out here.
Right now? Why?
We're waiting outside, so move it.
Thank you!
What's taking you so long?
Sorry about that.
- Seriously?
- I said I was sorry.
Mu Hyeok, follow him.
(Wash and Clean)
Wait, she's coming!
- Faster.
- But...
Run faster!
Darn it.
Mi Soon, hop in.
You couldn't have stopped earlier?
- Come on.
- Unbelievable.
Get in.
Let's go.
- Mr. Dong!
- Stop the van.
What took you so long?
Sorry about that.
The cab took a wrong turn.
- Just drive.
- Sure.
You can't cut in line like that.
Sorry.
- Could you turn up the AC?
- Sure.
There he is.
Drive faster. We'll lose him.
I want to,
but we have a kid on board.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't find a sitter.
Ok Cheol seems to be heading...
to the research lab.
What on earth is he up to?
(Michael: NIS is on to you.
Will be in touch.)
Sir, can you go a little faster?
Then I'd be going over the limit.
Drive faster!
Faster.
What's up with him?
Make a left to the research lab!
After all that,
he's heading back to the lab?
He made us.
He probably did at the coffee shop.
He's right.
I won't deny that
I am partially to blame here.
But would we have
failed this mission...
if Mi Soon had come out faster?
What?
I'm the only one
who came to work on time.
You've got to be kidding me.
I came as fast I could too,
but Mr. Dong summoned us
without much time to spare.
- You're right.
- Exactly.
So it's all my fault. Is that it?
Forget the mission
if that's how it'll be.
Pull over.
Come on.
Over there.
I'm not asking you
to have world-class teamwork.
I'm not even expecting
the best version of yourselves.
Still, shouldn't you at least
do the basics?
I'm sorry.
We'll get Michael's number
from Ok Cheol, okay?
I'd like to see you try.
Do you think we can't do it?
Because we don't know the basics?
We're not even up to par?
Hold on a second.
We just need to
get Ok Cheol's phone...
and find Michael's number on it.
Easier said than done.
How will you possibly
get your hands on his phone?
We'll swipe it, of course.
It'll take three seconds tops.
Mi Soon, please.
Ever since the beginning
of phase three,
he rarely leaves the research lab.
This was his first outing in a week.
Then we'll have to infiltrate
the research lab.
But another security system error...
will raise flags.
She's right.
Remember the one that glared at us?
He might catch on.
Really?
Your hard work paid off though...
because we now have a way in.
Time out.
Are you talking about
what I think you're talking about?
Hello?
Can you curl up a bit more?
No way.
My word is final.
I'm not going in there again. Never.
No.
No way.
Why must it be me?
You suggested the infiltration.
You said we should
head in there ourselves.
(Congratulations on
returning to the field)
Why am I the one
who always does these things?
Why? Why me?
Why do you always do this to me?
Why? Just why?
Forget it. I'm going home.
Drive.
Mi Soon.
I thought these tights
might help in there.
Either you take my place
or get that out of my sight.
Mi Soon, we'll be watching
from outside,
so don't be scared.
Activate Code Blue
if you're in trouble.
Either you take my place
or shut your trap.
This is a blind spot,
so no cameras will see you.
The parking lot never has
too many guards either.
Either you take my place...
or get lost.
Sure. I'll get lost.
A big sidestep.
Mi Soon, be careful.
What the...
Gosh.
Let's go.
That's it.
Okay.
She's in.
She's in. Get ready.
Yes, sir.
I can't believe...
I'm back in here.
What on earth?
Unbelievable.
I'll probably die
from a lung disease first.
It could be dangerous.
If things go south and we die,
then I'll be happy
not to have died alone.
My gosh.
Why did he have to scream?
Mr. Ok!
Are you all right?
Up there.
- Up there. I saw something.
- Up there?
There...
I'm sorry, but nothing's there.
- Nothing?
- Yes, there's nothing there.
Absolutely nothing.
It's up there.
I definitely saw it.
My gosh!
I killed him.
It's because of me...
Mr. Ok, you should take a break.
No, this can't be.
No...
All right.
Are you all right, sir?
Yes.
I'm sorry...
about before.
Don't mention it.
For a moment, I thought
you had seen the bouncing head.
The bouncing head?
Didn't you know?
This research lab
used to be a mental institution.
I didn't know.
I had no idea.
It obviously looks like a hospital.
All square and white.
I heard that many of the patients...
were incarcerated
against their will.
What's wrong with you?
Pick up the pace!
Get it done already.
Come on.
Okay, good.
Here we go. Keep going.
A fire broke out though...
and all the patients...
got trapped and burned alive.
Later on, they found a patient
at the front entrance.
He had died with his head stuck...
in the bars of the window.
The bouncing head?
What I saw...
wasn't the face of a human.
You're almost done.
There is no such thing
as ghosts though.
- Don't be silly, sir.
- I'm not kidding.
Unbelievable.
Just get in here, sir.
Look. There's no one there.
Right?
I'm sure it's just a story
the employees made up.
There is no such thing as ghosts.
Of course.
I'll get back to work then.
Hold on.
All right.
In the name of the Lord,
in the name of the Lord
We prevailed
In the name of the Lord,
in the name of the Lord
We prevailed
Amen
You.
You there!
This is killing me.
What now?
Gosh.
Are you kidding me?
Mr. Ok!
- What's up with him?
- Hello? Is this 911?
- My boss passed out.
- Gosh.
Hold on.
What happened to your face?
What about it?
- What's this?
- Did I get something on it?
Are you sure it went smoothly?
Of course.
Not even the spirits knew
that I was there.
I have access to Ok Cheol's phone.
All I need to do
is find Michael's contact number.
(Michael)
- What?
- You have it already?
It's on speed dial.
(Michael)
Michael. That's him, right?
Mounted stress and fatigue...
can weaken a person...
which can also lead
to losing consciousness.
There's nothing
to worry about though.
I just thought it was
because of something I said.
Thank you, doctor.
(Michael)
The phone is turned on.
Trace its location.
I need a trace...
on the number I sent you ASAP.
(NIS Chief Seo Gook Hwan)
(This afternoon, 1 p.m.,
the cafe in Royal Hotel)
(NIS is on to you.
Will be in touch.)
(NIS Chief Seo Gook Hwan)
(Epilogue)
I should've eaten more for dinner.
Gosh.
It's gotten all dirty.
Are you all right?
Is your neck okay?
Did you just hit me?
No, I didn't...
I wanted to sort out a few files,
but you were...
You were dozing off,
so I put a blanket over you...
This is why you should...
call it a day
and go home if you're tired!
Unbelievable.
(Good Casting)
Do you think Ok Cheol
found out about the cameras?
I want a report
on Baek Chan Mi's whereabouts...
off the record.
Who should I arrest first? Bingo.
Who sent you?
Are Kang Woo Won's memories back?
I don't know.
I'll drive today.
I'm quite a skilled driver.
- Don't swerve!
- Are we being informal now?
Eyes on the road.
Your father passed away?
I still don't get
why he went to Busan alone...
three years ago.
Show me how to use the rice cooker.
Are you kidding me?
This isn't where I should be today.
Baek Chan Mi
isn't your average agent.
If you're caught,
deal with her quietly.