(This drama is fictitious...)
(and all characters, events, organizations, and settings...)
(are unrelated to real life.)
(Wash and Clean)
I'm sure she went this way.
Darn it.
Didn't you get the message that our mission is over?
I got it too.
Then what? Should we lose Michael again...
and just let things go like we did three years ago?
What are you afraid of?
You and I both.
We're employees before we're agents.
Did you forget yelling "command and discipline"...
thousands of times when we were in training?
You're afraid you'll lose your job.
You too?
You know that...
I have a kid to support.
You wouldn't know because you're single,
but I have loans, interest, and tuition fees to pay next month.
This is my livelihood.
I can't just jump into something without weighing things out.
Even if,
just this once,
I beg for your help?
My goodness.
You know...
how important...
this job is to me.
Oh, my goodness.
Darn it.
Hide. It's my husband.
Oh, my gosh.
- Shoot. What now? - What now?
Why can't I see a thing?
Darn.
What...
So,
what's your plan?
Talk fast.
My goodness.
Wait. That truck...
What are you doing?
I woke up and you weren't in bed.
Anyway,
why are you out here at this hour?
I told you to throw this out and you never did.
I just couldn't stand the smell.
If I don't throw it out,
you just live with the trash, don't you?
Is it your lover?
I wish you'd hold me that lovingly.
My gosh, poor me.
I'm just a poor woman with rotten luck.
My goodness.
(Baek Chan Mi)
(Hwang Mi Soon)
(Lim Ye Eun)
(Lim Ye Eun and Kwon Min Seok were in a relationship.)
(Kwon Min Seok died the day their daughter was born.)
Kwon Min Seok?
Agent Baek...
will steal...
the ledger tomorrow.
(Good Casting)
(Il Kwang Hitech)
(Episode 10)
(Director Myeong Gye Cheol)
(Kang Woo Won's Manager Found Dead in Hospital)
You'll steal what's in Director Myeong's office?
Yes.
Are you in your right mind?
I am completely sane.
Look.
My pupils are the same size,
and the temperature between my eyebrows and nose are stable.
My brainwaves are 100-percent normal too.
It's against the rules to not return to base.
If we're caught doing something in the field,
it's really over for us all.
I realized something when I lost Michael three years ago.
To catch that jerk,
I must put my life on the line to get a shooting chance.
If this goes wrong,
we might never get another shot at getting him.
I don't need another shot.
Because I will get him this time.
I have a problem.
I can't log into the NIS network.
I have an even bigger problem.
The mission was canceled as of yesterday.
You must return all the equipment.
I returned everything.
I don't have anything.
I'd love to give you something, but I have nothing.
I can't give you what I don't have.
But...
How did he find that?
You're really thorough.
My goodness.
This could've pricked you. You have skills, I must say.
I'm not stupid.
I stored it safely between my toes.
I don't think I can...
hack into the network.
He took all my equipment.
The probability of failure is over 50 percent.
If it goes wrong, you don't just lose your agent status.
You could become a criminal for which you'll go to prison.
Are you okay with that?
Prison life suits me well. I can manage.
Even though the NIS could erase your whole life?
Chief Seo leaves or I leave.
It's one or the other.
Fine.
It's one or the other, life or death.
Let's do it!
A GPS tracker.
I managed to hide this.
I'll steal Director Myeong's ledger tonight.
How will you get into his office?
I already have a plan.
Is that really the only way?
If something goes wrong,
you have nothing to do with it.
I can't do that.
- You know that. - You know...
how I got where I am now.
If it hadn't been for your father,
I'd have starved or died in the streets.
Don't bring up the past. It's not fun.
I was an orphan no one cared about.
He fed me, educated me,
even sent me abroad to study.
He died before I even got a chance to repay him.
How am I to repay him now?
You're doing well enough now.
You paid him back.
I will get it done tonight.
That's final.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
(Wash and Clean)
It's impossible to access the NIS network,
so it'll be too risky to try and hack into it.
The only tool we have is the GPS device...
that Mi Soon managed to keep.
So we have no choice but to do it the traditional way.
"The traditional way"?
It's what we used to do...
before you started working here.
It sounds fancy.
But it's pretty much just manual labor.
(But it's pretty much just manual labor.)
Can you escort Mr. Yoon to his meeting later?
- Pardon? - Why do you look so startled?
It's not like I'm asking you to work overtime.
You're right.
Then I'll go...
and deliver this paperwork.
I'm going in now.
Okay, get it done in three minutes.
Chan Mi, can you show me the ceiling?
I can see it clearly now.
Why isn't there anything there?
Hurry up. We don't have time.
Is anyone there?
Hello? Is no one outside?
Excuse me.
Hurry up. We have one minute left.
There should be a card or fingerprint scanning device.
If not that, there should at least be a biometrics camera.
But why can't I see anything?
My gosh.
If you're unlucky, you might trigger an alarm.
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I'll get caught if I keep stalling.
I'm just going to leave.
Wait. I think I found it.
You recorded everything, right?
I'm going to leave now. Check the footage and let me know.
Hello.
Mr. Yoon signed the personnel evaluation results.
So I dropped by to give this to you.
You should've called. I would've picked it up myself.
Then I would've been able to meet Mr. Yoon.
Have a good one.
It's a beacon sensor.
"A beacon sensor"? What's that?
It's a security system that uses a device...
to send a bluetooth signal to open the door.
But Director Myeong doesn't have a smartphone.
He has nothing to connect the signal with.
As soon as the secretary came into the room,
the device on the door suddenly turned green.
I think that means she has something that has a sensor inside.
"A sensor"?
(No earrings)
(Accessory)
Zoom in on this.
It looks a bit different compared to mine.
Don't you see something shiny inside?
- Yes. - By the looks of it sparkling,
I'm pretty sure that's a beacon sensor.
Okay, that means we just need that badge.
No, wait.
The device needs to turn red in order for the door to open.
But it's still green.
So I think that means...
there's a set time to when you can enter.
What?
Then it will be useless to steal that badge.
Gosh.
That means we need to steal Director Myeong's sensor...
since that one has full access to that room.
Gosh, that's going to take some work.
The door will open...
as long as you have the beacon sensor,
and it's easy to duplicate.
So Director Myeong will always have it with him.
You need to find out what that is.
(Accessory 1: Tie pin)
(Accessory 2: Badge)
He has five accessories in total.
A tie pin, two cufflinks,
a badge, and a ring.
"Five"?
He's a guy, but he wears more accessories than me.
(Il Kwang Hitech NAND Flash Construction Site)
As soon as we start producing...
the 176-layer 4D NAND Flash,
we're going to add two more production lines...
to meet the increased volume of orders.
And that will be here and here.
It's not the badge.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
The cufflinks aren't it.
Sir, take this.
Oh, thank you.
Did you make this yourself?
I'm very dexterous.
- Where is the bathroom? - It's over there, sir.
I'll have it washed and returned to you.
- You can just give it to me now. - No, it's okay.
Sir, I need to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
It's not the ring.
The only one left is the tie pin.
The representative from Il Kwang Distribution will be your guide.
- It's nice to meet you. - Same here, sir.
You're very handsome, sir.
Did you say "Il Kwang"?
You scumbag!
I'm going to find another woman and live a good life.
Just leave.
(Congratulations on returning to the field)
Hello.
I'm Mr. Yoon's secretary. My name is Baek...
Excuse me... Secretary Baek?
Well then, follow me.
Let's go.
Come this way, Ms. Baek.
Of all the affiliates,
why did it have to be here?
Why? Why?
Let's not stand out. Let's just naturally...
disappear.
I can do it. I can do it.
Ms. Baek?
Ms. Baek.
I have something to ask you.
What's that?
I've always respected Mr. Yoon,
and I'd like to eat lunch with him.
What?
Why are you so startled?
(Safety Passage)
Okay, I think that's enough inspection for today.
Let's call it a day.
Yes, that's a great idea.
To be honest,
we'd love to eat lunch with you!
What a lunatic.
- Mr. Yoon! - Mr. Yoon!
Ladies!
We asked Mr. Yoon to join us for lunch today.
So please make sure...
you cook him a nice meal!
Thank you.
I've always wanted to enjoy a meal with you all.
And thanks to Mr. Woo, I finally get to do so.
And I'm very glad.
The NAND Flash is going to be a huge project for the company,
so I hope you all do your best...
in making sure the construction goes well.
A round of applause!
You should eat.
I have a cold.
I don't have an appetite.
You followed me out here when you're not feeling well?
What's Mr. Byun doing...
that he'd send a rookie secretary on an official trip?
He should know better than that.
(Janitor's Locker Room)
Wait, wait.
She's an outside hire who comes once a week.
Director Myeong hired her in person.
Ms. Baek, it looks like you don't have an appetite.
Shall I get you some scorched rice in water?
Mr. Woo. Don't you have a girlfriend?
I can tell right away that you have lots of lady friends.
Don't you even go there.
Mr. Woo has such rotten luck with women.
Actually, not long ago, I went on a blind date.
Oh, dear. Are you okay?
Here, drink some water.
Don't even talk about that.
The woman was a lunatic.
A psycho.
What was she like?
Ever since that day,
I've been getting physical therapy.
What, physical therapy?
The woman I met on the blind date...
My date was...
She was so crazy that she...
Mr. Yoon.
I think you should leave now.
I can take my time.
What about that woman?
Mr. Yoon.
You have another appointment.
I don't.
You do.
I do have one very important appointment.
Right?
So, about my blind date.
I'll hear about your blind date next time. Excuse me.
- Let's go. - What? Next time when?
- Goodbye. - Bye, sir.
To the office, please.
No. I have to make a stop on the way.
Checking the factory site...
was your last agenda of the day.
My most important appointment is left.
Is it unofficial?
You'll see when you get there.
Okay.
Everyone is talking about the sudden death of...
Kang Woo Won's manager.
Videos of Kang Woo Won's escapades are flooding the internet,
making people criticize his character.
People online and offline are making harsh comments.
There's something I don't understand.
Why is it Kang Woo Won's fault that his manager killed himself?
It's because of...
messages the manager left on his social media page.
While he worked for Kang Woo Won,
he wrote, "It's tough", "I want to die",
"I want to leave the country."
There was a long string of extreme messages.
He wanted to die because of Kang Woo Won...
Jerks like you should die.
- Go ahead and die. - Die.
- Die. - Why won't you die?
- Die. - Just die.
- Die. - Die.
Don't you just hate Kang Woo Won?
We barely got him to sign a contract and this happened.
Now the image of our rice cooker is lower than dirt.
Aren't you glad it's not drunk driving or drugs?
It's worse than that. Someone died.
He lost the drama role,
and all his commercials were canceled.
Shouldn't we pull our commercials as well?
The bosses will decide what to do.
(Kang Woo Won)
Hey, Lim.
Lim!
- Yes? - Your team leader called for you.
Will you keep your head screwed on?
The atmosphere is rotten as it is.
Go to Kang Woo Won...
and make him sign the annulment.
The annulment of his contract?
And this is to notify him we're suing for breach of contract.
The commercial is popular,
and sales jumped quite a bit.
Do we have to annul it?
He must be going through a lot as it is.
We're not a charity...
that makes money to look after celebrities that cause trouble.
This is the perfect time to cut him loose.
This is just the beginning.
The beginning of what?
The beginning of Kang Woo Won's downfall.
Kang Woo Won's downfall.
(Complaint)
Do I have to go in person?
You can send it by registered mail.
It'll be a hassle if he refuses to take the package.
Take it to him and watch him sign it.
Yes.
This is what I wanted so much.
I'll finally be free of him...
and can go back to my normal life.
How can I tell him?
I can't do it.
Never.
Poppy.
Why are you such a mess?
How long has he been stuck indoors?
Woo Won.
Mr. Kang.
(How to use a rice cooker)
I'll write down the instructions for you again.
You can't take back what you gave me.
But I'm the one who wrote it.
Taking things back is the worst.
I'll write you another one!
(How to use a rice cooker)
Woo Won.
Woo Won. Mr. Kang!
Oh, no!
Yes, 911.
911. Call 911.
Are you all right?
Don't make a fuss.
I'm not dying.
Are you fully awake?
Are you sure you're okay?
I just took a few sleeping pills.
I just couldn't sleep.
It doesn't look like just a few.
Why are you here?
Well...
It's nothing.
Do you think so too?
About what?
Pi Cheol Woong.
That he died because of me.
No.
I don't think he died because of you.
No way.
Why?
Because...
it wasn't your fault.
It wasn't your fault.
He died because of us.
I knew it.
I know you're just saying that out of pity.
Just go.
Get lost.
So the urgent business...
Give it a shot. I'll coach you.
That's all right. I'm good.
It's difficult for everyone at first.
I couldn't hit the target properly either.
Go on. I'll help you get the hang of it.
Go ahead.
Stabilize the gun with one arm. Have the other arm push against it.
Keep your eyes open.
Open your eyes.
What the...
You just hit the target. I see you're good at this.
That's too bad. It was so close.
It's harder than it looks.
Right. It isn't easy.
How many shots must I make...
to win that big stuffed animal?
It's impossible.
A smaller one...
can be won with 50 shots though.
50 shots?
That'll cost 50 dollars at least.
You can then trade 50 of those...
to one big stuffed animal.
So the place you stop by...
every time you're outside the office...
That was the hardest to win.
It took me 100 shots.
Or was it 150?
150 shots.
I've won 30 small stuffed animals,
so I'll be trading them for a big one in no time.
Is that something you want to win?
Why else would I be collecting these?
I stop by every time I think of my father.
Your father?
He used to take me hunting often when I was young.
The hunt was never successful...
and we mostly ate at a restaurant afterward,
but he said I was too cowardly for a boy...
and that it wasn't a good quality.
It's why he kept taking me.
Truth be told, I've always been fonder of...
looking at things instead.
There's definitely a resemblance.
I punch men too, you know.
Your punches will probably only tickle.
My hands may be small,
but they can really hurt.
Gosh. What are you doing?
My hands may be small, but they can really hurt.
Stay still.
What's wrong?
It's getting late.
We should head back.
Did you look into his tie pin?
Myeong Gye Cheol has it on 24-7...
which means it contains the sensor.
However,
it's a limited edition model from a luxury brand.
Less than 100 of them were bought in Korea.
His name isn't on the consumer list...
Ye Eun got us.
Can't we just make a duplicate?
You may not know this from only buying knock-offs,
but designer brands release their products...
with serial numbers.
We can return it before he notices.
The clock is ticking, so get us a duplicate.
Right now?
The NIS only has...
a few 3D printers available.
Let's say I managed to get to one undetected.
Operating it...
isn't a walk in the park.
Get it to us before end of business hours.
Just hang up.
What the...
They think whatever they ask of me is easy.
You're coming by often lately.
Don't be like that.
I came to remind you...
of the promise you seem to have forgotten.
- What promise? - I make you CEO...
and you fatten my dad's pockets in return.
It seemed to have slipped your mind.
I'm considering...
whether or not I should keep our deal.
I don't know...
if it's worth it anymore.
So you wanted to be CEO...
not because it's what your father wanted...
but because you had an ulterior motive.
An ulterior motive?
Only you know what goes on inside your head...
and why you changed your mind.
You're right about me changing my attitude.
I no longer wish to live...
suppressing my emotions.
Since when?
Keep acting out...
and I'll sell my shares of the company.
I wonder who'll benefit the most from them.
Are you hurt?
- I'm fine. - Leave it.
I'll clean it up myself. How clumsy of her.
Sir, I'm grateful for your help,
but you're making me uncomfortable.
Of course. I just can't seem to help myself.
I'll quickly have this cleaned up.
You seem jumpy...
like someone who has something to hide.
I thought you had left.
I see this is the sweet spot.
Please let me know if I can help you with anything.
Now I know...
why you sit here.
(You have a new message.)
Is that why you had someone follow me?
(CEO Sim Hwa Ran)
Does Seok Ho know...
your true identity?
You seem very interested in a nobody like me.
If I had known you weren't a nobody,
I would've had you removed ages ago.
(You have a new message.)
Package en route.
Then let's get to work.
The duplicate has no serial number on the back.
The target is here.
Got it.
You are to wrap this up before he notices.
My gosh, I'm so sorry!
Goodness gracious.
What are you doing with that dirty rag?
Get it off him.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Look where you're going, lady.
I apologize for knocking this off.
If you're done, get out of the way.
Sure, let me clean up...
The new town is developing high-value land...
and we're offering...
our VVIP clients a chance to hear the offer first.
The investment will be worthwhile...
I'm good.
The serial number is...
Wait, there isn't one.
There's nothing here.
Maybe I should've had random numbers carved in it.
Well, it's not like she can tell it's a knock-off.
It's a knock-off.
- A knock-off? - Yes.
Now I'm thinking that his cufflinks are knock-offs too.
I was worried about nothing.
Unbelievable.
That nutjob.
What now?
Is it okay to keep taking late-night snacks from Mr. Byun?
He said he'll treat us again when he gets this month's salary.
- Again? - So enjoy.
I'll buy next month, so eat up.
- Sure. - Enjoy.
Wait, what's up with the monitor?
What about the monitor?
It's out again.
(Emergency use only)
So 10 minutes tops.
- What? - What's going on?
The power must be out.
- Start the backup generators. - Yes, sir.
- Hurry! - Got it.
Okay, 10 minutes and counting down.
(Director Myeong Gye Cheol)
(Project Launch Expenses and Business Council Budget)
The security team is here.
Get out of there right now.
Why is this door locked?
- Can you get me the master key? - Sure.
What's taking you so long? Your 10 minutes is almost up.
Thanks.
- The power's back. - What?
Darn.
What are you doing in my office?
Aren't you CEO Yoon's secretary?
I found it suspicious too,
so I was about to report it.
How did you get the door to open?
The knock-off tie clip wouldn't have worked.
It's like I said, sir.
The door was open when I got here.
It was a trap set up by the sly viper.
Why hasn't Chan Mi gotten out of there?
I don't know.
Our call was disconnected.
What were you doing in my office?
I dropped an important letter...
when I came by earlier today.
You sneaked in here like a street cat at this hour...
just to retrieve this letter?
Am I supposed to believe that?
I understand how misleading this may seem,
but I'm telling you the truth.
"This letter which originated in the UK..."
"has brought good luck..."
"to its recipients all around the world."
Is this some kind of joke to you?
Check the security cameras.
I'm sorry, sir, but nothing was caught on camera...
due to the blackout.
Frisk her.
Don't just stand there and frisk her.
You are to check even what's in her hair.
Go ahead.
You can search everywhere...
including my hair.
(Project Launch Expenses and Business Council Budget)
(Date, Name, Amount)
(Sexual harassment in the workplace)
What on earth?
No! Darn it!
(54M 4393)
My secretary was caught snooping around your office?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
So what'll it be?
If you didn't know about this,
I'll have the police handle it.
If something goes wrong,
you have nothing to do with it.
Where are you right now?
Your new secretary...
was caught in a cheeky act.
She wouldn't confess so I had no choice...
but to call her boss.
You found nothing after frisking her.
Don't frame an innocent woman for something she didn't do...
and let her go.
It's suspicious enough...
that the cameras were down during the time.
You playing it dumb isn't helping anyone's case.
Well, that's your problem.
Meanwhile,
I'm disgusted by the fact...
that you're framing an innocent woman.
If people find out...
that the CEO's secretary was caught snooping around my office,
you'll be the one in the hot seat.
Do whatever you want.
Is she legally at-fault?
This is a new one for me too.
Since she's only a temp,
it could be better to let the police handle it.
No way.
Then she'll only be charged with breaking and entering.
It'll be better to report her to the NIS.
You never know.
She could be a corporate spy.
What do you think you're doing?
The fact that she's not back...
can only mean she's in trouble.
What if Chan Mi was caught?
What happens then?
This wasn't a sanctioned mission,
so disciplinary actions will be taken.
The same goes for us too.
We're lucky if it ends there.
If the police get involved, the NIS will cut ties with us.
Our lives will be ruined.
You've got to be kidding me.
It seems like you don't fully trust your secretary either.
Nothing will happen if she's innocent.
You'd better watch what you say.
We'll know once the truth comes out.
That's enough!
The one crossing the line and being irrational...
is you.
You see,
if that rat...
was sent here to steal from us,
I will make it my mission...
to have it rot in jail.
You think I'm bluffing?
I heard that you handpicked her.
Don't tell me that you're somehow involved too.
I'm sorry,
sir.
I told you...
that I'd work with someone bad at the job...
rather than someone I can't trust.
I will accept whatever punishment...
you deem as necessary.
I don't give people second chances.
You'll be the first.
Goodnight.
(Wash and Clean)
Gosh.
Hold on. How did you manage to get out of there?
Director Myeong wouldn't have let you go easily.
I don't know...
how I got out of there either.
What is it that you want?
The rights to the NAND flash project.
Hand it over.
Take it.
I'll be leaving with my secretary.
The lock requires a fingerprint.
I dropped an important letter...
when I came by earlier today.
Where's the safe?
Under the table.
Are you sure it requires a fingerprint?
I checked the safe...
just like you told me to. I'm sure.
What a shame.
I could've peeled off his flesh if the lock required a vein scan...
and plucked his eyeballs out if it required...
an iris scan.
It'll be sunrise soon.
We'll need a few hours to print his fingerprint,
so let's hurry.
Myeong Gye Cheol arrives at the office at 6 a.m. sharp.
We have a tight window, so move fast.
6 a.m.
Easy-peasy.
(Hope you get some rest.)
The man isn't even a second late.
Anyway, our guest has arrived.
You've got to be kidding me.
Ta-da!
What are you doing? Get out of there.
Sure thing.
Hold it.
(Good Casting)
The chief is a traitor?
I was only following up on an anonymous tip.
I have a feeling that the chief could be Michael.
It'll be over once we obtain that video.
Do you have Director Myeong's ledger?
Are you sure you have the video of Michael?
I'll await your comeback.
That darned ultra fine dust.
That's because Baek Chan Mi is in league with Michael.
Are you the one who got Agent Kwon killed?
Yes, it was my fault.
Don't let emotions sway you.
She trusted me and I took advantage of her trust.
What's worse is that Chief Seo might only be a pawn.
Baek Chan Mi?
(Epilogue)
The treatments don't seem to be helping.
You sometimes come across buildings like this in the field.
Buildings erected where they shouldn't have been built on.
The foundations were wrong to begin with.
How do you solve that issue then?
They must be torn down and built again.
But it's different with people.
It takes too darn long to repair the physical damages.
How did you injure yourself again?
- I was hit. - I was hit.
Hold on.
Both of you?
This isn't an injury one sustains in a simple fistfight.
Were you attacked by a mob?
No, it was 1-on-1.
Your opponent must've been a professional.
You have no idea.
You made the first move, didn't you?
You should be glad that this is the worst of it...
since your opponent sounds like a big guy.
Consider yourselves lucky.
Anyway, this might hurt a bit.
I shouldn't have...
agreed to meet this person.
gotten cocky.
For some reason though,
I can't get her out of my head.
Wait, "her"?
Baek Chan Mi!