(People, locations, cases, companies, and products...)
(in this drama are purely fictional.)
(The winning script of the 2018 MBC Script Contest)
Goodness.
- Oh no. - My gosh.
Mr. Ga!
Yeol Chan! Hey, kid!
Hang in there!
My gosh! Are you insane?
Hey. Goodness.
Can't you see that I'm breathing?
Over there,
you'll find my allergy shot.
I hate doing product placements,
but I will consider doing it.
- Thank you. - I'll just consider it.
I'll just think about it.
And let's make one thing clear.
Even if I end up doing it,
it's only because of Mr. Ga Yeol Chan.
Do you understand?
Thank you.
Thank you!
I'll just think about it. I'm just going to think about it.
(Episode 7)
Mr. Joo!
Have you had breakfast?
Yes.
Great job. You should eat breakfast.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - What is this?
Mr. Oh, come over here. You have to see this.
Why? What is it?
- What is it? - This is no joke.
What is it?
- It's out? - Yes, keep going. Keep it going.
Goodness.
Did you eat a rat alive?
No, I had chicken.
What is this?
My mouth is on fire.
What kind of chicken did you eat...
to make you look so sexy?
Spicy Chicken.
(Spicy Chicken Ramyeon, sponsored by Joonsu Food)
- I can't believe this! - My gosh.
Do you hear the sound of our sales spiking up?
Their ratings are at 30 percent and above,
and it's already sold overseas to be aired.
We're going to sell this abroad too?
Ms. Ban, can you stop us already?
- We can't seem to stop. - Have you seen a doctor?
Your face is still...
It looks wonderful. My gosh.
Will you please stop doing things like these?
What are you talking about? I look like this goblin?
- Stop it. - I thought it was you, Mr. Oh.
Is it my profile?
I'm trying to be nice. What's with him?
Do I really look like him?
("Will Park Mak Doong Become the Next Park Mak Rye?")
(A misdelivery leads to an unexpected promotion)
This is why you can't compete with a guy who's lucky with money.
Did that senior intern get Eun Hye Soo to do this too?
- No. - Yes.
I heard she singled out Mr. Lee...
and called him to the set.
They've been friends ever since she was a rookie.
- Really? - Yes.
That's true,
but I managed to pull the trigger.
Okay, of course.
I'm sure you managed this all right, Mr. Ga.
Mr. Ga, have you been dating someone?
Pardon?
You don't seem very focused recently.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
She's just saying that to help you stay on top of everything.
Look at what happened this time. You already know that...
you hold a position where you can't do well alone.
Yes, I understand.
Goodness, Mr. Namgoong.
Hey.
- My gosh. - Well...
I tried my best to ruin the Eun Hye Soo project, but...
Goodness, don't say that.
Take a seat for now.
Take a seat. Please sit down.
Goodness, it's okay.
Okay, let's sit down together.
Man Sic, I can finally breathe thanks to you.
Mr. Ga was just told off by my kkondae just now.
Do you need anything in the office?
Just say it.
Goodness.
How does it feel to be high up here? Isn't the air fresher?
You're right.
All right. Man Sic.
Please hang in there a bit more.
This will all end soon.
I hope...
to see you up here.
Yes, sir.
Coffee...
Mr. Lee.
Please bring four cups of coffee to the meeting room.
Mr. Lee, what's wrong?
Is there a problem with making coffee?
- No. - Thank you.
Mr. Lee, is the coffee...
What?
What is it? What?
What are you doing with the wrapper?
Make new ones.
No one else drinks coffee mix except for you and Mr. Ahn.
Please prepare Americano from now on. Do you understand?
You kids can make your own coffee.
"You kids"?
You should be thanking me for making coffee for you kids,
yet you're complaining about my being dirty.
And how clean are you, exactly?
Mr. Lee, let's make this clear.
You're an intern, not a director.
Do you think I'm like the other interns?
What's wrong?
- He wants me to make coffee. - She wants me to make coffee.
I'll make the coffee. You should attend the meeting.
He's so unbelievable.
My goodness.
Sir, you shouldn't have done that. She's your superior.
Superior, my foot. She's a mere contract worker.
I ought to snap her neck.
Sir.
Hey, come here and make some coffee.
- No, I can do it. - No.
Make four cups of Americano and bring them to the meeting room.
What?
- Where's the coffee? - The others are making it.
What are you writing?
"MF"?
"Male, female"?
Spicy Chicken brand or Joon Ramyeon's...
extension products are good.
It could be meat or curry.
They could be HMR collaborations.
(HMR: A type of instant foods)
The topic is "something new but familiar".
I'd like you guys to write up a proposal each.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
And I'd like the interns to help out.
Wait.
How about our interns also write up their own?
Mr. Lee was the one who made Ong Ramyeon.
Is that so?
Is this finally my chance to do some real work?
(Marketing and Sales Department)
Goodness.
This is good. I think it's all right.
Gosh, it's so neat.
Mr. Oh, my proposal is going to be breathtaking.
You're already breathtaking as is.
Gosh, that's spicy.
What do we have here?
(New, changes, challenges, evolution)
Does this help?
Yes.
Mind maps provide the optimal environment...
for our brains to work.
Our brains will reach the highest effectiveness.
Is there anything you have in mind?
We're told to use the products that already exist.
We have dried pollack.
I thought about adding a bunch of it.
Dried pollack ramyeon...
Is that it?
Yes.
That was too simple, wasn't it?
No, it sounds good.
No wonder you came up with Ong Ramyeon. You're brilliant.
Goodness.
Sir.
Have you ever had it before?
No, I haven't.
But I did add ramyeon to some dried pollack soup.
And it was amazing.
Since then, I tell my wife to add ramyeon...
whenever she cooks some dried pollack soup.
My son loves it as well.
It's that good?
Even kids like it.
Gosh.
That's great.
I guess so.
Is this finally my time to shine?
I feel so alive.
I've always been doing menial work.
And now, I'm finally doing some real work.
Yes, I'm still just as competent.
I truly am.
Sir.
Should I write up a proposal with your idea?
Goodness, you don't have to.
No, no. I really like it.
I'd be more than grateful.
All right, then.
How could I get the ingredients?
There was the limited edition Spicy Chicken Noodles.
I believe the downside was that it wasn't spicy enough.
We need to be unique.
Koreans are known to enjoy very spicy foods.
Isn't our brand known for producing such products?
(Something New but Familiar, Spicy Chicken Ramyeon with Eggs)
Mr. Joo. "Spicy Chicken Ramyeon with Eggs"?
Yes.
I thought about selling the original Spicy Chicken Ramyeon...
alongside a half-boiled egg.
To be honest, Spicy Chicken Ramyeon...
is too spicy for people like me.
That's why I thought adding an egg to it would neutralize...
the spiciness.
The expiration date...
I'll think about it.
Okay.
Oh, thank you.
Ms. Lee.
The name of the ramyeon is...
"We've Added Saury to the Ramyeon"?
Yes, it's abbreviated to WASR.
Like so, it'd be interesting to make an entire series.
For example, WASR.
"We've Added Saury to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Pig Fat to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Kkakdugi to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Chicken Heads to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Chicken Feet to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Loaches to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Salad to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Pupae to the Ramyeon".
Something like this.
Gosh, you're so weird.
No, I think it'll be fun.
You're so original.
All right.
(Something New but Familiar, Dried Pollack Ramyeon)
"Dried Pollack Ramyeon".
This is good.
What is this?
I added our dried pollack cube to our ramyeon.
Yes, that's right. It's dried pollack ramyeon.
Is the dried pollack cube the only thing you added?
Yes, just that one.
Come on, that's too easy.
Let's go with this.
It'd be fun to use the same dried pollack packaging.
Mr. Oh.
Great job.
I love you.
Mr. Lee, where's your proposal?
Sorry?
This dried pollack ramyeon was my idea.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my. What are you going on about?
Have you been dreaming?
I'm serious. You know that it was my idea.
What are you talking about?
Are you seriously doing this to me?
What have I done to you?
Come on, you're driving me crazy.
You're the one who's driving me crazy.
Why are you doing this to me?
Right. Witnesses. We have witnesses here.
Yoon Soo. Tae Lee. Didn't you see me...
explaining my idea to Mr. Oh? You saw that, right?
- I did? - Yes.
Well, you don't really count even if you were there.
Yoon Soo. Why don't you tell him?
Yes. Can you tell us what you saw?
He never...
did that.
Are you kidding me?
Come on.
Mr. Ga, it's so hard to work here.
So Mr. Lee won't be joining us because he's upset?
No, he won't.
He said he might upset his stomach because what happened wasn't fair.
It doesn't make any sense that he's the one who came up with the idea.
Gosh, that was such an absurd accusation.
I can't say anything to him because he's older than me.
Did you eat?
Whatever. As if I care.
I was the one who came up with that idea for the ramyeon!
Mr. Lee, you're in the office, right?
Yes.
I'm going to send you an email.
Make 10 copies of the email...
and bring them to the conference room. Make it quick.
- Okay. - What's your email address?
It's mansigi at ongol.co.kr.
- "Ongol"? - M-A-N-S...
Gosh.
Just...
go to my desk. The email is already open.
Check it and print it out.
The password is...
Darn you, Mr. Oh.
(Ga Yeol Chan)
(Inbox)
(Feedback for the New Product Proposal)
(Hello. This is Kang Seok Ho from CS Convenience Store.)
What's this?
Where are you going?
I think only our computers got infected.
- My gosh, this is crazy. - Look at this.
- It's a big mess here. - Mr. Oh.
- Hey, come to the meeting room. - Look at this.
- Hurry. - My goodness.
What is this?
- What a mess. - My gosh.
This...
"You want to cry"?
This is a virus.
- A virus. - What?
- That's it. Oh, no. - My gosh.
- All of them? - Did the company get the virus?
- Darn it. - Come on.
This generation checks the presence of a product on social media.
You can see that this has developed into...
Come on. We're in a meeting. Put the phone on vibrate.
Wait, that's me.
I'm sorry.
Hey, what is it?
What?
Ransomware?
What's that?
Whose computer?
Ga Yeol Chan?
Wait, what's going on?
The virus spread from Mr. Ga Yeol Chan's computer.
So all of the computers in the office got infected.
- You! - What are you talking about?
What happened?
That jerk, Lee Man Sic.
We checked the virus with the malicious code tool.
I did open another email.
I had no idea that it contained a virus.
You should've only opened up the email I told you to.
Why did you look through my emails?
- What's the damage? - 19 computers were infected.
During lunch, the network for each floor was different.
So the damage wasn't as severe. Otherwise, it would've been awful.
How can you fix this?
We did everything we can do on our end,
but it's not working out.
What's the demand?
3,000 dollars per computer.
19 computers were infected, so that's 57,000 dollars.
In Korean won, it's 70 million won.
They'll double it for each day you're late.
What?
Well,
do I have to pay for the ransom?
Is that what's important now?
I really don't think we should keep him here.
Shouldn't we take a stronger stand on this matter?
He's causing trouble every day.
Exactly. The company isn't some charity.
They want us to be patient until he gets better.
But until when must we wait?
I get that he can make mistakes.
But he said he came up with the idea for the ramyeon.
That's not a mistake.
He's like a thief. Don't you agree?
He told me that "You people make your own coffee."
That's my point.
He's getting in the way of everyone.
I really don't think someone like him should work here.
- Exactly. - Right.
It's not an understatement to call him a rotten apple.
There are so many smart people these days.
Exactly.
Why did he come to our team?
Seriously.
Who is that?
Hey.
Aren't you finished your shift?
My gosh. No one is waiting for me at home.
I was planning to go home after the meal.
Isn't it awful to eat your meal in the restroom?
Now that I've been doing that for a while,
I got used to it.
- The person you have reached is... - He's not answering?
No.
- Why don't you call him? - Okay. I'll call him.
If you're that worried, just answer it.
My gosh, hey.
- Hello? - Where are you?
What are you doing?
Do you think working here is a joke?
If you weren't coming back, request for a half day off.
Or you should never come back.
I'll quit.
I'll take responsibility for it and resign.
How can a mere intern take responsibility for it?
I can just submit my resignation.
Don't you know only employees can submit resignation?
Besides, let's get the fact straight.
You're not taking responsibility for it.
You're running away from it.
You ran away too that time.
Suit yourself.
I was quite surprised when I saw you here as an intern.
I questioned myself, "He's going to work under me?"
"At his age?"
So I thought perhaps, you might have changed.
But people don't change.
Yes.
It's not that easy for people to change.
So you must think you have some kind of important position here.
But in my eyes, you're just like that loser from a long time ago.
Loser?
Are you calling me a loser because you're quitting?
I didn't even get started, you punk.
Who are you to order me around? You're such a loser.
You must think you're some big shot now that you have a title.
You people aren't even close to Ongol.
How dare you brag in front of me?
If you like Ongol that much, go join them.
I'm on my way, you punk.
You're all talk. Just leave already.
Right now!
What a wimp.
You called me a wimp again!
My gosh, is this guy serious?
(Up Yours)
It's okay now. Good riddance to that man.
Everything will be okay now. Yes.
Of course. Yes.
I remember opening up something.
Why won't he pick up?
I told him to print it out ages ago.
Where did he go?
What's this?
(Check your bonus for the first half of the year.)
(Open)
Yes, Director. I'll be there right now.
It was fine until I opened it up.
Then could I have caused this?
Why haven't I thought of this until now?
You should've only opened up the email I told you to.
Why did you look through my emails?
Did I unconsciously want to conclude...
that it was his fault?
Then which email did he open up?
(Check your bonus for the first half of the year.)
(An activity in your online club: Mess with subordinates discreetly)
(Feedback on the new product proposal for limited-time items.)
What is this?
(Mirae Club)
(Mess with subordinates discreetly)
(It's the easiest to ignore them.)
(I took away important tasks from him, )
(nitpicked over smallest details, and gave petty tasks...)
(to make him feel nonexistent. I hope you tame your intern.)
He must be crazy.
My gosh.
He said he'll quit first.
He wouldn't have lasted even if it wasn't for me.
(Come at me, world! Fight with me, fiery chicken!)
Why should I be sorry?
It wasn't because of me.
Yes.
Then how does this make you different from him?
(Long Service Award)
(The Ongol Employee of the Year)
(Best Department Award)
(CEO Namgoong Joon Su)
What?
What? You expect me to crawl back and work for him?
- Come on. - Come back here, man.
- Let me go! - Sit down.
Have a drink first.
We're almost there. Our goal is right in front of us.
Exactly.
Just a little more. You just have to hold out a bit longer.
Goodness. Here.
- I didn't think Man Sic would... - Forget it.
do such a great job for me.
Exactly, sir.
What happened with that ransomware?
Exactly, Mr. Ahn. Don't you think he's a genius?
- Come on. - I'm not doing it.
Take a seat, will you?
Man Sic, please let me pour you a drink for this.
For the next vice president.
The vice...
president?
Here.
(Episode 8)
- Did they tell you anything? - So what happened is...
Mr. Ga is here. Get back to your seats.
- Hello. - Hello.
Good morning.
- Let's get back to work. - Yes, sir.
- Okay. - Thank you.
One second, everyone.
I'd like to tell you...
that as of today, Mr. Lee Man Sic...
Yes?
Mr. Ga, good morning.
I'm sorry for stepping over the line yesterday.
Is he really trying to say he'll crawl back to work...
after he told me off yesterday?
Mr. Ga, I'm so sorry.
I must have gone insane yesterday.
I'll put my head down to express my regret to you.
- Goodness, sir. - Old man, stop.
No, don't stop me. A guy like me...
- Whoa, stop this. - The corner! The corner!
- Old man, stop this. - Don't do this.
Please calm down.
- Calm down. - Goodness.
It's okay.
I'll buy coffee for everyone.
- Yoon Soo? - I'll go with IA.
- IA for me too. - I'll go with HA.
- IA with an extra shot. - Latte, please.
Mr. Ga, you take...
espresso doppio in lungo,
very dry cappuccino with whipped cream,
topped with chocolate drizzle and cinnamon powder.
You want that, don't you?
- Wow. - My goodness.
No, I want something else other than coffee today.
Could you head over to that new milk tea place out front...
and get me a cup of black sugar milk tea?
Oh, okay.
The tapioca pearls are in frogspawn or salamander egg sizes.
I want a 6 to 4 ratio of frogspawn and salamander eggs.
No, never mind. A 5 to 5 ratio.
And add premium cream.
Bring it when the leopard gradation gets darker as it goes down.
I'll take it like that.
- Goodness. - Oh, and...
shake it for about 15 seconds.
Shake it for 15 seconds. Remember that.
I can't believe this jerk.
In 5 to 5 ratio.
And add premium cream.
Bring it when the leopard gradation gets darker as it goes down.
I'll take it like that.
Oh, and shake it for about 15 seconds.
I'll take four of these...
and three IA.
Sure, we'll get that ready for you.
Did you shake it?
Here.
Yes, this is it.
- Thank you. - My pleasure.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
- I shook it for you. - Thank you.
That's Mr. Oh?
- This was what happened? - No way.
- My gosh. - I can't believe it.
How could he call himself a superior?
How could he do that?
What's wrong?
Well...
I think you should see this.
What is it?
A recording was uploaded on the intranet.
Let me hear it.
Anytime, now.
Okay.
(Anonymous Bulletin Board)
Is there anything you have in mind?
We're told to use the products that already exist.
We have dried pollack.
I thought about adding a bunch of it.
Dried pollack ramyeon... Is that it?
- Yes. - My gosh.
Come on.
The audio is of poor quality.
Someone must've fabricated this.
As if.
Don't be ridiculous.
This is neither the NFS nor the NIS.
Who'd fabricate that?
If you have a conscience, you should admit to your mistakes.
You guys aren't any better either! You all lied too.
Do you finally understand how competent I am?
I think...
it is Mr. Oh's proposal.
Sir.
It doesn't matter who came up with the idea.
Spitballing an idea doesn't make it complete.
It's only worthy if you can write up...
a convincing proposal.
Whoever wrote the proposal is the owner.
Do you understand?
If you feel upset about it,
you should submit your own.
Being competent also means you can protect your own ideas.
We'll keep that in mind.
I'm pretty sure it's her.
It must be this weirdo.
Don't you think Joo Yoon Soo seems a bit fishy at times?
Yes, you're right.
His face screams "betrayer".
He looks like a weasel.
Okay, you search his desk.
Okay.
Quiet down!
It's this! It's this!
You little fox.
"We've Added Saury to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Pig Fat to the Ramyeon".
"We've Added Kkakdugi to the Ramyeon".
- It's her, isn't it? - "We've Added Chicken Heads..."
- "We've Added Chicken Feet..." - "We've Added..."
Maybe she was just recording herself as practice.
Be quiet! She removed it.
You have no idea.
- I knew it. - "We've Added Pupae".
Lee Tae Lee...
Lee Tae Lee.
(Lee Tae Lee, Intern)
(Marketing and Sales Department)
- Ms. Lee. - Yes?
Can you organize these for me by the end of the day?
- Are you asking me? - Yes.
Mr. Joo is a bit busy today. I'm sorry.
Could you also bring me my lunch?
Yes, sir.
I'd like a Dragon King Lunchbox from the Palace of Sea Kings.
What are you doing to my mentee?
What?
Ms. Tak...
Please photocopy these.
Yes, ma'am.
Make three copies.
Thank you.
This card isn't working. Do you have another one?
Please wait a minute.
Yes, what is it?
The card isn't working?
Oh, dear. I gave you the wrong one.
I'm sorry, but I think you'll have to come back.
No, I'm not ready for a promotion.
Yes.
I'm riding airplanes all the time.
- Hello? - Where are you right now?
Did you buy the lunchbox?
Gosh, I'm so sorry,
but I'm craving sundae soup.
Can you get a refund?
Okay.
Here you go.
- Hello? - Ms. Lee.
Can you get kimchi fried rice instead?
I'm truly sorry. I'm sorry.
Ms. Lee.
Actually, I think I want the Dragon King Lunchbox after all.
Let's go back there. Okay.
Hey.
What's with him?
Ms. Lee was the one who uploaded the recording.
Who said that?
Mr. Oh.
Are you sure?
He found a voice recorder on her desk.
You should treat her better.
After all, she was trying to help you.
What?
She was the one...
who uploaded that?
Ms. Lee, I'm sorry. Can you just buy kimchi fried rice?
Okay.
Just eat anything.
Here you go.
- Goodness. - I brought it.
It must've been tiring. Good work.
Darn it!
The egg is hard-boiled.
When having kimchi fried rice,
you should be able to mix the yolk with the rice.
Don't you know that?
How am I to mix everything when it's so dry?
You know what? You can have this.
I... I was giving it to you.
How about we interns have a get-together?
I should've proposed this earlier...
as the eldest in the group.
How about some beef? It's my treat.
Deal.
I thought we were having beef.
Come on.
You know how much we get.
Let's have beef next time.
Here. Have a drink.
Here.
All right. Let's clink our glasses.
Since we got to know each other,
let's have a get-together from time to time.
What is it? Is it no fun to hang out with an old man?
No, sir.
Of course, it isn't.
I'll be honest.
You seem like a company director, not a colleague.
You little...
I know that you guys call me Kkon-tern.
But still, can't you treat me better face-to-face?
Kids these days are so impertinent.
I'm sorry.
It's a force of habit.
I'm sorry...
for scolding you.
It's probably because I was a superior for so long.
It's not easy to fix this habit.
Did you know?
There are two things senior employees...
have to keep in mind the most.
The first one is, don't be nosy.
Our experience isn't valuable.
The second one is, don't talk about your past.
No one is interested in your past.
I know that. I know all of it,
but...
My gosh. I'm getting the urge to talk about that.
Hey.
Thank you.
Ma'am, three servings of fried rice, please.
Hey, Tae Lee.
Thank you. Okay?
You were the one...
who salvaged the last bit...
of my remaining pride.
Thank you.
Hey.
But what's up with your hair?
Ma'am, a bottle of Coke, please.
If you cut out this horse-tail resembling hair of yours,
you'll look neat.
Come on. That's enough!
What do you know about fashion?
What do you, old people, know anything about two-tone hair?
I'm sorry.
Look. It's nice and neat.
You!
You scumbag!
Are you going back to the office now?
Yes. I want to fix the proposal I submitted the other day.
What about your hair?
Gosh.
I'll go to a hair salon and see what I can do.
Gosh. He's a much bigger kkondae than I expected.
But why didn't you say...
that you were the one who made the proposal?
You knew?
I can't be on my mentor's bad side.
It will be reflected in my evaluation.
My gosh.
Isn't he so evil?
In the end, he didn't lift a finger to do any of this.
Is that why you exposed him?
Expose whom?
I thought you were the one who uploaded the recording file.
Me?
Yes. That's why Mr. Lee bought us meat to thank you.
What?
Our brains will reach the highest effectiveness.
(1 day before the stealing incident of the proposal)
Yes, this is Joonsu Food.
Ms. Lee? What's her first name?
We're told to use the products that already exist.
We have dried pollack.
(Record)
How did you find me here?
(The day of the proposal-stealing incident)
There's a recording.
(Record)
I can recognize your voice, Ms. Lee.
- Did you already forget my voice? - We're told to use...
the products that already exist.
- We have dried pollack. - How did you find me here?
I thought I saw you...
- at Joonsu Food. - I thought about adding...
- So I looked into that. - a bunch of it.
- But you were really there. - Is that it?
Do you know you're stalking me?
That was too simple, wasn't it?
- I'm recording this. - No, it sounds good.
- Come on, I'm not your stalker. - No wonder you came up...
- Can't I call my former employee? - You're brilliant.
- We're pretty special, you know. - Sir.
Have you ever had it before?
No, I haven't.
(Something New but Familiar, Dried Pollack Ramyeon)
"Dried Pollack Ramyeon"?
We have dried pollack.
I thought about adding a bunch of it.
That was too simple, wasn't it?
Mr. Lee, where's your proposal?
Sorry?
This dried pollack ramyeon was my idea.
I submitted that, sir.
What are you guys talking about?
That was my idea.
You know that it was my idea.
What are you talking about?
Are you seriously doing this to me?
What have I done to you?
Come on, you're driving me crazy.
You're the one...
- All right. - who's driving me crazy.
- Even if I kick him out of here, - Right.
- but I'll have a clean conscience. - We have witnesses here.
I can recognize your voice, Ms. Lee.
- Did you already forget my voice? - We're told to use...
the products that already exist.
- We have dried pollack. - How did you find me here?
I thought I saw you...
- at Joonsu Food. - I thought about adding...
- Can you mute the call... - Okay.
and make the voice louder in the background?
Well, hold on.
(The Truth Behind the Dried Pollack Ramyeon)
(Recording)
(It's being processed. Please wait.)
(Save)
I think...
it is Mr. Oh's proposal.
Sir.
It doesn't matter who came up with the idea.
Spitballing an idea doesn't make it complete.
It's only worthy if you can write up...
a convincing proposal.
Whoever wrote the proposal is the owner.
Do you understand?
We'll keep that in mind.
Learn, Lee Man Sic.
I uploaded the recording to bring justice for your sake.
But I sided with Mr. Oh,
so Mr. Oh's dignity would be intact.
I'm such a good problem solver.
Let me know if there are considerate bosses like me.
Ms. Lee?
Mr. Ga.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ga. You're still here.
Yes. I forgot something here.
But what happened to your hair?
- Is it a trend or something? - My gosh.
No way.
Right?
Aren't you going home?
I'm staying behind for the proposal.
I see.
Nothing happened, right?
Pardon?
Like you're not in any danger?
What?
It's nothing.
If you need help,
don't hesitate to talk to me.
Okay.
Then,
bye.
Have a good weekend.
You too, Mr. Ga.
Okay.
Have a good weekend.
You too, Mr. Ga.
Okay.
He ate it.
He ate the candy I gave him.
Why is your company asking you to come in on a weekend?
Come on. I'm trying to do great things here.
Listen. You came home completely wasted last night.
You usually stay in bed until noon.
I'm only asking because you're out of bed already.
Don't you know anything about...
making yourself more competitive at work?
"More competitive"? My goodness.
Young man. Where is this place?
It's in this building.
(Daebak Computer Academy)
If you think this is unfair, try to fight for this.
Being competent also means you can protect your own ideas.
You're all dead. All of you.
During this class, we're going to learn...
adding color and images to your presentation.
In the lower part of your screen...
How am I supposed to do this?
Click the right button right here, and click it again.
Do it again. It's autofill.
The shape icon will show up.
I can't do this.
Click the button, and you'll see in the middle...
Do I press this twice?
Hey.
Look at this.
There's insert... Do you see "insert" up there?
And do you see the illustrations here?
Hey, it turned off.
My gosh, no. It's right here.
I thought I could learn this quickly.
No, I was actually scared that I may not be able to follow...
even after I learned this.
I asked you to do this, and you made it in no time.
This looks great. Excellent.
Hey, don't you think we make a great team?
Everyone who did...
these things for me at a word are all gone now.
That's amazing.
I'm all alone now,
and it seems like everyone is saying this old man is useless.
It was a scary and miserable night.
All right. Whatever. What am I trying to learn?
My subordinates will do this once I become the vice president.
Goodness.
Hey, Dad. Are you learning to use a computer?
No, I was just looking through.
Does a director have to make something like this?
Can't you just ask your subordinates to do it?
I can't just make my subordinates do this.
People don't respect bosses who can't do his job these days.
I have to learn at least one more to not fall behind.
You're a cool guy, Dad. I thought you were a kkondae.
Hey.
- It's back. - Don't press the wrong button.
Thanks.
(The frequency of drinking among office workers)
(Top 6 popular dishes to relieve hangovers)
(Dried pollack is especially helpful in relieving hangovers.)
Yes!
I did it.
Do you expect me to look over this junk?
Do you call this a proposal?
It's lengthy and out of style.
You can't bring me something that's not in a proper form.
You can teach me.
I don't know how to do this,
so you can teach me.
How many times do I have to teach you this?
Good morning!
Good morning.
Go back to your seat.
(Eom Han Gil)
What?
I'm not the one who spread the ransomware,
but it's him?
Excuse me, sir.
You probably need to see this.
Just pretend like you never saw that.
Yes, Mr. Namgoong.
This is Lee Man Sic.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
My gosh. What are you trying to say?
Goodness.
Mr. Lee!
You aren't like this because of me, are you? Say that it wasn't so.
I was going to tell you about the ransomware.
I was going to say it.
Don't die.
Don't die!
Don't die like this, please.
Are you acting like a lunatic...
because of what happened back then?
The owner of that rice soup place...
hasn't died yet, you idiot.
(We thank Jung Young Ju, Cho Han Cheul, and Lee Min Ji.)
(Kkondae Intern)
A customer is claiming that he found a cockroach...
- in Spicy Chicken Ramyeon. - Hello.
- All right. - Can you take this?
- Beom Jun. - Tae Lee.
Are you two acquainted?
I only signed the confirmation because of you.
Let's start over. I'll make you happy.
Why didn't he just say it came out of his place?
- Why is he blowing this up? - Mr. Ga!
Mr. Ga, the chairman told you to stay away from your duties.
Do you think we'll find any leads?
A dead body always leaves clues behind.