- Give me the phone number.
- Hey.
- I told you not to sell anything.
- Come on, cut me some slack.
- Just record it here.
- You can't sell this here.
- You're making me frustrated.
- Goodness.
- My gosh.
- Stop making me angry.
- Hey, lady.
- What's with them?
This stop is
Jeonchan Borough Office Station.
The doors are on your right.
- My gosh.
- What is he doing?
- What was that?
- Man, that's disgusting.
- Why doesn't he just stay at home?
- My gosh.
What's with that old man?
The definition of "kkondae" is...
slang for
an old person or a teacher.
Peek-a-boo.
You should sit here.
It must be tough
to bring up a child.
No, it's all right.
But not all old people are kkondaes.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Exactly. Why did you ignore me?
- Pardon?
- "Pardon"? You didn't see my text?
How can you fall asleep
while you talk to your senior?
I'm sorry.
I can't believe kids these days.
Why don't you sleep forever?
I'm sorry.
Young kkondaes also exist.
What's up with your jacket?
A kkondae is a person who forces
others to accept...
their old-fashioned beliefs
regardless of how old they are.
And he's one of them.
Move aside.
Can't you see
that this is the elderly's seat?
I have the right to sit here too.
Someone as young as you
should just obey the elders.
How dare you talk back?
What's your deal?
What? What did you say?
What?
You little punk. Hey!
Hey. Hey.
Don't make me look back.
I've been studying too much
that I got anemia.
You should've told me.
I did.
I said I had the right
to sit there too.
Hey.
What a weird, old man.
- Why did you bother him?
- He's anemic.
What's wrong with him?
Have your meals on time.
How could a young man like you
be anemic?
Kids these days...
are so weak.
It's a problem.
He was a one-of-a-kind kkondae.
(Episode 1)
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Good morning.
- You too.
How dare that punk to come to work
later than the general manager?
I'm sorry for being late.
And...
I was his underling.
- Yeol Chan.
- Yes?
Have you finalized the proposal
for the private brands?
- No, sir.
- What?
Actually, I'm almost done.
What's taking you so long?
I told you to pick a few
from the ones that were rejected.
I'm organizing it right now.
Just give it to me.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
What? What's wrong with this?
What is this?
Why is the quality so poor?
Did you do something?
What? Are you still
in the World Cup season?
Why are you still using
the 2002 version of the program?
There was a problem
with compatibility.
You should update your program
and yourself as well.
Yes, sir.
I'll update it right now
and re-print this.
Don't! Just sit still.
Mr. Kim, pick out a few
from the list.
Cup noodles or packaged ones?
- The former.
- Yes, sir.
Sir... Sir.
Should I buy some coffee?
Just stay still! Don't do anything!
I know you're just an intern,
but how could you do so poorly?
Come on.
He could get us some coffee.
He seems like
the best intern so far.
Who? Him?
Hey, Mi Jin. Do you like him?
Don't be ridiculous.
Then why are you siding
with him? Why?
Are you trying to seduce him?
What do young people think?
Yeol Chan, be honest.
Which ramyeon is the tastiest?
May I be honest?
Of course. That's why you're here.
I think Joonsoo Food's Sam Ramyeon
made an outstanding change.
Our Ong Ramyeon changed
in taste as well.
But it doesn't seem
as tasty as before.
What did you say?
How dare an intern
blabber about such things?
If you love Joonsoo Food so much,
you should've joined them.
Why did you even choose to join us?
Do you even know
how great our ramyeon is?
Let's call it Fiery Squid Ramyeon.
That was our intern's idea.
- What?
- That was...
Yeol Chan's idea.
He mentioned it last time.
I submitted that, sir.
What are you guys talking about?
That was my idea.
Hey, are you sure
you two aren't dating?
We're not.
Then why do you keep siding
with him?
I must've gotten confused.
Fiery Squid Ramyeon was your idea.
She's right.
It was your idea.
- Yes, you're right.
- You're right.
- It was his idea.
- Hey!
It's a bit too late, isn't it?
You ruined my mood already.
Forget it.
This never happened.
Sir...
Also, who is it
that keeps giving him work?
Stop giving him work!
Hey, Mom. What is it?
Are there still
some side dishes left?
I heard at small studio apartments,
your neighbors steal your food.
That never happened.
Does that mean you don't need
any extra side dishes?
I made some geotjeori at work.
It was tasty,
so I packed some for you.
Did you get a part-time job again?
You recently got surgery
for the slipped disc.
Don't do anything
and just stay at home!
Do you even know how it feels
to do nothing?
How's work?
I get scolded at
no matter what I do.
That's the life of an intern.
Just endure it.
I was so jealous of you
when I heard you got in.
Were you?
Hey.
What's wrong?
You can't even drink.
Don't scare me like this.
Gosh.
I can do well.
I really can.
Darn it.
Why won't they give me a chance?
- Hey, Yeol Chan.
- Yes, sir?
I need you to do something.
Sure.
You need a lot more sticks,
don't you?
I'm doing this all for your sake.
It's your job
to lessen your superior's work.
By the way,
are you my dad's subordinate?
(Mr. Lee Man Sic)
- Hello?
- Are you still working on it?
No, sir. I'm done.
Then why aren't you here already?
Since you're not here,
your colleagues are getting scolded.
I'll be there soon.
No, don't come here.
Go to Yeonwoong Market.
"Yeonwoong Market"?
Yes, hurry.
Yes, sir.
Gosh.
Darn it.
(Ox Head Rice Soup)
("Ongol Did Not Steal the Recipe")
It's nothing serious.
This guy sued the company,
claiming that we copied...
his ox head rice soup recipe for
our product, ox head noodle soup.
So the company went to court
against the owner of the restaurant.
That guy lost the lawsuit,
but he won't accept the ruling.
He's threatening to kill himself.
He's been bothering the company.
Go to him, buy him a drink,
and just listen to him,
yapping about that.
Go straight down and turn left.
You'll see it then.
- Thank you.
(Hong Tent Bar)
(Gol Marketplace
Rice Soup Restaurant)
(We are closed on Sunday.)
(Gol Marketplace
Rice Soup Restaurant)
Is anyone inside?
(Gol Marketplace
Rice Soup Restaurant)
Is anyone inside?
(Gol Marketplace
Rice Soup Restaurant)
Sir, are you okay?
Hey! Wait. Help!
No.
Are you okay?
Sir. Sir!
Darn it.
You won't even let me die in peace!
Stop torturing me.
Well,
how's your neck?
Do you want some water?
If you don't want water,
should I peel you a Korean melon?
These melons are from Seongju.
I bought them because
I heard they are very sweet.
I was about to die
a few moments ago.
Do you think I want to eat
Korean melons now?
If you don't like them,
what do you like?
Let's eat something you like.
It's my treat.
It looks like you were very close to
the chairman.
Then, did you think I was lying?
No. No, sir.
I never thought that you were lying.
I don't have anything to discuss
with a rookie like you.
Leave now.
How come
you still haven't had dinner?
(The person you have reached
is unavailable.)
Why won't he answer the phone?
Then he sold his house
His house
He sold his paintings
and his shelter
And with all the money he got
(Intern Yeol Chan)
Sing it.
A million scarlet roses
You can see from the window
The one who is seriously in love
He really tried to kill himself.
He hanged himself.
Goodness. That's what he does.
So did he really die?
- No.
- See?
You should be glad
that you're over there.
It's us you should be worried.
We're about to die.
But just in case,
could you come over here?
I don't think
I can handle this by myself.
I'm serious. Something
about this doesn't feel right.
Hey.
Are you trying to get a compliment
for what you did for him?
Fine.
I'll make sure I tell the general
manager about what you did.
Happy now?
- Bye.
- No. Can you come...
Hello?
(Restaurant with
50 years of experience)
Here.
I should be the one
treating you to a meal.
Stop talking nonsense. Just eat.
Thank you for the food.
What is it? Do you not like it?
No. It's good.
Excuse me, sir.
Please don't get any bad ideas.
(Gol Marketplace
Rice Soup Restaurant)
(Everything on the menu
is available for takeouts.)
(We are closed on Sunday.)
(1000, 1004, 1100, 1101:
Not available)
(1200, 1300, 1301, 1302:
(Jeonchan Borough Office Station)
Mr. Ga Yeol Chan.
If things were that serious,
shouldn't you have reported it
to your boss?
- Yes.
- But how did you handle it?
I called the general manager
several times to report to him,
- but he didn't answer it.
- He failed to answer the phone...
as he was about to sign
a big contract.
Listen. Before you visited him,
the owner seemed fine.
What on earth did you tell him?
What?
No, he said the owner
was about to kill himself...
and was bothering the company.
If it was that serious, do you think
he would have sent an intern?
On your statement, you wrote
Lee Man Sic didn't answer the phone,
so you called Kim Do Yeong instead.
But Kim Do Yeong also said...
that you didn't mention...
the gravity of the situation at all.
Is that true?
I'm sorry.
(Ongol Food)
Mr. Ga Yeol Chan. Put your head up.
Who else knows about this?
No one.
No one else knows other than
people in the Marketing Department.
Excuse me.
What happened to that person?
Could you give me
the family's number...
Why do you want to know?
Don't do anything rash
and create more problems.
Just stay still.
We'll take action as a company.
Here.
What are you doing?
Pick up the glass.
You've never been to
a place like this, have you?
It's true that the chairman
had been a regular for 30 years.
And it's true that the chairman...
always joked around
and asked them for their recipe.
But you've never had
their rice soup, have you?
That old man became too old
and can't taste things anymore.
Of course, customers stopped coming,
and that's when we released
our ox head noodle soup,
so they figured they could
make a case around this.
That's why they went on.
Do you understand?
He couldn't accept the fact
that he's useless now.
Where's the recipe book?
I heard you stole it, Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee Man Sic stole it.
The notebook that my father
handed down to me.
The recipe and secrets
to making ox head rice soup...
are all in that notebook.
Wait, why would I steal that?
Do you really believe
what that crazy old man is saying?
My gosh.
I think he heard something
from that old man.
- We shouldn't cause more problems.
- No, sir.
Reinstate him for now,
then you can get rid of him.
You're good at that.
(Ong Ramyeon
Marketing Strategy Report)
- Do it over.
- You didn't even open it.
I don't have to.
(2015 Ong Ramyeon
Marketing Strategy Report)
Do it over.
Yes, I'll send Mr. Kim.
(Ong Ramyeon
Marketing Strategy Report)
No, he worked overtime yesterday.
(Do it over.)
Do it over. Do it over. Do it over.
(2015 Ong Ramyeon
Marketing Strategy Report)
This isn't going to work.
Don't do anything from now on, okay?
This is such a waste of paper.
Stand right here.
Repeat after me.
I will not do anything.
"I will not do anything."
Louder. I will not do anything.
That's how I can help out my team.
"That's how I can help out my team."
I will not do anything
and take my paycheck.
"I will not do anything
and take my..."
"paycheck."
Then one day,
I will disappear
as if I had never been here.
- Great work!
- Great job.
- Cheers!
- Great work!
- Great job today!
- All right!
- Cheers!
You're here. Sit over here.
- Sit down.
- Take a seat.
You idiot!
You haven't quit your job?
How dare you join us? How dare you?
- Goodness.
- Mr. Lee, this is company dinner.
- Who called him here?
- Goodness!
Who called him here
and ruined my mood?
Get rid of that thing!
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
My gosh,
I don't even want to hear him speak.
Hey, get rid of that thing.
Get rid of him now!
Darn it. I can't believe
that useless idiot.
I can't believe
we hired an idiot like him.
If we hired a cat, it would've done
a better job than you!
That useless idiot.
Why did you call him here?
Who called him?
Where's the recipe book?
I heard you stole it, Mr. Lee.
(Contract with China,
Contract with Russia)
Mr. Lee.
Isn't one of your interns
named Ga Yeol Chan?
Yes. What about him?
He just sent an email
to the entire company...
saying he's exposing
General Manager Lee Man Sic.
I quickly caught it
and deleted everything, though.
No one read it?
No. You won't have to
worry about that.
I'm about to send you
this security footage.
Could you check?
This is unbelievable.
What's with this lunatic?
(Gaeryong Residence)
What brings you here, Mr. Lee?
You jerk.
Why do you do this to me?
Why in the world
do you do this to me?
Because you won't listen to me.
I told you to stay still,
but you just won't listen!
What do you know?
What do you think you know
to act up like this?
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Good morning, Mr. Lee.
- So you scored over 100 yesterday?
- Of course.
Man. My goodness.
(Letter of Resignation)
(Gol Marketplace
Rice Soup Restaurant)
(Closed due to personal reasons)
No idea. We don't know
what happened after that.
I'm not sure
if he had a proper funeral.
By any chance, was anyone...
in this marketplace close to him?
That old man always
complained about our products...
and was very picky,
so no one wanted to deal with him.
Do you have any young radish?
Young radish?
Give me a second.
I got some more in there.
Mr. Lee!
We got the contract with Russia!
- We did it!
- Great job.
- Great work.
- You've done so well.
- Great job!
- All right!
Mr. Lee, what will you do
with the incentive?
Will you really buy a car?
Hey, he won't just get a car.
He might get promoted to
the director!
- That might happen!
- There's no doubt about it!
Come on, everyone.
Stop flattering me.
- Come on.
- Mr. Lee.
- Mr. Lee!
- My gosh, stop it.
- Stop it!
- Mr. Lee!
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'm on my way right now.
I'm in my car. My car.
But there's a bit of traffic.
Yes, I'm showing off my new car.
Anyway, who else
will be there today?
What?
Goodness.
Does this mean I'll really
get promoted to a director?
Come and give it
Come and give it to me
(Mom)
You aren't even making money.
You don't have to
keep sending me some.
Great job.
You can always quit a company
that doesn't suit you.
Forget that company or whatever.
You're the most important to me
in this world.
Yeol Chan.
Don't get any bad ideas. Okay?
Excuse me, sir.
Please don't get any bad ideas.
I will live.
I'll survive.
I'll survive...
and show this world...
that I'm still useful.
(Come at me, world!
Fight with me, fiery chicken!)
(5 years later)
(2020 61st Trade Day)
(2020 61st Trade Day, Korea
International Trade Association)
(Energetic Korean trade!
Another leap for Korea!)
The next award is for those...
who reached
200 million dollars in export.
Chairman Namgoong Pyo
and General Manager Ga Yeol Chan...
of Joonsoo Food are
here to accept the award.
(Energetic Korean trade!
Another leap for Korea!)
(2020 61st Trade Day)
The President is here
to present the award himself.
Chairman Namgoong Pyo is the man
who made the first ramyeon in Korea.
General Manager Ga Yeol Chan is
the maker of Spicy Chicken Ramyeon,
who made a direct contribution...
in increasing their export
to 200 million dollars.
(2020 61st Trade Day)
(Citation Award)
Congratulations.
Please share your speech.
Our chairman hates spicy food.
And I brought Spicy Chicken Ramyeon
to a guy like him.
He turned me down
well over a hundred times.
But regardless of his taste,
he accepted the opinions
of the younger generation.
I'd like to give the honor...
to Chairman Namgoong Pyo,
the father of ramyeon.
And we won't stop here
with an increase in our export.
We'll continue to use...
Spicy Chicken brand
to lead the K-food craze.
Thank you.
(2020 61st Trade Day)
All right!
Let's celebrate
the 200 million dollars in export,
achieved by
General Manager Ga Yeol Chan!
- Goodness.
- Congratulations! All right!
- Congratulations!
- All right!
- Goodness.
Seung Jin, you need to
chug that down at once.
Mr. Ga, I really look up to...
the sharp eye you have
for seeing into the future.
So what about our incentives?
I'll be frank.
- How much will it be? I'm curious.
- The incentive?
That's my main focus.
I'll bring it up.
All right, then.
Mr. Ga, could you show us?
- Shall I?
- All right!
All right, now. Everyone,
let's give him our attention.
Attention, please.
Everyone, check this out.
- Move aside.
- He looks cool.
- Ga Yeol Chan!
- Bravo!
- Nice!
That was awesome!
Can a company get-together
be this simple?
My score is usually around
two hundred points.
- My goodness!
- Goodness.
Look at this sunshine.
Even after partying so hard,
the sun is still up.
Having afternoon get-togethers
is the trend nowadays.
When I heard that
get-togethers are also...
a part of work, I thought to myself,
"If I ever become a superior,"
"I will schedule my get-togethers
during working hours."
What? It's already 6 p.m.
What are you doing? Go home, now.
Right.
I value my personal time,
so I should get going.
- Goodbye.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
"What are you doing? Go home, now."
We're so blessed.
They will be able to enjoy
their evening thanks to me.
(Ongol)
Ong!
Honey, you're getting promoted
today, right?
Come on. You should focus on
tending to the house.
What's the monthly pay
for a director?
20,000 dollars? 30,000 dollars?
Don't be so superficial.
Your husband's working hard,
but all you care about is the money.
Hello, sir.
(Ongol Food)
Sir, Mr. Lee Man Sic is here.
Tell him to come in.
Yes, sir.
Sorry?
You want me to take care
of the warehouses?
What did I do so wrong?
You didn't.
Then what?
Don't tell me it's because I'm old.
You know that...
people our age
are subjected to such things.
I do, but why does it have to be me?
(Director Lee Man Sic)
(Ongol)
(Opening Ceremony of Ongol's
Ready-Made Culinary Culture)
I was the one who helped Ongol
become successful.
You can't barge in like this, sir.
Sir.
No matter how much
I think about it,
you shouldn't kick me out like this.
I refuse to be ousted like this.
I was never there for my wife...
when she was giving birth to
both of my kids.
Sir. I mean...
You know that.
Even when my mother passed away,
I wasn't there for her.
Why? Because I had work.
You guys needed me!
You said it had to be me!
I dedicated everything
to this company.
What do you expect me to do
once I leave this place?
Should I suddenly become
a loving father to my kids?
Should I become a good son
to my late mother?
You turned me into a workaholic,
- so what do you expect?
- Hey.
Isn't the warehouse
also a part of Ongol?
You can work hard there as well.
Is that why you're sending me
down south?
You're obviously telling me to quit.
Darn it.
After all I've done
for this company?
Do you think
I have nowhere else to go?
Come on.
- Sir.
- What?
You always told me to join you.
I didn't really mean it.
- What?
- It's not too late.
Tell them you'll work
at the warehouse.
No other company
will offer you such a job.
Customer number 508.
Your desired salary is...
It's written there.
(Employment Application)
(Salary: 50,000 dollar or more)
Do you have any certificates
or licenses?
I wrote that down too.
I have a class one driver's license.
I'm also level three in pen writing.
Hello, sir.
It's me, Man Sic.
I see. Why have you called?
About that warehouse position...
Is that still available?
Of course, not.
That's why you should've...
I'm not interested!
I never said I was!
Hey. Hey, where are you?
You little punk...
- It's nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
Look.
Do you want to go to
this place with me?
Are you telling me I should be
a security guard?
Yes.
(Physical Exam for Open Recruitment
for Yuseong Apartment)
My gosh. They are just hiring
a security guard.
Why would they run
this kind of silly test?
Hey, be careful.
You're quite old now.
(Physical Exam for Open Recruitment
for Yuseong Apartment)
Unit Three, come forward.
(Lee Man Sic)
Ready.
Darn it!
(Lee Man Sic)
(Um Han Gil)
All right!
All right.
Here I go.
(Lee Man Sic)
Mr. Um. My gosh. That guy.
He took the wrong path again.
You were supposed to come here.
(Um Han Gil)
(Lee Man Sic)
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I know you guys are working hard,
but I won't be able to join you.
But are you sure there will be
a job waiting for me?
I'm going to return
after I deliver this baby.
- My goodness.
- Of course.
Mr. Oh is back now.
We'll visit you to see the baby.
You'd better.
Have a healthy baby.
- That's so considerate of you.
- All right.
- I got you a bigger present.
- My goodness.
I know how you must feel now.
- Everyone, say it with me.
- My gosh.
- Healthy baby!
- Healthy...
- It's like I'm giving birth now.
Stop it!
She's just going to give birth to
a baby. What's all the fuss about?
What happened with Mumbai Food?
You acted as if
you already got the deal.
Did they pull out?
My gosh.
Hello.
Wait a minute, sir.
Mr. Ga, Mr. Rancho is on the phone.
- Okay.
- Mr. Rancho?
This is Ga Yeol Chan speaking.
Hello, Mr. Rancho.
Is that so? Thank you.
- We entered the Indian market now.
- Yes!
Okay. I'll proceed as you said.
- We did it.
- I'm so happy.
I can't believe this.
Me?
Have you ever had
Spicy Chicken Ramyeon?
Are you teasing me now?
You know that I'm dying to try it,
but I can't ever eat that.
I made this just for you.
(Hot Chicken Noodle)
It's Hot Chicken Noodle
without the chicken in it.
There's no chicken
in Hot Chicken Noodle?
My goodness.
I must tell the world about this.
Everyone, there's no chicken
in Hot Chicken Noodle!
(Hot Chicken Noodle)
Now, you can try the Vegan
Hot Chicken Noodle.
Korea.
My goodness. I can't believe
someone like him is working for me.
- He's the best person for the job.
- Yes.
What's the big deal
selling our products in India?
I doubt that they would eat
a lot of ramyeon over there.
The scale of the market
for ramyeon in India is...
one billion dollars.
- He got our product in...
- But...
if they can eat tandoori chicken,
can't they eat
Spicy Chicken Ramyeon?
Do they have to get rid of beef?
Or is it pork?
Anyway, why would
they get rid of chicken?
It's not just about their religion.
40 percent of the Indian population
is vegetarian.
It's the biggest
vegetarian-friendly country.
The total population of India
is 1.38 billion.
What's 40 percent of that?
- Stop. Are you womansplaining me?
- 1.38 billion...
But isn't this more suspicious
when you think about it?
He's not even a celebrity.
Why would he film the commercial?
The moment the chairman
of Mumbai Food saw Mr. Ga,
he was smitten with Mr. Ga.
Exactly. Could it be possible
that he has ties to the chairman?
What is it?
There's a rumor
that he's your boy toy too.
What did you say, punk?
Why are you getting mad?
Hold on.
Dad. Dad.
Is it true that...
you guys had a fling
when she was young?
Hey, you...
Oh, my gosh.
So you, that woman,
and Ga Yeol Chan...
- are in a love triangle.
- Hey! You punk. Get out.
- Get out!
- A love triangle.
Fine. I'll leave.
My gosh, if Yeol Chan was my son,
things would've been so good. Right?
Hey.
You startled me.
Don't play innocent.
Show us where your loyalty lies.
You'll be kicked out if things
go south for Ga Yeol Chan.
My gosh, this perfume is expensive.
You're wearing expensive perfume,
but why does it smell cheap?
Gosh.
How come I can't find
any dirt on this guy?
Exactly.
My old man keeps saying that
instead of driving down...
the company to the gutter,
he'd rather give it to someone else.
What if he gives it...
- to Ga Yeol Chan?
- My gosh.
- No way.
- Dig deeper.
Dig more thoroughly, okay?
You ought to give me something!
Okay. I will.
(Intern Recruitment
for the First Half)
My gosh. I don't think
they'll get the job done.
When will the interns start working?
Did you see this?
It's an Indian commercial
for ramyeon.
- It's so funny.
- Let me see.
Hold on. Let me see.
My gosh. Seriously? He used to
be an intern at my company.
His last name was
really unique. Ga...
Ga...
- Ga Yeol Chan.
- Ga Yeol Chan?
Why is he in this commercial?
Isn't it so funny?
- Yes. Totally.
- It's so weird.
That jerk, Ga Yeol Chan,
used to work for Ongol.
Ongol?
Then, why didn't he say that?
It wasn't on his resume.
That means
he wants to hide something.
Okay. I got an idea.
This is it. Great.
My goodness.
Gosh.
I can't do this.
It's obvious that
this wasn't the baby's poop.
It's definitely from an adult.
The previous security guard
was good at this.
They kicked out all the good ones.
Why did they hire someone like him?
You should call
other security guards.
Throw that out on your way out.
(Ong Ramyeon)
Ongol.
Yes? Hello?
Who?
Ahn Sang Jong?
My archenemy...
and my one and only rival...
who works for Joonsoo Food,
All right. Here they come!
Are they here?
- Well...
- Is it a man or a woman?
One man and one woman.
Bring me their resumes.
All right, stay focused.
I'll have it.
Why do you look so nervous?
I'm not nervous.
- You can see them for yourself.
- Tell me.
- A woman?
- Let me see.
Attention, please.
Say hello to them.
For the next six months, they'll be
a part of Marketing and Sales,
Ms. Lee Tae Lee and Joo Yoon Soo.
Hello, I'm Lee Tae Lee.
You're right. My name sounds
like "Italy", Lee Tae Lee.
But I haven't been there yet.
Nice to meet you.
Tae Lee, Tae Lee, Lee Tae Lee.
What's with this awful introduction?
She seems very witty.
Yes, your turn.
He... Hello.
I'm Joo Yoon Soo. Nice to meet you.
Gosh.
Why does he sound like a goat?
Why did the ones I gave
the worst scores make the cut?
Well.
Why do we only have two interns?
Didn't you say
we'll get three in total?
It's because
they got here way too early.
It's not time yet.
- We still have hope.
- Yes.
Will it be a woman?
I hope she's pretty.
Hello!
I'm the senior intern
who'll begin as of today,
Lee Man Sic.
Why are you here, Mr. Lee?
Who are you?
Do you know me?
You're...
(We thank Lee Min Ji, Kim Hyun Mok,
Kwon Soo Hyun, Heo Il Hoo.)
(Kkondae Intern)
There are no relationships
that are 100 percent bad...
- in our lives.
- You're here.
Something good that happens now
might begin something bad,
and something
that's seemingly bad now...
may become the beginning
of something good.
Do you want a cup of morning coffee?
Do you want
a cold cup of iced coffee?
So you're planning on doing this?