(Episode 3)
(Interviewer)
(Blind Recruit Application)
(Internship, Ssukussuku, June 2019 to December 2019)
You did an internship at Ssukussuku.
I see. Ssukussuku in Indonesia?
Yes, I'm a guy who has had quite a lot of ramyeon in Indonesia.
Indonesia is big on ramyeon,
recording the second place in the world ramyeon consumption.
They eat about 12.5 billion ramyeon in a year.
And Ssukussuku dominates 70 percent of that huge industry.
Okay. He's our guy.
(100 points)
(0 points)
Hello! I'm Lee Tae Lee.
You're right.
My name sounds like "Italy", Lee Tae Lee.
But I haven't been there yet.
Nice to meet you.
Tae Lee, Tae Lee, Lee Tae Lee.
What's with this awful introduction?
I see.
- Ms. Lee? - Yes?
Why is your hair dyed in that color?
Don't you know what ombre hair is?
This is the hottest style right now.
I believe people who make food...
should be sensitive about trends.
Not only that, but we should also be the leaders who make trends.
You fail.
Ombre has been out for a while.
(0 points)
(Interviewers)
(100 points)
He... Hello.
I'm Joo Yoon Soo. Nice to meet you.
Why does he sound like a goat?
What do you think about our Spicy Chicken Ramyeon?
Well...
May I be honest?
Sure.
Why do people like something that's painfully spicy?
You fail.
(Grading sheet: 0 points, 0 points)
(Total: 0 points)
What are you doing?
(Total: 100 points)
What about that kkondae?
I'm meeting him tonight.
How dare a company like Joonsu Food...
call out a man who's with the great Ongol?
How dare you?
Goodness, Man Sic. You still got your game.
You and your Ongol pride.
Drink up.
People will get suspicious...
if you and I sit around like this.
They'll think we're in league or one of us is an industrial spy.
Don't you know that people talk?
Hey.
You said you quit. What are you so worried about?
Drink up.
So what is it?
Man Sic.
Do you want to work for our company?
Darn it.
What?
Are you telling me to become a traitor?
You're hardly a traitor.
Your country abandoned you first.
Once your country abandons you,
you abandon your country too.
So? Will you trust me...
and get a fresh start in a new country?
You know what? Joonsu Food copied everything we made!
- Hey, man! - What? We didn't copy anything.
You always say Joonsu Food copied everything you made!
Hey!
You jerk! If you're that good, why did you copy...
King Jjambbong?
Hey, no matter how much you people try to copy it,
you can't recreate that flavor.
This is... This is why people like the original stuff better.
- Do you know what that means? - Hey, you jerk.
We didn't copy anything, you jerk.
Listen to this guy.
Hey, everyone in this industry can think of jjambbong ramyeon.
Is that why you copied ours?
- What? - You copied Jjapaguri...
and made Dripping Chunjang.
You jerk. Are you all finished?
Yes, so what? I'm all done.
You make something ridiculous like Dripping Chunjang.
How dare you stand up against this Lee Man Sic?
I wouldn't work there even if I was a board member!
What? An internship?
An internship?
Go play badminton, you jerk.
Intern, badminton?
Internship, my foot.
Hey, that's my jacket, you thief!
What's with you?
This guy copied every single product we made.
This guy got fired from Ongol.
Hey, man. Come here.
It's not just an internship.
It's a pre-employment internship.
Call me if you change your mind.
How long have you been working here?
About three years now.
Over the last three years,
did you ever think that you work for...
such a great company?
No, I often thought that I work for...
such an awful company.
Back when I worked for my old company,
it'd get steaming hot outside,
but I'd sit in my office with the air conditioner blowing on max.
That was one time when I had a thought...
I work for a great company.
You should forget those days as soon as possible.
How can someone park here?
Where is he? Where are the guards?
- Guards! - Darn it.
- Guards! - We should go.
You don't see him, do you?
See? I'm working for such an awful company.
- Guards! - We're running late.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
(Joonsu Food)
Hey, what is this?
Are you sure you persuaded him?
Gosh, it's...
We did get into a bit of a quarrel.
Hey.
- You're late. - I'm sorry.
Mr. Lee Man Sic.
Yes, sir.
(Marketing and Sales Department)
Hello!
I'm the senior intern...
who'll begin as of today, Lee Man Sic.
Why are you here, Mr. Lee?
Who are you?
Do you know me?
You're...
- I can work somewhere else. - Man Sic, don't go anywhere.
- Let me go! - My goodness, man.
Hey! Come on.
Do you expect me to work for that kid?
Is that why you asked me so much about Ga Yeol Chan?
What kind of nonsense is this?
Hey. Calm down, okay?
- Okay? - Darn it.
Do you know him?
Who is this man...
that you want to pressure the human resources...
without staying within your boundaries?
- It's not like that... - I know it's you,
but you can't do that.
I was complimented for once by our chairman...
after I suggested we implement a senior internship.
So it doesn't matter even if this is you.
I can't call this off.
Then I'll have to understand.
You shouldn't be focused on saving face.
I heard you spent all your severance pay...
on your ill parent.
You won't be an intern forever.
You know that our company has a high percentage...
of turning contract workers into full-time employees.
I work directly under the CEO.
I'll help you.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Because I'm afraid.
As long as he's here, I won't be able to get a promotion.
Let's oust Yeol Chan and climb up the ladder together.
What do you say, Man Sic?
Hey, is he that powerful?
I don't know what he did,
but the chairman dotes on him.
Rumors say that not only did he give him a house and a car,
but also some of his stocks.
How did he become so successful?
The CEO would like to see you soon.
You haven't quit your job?
How dare you join us? How dare you?
Hey, get rid of that thing.
That useless idiot. Why did you call him here?
Who called him?
Hey, did you call him? Why would you?
What year were you guys born in?
I was born in 1993.
I was born in 1992.
I see.
Since you guys are younger than me, I'll speak casually.
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm not trying to intimidate you.
It's just more convenient when teaching things to my juniors.
By the way, what year were you born in?
Why would you ask that?
I was born in 1992.
- Sorry? - What?
I was born near the beginning of 1992.
He was born in 1992?
By the way, may I ask you your age?
People live up to 100 years these days. I'm still young.
You don't have to be so formal with me.
Just call me sir.
Right.
How should I address you?
How should we address you?
Intern Lee? Sir?
Mr. Lee Man Sic.
That's his name. How else should we call him?
You're right. It's his name, all right.
But why do I feel so uncomfortable?
Goodness.
I'll only feel uncomfortable if you think that way.
Please treat me the same way you'd treat them.
This is my motto. "Be an adult, not a kkondae."
You're not old-fashioned at all.
I really enjoyed that movie starring Robert Downey, Jr.
- That's Robert De Niro. - By the way,
how do you and Mr. Ga know each other?
Us?
He said I looked exactly like someone he knew.
(Ga Yeol Chan)
I need to speak with you on the rooftop.
It's you, right, Yeol Chan?
You've changed so much.
I wouldn't have recognized you while passing by.
By the way,
shouldn't I take some credit for your Spicy Chicken Ramyeon?
It's obvious that you got that from my Fiery Squid Ramyeon.
You haven't changed one bit.
Is that so?
How are you here as a senior intern?
Well, after retiring, I wasn't happy with my life.
Why did you leave Ongol?
I decided to quit.
Because of me, those below me couldn't get promoted.
You know what I mean.
I didn't know you cared so much for your juniors.
Then why did you treat me that way?
Gosh.
Are you still upset about that?
I just don't get it.
You could've opened up a small store with your severance pay.
Or you could've joined some other company.
Do you think you can work under me?
Why not?
I'm completely fine.
Is that so?
Sure thing.
Then try holding out.
All right.
I'd like to make one more thing clear.
You and I...
Mr. Lee, you and I...
have never met before.
Do you understand?
Sure.
I'm your superior. Where are your manners?
Yes, sir.
Also, "senior intern"?
I don't care about that.
Don't expect...
to be treated well...
just because you're old.
Yes, sir.
He's completely changed.
Cheer up.
(Analysis of Joonsu's Products)
Mr. Ga, I've personally analyzed our products.
- You did? - Yes, sir.
(Analysis of Joonsu's Products)
300 pages?
How could he attach these to all 300 pages?
Why did he highlight everything?
I'll take my time to read through this.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Ms. Lee, are you eating something?
No, sir.
- Can you give that to me? - Okay.
Please do that.
Okay, please make it quick. Thank you.
- Mr. Oh. - Yes?
About what I told you yesterday...
A group of idiots...
joined my team.
Thank you, Ms. Tak.
Attention, please.
Shall we gather in the meeting room?
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
We have new family members.
I'd like to welcome our interns,
Mr. Joo Yoon Soo, Ms. Lee Tae Lee,
and Mr. Lee Man Sic.
This is the Marketing and Sales Department, and I'm...
The leader!
Yes, I'm the leader. My name is Ga Yeol Chan.
- Clap. - Clap.
(Marketing and Sales Department)
Okay.
Let's cut to the chase.
I'll brief you guys on what you'll be doing.
Many people think interns only do trivial tasks.
That's right.
To be frank, that's the basis and the main job of an intern.
Someone needs to do that.
Mr. Lee, you're not an exception.
However,
giving only menial tasks to you guys...
is a loss to the company and a waste of our resources.
So you will be able to participate in real projects as well.
Your attitude, projects, and performance will be...
reflected on your evaluation for the full-time positions. Okay?
- Okay. - Okay.
Up until now, the assistant manager, Mr. Oh Dong Geun,
was in charge of supervising the interns.
But as there are three interns in this quarter,
we will divide the roles again.
In order to help the interns participate in our projects...
as soon as possible,
we will proceed...
with a mentor-mentee program where each intern will get a mentor.
I will now announce each mentee's mentor...
who will partner up with them and work as their supervisor.
- Mr. Joo Yoon Soo is with... - I hope we can work well together.
- Mr. Oh Dong Geun. - Same here.
- Ms. Lee Tae Lee is with... - I hope we can work well together.
Ms. Tak Jung Eun.
And lastly, Mr. Lee Man Sic is with...
me.
Mr. Kim Seung Jin, try to help them out as much as you can.
Yes, sir.
As Mr. Kim was an intern like yourselves only a year ago,
you should try to get tips on how to become a full-time position.
- Okay. - Okay.
My gosh. I hope we can work well together.
First of all, Mr. Oh talks too much.
Whenever he talks, it just ends up ruining his image. You know?
He speaks thoughtlessly once a day. And he's a cheapskate too.
He likes to use everyone else's stuff as if it's his.
But he catches on really fast.
So keep a straight face.
Okay.
After returning from his paternity leave, he became so cheap.
What are you doing? Are you taking care of your health alone again?
I'm just using eye drops because my eyes are dry.
Hey, Yoon Soo. You got a haircut because it's your first day of work.
- Yes, I did. - Where did you get it?
Are you planning to go there?
My gosh, you think I'm crazy?
I was just wondering where you got that ridiculous haircut from.
You need to trim your bangs, right? You look stuffy.
It looks like you'll keep having a frustrating life. Okay.
Right. If he acts all friendly and is nice to you,
he's trying to give you his work.
- So be careful. - Your haircut looks great. Okay?
Yoon Soo.
Do you want to analyze on the dry noodles?
I can do it myself,
but I thought you'd be good at it.
I don't ask anyone to do this, you know.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Let's give it a try.
All right. As for Ms. Tak,
she's a contract worker which is rare at our company...
since 95 percent of our employees have permanent positions.
And it's her fifth year here.
Can you guess what kind of person she is?
Yes.
(Restroom, Lee Tae Lee)
She thinks interns and other contract workers...
are her competition.
She doesn't befriend anyone, so don't be offended by that.
Right. And she won't give you proper projects.
Why? Because projects will lead to your performance.
I'm the queen of the copy machine.
No matter how menial a task is, if I work hard, I'll have a chance.
But it looks like...
all I'll be doing is copying documents.
This is the office pantry.
You don't have to worry about Mr. Ga at all.
He's the best boss ever.
He's such an angel.
Is that so?
Yes. This is the coffee machine.
You can just press the button for Americano.
What's the order?
- Mr. Ga. - Next.
- And who's next? - No.
- It's you, Mr. Oh. - Okay.
- And next? - And there are employees.
- Right. They are mere employees. - Yes.
You're very good.
You have already understood the dynamic of our office.
That's great.
Mr. Ga.
What should I do?
Don't do anything.
It's your first day here.
Rest up. And try to observe the tasks...
other employees are on.
I see.
Should I learn about their tasks?
On my own?
Yes.
- Well, we need to make a profit. - But the date...
- I don't think it will work. - Okay.
- Can you wait until the first? - Okay.
- Okay. I see. Now... - Give me that.
Hold on.
Wait. I'll call you right back.
Yes, sir.
(Get ready to turn off the computer.)
All right. It's over.
- How nice. - Good work.
- Good work. - Good work, everyone.
All right. Good job today.
What's this?
I analyzed the pros and cons...
of our products and wrote how we can improve our products.
(Chapter 6: Conclusion)
(Chapter 1: Introduction)
Did you write this yourself?
My gosh. You've been working in this industry for 30 years.
I can tell you're experienced.
You are indeed.
Indeed.
It's awful.
I can't use any of it.
Right.
Mr. Ga is back.
All right.
Let's call it a day.
You said we're having a company dinner with the interns today.
I'm sorry. I got a last-minute meeting.
Let's have it some other time.
Okay.
My gosh.
Number one, laugh.
Number two, laugh louder.
Number three, laugh really loud.
- All right. I'm on my way home. - Bring us snacks!
My gosh.
Didn't Mr. Ga seem a bit off today?
What about Mr. Ga?
Think about it. He said he'd be a mentor to the senior intern.
But he didn't talk to the intern at all.
That's not true.
He read the intern's analysis of our products.
Mr. Ga complimented on it. He was really considerate.
- Exactly, my point. - Right.
Really?
I didn't know.
Why did they hire someone like him?
How can I order around an intern as old as him?
His presence is making me feel very uncomfortable.
Do you want to get drinks? Just us, the interns?
- Why? - It's our first day at work,
so I don't want to go home yet.
Mr. Lee, do you want to come...
Should we clink our glasses?
Cheers.
I'll have only one glass and go home after I finish.
I came with you because it seemed you desperately wanted to drink.
If we drink beer together, people might talk behind our backs.
What?
Let me explain.
If we were having a get-together,
we should have invited Mr. Lee too. I was wondering why you didn't.
I just thought you might have an ulterior motive.
It's not that, you know.
If he joins us, it will be just uncomfortable.
Besides, I saw that you two were talking earlier.
And he kept asking personal questions.
He did. It's a good thing you didn't invite him.
I don't know why he's so interested in my father's job.
By the way, when they get new interns,
are they supposed to treat us as if we're nobodies?
And is it normal for them to skip our welcoming party?
Well, other companies don't throw us a grand welcoming party.
Why? Did you expect a party?
- Yes. - That's interesting.
I guess some people look forward to those parties.
That kind of an occasion is more uncomfortable for me.
It makes me feel uncomfortable too.
Then why...
I wanted to eat meat.
Meat?
I wanted beef.
And it's my first time...
working for such a big-name company.
I think there are things that are meant to happen.
I kind of expected to make it this time.
It seemed like Mr. Ga had a connection with me.
Of course. He seemed very open just as I have heard.
I regretted having said something bad about Spicy Chicken Ramyeon,
but I think that captured his heart.
So I plan to continue...
to share my honest opinion with Mr. Ga.
Sounds great.
Cheers.
I'll update it right now and re-print this.
Just stay still! Don't do anything!
Don't do anything from now on, okay?
Mr. Ga? What should I do?
Don't do anything.
It's awful. I can't use any of it.
Is that all you got? Repeating everything that I did?
You're no match for me.
- Thank you for dinner! - Thank you!
Let's go for another drink!
- Round 2! Round 2! - Round 2! Round 2!
- Round 2! Round 2! - Okay, let's go!
- All right! - Let's go for round two!
Our son just became first place in school.
Does he want to eat anything?
(Report Card)
My son!
I'm so proud of you.
Sure.
I heard our family will have a doctor one day.
I knew it would be you, Man Sae.
My son! Make sure you get into Seoul National University.
It's a national university, so it's much cheaper.
Life would be wonderful if it's always like this.
My husband just got a job as a director,
and my son just became first place in school.
I couldn't believe my luck,
so I suddenly got scared today.
Don't get scared over nothing.
My son.
Have some fruit before you go in.
("Science", Man Sae, year 2, class 2, number 36)
Man Sae.
I need to hold out until he goes to college.
(Lee Man Sic)
There are no relationships that are 100 percent bad.
Life is full of ironies.
Something good that happens now might begin something bad,
and something that's seemingly bad now...
may become the beginning of something good.
Relationships between people are also as such.
One day, you can smile thinking of your ill-fated relationships and...
His elder is offering him a hand first.
There's no way he can turn that down.
(Episode 4)
There's Mr. Ga.
- Good morning. - Hello.
- Hello. - You're here, Mr. Ga.
Mr. Ga, would you like a cup of morning coffee?
Do you want a cup of cold iced coffee?
So this is your plan?
I don't drink the coffee here.
- Should I go and buy one instead? - Would you?
Of course, let me know.
Well. I take an espresso lungo,
then make it into dry cappuccino with whipped cream,
topped with chocolate drizzle and powdered cinnamon.
Everyone, make your order.
Goodness. How can an old man like him get that?
You should either make Ms. Lee or Ms. Joo do it.
- Yes, we'll go. - Yes.
What should I do, Mr. Lee?
I'll go.
See that? Make your order.
Here's my credit card.
Then iced Americano with an extra shot for me.
- I'll take iced Americano too. - Iced Americano for me too.
- Iced Americano. - Caramel macchiato, iced.
Please stamp my card.
Okay.
One iced caramel macchiato.
Five iced Americano.
- One second. - Pardon?
Espresso doppio...
Londo.
Let's see. Very dry...
cappuccino.
- What does this... - I'll take that.
One iced macchiato.
5 iced Americano, but 1 with an extra shot.
Espresso doppio in lungo, dry cappuccino with whipped cream,
topped with chocolate drizzle and cinnamon powder.
Okay.
Is that all?
- Next, please. - The coupon.
Mr. Lee asked me yesterday...
to make him work exactly like other young interns.
He said that's how I can help him.
I knew it, Mr. Ga.
We were prejudice against him because he was too old.
We didn't make him work, but we talked behind his back.
We learn from you yet again, Mr. Ga.
You can never learn enough. Isn't that so?
- Yes. - Yes.
Good. You two answer me so well too.
What's taking the coffee this long?
(Marketing and Sales Department)
Thanks.
- Here. - Thank you.
Oh, right.
I should've asked you to get us some sandwiches.
I don't have enough time to eat.
I'll go back.
Will you?
Then can you go to the Metro Sandwich...
and get me bacon basil shrimp BLT?
Don't let the bread get too crispy. A medium crisp will do.
Double cheese, no cucumbers, add jalapenos, and raw onion.
Hot chili sauce and Thousand Island in 3 to 7 ratio...
No, in 4 to 6 ratio.
Then top it with a bit of truffle oil, salt, and pepper.
Okay?
If anyone else wants a sandwich, go ahead and order.
It's on me.
Goodness, how can an old man like him get that order?
No, no! Enough with your prejudice.
You just learned from Mr. Ga.
Here. Take the card.
Hot chili sauce and Thousand Island in 3 to 7 ratio...
No, in 4 to 6 ratio.
Then top it with a bit of truffle oil, salt, and pepper.
Okay? If anyone else wants some, go ahead and order.
It's on me.
Goodness, how can an old man like him get that order?
No, no! Enough with your prejudice.
That jerk has it in for me.
What is this energy?
This isn't enough.
Gosh, it's raining. When did it start raining?
I was too focused to notice.
Sir, what should we have for dinner?
Any ideas?
Since it's raining, how about we have some hot pollack soup?
How about seafood kalguksu?
There's that tasty place nearby.
What do you think, Mr. Lee?
I like both pollack soup and seafood kalguksu.
Since it's raining, let's have something hot and spicy.
How about hot, spicy pizza?
"Hot, spicy pizza"?
That guy always needs some kind of broth when eating.
Are you trying to kill me with bread?
You forced me to eat it for lunch as well.
(Yes, you are amazing today once again.)
It's not bad to have hot, spicy pizza on a rainy day.
Right, Ms. Lee?
Yes, it's scrumptious.
You're eating really well.
It's delicious.
It's really good.
You're eating so well.
- Come here and eat. - Okay.
There should always be some broth during a meal.
Hot, spicy pizza, my foot.
What are you doing here?
I was going to tell you anyway.
He and I are childhood friends.
I just got him something to eat while ordering mine.
What's wrong?
Well... You see...
He wanted both jjamppong and tangsuyuk.
But the set menu required him to order two bowls of jjamppong.
They sold beef brisket jjamppong as a set menu?
What are you doing here?
How dare you come in here and scold him?
Can't you see that we're eating?
Stop it. I'm fine.
You're not helping me at all.
Sang Jong.
This is no place for your personal relationships.
"Sang Jong"?
Hey! This is my room!
He's calling me by my first name in my room,
so what's it to you?
Not at all, sir.
I'm sorry, sir. I am.
Let's talk outside, sir.
Where do you think you're going?
Aren't you going to eat this?
May I quickly eat first?
Your colleagues are stuffing dry bread in their mouths.
How could you even think about slurping on that broth?
I'm not the one who ordered pizza.
What? Hey, eat this first.
Just take it home.
It's raining today. We haven't had a drink in a while.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
I heard that some interesting interns joined you.
Yes.
All those oddballs during the interviews...
joined your team. Will you be all right?
If I guide them properly, I'm sure they'll be outstanding.
You're amazing. There's no boss like you.
You're flattering me.
By the way, are you fine with drinking alone with me?
- Sorry? - I mean,
there were rumors at the company about us dating.
It's possible since we're both good-looking.
Why? Why are you laughing?
I don't feel that great.
Anyway,
even if people talk about you,
you can easily subdue them through your competence.
You know that, right?
I do.
I'm always grateful.
You know you're a great supporter, right?
Don't be ridiculous. I'm the one who's grateful.
Thanks to you, I'm in this position.
Did you say people from Hauhau are visiting us tomorrow?
Yes.
Those from Mongolia are after them as well.
Will you be all right?
I'm not too sure,
but I'll have to try.
Ma'am.
Here.
Thank you.
You look so haggard.
Mr. Ga must be giving you a hard time.
Not at all, sir.
I wanted to see you in private for some time now.
I'm sorry it took so long.
I had no idea you were struggling so much.
So why did you want to see me?
I'm going to be straightforward with you.
- Make Mr. Ga struggle. - Sorry?
Six months from now, they'll be voting for the CEO.
They'll be picking the board members.
Please make sure he doesn't undermine me.
I'm a mere intern.
I have no power.
Not at all. You're the only one who can do this.
Goodness.
What could I do?
Nothing.
Sorry?
I don't understand.
From the way I see it, he's already struggling.
When you're having a hard time, you're bound to make a mistake.
Just hang in there.
Don't whine and talk about quitting.
If you hold out, I'll repay you in any way you want.
By "repay",
do you mean you could hire me as a full-time employee?
"Full-time"?
Hey, that's not a big deal.
Come on, I'm the boss here.
What's with you? Goodness.
Here, have some soju.
Thank you.
Goodness. Here you go.
Drink.
You can do it, Man Sic.
That's right, that's right.
It's not like he asked you to do something bad.
He just wants you to hang in there.
That's nothing. I can do that.
My heyday is approaching once again.
My goodness.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Honey.
Where's that red ginseng your mother brought last time?
What?
You said you didn't want it, so I've been giving it to Man Sae.
You shouldn't. Give that to me.
Why? Why all of a sudden?
Mr. Lee, I'm meeting with a Chinese client. Come with me.
I know you're good at that.
Yes, sir.
I'll come.
You seemed to enjoy this place last time,
so I made another reservation here. Is that okay with you?
I couldn't forget this place. I've wanted to come back.
I'm glad you liked it.
I had such a good meal that day,
so I gained weight.
There's no interpreter?
I canceled it because Mr. Ga told me to do so this morning.
We can all speak a bit of Chinese anyway.
You'll try to hurt my pride with my educational background?
By the way, he's...
Wait, did you bring an executive because this is a big contract?
No, you don't have to get up.
He came here to grill the meat.
What happened? What?
He's the best at grilling pork belly.
I see. I knew it. He did exude an aura of a master.
Mr. Lee.
Yes?
Come over here and grill the meat.
Okay.
Sure. Shall I?
My time has come at last.
I must place the pork belly after preheating the grill sufficiently.
It's to quickly grill the meat while sealing in the juices.
The masters know one ought to flip the pork belly...
only twice.
Flip it for the first time when the blood seeps out from the meat.
And flip it again when the juice seeps out from the bottom side.
Mr. Binghao, are you all right?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry. It's been 30 years since I last grilled meat.
I made a mistake.
- Let me grill the meat. - No.
I'll do it.
I got the hang of it.
- Come on! - My gosh.
Are you all right?
Did you get burned?
Seung Jin, why don't you grill meat?
- Okay. - Let's switch.
Just come over here. And eat the meat.
- No. - I'll do it.
- I'll do it. - No, come on.
- You... - My gosh.
Do whatever it takes to stop him.
Stop the contract from going through. Okay?
Hey, by the way,
the company will suffer from this. Is that the right thing to do?
Why would the company suffer from this?
Only Ga Yeol Chan will be suffering from this.
If the contract falls through,
we're going to try to steal back the contract he lost.
Goodness. Even I thought that was a fantastic performance.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Binghao.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
Right here.
My gosh, he totally got me.
All right. That's not enough.
- Binghao. - Me?
Don't do it.
Sorry.
- What's wrong with you? - Are you okay?
- Hey! - It's okay.
I'm fine.
Binghao.
- No, stop that. - It's okay.
My gosh. All right.
There you go.
Nice.
- No. - Look.
Look at that.
- Binghao. - Wait, that's...
Binghao.
No.
That jerk.
I'll love you unconditionally
Binghao.
- Unbelievable. What are you doing? - Hey.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Call me when you need me
I'll run to you whenever
You can call me during the day and night
- I'll run to you whenever - You can call me
When other people call me
I'll think about it for a long time
Binghao.
Look at me.
I have unconditional love for you
My love for you is special
All right. Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Mr. Binghao, I can't drink anymore. I'll drink Sprite.
- Hey, drink that. - No.
Mr. Binghao hates it when someone can outdrink him.
- Pretend that you can match him, - Binghao.
- but you must let him outdrink you. - Cheers.
Okay?
Beat him. Outdrink him.
Isn't that your strong suit?
I won't lose. I won't.
Hey, Binghao.
Can you do this?
I can't do that.
What? Drink that.
Binghao.
1, 2, 3. Game over.
I'm happy that we will be working together again.
I'm happy to work with a reliable team.
I'll trust your team.
I hope we can work well together moving forward.
I'll do my best.
Rip the contract.
No. I can't.
No.
I wish you a safe trip back. Thank you once again.
Thank you. I hope our companies work well together.
Mr. Ga scored a big one once again.
By the way, what happened last night?
Thank you, Man Sic.
"Man Sic"?
What's wrong?
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Hey.
What's wrong with you? Hey, Mr. Bing.
Hey, are you all right?
Man Sic...
Man Sic, don't tell my team that I threw up.
If they found out, I'll be teased for life.
What are you talking about right after you almost died?
What? You won't do it for free?
Do whatever you want.
Fine, then.
Since you saved my life,
I'll sign the contract with your company. Happy?
Sure.
- Okay? - Okay.
Do we have a deal?
Okay. Yes, okay.
Why is that young kid calling me by my name?
Go away.
Goodness.
- Hey. - Hey.
Did he leave something behind?
What happened?
You said it'll be tough to seal that deal.
You've worked so hard, Mr. Ga.
Then who?
Well.
Mr. Ga!
We should relieve our hangover.
Goodness, look at the time.
Let's all eat lunch.
Why don't we eat...
Shock Shock Burger for lunch?
What? Burger? Did he just say burgers?
Gosh, I don't feel well.
Hey, put that away.
It smells, man.
Yes, the smell is coming at me.
Try some.
Don't you think Mr. Ga is insane?
How can we eat burgers after we drank so much last night?
Yes, exactly.
And he told someone who's old enough to be his dad to grill meat.
- I loathe that. - "Loathe"?
What has gotten into him lately?
People should always be consistent.
Is he crazy for money? He's really annoying.
Mr. Oh, you should be consistent too.
That's when I reached this conviction.
You stand no chance against me.
Something is seriously wrong.
(Kkondae Intern)
Those young jerks.
I'll destroy you all. I'll get you all.
Mr. Lee, you aren't a stumbling block, but a stepping stone.
Don't you know who Hye Soo is?
Hye Soo? Do you want me to call her?
Hye Soo, can you do this for me?
I really can't do this to you if I think about our old days.
I apologize for how rude I was without recognizing you.
What is this? Are you a troublemaker?
Why do you always get in trouble?
A man might have died because of you!
No one is dying because of me!
Enough is enough!
Car. Watch out for the car!