- My goodness. - Why do they have to be so cute?
My gosh.
I won't get bewitched by you guys.
Why are you talking to yourself?
I thought you did aerobics, but it looks like you're in a circus.
I need to dress in fancy colors to stand out. You know nothing.
What are you doing here?
Mom.
Let's go on a date.
What will you buy for me?
Just hurry up and get changed.
Make sure you get changed, okay?
Is this it?
- Buy me more. - No, stop
We bought enough.
My goodness, come here.
Ever since I was young, I thought there'd be a secret to my birth.
I guess I was right. A real mother wouldn't have done this.
If I wasn't your real mom,
I wouldn't have bought you something so expensive.
It looks so fancy and beautiful on you.
It suits you so well.
Whatever. You're just sorry.
Let's say I bought you that because I felt sorry.
But what about you? Why did you buy me all these gifts?
Did you get yourself in trouble?
Gosh, no. Why would I get myself in trouble?
Why don't you ever get yourself in trouble?
You're almost 40. You should be more adventurous.
You're too honest and kind.
My goodness.
Then I guess I should get myself in big trouble.
You'd better not change your mind.
Promise me.
Why do I need to promise? What's with you?
I made up my mind.
And I hope you cooperate.
Hey. You guys.
Can you not fight today? I even baked cookies for you guys.
- You know how to bake cookies? - Sit down.
Did you bake it with dirt?
You're such a picky eater unlike how you look.
Let's order pig trotters.
Pig trotters, my foot.
It's a special party. Let's order chicken.
I haven't been out in three months.
I haven't had fun for six months.
I've been craving pig trotters for a few months now.
Every day, I tell myself that I'll eat pig trotters tonight.
I promise myself that.
But once I clean the house, clean after the kids,
cook dinner for my husband, and eat the leftover food,
I suddenly lose my appetite.
That's why I still haven't had pig trotters.
And in three hours,
I'll be back in a world where there are no pig trotters.
- Order pig trotters. - Got it.
Yes, order chicken.
Why do you have to be friends with a guy like him?
We were friends first. You came later.
Darn you. You're so annoying.
What's with her? Is she bipolar?
Don't mess with her. She has twin boys.
My goodness.
Look at you. Are you an alcoholic?
I think so. He got divorced, you know
I can hear you.
- Just order pig trotters. - Order chicken.
- Pig trotters! - Chicken!
- Trotters. - Fried chicken.
I...
Shut it, both of you.
Before I order one of the two,
I have an announcement to make.
First, fill your glasses.
This party...
is to celebrate the second chapter of my life.
I, Jang Ha Ri, have decided not to get married.
Guys, why aren't you saying anything?
Whether you announce it or not,
it's not really up to you.
Take me for instance. I grew up never wanting to get married.
All I agreed to was a cup of coffee, but look at where I am now.
What's there to announce?
There was a slim chance of you getting married anyway.
Is this because of that blind date?
No, that didn't go any further because we weren't compatible.
- Unbelievable. - Do you have dementia?
Have you forgotten...
that you were never the dating type?
Don't you remember?
Ms. Jang?
- Gosh, what brings you here? - I had business nearby.
Anyway, I've been meaning to call you.
But that would've been a mistake since you have a boyfriend.
He's just a friend. The son of my mom's friend.
Is that so?
Right, then are you free this weekend?
I have tickets to a musical if you're up for it.
I'll even buy dinner.
A deadline is coming up for me, so maybe you can take someone else.
The tickets are until this month. Would you be available?
I don't want to make a promise I can't keep.
By the way, did you see the announcement I sent out?
I'll have Mr. Kim look at it.
He'll now be taking over.
- I'll see you around. - You too.
What the...
He just asked you out on a date, you moron.
When will you ever learn?
This is why I never wanted to set you up with anyone.
I was clueless back then.
No, your DNA has been wired this way.
You're right.
I've never been good at dating...
and marriage is a long-shot for me.
So what?
There are more things we can't do compared to the ones we can.
Then why have you been desperate to get married?
Gosh.
You know what? Good for you.
Marriage only leads to a dishtowel or a rag in your hand.
Just like you have been so far,
live your life with a laptop in one hand...
and a take-out coffee in another.
Right. Well, thanks for your sincere support.
Anyway, there's something else I wanted to tell you.
Hold on. But I've received so many monetary gifts from you.
You know what? I'll buy you something for this occasion.
Tell me whatever you need.
That's not necessary. Save it for yourself.
- It's not even important. - Just take it.
This is probably your last chance to receive any celebratory gift.
Zip it...
or you'll taste my foot in your mouth.
Anyway, I...
So did you order the trotters?
Fried chicken comes first.
Order the trotters right away.
- No, fried chicken. - Trotters.
Fried chicken!
- You two... - No to trotters!
- You two! - Fine, I'll order it myself.
- Trotters are what I love. - Unbelievable.
- I have no one looking out for me. - You jerk.
(Hangang Library)
("Pregnancy for Endometriosis Patients")
(The chances of a natural pregnancy)
(Hormones, Drug treatment, Surgery, Intracytoplasmic sperm injection)
(The chances of a natural pregnancy is about 15 percent.)
(4. Ethical issues)
You can't receive infertility treatments...
unless you're married.
The only exceptions are for women in a de facto marriage.
You need a spouse's consent to receive sperm from a donor.
So what's the best way to get pregnant within six months?
You can marry a man and get pregnant with him...
or...
find some random guy and get knocked up.
What happens if I have the baby without his knowledge...
and he finds out that I lied about it?
Well...
It's like the storyline of my favorite soap opera.
Anyway, an unmarried woman can't find a sperm donor in Korea.
There aren't many donors for even all the infertile couples.
I'm also a patient who was diagnosed as infertile.
The law is against it, so you must find another way.
- I must find another way? - That's right.
On your own.
(Han Se Sang)
- It's me. - Why haven't you been picking up?
- How was the move? - Fine.
It's the anniversary of dad's death next Wednesday.
I know.
You'll be there, right?
Sure.
Be there. Mom's hoping to see you.
Ms. Jang.
Are you still embarrassed to see me?
No, I couldn't be more comfortable around you.
Is that so? Me too.
What? What now?
Thank you for working with us on the cover.
Let me thank you for the car ride with a meal.
Just tell me what it is you want.
It's not like we're close enough to communicate through gazes.
I got it. I take back what I said about avoiding you.
- Bingo. - Gosh, I'm smart.
Like I said...
Was I tricked just now?
Unbelievable.
Sorry, everyone.
- Be more punctual. - Sure thing.
"How Won Bin and Lee Na Young raise their son."
(Special Interview with Won Bin and Lee Na Young)
How exactly do they raise their son?
- I'll meet them and ask. - How do you expect to do that?
I'll try and schedule an interview.
Go ahead. Who knows?
We might have our first sold-out issue thanks to you.
Yes, boss.
Interviewing celebrities...
won't help you get hired at a fashion magazine.
Suggest items that are doable, not those that are a dream of yours.
Next.
Where are we on the search for a columnist?
What about that friend who's living off you and your mom?
He's a single dad with a decent enough profile.
- Yoon Jae Young? - Yes.
But he's clueless.
Well, Sung Woo will be here.
Sung Woo too?
Do Ah, would you like some baby food?
Or how about this since you're older now?
I'm sure you're old enough for this.
He's a fun character.
It's better to feature a mess than an expert in childrearing.
Try to get him on board.
Since I'm back, we should grab some dinner.
Ask when the Advertising Department...
and the people at the studio will be free.
Can we go to my favorite restaurant?
I'll book it myself.
How about we get some raw fish?
- No, Korean beef barbecue. - What?
They're clueless, aren't they?
- Sushi. - We should eat beef.
- But it's a company dinner. - Come now. We should get sushi.
(Infertility Forum: Success Stories)
Here's your food.
Do Ah, do you want to eat this?
Or this?
Trust Daddy, okay?
Brand name foods are the best.
I smell cheonggukjang.
You pooped, didn't you?
Wipes.
Let's go in. Hold on.
Why isn't there a changing table in the men's room?
There it is. Hold on. Good girl.
Good.
We're here.
It's full.
- What's wrong with you? - I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We're home. It's okay.
Daddy's sorry. Hold on.
Sorry. Daddy's sorry.
You must be embarrassed.
Daddy's sorry. I'll change your diaper quickly.
Mister. Are you raising a baby on the street?
- What? - What did the baby do wrong?
Don't use the stroller for garbage.
Put the baby in it.
That's not mine. It's his.
Is it your friend's?
He isn't my friend.
He must be from a different district.
Look.
How do I look homeless to you?
Isn't it obvious at a glance?
Of course. Just look at him. Everything screams "I'm homeless."
I guess I am homeless.
Do Ah, I bought this earlier.
It's a bit small.
My baby. Did that scare you?
Look at it. Look.
How many years has it been?
I've wondered how you were doing after you left like that.
That's what I thought. That's why I came to see you.
Since it was a trip nonetheless.
I'm glad you were relaxed enough to shop for a gift.
Are you working again?
Yes.
You must make the effort to get along with people.
Being in large groups gives you confidence.
Confidence.
What about corn-fidence?
Wait for me.
That must hurt.
They're new, that's why.
Can't you give up on heels?
The heels are an extension of the legs.
True. I wore heels all the time in my 20s.
They'll kill your knees. Comfort is the best.
Did I just sound super old?
I'm glad you know.
- I need to stop by a pharmacy. - Okay.
Auntie!
Bye.
"Baby" or "Children"?
Aren't they the same thing?
I don't like it.
Will there be many staff members?
I don't like having too many people.
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
- Let me see. Is it... - No.
- Is it bad? - No.
Are you okay?
Wait right here.
Leave it. I'll do it.
It's not heavy.
Exactly. So let me do it.
You won't die if a man helps you, will you?
It's my job. It really isn't heavy.
Let go. I'll do it. I'll put it there.
Should I suspect?
Should I get the wrong idea?
Is it weird if I'm nice?
Very. Extremely.
Come to think of it,
I ran into you unexpectedly many times.
Talk about luck.
You mean bad luck.
Bad luck?
Don't hate me so much.
It's harder to hate someone than it is to like someone.
What does that mean?
Well...
You have a bruise on your forehead.
What is this?
I almost got the wrong idea.
Darn it.
I said to wait there.
What is that?
Your heel must hurt a lot.
Why do you care about my heel? This is awkward.
Right? I may put it on wrong.
I'll just take these.
Just be a colleague.
Okay.
He just doesn't get it.
What a bother.
Chunhang confirmed the order 2,000 of strawberry-flavored toothpaste.
Kiwi confirmed 1,000 orders of cotton-soft...
baby wipes.
Hold on.
Just toothpaste.
Yes.
Can you brush your teeth with just toothpaste?
- No, sir. - Then what you do need?
I need toothpaste.
If you know that...
I'll give you another chance.
Try to tack on toothbrushes too.
Yes, sir.
What did I tell you?
Sales are all about networking.
Visit a customer twice instead of once.
You need to check every little thing...
in fine detail.
- Don't forget. - No, sir, I won't.
Just earlier, Ms. Choi Hyo Joo had a cut on her right heel,
so I ran over and bought her a band aid.
Why you...
I teach you 1 thing, and you learn 10.
Good job.
Customers are important too, but your reputation at work...
shouldn't be ignored. Particularly...
the editors.
I told you, they're comrades as well as enemies.
You need to make sure they are on your side.
Yes, sir.
What is this? What does she wear?
What are you doing at home? Is today a special day?
No. Do Ah's poop got on my clothes.
What a good daughter. She made her dad shower.
Is she sleeping?
Yes.
I don't see your laundry.
We should do our own laundry.
We shouldn't make someone else do it for us.
Anyway, I need to start working again.
But I'm worried because Do Ah is so young.
I can't just leave her at a daycare center all day.
My goodness, my back.
I think I have a herniated disk.
Child abuse is a big issue these days.
So I can't seem to trust anyone.
It'd be great if I could leave her with someone I know.
Why does my wrist hurt so much?
I think I have carpal terminal syndrome.
Are you going on a trip?
It's carpal tunnel syndrome.
Oh, right. Yes, that's what it is.
You're right. You shouldn't overwork yourself at your age.
Raising a baby isn't an easy job.
I feel like it's become harder to raise kids than before.
I don't do much, but it's still very tiring.
I used to carry Ha Ri on my back when I used to run my own business.
It was tiring, but Ha Ri was adorable back then.
She was gentle, and she always smiled.
Kids grow up so quickly, but that memory lasts a lifetime.
I can babysit Do Ah from time to time,
but you can't expect me to take care of her all the time.
No one will care for your child better than yourself.
The time you spend with her now will stay with you forever.
(From: The Best Donor, Why don't we meet up and talk?)
Anyway, an unmarried woman...
can't find a sperm donor in Korea.
Welcome.
Excuse me.
Are you The Best Donor?
Yes, hello. I'm The Best Donor.
Take a seat.
I'm 180cm tall.
My IQ is 148. My blood type is O.
I was in the special forces.
I'm a student at Hanguk University.
I can assure you that I have the best-quality sperm.
The best quality. Right.
I'll take that. Thanks.
Gosh, that's hot.
Well...
The thing is,
I haven't decided to receive your sperm yet.
But I'd like to know how this all works.
It's like a preliminary investigation.
I'm a journalist, so I feel the urge to investigate.
You're a journalist?
No, I'm not a news journalist.
I work at a magazine company.
You know those magazines you see at hair salons?
I won't publish an article.
But still...
I should know how it works...
before I decide to take your sperm.
Can you tell me how you plan to give me your sperm...
and if it's safe?
I'm sure it's not for free.
I do this with a sense of duty...
for those who desperately wish to have babies.
Sperm donation is the same thing as organ donation.
One saves lives,
and the other creates lives. They're both equally important.
So I only receive...
10,000 dollars.
- 10,000 dollars? - Yes.
I do it until you get pregnant. It's not enough, is it?
Do you get requests from a lot of people?
As you can see, I have the best genes.
So, women agree to take my sperm as soon as they see me.
Then you must have a lot of unknown children.
I can't do this job if I think of it that way.
Yes, you're right.
Exactly.
And it's very important to give birth to a healthy baby.
So instead of doing an IVF or artificial insemination,
a lot of women prefer to get naturally pregnant.
- "Naturally pregnant"? - Yes.
I sleep with women every night...
during their ovulation period.
- "Every night"? - Yes, that's right.
It's hard to get a woman pregnant in one try.
This is a very tiring job for me.
But I think of it as doing you guys a favor.
If you're interested, let me know.
And I noticed...
that you're my type. I'll treat you nicely.
Every night.
You darn punk. Have you gone crazy?
What is in your darn head?
Stay right there. I'm going to call the cops.
Has this middle-aged lady lost her mind?
What did you just call me?
You told me you have good eyesight. That was a lie, wasn't it?
You don't go to Hanguk University either, do you?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
- I'll teach you a lesson. - You wanted my sperm.
So why should I be ashamed of myself?
Be quiet. I'm calling the cops.
- Give me that. - Hey! Hey!
Hey!
That's you, right? We're the police.
Someone reported you for illegal sperm donation and forgery.
You impersonated a Hanguk University student, right?
- Let's go to the police station. - No.
I'm glad you're here.
I was just about to call you guys.
Hurry up and take him. This guy is a bad seed.
You need to come with us as well.
Me? Why?
You got caught trying to make a deal.
I didn't buy anything.
I'm serious. I didn't even get to see his sperm.
- Bye then. - Do you want to get handcuffed?
Did you bring a car?
Let's go.
There he is.
How do you feel right now?
Get out of the way. Move.
- Let's go. - Tell us how you feel.
- How do you feel? - Tell us what you think.
We're from the TV show...
called "Unbelievable Incidents".
- Can you tell us... - I have nothing to say.
- Why were you with him? - I feel so wronged.
Tell us what happened.
Excuse me.
Tell us why you feel wronged.
Sir, I was really scared.
I was scared that he might be in some kind of a crime syndicate.
I went there to do my job as a journalist.
Look at my hands. They're shaking.
I'm not brave enough to break the law.
You must have a high arrest rate.
Live a normal life.
What's a normal life?
Stick to the law and live like everyone else.
Of course, I should stick to the law.
But sometimes, the law can't guarantee an individual's happiness.
Ms. Jang, if you keep talking back, the investigation will last longer.
I didn't exactly talk back.
Hey.
(Hanguk University College of Medicine, Yoon Jae Young)
I'm Yoon Jae Young. I'm here to guarantee her identity.
- Are you a lawyer? - No, I'm a doctor.
I'm a pediatrician.
Did you say something to her?
(Hanguk University Hospital, Yoon Jae Young)
You really are a pediatrician at Hanguk University Hospital.
You're the one...
who contacted the scumbag...
from the online community for infertile patients.
Be honest and tell me why you contacted him.
Like I said...
I proved that I'm a doctor,
but I have no proof that you're a cop.
She was at the exchange site which is only circumstantial evidence.
But instead of getting a witness statement from her,
you're questioning her as if she's the perp.
Did you give him any money?
I'd rather help the unfortunate if I had any to spare.
See?
She's a curious woman with a tendency to take action,
not one who'd be involved in an illicit crime.
Didn't you receive numerous prizes for good conduct as a kid?
Yes, I led the volunteer club.
Con artists are basically good people too.
You may have to investigate to know about her,
but I already know her all too well.
It's why I vouch for her.
Are you sure you were working undercover?
Yes.
All right.
There was no money transaction, and I vouched for her.
May we go now?
Her identity has been vouched for,
so you may go.
Come on. Let's go.
Sure thing.
Look at you with your head held up high.
Well, I did nothing wrong.
You're a brazen one, aren't you?
You're not good at a lot of things, but lying is at the top of the list.
What do you mean you are an undercover journalist?
What were you going to do with that sperm-selling jerk?
I'm going to have a baby.
What? With a 24-year-old?
Say that you love him, and I'll kill you.
It's not like that.
He offered up his sperm.
But for 10,000 dollars. Sounds like a scam, right?
You were going to buy his sperm?
Do Ah's asleep, so keep it down.
This is a new kind of crazy, even for you.
Did not being able to get married drive you to insanity?
I want to have a baby without getting married.
Forget it.
It's not like you'd understand,
and I don't expect you to.
You've gone crazy.
I know that it comes with all sorts of ethical problems.
But isn't it weird...
that only a pregnancy by a married couple is deemed ethical?
Sperm can't be donated to unmarried women.
So you thought of a way to get it done yourself?
Well, I did my research.
I don't know what to do with you.
It's not my intention to break the law to get pregnant.
I know I shouldn't have even thought about it,
and I'm sorry.
Aren't you sorry for wanting a baby alone?
I understand why you don't want to get married...
and that you adore kids.
But can't you...
just get married and have children and live an ordinary life?
I'm doing this to have an ordinary life.
I'm 39.
I still hope to meet...
the man of my dreams as soon as I step outside those doors.
But my reality is, I'm being called an old lady.
I don't know what qualifies as normal or ordinary,
but I don't want to give up on my dreams...
because people can frown upon me.
Should I be complacent and live with what life throws at me?
39 is way too young for that.
Unbelievable.
How can you bring Do Ah out without a blanket?
She's probably cold.
Here you go.
Hold the jacket. You've got to be kidding me.
[VIU Ver] tvN E03 'Oh My Baby'
"Ha Ri's Single Life"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I want his. His is bigger.
They're the same.
No, his is bigger.
I want what he has.
Take it then.
Wait. Guys, no.
- Hold on. - Don't fight.
- Look at this. - Are you kidding me?
Come on, let's go.
Goodness me.
Here you go. Please don't cry.
You're okay. Enough with the tears.
Who can watch the baby?
Can someone take the baby?
- Here. - I don't even hold my own nephew.
- The baby... - My arm's killing me.
Out of the blue?
Can't anyone look after the baby?
- Oh, no. - I'm here.
Ms. Jang, the baby's crying.
What are you so scared about?
If the baby's crying,
all you have to do is rock it gently.
Was it that upsetting? I hear you.
Who did this to you? Goodness.
There you go.
It's like she came to the rescue.
- Guys. - Over here!
- There you go. - How sweet.
- Just a little bit more. - Good.
Can you face each other? Delicious, isn't it?
Turn only your heads this way.
Yes, just the heads.
Good job. Could you face this way?
You too, sweetie. There we go.
There we go. Nice!
Offer it to each other.
Can you look this way?
Over here.
Ha Woon, let's have you turn around.
Now look at the camera guy.
Here you go.
What?
- I'll buy the beer. - No.
- Am I buying the meal too? - No.
Thank you for helping with the photo shoot.
Bingo.
Why do you hate kids?
Not everyone has to like kids.
I just want to know if there's a particular reason.
There isn't.
What if you need help with the kids like you did today?
It's not like I can come to the rescue every time.
How about you get some practice while working with us?
Does practice make perfect?
Yes, of course.
Find something to adore, and you'll adore that person.
Trying to like someone will make it real.
You hating kids might be the key factor.
- Do you want me? - Will my answer change your mind?
- No. - I knew it.
Can I ask you a personal question?
Do I want to stay single because I hate kids?
- How did you know I'd ask that? - You were building up to it.
I see you get asked this a lot.
Let's say that I do.
What if you meet someone you love?
And what if there's an unexpected pregnancy?
That won't happen.
I may not seem that way,
but the wall I have up are fairly thick.
So you've never once wanted to be a dad?
No. Never. Not even once.
Let me see.
Where are all my clothes?
Here it is.
When did Mom last do the laundry?
Seriously.
What is this?
What is all this?
That little...
Jae Young, you're dead.
- Are you leaving? - No.
I get to use my self-defense skills.
Hey. Why are you beating him up first thing in the morning?
I need to teach this punk a lesson.
You cuckoo punk.
How dare you put your dirty laundry in my hamper?
I know you go through my stuff.
What did you steal?
I thought you'd do at least that much for me.
I helped you out with your undercover project.
Do you think that was easy?
Hey.
How dare you throw that tiny, disgusting trotter?
This is wrinkled.
You should've told me if you had laundry. I would've run it for you.
You said you'd do your own laundry. Just put it in the hamper.
- Come have breakfast. - Okay.
Should I remove my laundry from the hamper?
Hey. Just leave it. It's fine!
- Let go. - Brother.
- I shall wash your laundry for you. - Fine. Let go.
That annoying cuckoo punk.
Auntie!
Wait for me. Come on.
- Isn't it so cold? - Sure.
Auntie. Have you had breakfast? Auntie?
Yes, I did.
- Have a nice day. - Going up.
Hello.
Auntie. Lunch in the cafeteria today?
Sure.
- Have a nice day. See you later. - Going up.
That's right. Auntie. We have a company dinner tonight.
You're going, right?
I'm not sure.
Okay. You're going.
Have a nice day. What a great morning.
That's right. Auntie, you...
Eu Ddeum. There are no aunties at work.
There are only bosses, bosses, and bosses. Understood?
Okay.
Going up.
What was that?
Look over there.
(Why was she meeting a sperm donor con artist?)
Auntie. I mean, she looks like you, Ms. Jang.
I feel so wrongly accused.
So tell us.
Please tell us.
No pictures.
Drink. Drink up. Let's drink.
This woman who claims she was just curious.
She's single.
Plus, she is a reporter at a magazine.
She stated that she was doing an undercover investigation.
However, our findings show...
that the magazine is not doing an undercover investigation.
This is unfair.
I only contacted him out of curiosity.
He said his sperm was superior...
I didn't buy it!
I didn't even get to see it.
How could that be me?
How could that be me? That's absurd.
Yes. The bruise on your forehead. It's the same.
Why did this woman, who is a reporter,
- meet this man... - My stomach...
- My stomach. - It's there.
- My stomach. - We want to know.
Gosh.
Mom.
Come in.
- Mom. - Why you...
You tried to buy what illegally?
Is life too boring? Do you want to go to jail?
Auntie. You should hear her out before you hit her.
She was undercover.
You know how reporters go in secretly and investigate a story.
She's amazing.
Is that right? Is it?
Yes.
Your face says otherwise.
Tell me the truth.
Did you try to buy sperm?
Why would you buy sperm?
Mom.
I'm thinking of getting a sperm donor and having a baby.
I'm sorry for upsetting you, but I won't get married.
It's not like getting married guarantees happiness.
And... Mom, I...
You'll have a baby by yourself without getting married?
You want to be a single mom?
- Mom... - Do you know how hard it is...
to raise a child alone? Have you gone mad?
I raised you alone, so my heart aches for single moms.
But people don't try to understand why you're doing it alone.
Even if they see a single mom walking by,
they criticize her and say she's tough and has bad luck.
It was bad enough I had to hear that. Why should you?
Then should I...
live alone for the rest of my life?
If I don't get married?
If you're gone?
Should I live just for myself?
You say you live for me.
Should I live alone without any family,
living just for myself, and then die alone?
I want to live for someone too.
You crazy witch.
You saw how I lived.
How could you even think about having a kid alone?
You should think about being happily married!
You raised me just fine without a husband.
No. It was hard even when Dad was around.
I grew up watching you and Dad fight all the time.
You only showed me that marriage makes you sad.
Why are you telling me to do something you couldn't?
Is it my fault you're not married?
Did I tell you to learn from me?
Why is it my fault that your life is messed up?
Why is my life messed up?
Is it messed up not to get married in case...
- I end up like you? - Hey.
That's enough.
Auntie. Calm down. Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Get out.
Don't learn from me and ruin your life.
You're smart, so get out and live as you want.
Get out. Get out.
Get out right now! Get out.
Wait outside.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Don't cry.
What are you doing?
You said this is what I should do when someone cries.
I'm not a kid.
You look like one right now.
Thanks.
Please don't ask me what happened.
I wasn't going to.
I figured it might be too embarrassing for you.
I'm so pathetic.
I'm about to turn 40, but I'm still so immature.
You're good as long as...
you didn't run outside after you got scolded by your mom.
I'm 41.
But I still don't know what it means to be an adult.
My body keeps aging, but my heart is still young.
When I see something nice, I want to have it.
When someone offends me, I get angry.
When I suffer a loss, I feel upset.
I still feel everything I felt as a kid.
So I don't get what's so different about being 40.
There's nothing good about aging.
But if I have to choose, I guess the only good thing...
is that I have a better judgment of character.
Even if you were that weird lady on TV,
I know for a fact...
that you're a good person.
Ha Ri.
What are you doing out here after fighting with your mom?
I didn't fight with my mom.
We meet again.
You didn't have to come looking for me. I was going to go home.
Why did you wear my slippers?
They're expensive. They're my favorite.
Hurry up and wear your shoes.
What are you doing?
What? Hurry up so we can go home.
Let's go.
We live together.
- What are you saying? - Let's go.
Why are you so loud?
- I'm not loud. - Be quiet!
I'm the quietest person on earth.
I can't believe you were talking to a guy after you ran out like that.
Do you really have to say it like that?
I've had enough for today. Let's just walk home quietly.
I'm not being sarcastic.
Don't care about what others say.
I'm just saying you should do whatever you want...
regardless of what others might think.
What's with you? I'll see you.
I quit working at the hospital.
But you still have some time until your leave is over.
I thought you wanted to become a professor.
I won't have time to do lectures, treat patients,
and write theses.
I feel so upset that I can't get to do what I wanted.
But what can I do? I'll just have to get by.
How exactly?
I'm going to open up a hospital...
with the money I got from selling my apartment.
That's why I moved into your place.
I've been wasting away my life after I was left with Do Ah.
But funnily enough, I found myself...
gaining strength from her.
I know it's hard for me to fully understand you.
But if you need someone,
and you want that to be a baby, I'd understand.
I'm also a dad.
And you're probably doing your best to get by just like me.
I'll publish an interview about your hospital...
to congratulate your grand opening.
It'll be a series. You can give medical consultations.
Sure.
But wait a minute.
I will...
do it if you let Do Ah participate.
Mr. Yoon.
Not everyone thinks Do Ah is adorable.
What are you talking about? She takes after me.
- That's her flaw. Now, go home. - My goodness.
I'm going to go do an interview.
Where are you going? You have something to tell me.
- No, I don't. - Yes, you do.
Go inside the meeting room.
Hey, wait.
You didn't shoot the probiotics ad yet, did you?
- Why? - They want a doctor...
to recommend the product.
You know a pediatrician, right?
Yes, of course. I know a very nice pediatrician.
I'll go bring him.
Why don't you just call?
Does she prefer to meet people face to face?
Don't ask.
Okay, great.
How does it look?
- It looks fine. - Seung Ho.
Bring the doctor.
Sir, we're going to do a test shoot.
Come this way and stand right here.
- Thank you. - Tell me the truth.
You were that woman who tried to buy sperm, right?
No.
You're a very adventurous woman.
Are you going to keep looking for someone's sperm?
Why don't you just sleep with someone?
Then things will get too complicated.
It'll be a problem even if the guy offers to be the father.
And if I have the baby without telling him,
I might go to the fiery pit.
That's against moral ethics.
I just want to get someone's sperm with their consent...
and have a baby.
What? Like in Hollywood movies?
They get it from a drunk colleague or a friend.
I don't know any guys.
- Hello. - My goodness.
This is the product. It takes you straight to the bathroom.
- Oh, I see. - Here. Take a look.
(Oh My Baby)
Don't look her way.
The look in her eyes is telling me...
that a crazy idea is forming inside her head.
Acknowledge her now and you'll be in trouble.
Where are you three going?
Why would two friends be living together?
It's not wrong at all, you know.
Especially given our close relationship.
He's a dangerous one.
He looks like a con artist.
You think I'll fall for a bad boy...
and burn myself?
Only make mistakes with me, okay?
I don't want you to fall for some random guy because you're lonely.
Younger specimens would have better sperms, right?