(Good job!)
It's us grown-ups who really need compliments.
Good job, Mr. Han.
As much as I'll be here on time at 8am,
please make sure I can leave every day at 7pm.
I expect to get paid extra even if you're 10 minutes late.
And I don't work on weekends.
If you want a premium service such as baby massages...
and premium baby food, you need to pay 300 dollars more.
Do you have any questions?
- We'll go broke if we are late... - Don't.
Should I ask her? No?
If I get off work early, will I get a discount?
My goodness, I didn't know you guys were married.
My gosh, I guess you really weren't homeless after all.
Then what about that other kid? Was that your second child?
Is this your second marriage?
Did you have an affair?
My goodness, I guess that must be it.
Did they really have an affair?
My goodness.
- Goodbye. - See you at our aerobics class!
- Bye! - Goodbye.
Did you recommend her, Mom?
This is absurd.
My gosh, this is exhausting.
It's so hard to get a babysitter.
What are you going to do? Your hospital is going to open soon.
I'll leave her at the daycare center until 3pm.
Then I'll just have to bring her to my office.
By the way, how do you know all those women?
How about you?
I don't even want to talk about it.
Ha Ri.
What are you going to do now?
Why don't you help me prepare some stuff for the opening?
How about we have some fun?
Don't even think about it and pay me if you want my service.
It was worth a try.
Hello.
Good to see you.
This is our schedule for the day.
(10am: I Sang and Ha Ri: My Child's First Friend of the Opposite Sex)
Ms. Jang has a photoshoot?
She takes her job very seriously.
Her suspension only means that she needs to stay clear of her boss.
Good morning.
What's the photoshoot for?
Don't be so obvious.
It's an article on children having friends of the opposite sex.
My gosh, you startled me.
- What gives? - I'm sorry about that.
This isn't your photoshoot though.
I told Ha Ri to stay home...
since I could manage this myself.
It's a monthly series of ours, so Sang Hee knows what to do.
Would she be in the mood to work when she was suspended?
I told her to stay well away from this place.
That's unnecessary camaraderie.
- Sorry? - What kind of photos do you need?
Unbelievable...
I want the two of them shot from the front...
- but leave some space up top. - Gosh.
I see right through you.
Please leave some space up top for the title.
I heard you.
- Just a bit more... - I'll adjust as we go.
(Episode 5: When We Wish to Believe in Fate)
Mom.
Hold on. What brings you by?
- Hello, sir. - Hi.
Here you go.
Why are you treating me like a patient?
Because you are.
You should stick to food that is easy to digest.
Gosh.
Are you aiming to be a professional guitarist?
You shouldn't play in this condition of yours.
My sore wrist goes back to my days working in diners.
I can't believe the pain is back after a few guitar strokes.
Don't overexert yourself. It's just a stupid guitar.
It isn't for me.
Playing "Spanish Romance" has been a lifelong dream of mine.
Your father distracted me though,
so I was only able to manage "Edelweiss".
Darn it. When you fall for someone,
you tend to fall hard.
Luck seems to have found you in your later years though.
Your cancer was detected in the early stages...
and you have enough money to do what you want in your life.
That doesn't mean a thing to me...
because my body isn't what it used to be.
How great would it be to do everything I missed out on...
when I had to work hard to keep food on the table?
Exactly.
We all should do what we want in life.
It's why I want to give birth to a child.
I'm not producing enough eggs...
and my chances of pregnancy will only get slimmer...
once I receive surgery for my endometriosis.
It's nothing serious though.
Wait.
Was that about you?
I can have the baby...
and receive surgery for endometriosis.
It's nothing.
Now eat up before it gets cold.
Come on.
There you go.
You want to go through IVF on your own?
Did I misunderstand that or are you insane?
I told you I was done wanting a marriage.
I'd rather have a kid instead.
You really are insane, aren't you?
People will constantly judge me for this,
so can you at least be on my side?
I'm all on board with you buying green onions.
But how can I support you when it's sperms you want to buy?
I'm not buying anything.
It'll be consensual.
And keep your voice down.
My friend, Ha Ri, I strongly am against this idea.
- Well, I think it's perfect. - Wait.
So you're seriously thinking about having this baby?
On your own when it's hard enough to raise a child with a partner?
Fine. Let's say that it's doable.
What if a decent man comes your way?
I tortured myself with that thought for 20 years.
I'm done trying to meet a husband.
My friend, don't close the door to your options...
and reconsider the men...
that you once dumped or took a pass on.
You'll be surprised by the revelation it could bring you.
Just keep digging, okay? There are many decent men out there.
Like whom? Do you know anyone?
Wait. What about my sister's husband?
As you know,
he makes himself breakfast before going to work,
get the kids to school,
takes the family abroad every year,
and only has eyes for my sister.
I know.
Your brother-in-law is the best.
See?
He must be here to shop with your sister.
That's him, right?
Did your sister lose weight?
Check out her slender figure.
Here.
Who's the young woman?
- Don't wait for me. - What?
Eun Young, take a photo first.
As evidence!
Brother-in-law?
Who is this woman?
You have the wrong person.
Hold on. Wait. Stop right there.
Stop!
You have the wrong person.
Oh, dear.
I'm not your brother-in-law.
- Stop! - Darn it.
- I'm not who you think I am. - Stop!
Wait!
- I'm not your brother-in-law. - You are!
I'm not!
Eun Young used to think I was pathetic...
for wanting to get married.
As a successful app developer,
she was on the verge of launching her startup.
She went to an investor for an investment...
and her life got turned upside down.
A sudden attraction...
led to marriage and pregnancy.
Until then, she was confident...
that she could be a working mom...
which was tough even for Superwoman.
That's because she had no idea she'd have pre-eclampsia...
and would nearly die giving birth prematurely to twins.
Who knew she'd go from dreaming to be a successful entrepreneur...
to a woman fixated on childbirth?
Who knew she'd one day run after her cheating brother-in-law?
What I learned in my life of 39 years...
is that good things just don't happen to you.
Only the unfortunate smack you from behind.
Nothing will happen if you don't take action.
That is why...
I must do something.
Yoon Jae Young.
From an objective point of view,
he does have good qualities I'd want in my child.
If I asked him for his sperm though,
he'd patronize me.
(Potential sperm donor no. 2: Yoon Jae Young)
Han I Sang.
See? He's not that bad either.
Most of all,
he's kind of cool.
Why am I smiling though...
when he'd never agree to it?
(Potential sperm donor no. 3: Han I Sang)
Choi Kang Eu Ddeum.
Of course.
(Potential sperm donor no. 1: Choi Kang Eu Ddeum)
Unbelievable.
Eu Ddeum, can I talk to you?
Sure thing.
How can you write up a report like this?
What a joke.
A project proposal should be simple and impressive.
The client should take a glimpse at it...
and want to bring its advertisements to us.
- It needs to be a sales pitch. - As if could do any better.
How is it that you still can't get this right?
I'll write up another one.
So much for being a fast learner.
He acted like he knew everything.
Seriously.
How will he ever survive?
Eu Ddeum.
This is a true or false quiz.
True and false? I can do it.
A man donated his sperm.
Only one infertile couple may receive the sperm.
True or false?
Choi Kang Eu Ddeum. False.
- Correct. - Yes.
If we were to submit a proposal...
to a fertility clinic regarding a sperm donation campaign...
Because that's what you're interested in?
Let's say that's true.
What would be more effective,
writing down...
the benefits of advertising...
or a quiz like just now?
- A quiz. - Right?
That's how you should write the proposal.
Think of a concept the client may be interested in,
and come up with a magazine ad or a video.
Consult the reporters.
You're like a lecturer.
Ha Ri came.
Why? Did something happen?
No. She and Eu Ddeum...
were doing something in secret.
With Eu Ddeum?
What?
They were in a conference room, so it was probably a meeting.
What's wrong with my eyes?
They sting.
I've been staring at the monitor for too long.
Hey. Open the windows and air out the place.
Okay.
So...
What do you think...
about sperm donation, now that you've heard about it?
Not the proposal, but sperm donation?
No, well... I just wonder if my explanation...
was effective.
But you can't receive sperm...
even if you want to.
Because you're single.
I'm looking for a way.
Something not illegal.
What if...
the child wants to know about the dad later?
That's why I plan to get his consent first.
Whether or not I can tell the child about him if the child asks.
If he's willing to meet the child if the child...
wants to meet him.
To the donor?
Yes.
But first, I'd have to explain it to the child...
so he or she understands.
"Mommy wanted to meet you so badly,"
"that I asked a kind man for help."
"But just because he gave you life..."
"doesn't make him your dad."
"Not because he doesn't love you,"
"but because he and Mommy don't love each other."
"That's why."
I know for sure I can love my baby,
but the baby will want more, right?
I'm sure your child...
will be lucky to have you for a mom.
Thank you.
So...
the biological dad...
needs to have healthy genes...
Exactly.
How do you find out?
So...
You must be done with the proposal if you're hanging out here.
And you didn't get your physical, did you?
You have to get it this week.
Yes, sir.
Me too.
I need to get mine too.
I will.
- Are you leaving? - Yes.
Hey.
What?
What is it?
Shall we?
What do you want?
That hits the spot.
Are you not over In Ah?
How do you ask that without even a warning?
I wondered...
if that was why you can't date someone even if you like her.
I'm not dating because it's comfortable being alone.
To be honest, you envy me.
Like crazy.
I worried a lot about you two.
During the retreat during your freshman year in college,
when we went to Daeseong-ri, you two sneaked out...
and I caught you kissing.
I watched you guys for 17 years since.
You have an incredible memory.
You two were doing so well without a hitch but suddenly broke up.
I felt terrible.
You were so hurt at the time,
that I couldn't ask.
Why did you break up?
Why is it here again?
Can't you put it somewhere convenient?
In Ah.
That was there the whole time.
Nothing changed.
Not a thing.
What?
Everything changed.
We fought about the littlest things.
We started to hate even the habits that we liked.
Well... We just got tired of it.
Are you afraid it'll happen again?
Is that why you want to live alone?
Try to meet a nice person. It may be different.
Soo Chul.
Even the person I loved for 17 years couldn't do it.
Why would I make a nice person deal with my problems?
I'll just deal with it alone.
I'm drunk.
There is no way the love will...
I Sang!
You saw me, didn't you?
I did.
Did you just ignore me?
Yes, that's right.
Why?
Can't I do as I please?
You're drunk.
Yes.
Correct.
Oh my gosh.
That's so funny.
My goodness.
Why are you following me?
Because the park is round.
So is Earth.
The Earth is round, so if we keep walking, we'll meet.
- You're drunk. - Don't underestimate my tolerance.
Drunk I Sang.
Can you find your way home okay?
What do you take me for?
So...
what did I do to deserve the "Good Job" stamp?
- What? - I mean...
Be more specific. What exactly did I do...
to receive a compliment?
I Sang.
You're tall...
and handsome.
And you have a good personality.
I'm 41 years old.
I'm not a little kid.
You become funny when you're drunk.
Why don't we drink together?
I want to enjoy this a bit more.
No?
Today,
I need to be alone.
If I stay with you,
something bad might happen.
You don't scare me anymore.
I'll see you.
Bye.
Hello. Her name is Do Ah.
Hi, Do Ah.
- Careful. - Okay.
I'll see you later. Have fun with your teacher, okay?
If you're worried, you can stay and watch since it's her first day.
No, it's okay. We'll have to do this every day from now on.
So she needs to learn to accept that.
Do Ah, don't cry, and be a good girl, okay?
Look!
Do Ah.
She's having fun without me.
Yes, good. What about this one?
I'm glad she's being a good girl, but I do feel a little sad.
- Move it to the left! - Okay.
Move it a bit more.
It looks nice.
Do you think she's doing okay?
- Pardon? - My daughter, Do Ah.
(Resume)
- Ms. Moon Oh Bin? - Yes.
Gosh, you worked at this hospital for a very long time.
Yes, I had to quit because the doctor...
ended up emigrating abroad.
Oh, dear.
I'm going to work here until the day I die.
So you don't need to worry about retirement.
I see.
But I have a question.
Do I also need to take care of your baby?
I raise my kid with the help of technology.
Ta-da.
My goodness.
So you don't need to take care of her.
And once things settle, I'll have her stay at the daycare center.
I plan to take care of her until then.
She doesn't like saying goodbye, does she?
No, it's not that.
I'm the one who can't seem to adjust.
Pardon?
It's no problem.
Gosh, there are so many things to fill out.
I've never gotten a checkup before.
I also had my first checkup after I started working here.
Are you just going to take the basic test?
No, I'm going to check everything.
Excuse me. Can you help me?
What are the extra tests I can take?
If you look here, you can check your brain, heart,
and there's also a male checkup.
Take a look at the list and check the ones you want to get tested.
- Okay, thank you. - Sure.
- Thank you. - No problem.
You should get everything tested.
- Everything? - But there's too many.
Just do it while you're here.
(Gastroscopy, Carotid ultrasound,)
(Echocardiography, Physical strength...)
- Ms. Jang. - Yes?
Hey, hey!
You're all done.
I bet you didn't know she drew your blood because it hurt too much.
But my cheek hurts as well.
Hey, you punk.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm here, you darn jerk.
You fool.
Stop being such a crybaby.
You darn punk.
Mind your own business.
Sperm donation.
- Eu Ddeum, are you okay? - Sperm donation.
What about sperm donation.
It gives hope to couples...
who can't have babies.
My goodness.
I'm kind of nervous about the checkup.
I hope there's nothing wrong with me.
I know we can't ever be sure about your health,
but I bet you're fine.
You could even swallow a stone and you will still be fine.
Once you get the results, will you let me know...
regardless of how good or bad it is?
I'm just worried. That's all.
Sure. I promise I'll tell you.
- You promise? - Yes, I promise.
Ms. Jang!
Everything is normal. I'm really healthy.
I knew it.
And I have something to brag about.
Even the doctor was shocked. He told me this is very rare.
I have 10 times more than the average man.
What are you talking about?
The number of sperm!
(Choi Kang Eu Ddeum)
10 times? My gosh.
What are you going to do with all that sperm?
I didn't expect this either.
So I don't know.
As you know,
we've been doing some research regarding sperm donation.
Oh, right. Sperm donation.
Exactly.
Should I share it with the boss?
Really?
It's not easy to do if you think about it,
but it's also not that difficult.
Comparing it to blood donation might be a stretch,
but it could be done if it's about helping...
one's wish come true.
The donor will stay anonymous,
so it'll be like doing a good deed in secret.
Still, it's not something...
you should easily decide.
I don't have to be a father to the kid,
so consider it as my good deed.
I'm grateful for the offer,
but think about it some more.
It could become a problem when you get married later on.
You might even date someone...
- when I'm pregnant. - Don't you worry.
I don't know about my future wife,
but I'll seek approval from my parents.
What?
Your parents?
I'll be fathering a kid I won't have custody of.
My parents should know.
Right, I guess they should.
Of course.
They'll be having a grandchild they won't know about.
Then they'll be quite shocked.
Exactly. I shouldn't be a part of the kid's life,
so I should ask if my parents could...
forget about the kid too.
- I'll head back inside then. - Sure.
This won't be easy.
Yes, Auntie.
Wait, hold on. Please calm down first.
Please head to the ER and I'll be right there.
Thanks.
Ms. Shim, Mr. Joo is asking for you.
Got it.
(Dachae Media Sales Report)
Only "The Baby"...
reported a down in sales.
You see, the industry is in recession...
(Hubby: The result for our baby is out.)
- Ms. Shim. - Yes?
Now that you're back from your maternity leave,
I'd like you to focus on your department's sales.
It's been doing the worst for the past three years...
and you've been losing your advertisement deals.
Shouldn't you feel responsible?
The journalists and I have been proposing advertisement deals...
just as much as the Advertising Department.
I didn't even take time off to care for my child longer.
You should...
if you're sure you'll be back.
Child-rearing doesn't end with just three months,
so if you don't come back after taking all that time off,
you'll only be costing the company money.
I know, sir. It's why I didn't take time off...
even though I'm entitled to.
You keep suggesting I shouldn't.
Sir, no matter how hard we work,
we can't do anything about the low birthrate or...
Fine.
Anyway,
we were asked to advertise Mureung City.
"The Baby" should take it.
It was originally meant for "The Deco",
but I'm only giving it to you to boost your sales,
so do a good job on it.
If Mureung City is pleased with the outcome,
all the projects from local governments...
will be turned over to "The Baby".
Mr. Joo, my gosh. You were...
only being hard on us to offer us this deal,
but we were too stupid...
to read into your intentions.
Thank you, sir.
It's why being in this position can get lonely.
Seriously? What are you doing here? Go home and have fun.
I don't feel comfortable doing so.
That's your punishment.
I'd rather have fun here while being uncomfortable.
The City of Mureung has asked us to run an advertisement piece.
You'll take the plane there and gather notes for a day.
Other media outlets will be there,
so make sure you come up with a piece...
that blows the minds of the people of Mureung City.
Who wants to go?
My gosh. I covered 15 stories this month.
Well, I'm going to Gangwon Province...
to run a piece on the wholesale warehouse.
Actually, I'd like to ask what our plans are for...
the readers of our first issue.
Ha Ri is terrified to fly.
Exactly. Besides, how can she go when she's been suspended?
She can't since she's out having fun.
Since I've been suspended, I'll write this piece.
I can't go.
Why not?
I made a drunken mistake in front of Ms. Jang.
No way.
You showed her your cute side?
You idiot!
How can you look Ms. Jang in the eyes now?
The embarrassment might just kill me,
but I'll try and hang in there.
The photos are important for this piece...
so they need an expert photographer,
but I busted my arm.
I can't bring in the money with a busted arm...
which means I can't hire a freelancer.
Unbelievable.
- I'll have to give up the studio. - That's enough.
I can't look Ms. Jang in the eyes anymore.
This is all on you now!
Mr. Nam, the photographer hasn't contacted me yet.
Don't tell me you still haven't hired one.
He'll be there somewhere.
He's your partner, so look around.
What? My partner?
What the...
I found him.
Shall we?
Why didn't you call to say you were joining me?
We could've carpooled.
- Do you want this? - No.
How about buttered squid or beef jerky?
I'm good.
How about we grab a drink afterward?
I like how alcohol makes you cute and sincere.
Can't I do as I please?
Yes.
Correct.
This isn't a vacation, you know.
But it's still a trip.
What's so bad about buying snacks and getting in the mood?
We're even getting on a plane.
Unbelievable. I hate planes.
But we're not going...
on a vacation though.
So you don't want any snacks?
Isn't that a bit too much?
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
We welcome you on our flight.
The flight attendants are here to make sure you have...
- a safe journey. - Are you all right?
I just get nervous before the plane takes off.
I'll be fine once we're in the air.
You're not sick or anything, right?
- I'm good. - Thank you for...
your cooperation and we hope...
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Did Ha Ri not come with you?
Ha Ri went on a business trip to Mureung City with Mr. Han.
To that very far city of Mureung...
alone with Mr. Han, with no other staff members.
They went together.
What are they doing there, that they went...
by themselves?
What a load of crock.
Ladies and gentlemen, the pilot has turned off the seat belt sign.
However, because there may be turbulence,
please keep your seat belts on when you are seated.
When the seat belt light is on,
we will not be serving food and beverages for safety reasons.
- Oh dear. - Oh my gosh.
Are you okay, sir?
Maybe he could be the one...
Is it him?
The bus that I missed.
This always happens.
Especially when I'm late for an important appointment,
the bus won't show up.
If I hop in a cab to save time, we get stuck in traffic,
and the bus I was waiting for...
speeds along in the bus express lane.
If my impatience took control,
and made me miss a destined meeting,
will I...
regret not holding his hand later on?
Why won't this open?
Gosh.
It opened easily.
They made it well. You know...
- Do you want this? - No.
Okay.
Sir.
Thank you.
I was giving you my handkerchief, not my hand.
Yes, handkerchief.
- What? - Hey, Ha Ri.
Should I keep my lab coat on or take it off?
Why are you asking me about you taking clothes off?
- Ask the reporter there. - What?
Both look good?
Stop joking around. You're embarrassing me.
Okay. Should I take the pictures with or without?
Take it off if you want. I don't care.
Gosh.
It's better with it on?
Okay, got it. Work hard.
She says I look good with it on.
Okay.
Gosh.
- Was that Dr. Yoon Jae Young? - Yes.
What is it this time?
Should I sit or stand for the picture?
It would be better standing by the window looking cool. right?
It'll bet better seated at my desk so that my nameplate shows.
Sit for the photo...
and cover your gut.
Sure, got it. Okay. Work hard.
Let's start.
What? Why? What? What?
Should I smile or not?
It's best not smiling, right?
To look serious and professional.
No. Smiling may be better.
This is a local hospital.
So it'll be better to look friendly.
Just shut your trap and take the picture, you punk.
Okay.
I look great both ways? What?
Enough, Ha Ri.
Doctor.
It'll be this big.
(My child whines if I don't let her watch on my smartphone.)
That won't be easy.
Mureung is named that because there are no royal tombs.
In order to hide the location of the kings' graves,
they built fake graves here.
There is a legend that a dragon rose from there.
So the saying goes.
- Take all the pictures you want. - Thank you.
Should I take some that way?
I think it'll look good.
Here.
Excuse me.
- Okay, good. - Good?
Shall we go?
Okay. The official schedule for the day is over.
Feel free to take more pictures.
If you want to hang out more, feel free to do that as well.
Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Ha Ri. Don't you think we need something better for the main shot?
Right? Should we take some pictures of the sunset?
Is Ha Ri not back yet?
She went to Mureung. She'll probably be home late.
- Come eat. - Auntie.
The photographer is a man.
What if something happens while they're alone together?
Like what?
Something frightening.
I wonder if we needed to rent a car just to go take one picture.
You said your pride is on the line.
It'll say, "Photo by Han I Sang."
So my pride is on the line too.
Even if I did refuse to do this,
I've never given less than 100 percent.
I know.
Will we have enough time?
We can make our flight if we rush.
Okay.
How about this for your explanation of Mureung City?
What?
You're the first photographer to takes pictures...
with the article in mind.
It's perfect.
- Should we take a few more? - Okay.
She went there for work. What could possibly happen?
She went on multi-day business trips with men, and nothing happened.
What if something happens this time?
You've heard of incidents like that.
You work like crazy and miss the train.
You look for a place to stay, and there's only one.
Furthermore, they have one vacant room.
I hate these cliche and offensive things...
so much.
Why couldn't she come home just because there's no train?
- Right? - Unless there is a rainstorm...
What?
It looks like rain.
Rain?
They can't go anywhere, and it's raining.
Their clothes are drenched, and they become chilly.
And the boiler at the inn is broken.
They need to be in a situation where they can't help...
but share each other's body temperature.
That's when something will finally happen. You know nothing.
I don't even want to think about it.
Our flight got canceled.
The express bus drivers are on a strike,
and the train tickets are all sold out.
What should we do?
We'll just have to borrow the car for a bit longer.
We can't take the plane home anyway.
Do you think we'll be able to go home?
As long as the road doesn't get blocked due to a landslide,
we'll be able to go home.
Don't worry.
We have breaking news. Due to the heavy rain in the southwest,
a landslide has occurred in Mureung City...
which ended up blocking the nearby coastal road.
The authorities have sent people to urgently clear up the road,
and they announced that it'll take around six hours.
We will update you...
- as soon as we hear more. - She can't be there, right?
- We will move onto the next news. - No way.
How is this even possible?
How can this happen?
It's like someone planned this.
Are you saying I planned this?
You were the one who suggested that we should come here.
I knew something was weird when you insisted on...
renting a car just so we could come all the way here.
I can't believe you used the main cut as bait.
It was a great idea. You totally fooled me.
Will you stop talking nonsense?
Then are you saying I caused the landslide?
No, but you could've seen the weather forecast.
Isn't it more plausible to say you created this scenario?
No, I'm very up to date when it comes to romance.
This kind of stuff doesn't even happen in dramas.
This kind of scenario is for people who are lame...
just like you.
What? "Lame"?
Are you seriously going to blame it on me?
We'll soon find out.
You just wait and see.
We'll end up going to a bed and breakfast...
that's run by an old lady.
(Bed and Breakfast)
Hello?
Is anyone here?
Is this the only place you could find?
You saw the map as well. This was the only bed and breakfast.
Exactly. It's weird that you drove to a place...
where there's only one bed and breakfast.
Is no one here?
Are you here...
to stay the night?
Yes, we're here to stay the night.
I bet she'll say there's only one room left.
There are three rooms.
But do you only need one room?
You can rent an entire annex.
We'll... We'll pay for the annex.
We'll take a room each.
And she'll even use the extra room.
We'll sleep separately...
and make sure we don't even touch.
Do as you wish.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
I guess we need to use that to cook our own rice.
I guess so.
But do you think you can sleep here?
I'll just sleep in the car.
- No, I'll sleep in the car. - Here.
You can change into this.
Okay.
You're so kind.
We'll get changed.
- The phone is turned off. - Ha Ri isn't home yet.
Her phone's turned off as well.
She told me she's low on battery. She can't come home tonight.
She's going to sleep outside?
She's with Mr. Han, isn't she?
Are you going to let your daughter spend the night with a guy?
You should go there and drag her home.
I'm actually glad that my daughter's spending the night with a guy.
What kind of guy is he?
Is he normal? How old is he? Does he have his own house?
Is he diligent?
He doesn't own anything, and he's very old.
On top of that, he looks very scary. He has really dark skin.
He's a weirdo. I don't like him.
Then why don't you marry Ha Ri?
I'm just worried about her like an older brother.
Don't take it out on me.
An older brother, my foot. You were born a month later.
Wait until she comes home. I'll teach that brat a lesson.
The phone doesn't work here.
I Sang, you're like a country boy.
What are you talking about?
People think I'm from abroad. They call me Kevin.
Daniel.
Sure.
Why are you burning firewood?
We have a stove.
It's an induction stove. Is that why you couldn't find it?
We saw an iron cauldron.
I put that there to make the place look nice.
Did you cook rice?
We provide meals for our guests.
We bring it all the way to your room like a hotel room service.
You guys are very old-fashioned.
It's nice and warm.
Here's your coffee.
- Thank you. - No problem.
I've never had coffee in a bowl.
Bowl coffee.
I Sang, how did you end up doing photography?
My dad used to enjoy taking photos.
I used to follow my dad to the photo studio...
every time he went there to get his photos printed out.
Then I'd follow him again once the photos were ready.
I enjoyed doing that.
I guess that's why your photos are always so warm.
Your photos are just like you.
Back in the past, we had to wait...
until the photos came out.
It was exciting to wait for them.
It's just like how I can't wait to find out...
what will happen tomorrow.
I'm more curious about today.
I wonder how we'll end up spending the night together.
It's good, right?
- Are you done washing up? - Yes.
Well, I was just about to wash up myself.
I see.
Do they have hot water?
Yes, lots of it.
Right. Good night then.
- Good night. - You too.
(Mr. Han, are you awake?)
Mr. Han!
What are you doing over there?
What is it?
Just a second.
Why are you whispering?
Wait.
This looks so cool.
Gosh, the wind.
My hair's all over the place.
- What a windy day. - What?
Being a big guy, I'm sure you can block the wind for me...
(The herbal infertility treatment introduced in the first episode...)
(was only fabricated for the purpose of the show.)
(Oh My Baby)
You spend the night with him,
but you're telling me you are in a meeting?
Sorry about that.
Why are you apologizing? It's even more annoying.
You need to be wise when choosing men.
Don't be swooned by what you see on the outside.
- You... - I don't need you to protect me.
I'm 39, not 19.
Shouldn't you explain yourself?
I'll start by saying we live under the same roof.
Being this small should be a crime since it makes you...
snugly fit in my embrace.
How do you think of me as a woman?
What?