It's so windy.
We should go back inside.
Okay.
Was I supposed to kiss him?
No, he turned away.
"Start flirting with other guys..."
"so he'll think it was a joke."
(How to seduce a man if you failed already.)
No, this one doesn't sound right.
"Act like nothing ever happened."
No, I don't think I can do that.
(Jae Young)
(I'm in a meeting.)
(I'm in a meeting. I'll call you back soon.)
"A meeting"?
You can't be back yet, and you're in a meeting?
You spent the night with him, and you say you're in a meeting?
(Give it one more try and hit on him properly.)
"Give it one more try and hit on him properly."
- What? - What?
What? What's the matter?
What? What do you mean? What did I do?
What... I... I'm sorry.
I think I heard something.
I didn't say anything.
Didn't you say you're going to do something properly?
No, I really didn't say anything.
I'm sorry.
Why? Did you do something to upset me?
No... No.
- I'm sorry. - You just apologized again.
Why do you keep apologizing? You're starting to offend me.
- I'm sorry. - Hey!
What?
I think we should just be quiet.
Okay.
You can drop me off over there.
I'll...
I'll drive you to your house.
- It's okay. - No, I'll just get off here.
Hey.
Do you like guys by any chance?
What?
How... Don't I look...
pretty straight?
Well, I just thought you might be single...
because of that.
I totally respect people's different sexual orientations.
Well, I don't like guys.
Okay.
By the way,
I hope my apology...
doesn't end up keeping you awake at night.
Good night.
Oh, my gosh!
Are you crazy? What are you doing there?
What took you so long to come home?
Were you with Mr. Han all day?
I'm tired. Save the nagging for tomorrow.
Why did you spend the night? I thought it was a day trip.
I know, right? I can't believe I spent the night.
You're starting to go a little crazy these days.
Don't tell me you slept with him yesterday.
Maybe I should've.
Are you serious?
Hey.
How do you think of me as a woman?
What?
- Am I unattractive? - No.
You're not unattractive.
Right?
If you flirt with a guy, and he shows no reaction,
he's probably a priest, a monk,
or asexual.
Right.
What's the meaning behind that smile?
You need to be wise when choosing men.
Don't be swooned by what you see on the outside. Okay?
Ha Ri.
What in the world happened between them?
I should've kissed her, right?
I mean, come on.
It wouldn't have been a bad idea to kiss her, right?
No? You think it's wrong?
Forget it.
(Good job!)
(Episode 5: Hard to Hide Our Feelings)
My gosh, go away if you don't want to eat.
Give it back to me right now.
You can't eat bibimbap without a fried egg.
What makes you think you deserve this?
Do you have a death wish?
My gosh, here's another one.
Seeing him eat just made me lose my appetite.
Will you two stop? You're both too old for this.
You make a great couple,
so why won't you get together already?
- Why would I... - Auntie, I'm eating.
- What you said is disgusting. - I might throw up.
Shut it, the both of you.
What are you looking at?
Gosh, the letters are so tiny.
- Can you send a text for me? - Sure.
"Got it."
(Got it.)
Did you send it?
Is your mountaineering club going somewhere?
An overnight trip to the East Sea.
- An overnight trip? - Gosh.
Are you sure you're going as a group?
Who's the mystery guy?
Should I get ready to be shocked?
No, but brace yourself for a smack.
- It hurts. - You should focus...
on your dating life, not mine.
Well, I'm looking for a donor...
who isn't embarrassed.
You failed to find an ordinary guy to marry,
so I doubt the search will get you anywhere.
Mom, don't forget to buy squid!
Do you know when voters show the most hostility to politicians?
What are you getting at?
It's when they don't live up to their promises.
They shouldn't promise a better economy...
and receive bribes to fill their own pockets.
So?
Keep that in mind.
You're searching for a sperm donor, not a husband.
I'm fully supportive of you,
so don't go back on your promise, Ha Ri.
Just get back to your meal.
Sure. Why not?
Eat quietly.
This is the quietest I've ever been while eating.
You're so annoying.
So when you called Ha Ri the other day,
she said she couldn't come home because of a landslide?
I saw the expenses report she handed in earlier...
and she booked herself a room.
- Then they slept together. - Many babies are conceived...
during big events, right?
- Think of the 2002 World Cup. - My gosh!
Hold on. Are you older than I am?
I read it in a news article.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
- Hold on. - How should we greet her?
Goodness.
A sudden overnight trip is also...
how I got married.
Was there something going on between them?
Who cares when Mother Nature gave them a nudge?
Only idiots would've passed up on that chance.
- Hi, Ha Ri. - Hi.
You seem to be in a good mood.
What? That's ridiculous.
But you're glowing today.
Don't be silly. So how's the special feature coming along?
You have no idea how busy I've been.
Well, I wish you luck.
Bye.
Right? Of course she can't help but smile.
The world must be in different shades of pink to her.
How about pink bed sheets as a wedding gift?
Wouldn't money be better?
Have we already sent her down the aisle?
It might be better to throw her a baby shower.
- Gosh! - You're right.
- What's going on? - Why the sudden mood change?
My gosh.
Did it not happen?
Is it true that she never had luck with blind dates?
She's only good at fending them off.
No way. I bet she was only swept up in sad thoughts.
She hasn't dated for 10 years,
so she no longer knows how to be in the mood.
It's the same with I Sang.
He only had one long-term girlfriend...
which means he has zero dating experience.
He's a sap in that department.
What did we even expect?
("The Joy of Living Alone")
What? No.
Stop it.
This is wrong.
Ms. Jang.
Unbelievable.
You're even stopping yourself from daydreaming?
Now I'm seeing things.
Exactly. This is what happens when you're sexually frustrated.
I'm only telling you this because it's all in my head.
This is me doing my utmost best to hold back.
Why are you holding back though? I'm 39, not 19.
There's no need to be a gentleman.
We're both adults,
so an R-rated scene won't be a problem.
I'm being this way because of our age.
We should meet someone
we want to spend the rest of our lives with,
not someone we want to enjoy a heated night with.
Can't you see that I've been...
making room for you in my heart?
If I finally come around to kiss you,
then I'll never let you go.
You're being awfully dramatic for a simple kiss.
By the way, where's your bedroom? What a nice house.
My bedroom?
Where are you off to?
- Here? - Ms. Jang?
What a nice house.
Wait. You can't do this to me.
You...
What on earth was that?
Am I really sexually frustrated?
What's wrong with me?
- Hyo Joo. - Yes?
Weren't you supposed to take photos of the cooking process?
The instructions seemed easy, so I thought I'd write them down.
Young moms don't know how finely they should chop up the ingredients.
The ingredient's size differs depending on the children's age,
so how can we not show pictures?
The dishes are styled beautifully.
Photos of the cooking process will only ruin the aesthetic.
Do you think I'm glaring at you to hear your excuses?
I'll have the photos taken.
Make sure you have the Advertising Department...
confirm the expiration date on the toothpaste.
They won't bother if you don't remind them.
Shouldn't she be grateful by the fact...
that someone as beautiful as me...
- is working here? - What...
Ms. Choi!
Are you off to lunch? I'm just coming back from work outside.
Is something up?
You seem upset.
Did you get an earful?
What on earth are you talking about?
I guess you didn't.
But that's what your expression told me.
Mr. Choi Kang,
could you please mind your own business?
When one doesn't answer you,
it means that he or she doesn't want to talk.
Sorry about that. I don't take hints well, do I?
You really don't.
You're awful at taking hints!
Let's just stick to polite greetings, okay?
Sure thing. I will from now on.
I'll get going then since I'm only making you uncomfortable.
What an idiot.
Are you kidding me?
Gosh, it hurts.
Let's just stick to polite greetings, okay?
Good luck.
He left without helping?
Get out of there!
My gosh.
Unbelievable.
As if this would kill my vibe.
Why is it so dark in here?
I mean...
What's going on? Are you sick?
I see her when my eyes are open...
and when they're closed.
This is killing me.
What's wrong? Are you having hallucinations?
What's the problem?
Is it here or here?
I can't tell if it's my mind or heart...
that's hurting.
All I know is that it hurts.
There's a song called "A Disease Called Love".
I especially like Part Two.
Why are you here?
I'm swamped with photoshoots today.
Ms. Jang has an important one which involves...
an infertile couple.
Could you...
perhaps take the job?
You've got to be kidding me.
Why? In case it'll hurt more?
Hey.
Get dressed.
Come on.
Do this shoot for me.
A picture of the product and one for a review.
Why should I?
It's an excuse to go to the studio.
Mr. Han is there.
Mr. Nam went to the hospital and is out.
Stop that.
Listen. If something happened,
you need to go with it and make it something more.
Don't jump to conclusions, and don't give me advice.
Just drink your watermelon juice.
Did you hold hands?
- We did not. - You put the moves on though.
I did not.
You did send him clear signs, right?
Why are you guys so interested in my love life?
It's fun.
You're bored, right? You don't have enough work, do you?
I'm sorry.
Go. Get to work.
Stop it.
It's a hallucination.
Don't fall apart. No.
What are you doing?
Seriously. Again?
Are you back?
Okay. Hi.
You're copying me now, too?
What?
I actually felt something. Are you a human?
Look. I've been saying hi.
Do you feel sick?
Okay. Let's go in.
Snap out of it.
"Signals that are 100 percent effective."
(Rest your head on his shoulder and tilt it 45 degrees)
"Rest your head on his shoulder and tilt it 45 degrees."
"Pucker your lips toward his face."
Mr. Han, can we chat?
Okay.
I'm not sure at which angle we should take this.
We should look at it thoroughly.
I think we can just take it.
Right? We can just take it.
I'm sleepy.
You're sleepy?
Yes.
I'll take the pictures. Take a nap.
What?
Where did my camera go? Here it is.
Nice, everyone's gone!
Awesome.
Goodness.
What's this?
I hope your feet will be comfortable in these.
This is seriously so nasty.
Where did he even find this?
This is Cucci, not Gucci.
Do you not like it?
Can't you tell what my style is?
They had Brada too. I should've gotten those.
You really are amazing, Mr. Choi Kang.
You're too kind.
Wear these for now.
I'll get you Brada and Ballemciaga next time.
It's 2 for 10 dollars.
It's fine. Don't bother.
I'm happy with these.
Do you mean it?
These are very durable.
Stop talking.
That looks super fancy.
I make even these look good.
I guess designer goods make the person look classy.
They look great on you.
Wear them for a long, long time. I'll go now.
Have a nice day.
A long, long time.
What is he yapping about after buying me knock-offs?
My gosh. How cheap. They're not Gucci, they're Gucheap.
These are so nice.
It's like they were made for me.
Are you doing the shoot?
The schedule was posted. Did you miss it because you were sleeping?
I did not.
This project receives attention nationwide,
so it'll be good for your career as well.
You sound so sweet. Is it because you slept so well?
I did not sleep well.
I worked hard on this series. I wish you'd keep working on it.
No.
Once his files come out, I hope you stick to this project with Soo Chul.
Okay.
Get in.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
How do you feel?
I thought I'd be okay since it's our second,
but I'm twice as nervous.
I can totally understand.
- Come in. - Okay.
Okay.
We'll film the consultation...
as well as the steps afterward.
(Fertility Clinic)
Hello.
Okay.
You've done it before, so you know you need to relax, right?
Yes.
Many people get fertility treatments,
so don't think it's only you.
Think of it as a special way to meet your child.
Okay.
Do you have any questions?
Are there any medications she should avoid?
Vitamins are fine.
You have to consult me first before taking anything else.
Are you taking anything now?
I'm only taking lactobacillus at the moment.
That's fine.
Give her a lot of help.
I will.
Please tell me if there's anything I should do for her.
Just be supportive.
I really hope it works this time.
Must they work so hard and force it?
You have to sacrifice so much...
for a being that doesn't exist.
Look over there.
How could they make a face like that?
When you look at a mom looking at her baby,
isn't it amazing?
Just how must a person love another person...
to make a face like that?
How can a person...
give another person unconditional love...
without wanting anything in return?
I feel like having someone to love like that in itself...
would set me free from being lonely.
Is that why women always choose the baby...
if they had to choose...
between the person they love or their baby?
I won't let go...
of the person I love.
I know that having a baby is a miracle.
But I haven't fallen in love for the past 10 years,
so love is also a miracle to me.
I brought you some popular baby stuff...
for you and Do Ah.
Babies have sensitive skin, so it's important to wash them...
with filtered and clean water.
You're also starting a new life,
so wash yourself properly and become a new person.
Use it well.
And you just need to take a photo to prove that you're using it well.
No, I don't feel any sincerity in what you're saying right now.
You'll realize that I'm sincere once you see all the baby stuff...
that I'll be bringing from now on.
Really? Then let me see that.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you giving it to me? All I did was grab it.
Look how hard you're holding onto it.
Fine. Let's just stay like this all night.
I just changed the showerhead.
And I did it in one go.
I see.
You're turning 40 soon, but you're still so tiny.
I can hug you with just one arm. What's the matter with you?
You should exercise your shoulders and increase your strength.
What do you want? Do you want me to beat you up?
How about I beat you up tonight?
Do Ah, it's time for a bath.
It's warm, isn't it?
My sweetheart.
What are you doing? What's with your face?
I'm trying to look natural as I wash my kid.
Just be yourself. Don't look at the camera.
Do Ah, cover your ears.
I never washed her with her mom, so this is new to me.
I'm just saying.
I was just talking about the situation.
It was just the theme of the shoot.
I'm done taking photos.
I may not be her mom,
but I take care of her like an aunt.
Actually, that's what I am. I'm her aunt.
You're not her aunt. You're just a stranger.
My gosh, don't be so coldhearted.
We're not strangers.
Then what are we?
We're not a family. We're not married.
We're pretty much a family.
Right, Do Ah?
Come here and help me wash her. Hurry up and sit down.
Here. You told me this is good.
(Bareun Hospital)
(The Baby Jang Ha Ri)
- Hello, Ms. Shim. - Hey, Ha Ri.
The babysitter called and said she can't make it today,
so I have to stay with my baby today.
Is your baby okay?
She just needs to take a few tests at the hospital.
Tell them that I'll send them the report soon.
Can you just check the manuscript that needs to be sent today?
Okay, sure.
Oh, dear.
Hey, Jae Yi.
It's okay. I'll hold you.
There, there.
Just a second. I need to get some work done.
(The Baby Booklet Plan: May, Children's Day)
It's okay.
(Do Yeon's Daycare Center)
Hello, ma'am.
Did I not pack Do Yeon's blanket?
I'm sorry. Right now, I'm with her sister at the hospital.
What should I do? There's no one I can send to fetch her blanket.
Yes, can you just cover her with that?
Okay, thank you. Bye.
Jae Yi.
It's okay.
I can do this alone.
We're at the hospital.
You're okay now.
Ms. Shim.
Did Ms. Shim go home?
She took the day off.
Why do you keep coming to the office?
Do you think your suspension is a joke?
No, sir.
Tell Ms. Shim to send me the content management report.
You heard him, right? I need to disappear now.
So hurry up and finish the manuscript.
- Okay. - I'm off to the studio.
Hello?
Ha Ri is late.
Who keeps sending me text messages?
What?
(Hey, isn't this your friend?)
Stay still. My goodness.
Okay, good job.
His lungs sound fine.
I'll prescribe three days' worth of medicine for his cold,
so come back after he takes them.
- Okay. - You're all done.
- I'm going to jump on the bed. - Can you check him too?
He's also going to catch a cold soon.
He needs to show symptoms.
- Go on. - I want to go!
Hey! Don't cause trouble.
Then prescribe medicine for both of them with no charge.
Do you think this is a supermarket?
You talk as if I'm holding a buy 1 and get 1 free event.
I need two for everything.
Can't you do this for a friend?
You told me you didn't want to be my friend.
Think about what you did.
You cut all ties with us after you got married.
It's not easy to bring my kids to a hospital.
Just do me a favor.
What's your number? Let me introduce you to a psychiatrist.
You're showing severe symptoms.
What's your phone number?
I'll report you for refusing to treat your patient.
(The Shocking Sperm Lady)
What's this?
Isn't this Ha Ri?
What? "Ha Ri"?
(The Shocking Sperm Lady)
This is Ha Ri.
Hello, this is the Editing Department for The Baby.
It's her personal life, so we don't know.
It has nothing to do with our magazine,
so you don't need to worry.
No, I don't know anything about it.
Hello, this is the Editing Department for The Baby.
What? What lady? No, she's not here.
Yes, hello. No, I don't know who told you that.
But it's not true. Don't worry.
Hello, this is the Editing Department for The Baby.
I'm sorry. I have nothing to tell you. Sorry.
Gosh, I can't believe this!
Hasn't anyone heard from Ha Ri?
Hello, this is the Editing Department for The Baby.
- The receiver cannot be reached... - My goodness.
She won't pick up.
I have to tell her to not answer any phone calls from journalists.
Where in the world is she? People are saying crazy things.
I can't believe her personal information got leaked.
My goodness.
My gosh, I can't believe this.
Hey, where...
Ha Ri, what's going on?
I turned in the posts online as evidence...
and asked for them to be removed.
Good thinking. I contacted some people too...
and asked them to delete your personal information...
and hate comments that were posted online.
But Ha Ri... Ha Ri?
Ha Ri?
Are you all right though? Are you okay?
Sorry about that. What did you say you did?
Don't be intimidated, okay?
I warned those who wrote hate comments.
If they keep this up, I'll cut off their fingers myself.
How dare they speak ill of you.
Don't be like that to strangers.
Ha Ri, don't worry too much.
Right.
Thanks for everything. I'll call you back. Sorry.
- Ms. Jang... - What the...
Mr. Choi Kang? What...
What's going on?
(Noodles)
Everyone was worried...
because they couldn't get in touch with Ms. Jang.
I asked HR for her address...
and was headed there to see her.
I was just walking by. I live around here, you see.
This is your fault for not answering your phone.
It was ringing like crazy, so I needed a break.
Did you file a report with the police?
Yes, but it's not just...
my personal information that's the issue.
They know where I work now too.
Don't read any of the online comments, okay?
I don't why they're saying these awful things.
That's not who you are.
Sperm Lady, also known as, gold-digger, right?
They're also saying things about my name too.
For the first time in my 39 years, I learned that my name...
has sexual innuendo.
Don't read your emails or messages you receive on social media.
Also, take time off work and get some rest.
You should. That sounds like a plan.
It'll blow over when a new scandal breaks out.
People only see what I did wrong.
But all I wanted was to become a mom.
Ms. Jang.
Let me know if you need any help.
- Sure. - What kind of help...
can a colleague give her?
You should let your roommate know.
The roommate should stick to issues around the house...
and leave work-related problems to her colleagues.
That's me then. I'm your colleague, right?
So you're drawing the line...
and saying that you're only colleagues. Right?
Actually, we've always been colleagues.
It seems like you need to clear the air...
in regard to who you are to her as well.
I'm the person who lives with her.
I told you that numerous times, so what else should I say?
- Unbelievable. - Gosh.
It's been a while since we got together so...
- How much is it? - 53 dollars.
No, don't.
- I'll buy. - Save it.
- But I said I'd buy. - It's okay.
- It's all right. - Let us pick up the bill...
and wait for us outside.
- Here. - Here.
I don't know if it's cute or childish.
It's okay. Let me pay for today.
- Let me. - No, let me.
- Take it back. - Here you go.
You're starting to upset me. Let me pay for this.
Why would you though?
Is there a reason why I can't? Here's my card.
I don't let those younger treat me to meals.
What?
I'm probably richer than you are.
Wait. Well,
I didn't want to say this,
but the unit I live in looks over the Han River.
What?
Well, I'm a doctor...
which means I have the potential to end up richer than you.
- Then. - Let me buy instead.
It's only 53 dollars. Here.
You're right, it's her.
See?
- Right? - You're right.
- Then... - Hush!
Sperm Lady!
Don't be like that.
You're the Sperm Lady, right?
Stop it.
What did I tell you?
I told you that it was her.
Gosh.
You're way prettier in person though.
You have the wrong person.
Hold on a second.
You need a guy, right?
Let go of me if you want to go home to your wife in one piece.
Look at her playing hard to get. How adorable!
Just so you know, my sperms conceived triplets.
So put your faith in me...
and join me for a glass of wine.
Get your filthy hands off me!
Harassing someone isn't something to be proud of.
Humiliating a person is an act of violence too.
How dare you.
Who do you think you are?
Why are you making me feel ashamed of my good intentions?
- Why? - Thanks for the meal.
Ha Ri?
I don't need the receipt.
What's wrong?
Who do you think you are?
What's the meaning of this?
Who are you people?
Why on earth is she in tears?
Must we even ask? She's in tears for crying out loud.
- What did you do to her? - Look here, guys.
Anyone can tell that I'm the victim here.
She hit me with her purse.
- Let's call the cops. - Yes, let's call the cops.
Call the cops! That crazy cow will be buried deep...
- once I'm through with her. - Hey!
Fine. Call the cops. I'll make sure you're buried too.
- Should we call the cops? - Hold on a second.
What did you call her?
"A crazy cow"?
Say it again.
I dare you to say it again.
Unbelievable!
Guys, just think about this for a second.
We saw her photo online.
It's all over the Internet!
It's just there for everyone to see.
We saw her photo online...
and just acknowledged that we recognized her.
But she got all crazy.
She kicked me...
and hit me with her purse.
That crazy Sperm Lady...
Please don't.
Let's just go.
Mr. Han, don't.
He's not worth it.
Don't be upset over what those mindless jerks said.
You did nothing wrong.
He's right.
You didn't have to walk me all the way home.
We felt bad, so we wanted to.
That's right.
Besides, I was able to flex my muscles thanks to you.
What a waste.
I wanted to show off my intellect.
I lost my chance.
Ms. Jang.
Look at this.
That guy from earlier. Should we report him?
Show them.
Were you an art major?
- You're good. - You really are.
If you make me laugh like this, I'll shake it off and sleep well.
Thank you. I mean it.
Get home safely.
- Good night. - Thank you both.
- I mean it. - Good night.
- What? - Keep walking.
- Why are you following me? - The front door will wake Do Ah.
- Open it carefully then. - I'll go through your place.
Seriously?
Get out of my way.
They really do live together.
Are they together?
I'm sure they're just friends.
Ms. Jang looked so frail today.
I'll have to protect her more going forward.
Shall we go?
Open up.
It's urgent.
Ha Ri! Hurry!
Ta-da.
When I'm sad, I read comic books.
Yes?
Should I post something saying you're not like that?
It's okay.
That won't make anyone understand me.
I'm financially stable,
and I know I can raise a baby well.
But there's no way to have a baby unless I get married.
But I don't have a man or the confidence...
to get married.
How many people would understand if I say that's why I did it?
It would be hard even 40 years from now.
Don't blame yourself.
Whatever the reason was, no one has the right...
to share your identity or judge you.
No one.
This let me see who's really on my side.
So it's fine.
Me?
That's right.
Oh no.
Oh no. Do Ah.
Were you scared because you were alone?
Is that right, Do Ah?
Don't cry. It's okay.
It's okay.
Goodness. You were scared because you were all alone.
- Goodness. - Ha Ri.
Do you want to marry me?
Ha Ri.
Listen. If you want a babysitter, pay for one.
It's hard to get sperm.
Why don't you just raise Do Ah as your own?
Don't look at me like that.
There's an easy path before you. Why take a detour?
It's easy for you.
I don't need a man.
Am I a man?
Then what? Are you a woman?
A Miss? Ms. Jae Young?
We'll stop for a picture.
- Okay. - Come quickly.
- Look here. - Come this way.
- Okay. - It's so nice.
This is the spot.
- It's nice out. - Okay.
- Ready? - Yes!
1, 2, 3.
- Cheese. - One more time.
Cheese!
Okay. Good.
It's so nice out.
- Hey. - Yes?
Your daughter's name is Jang Ha Ri, right? And she works for a magazine.
Why do you ask?
My daughter tells me...
your daughter is all over the Internet.
If you type in her name, her articles will show up.
That's true for all reporters. She isn't famous.
No. I hear your daughter is famous.
What was it?
"Sperm Lady"?
She should find a man, not buy sperm.
Is something wrong with her?
What did I tell you?
I told you to make her quit when she said...
she was too busy as a journalist to date.
She couldn't get married yet at her age.
She may not have a record, but she's a criminal.
Gosh. That poor thing.
She'll never get married.
Are you out of your mind? Whom are you calling a criminal?
Who are you to call my daughter a criminal?
What's wrong with you?
- Hey! - Separate them!
- Separate them! Goodness! - What's going on?
I'm losing my mind.
Hey.
What? You can't go in?
Mr. Joo called me in at this hour.
It can't be out of consideration so people don't see me.
It means it's very serious.
I'm a bit scared.
I can't go in for you.
But I'll show you this.
Want to see? Ta-da.
How's that for the main photo?
You're so dependable.
I may be scolded today, but I'll be praised later on.
I wanted to develop the photos with you.
Next time.
Next time, let's go together for sure.
Okay.
Next time.
Sperm Lady.
The chairman wants an apology.
The chairman is very concerned because of the complaints...
from readers.
Publish an apology...
in lieu of the editor's column.
What...
She's the victim. Why should she apologize?
This got out of hand.
She should explain and apologize...
to the readers.
This is her personal matter.
I'm against it becoming public as a magazine matter.
I won't waste a precious page for a flimsy apology.
It's not a flimsy apology!
She should apologize sincerely and calm the readers down.
Why are you so dense?
So... I... I know...
I was wrong.
I know I disappointed the readers.
I'm very sorry for hurting the magazine's credibility...
and hurting the company.
However,
do you really think my apology will make the readers...
read our magazine again?
I'll take responsibility for what happened.
How?
First of all, I'll ask our readers to understand my situation.
"Understand"?
Ms. Jang.
This isn't a piece of advice. It's an order.
I want you to stop our readers from complaining so much!
We're not getting any advertisements because of you.
If there's a decrease in sales,
will I get suspended again?
No.
This time, you'll get fired.
What should I do?
Why are you asking me? It's not my responsibility.
Hurry up and decide. Are you going to write a column or not?
I could get fired. Give me some time to think.
I need to help my husband take care of the children. Go home.
Okay.
Don't trust Mr. Joo.
He's a jerk, too.
Hey, honey.
Did her fever go down, honey?
I know, honey.
I love you, honey.
Hello? We don't know the details.
Okay, bye. Sorry.
Just block them from leaving comments on our website.
That's impossible.
Most people are just calling to curse at us.
Gosh, why do I need to hear them curse at me?
We should sue them for slander.
Let's start by suing them for obstruction of business.
I can't do any work because of them.
That's a great excuse to quit.
Not enough to actually make me quit.
That's a pity.
I'm going to go home now. Don't overwork yourselves already.
And...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you take care of my mess.
I told you that I'm your future, but I take it back.
I don't want any of you to go through this.
Forget it. Just buy us some food before you go.
I'll buy you something nice.
(Letter of Apology)
Hey, Mom.
Mom, what happened to your hair? You said you'll be back tomorrow.
You brat!
Why did you ask me to buy you squid? You're only going to drink more!
Do you know how hard it was to...
I fell while trying to buy that.
Sorry.
Don't let yourself feel small just because I'm angry at you.
And don't blame yourself or feel like you made a mistake...
just because people badmouth you.
I know very well that you did nothing wrong.
(Dachae Media)
Ms. Jang.
Did you write an apology? Today's the due date.
Ms. Jang, just write an apology.
Our clients are really angry.
They might withdraw their ads starting from next month.
If I publish an apology, will they change their minds?
It's important to take action.
We need to show them that we're sorry and that we'll do well...
and that they can trust us.
That's the only way I'll be able to convince them.
Just do what's best for everyone.
Mr. Kim, I don't think my apology will solve everything.
If I admit that I made a mistake, they'll use that to withdraw the ad.
I'm not doing this to save my pride.
Do you at least have a solution to this?
Yes.
I have endometriosis.
My ovaries are 40 years old.
And the possibility for me to get naturally pregnant...
is less than seven percent.
I'm subfertile.
That's ours, right? Let me take that.
Thank you.
(Am I not allowed to have a baby without getting married?)
I'm subfertile.
I'm 39 years old.
And I'm single.
My love for babies...
prevents me from quitting my job at a baby magazine company.
That's the kind of person I am.
As I'm about to turn 40,
I found myself at a crossroad where I might have to give up...
on getting married and pregnant.
And that really made me want to have a baby.
My doctor told me that I should get pregnant within six months.
And it felt like that was how much time I had left to live.
Growing up, I was always an obedient student.
So I chose to listen to my doctor.
If you ask me why I'm taking things this far to have a baby,
I honestly don't know what to say.
I just like babies,
and I want to become a mom.
How else can I explain that?
I don't know...
what's right and wrong.
I just think my efforts...
will become a process to find the right answer.
(I'd like to share my story with you...)
I'd like to share my story with you...
every month...
(I'd like to share my story with you every month...)
and find the answer to this together.
(and find the answer to this together.)
(Am I not allowed to have a baby without getting married?)
Am I not allowed...
to have a baby without getting married?
(Dr. Moon, Urology)
What brings you here, Mr. Han?
Well...
Is there a way for me...
to have a baby?
(Oh My Baby)
It's me you want, right?
- I'll give you mine. - What?
I want to be good for you.
- Did you sleep with him? - Don't be ridiculous.
I thought about it...
while factoring in our friendship of 39 years.
There's no reason for me to deny your last wish.
I'll marry you.
Of course not.
I had no idea my heart would ache this much for you.
Ms. Jang, consider this...
as a stamp.
Good job.