(Jambi Studio)
Just a second.
How long do we need to do this? I'm getting cramps on my face.
Don't look her way.
The look in her eyes is telling me...
that a crazy idea is forming inside her head.
Acknowledge her now, and you'll be in trouble.
Why? Why will we be in trouble?
There's no safe zone around Jang Ha Ri.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm a bit scared.
Since you think you're fine, why don't you deal with her?
Is that really necessary?
I should leave before she talks to me.
Okay, we'll start shooting now.
Loosen up. Bring your shoulders down.
Put your chin down. Look into the camera lens.
1, 2, 3. Let's see you smile.
One more time.
Yoon Jae Young.
He may sound rough, but he has a nice personality.
If my baby takes after him, it'll be smart.
No.
He's too much like a brother.
Han I Sang.
He seems to have a bad personality,
but he's sometimes kind as well.
I like his curiosity and how challenging he is.
No, I won't be able to tell him.
Choi Kang Eu Ddeum.
What is his deal?
- Great work. - You did great.
- Good work. - Great work.
- Thank you. - See you guys.
What?
You're going?
She just left.
- You did great. - You too.
Where are you three going?
I need to go home and take care of Do Ah.
Your mom's probably having a hard time.
I'm going to tell Mr. Kim that the shoot went well.
I need to go to a shoot after lunch. Do you have something to say?
Let me buy you lunch.
That's great. You guys can eat together.
- He's right. - Enjoy.
Where are you going?
My mom's free all afternoon.
What's the matter with you?
She can't watch Do Ah all day. She'll be exhausted.
Then don't make her cook for you. Eat lunch with me.
She's right. The three of you can chat...
and have fun together.
Eu Ddeum, you should come with us.
Mr. Kim left to meet a client.
He's probably back by now.
This morning, I heard him say very loudly...
that he has a lunch meeting with a client.
- Eu Ddeum. - Yes?
I have a lunch meeting with a client.
I'll be back pretty late.
Sorry. What?
I'm going to be back...
after lunch.
I'm going to have lunch outside.
I'll be back late.
Let's go.
Come on.
Brace yourselves. We'll be okay.
What's going on? Are you picking your future husband?
Let me see.
I choose...
I'll send you a text.
Good luck.
Why isn't anyone sitting beside me?
Right now, we're on the same side.
Why did you suddenly want to eat with us?
I just figured we should be friends.
The three of you got to know each other,
so I think we should take that friendship to another level.
I guess we were scared for nothing.
We became close because we were all scared of you.
You're pretty fearless.
It's because he's young. He doesn't know what's coming.
Am I scary?
Look in the mirror and see your eyes. They're very scary.
Well...
Now that I've aged, I realize that friends are precious.
Let's get together often like this, get close,
and check on each other's health status.
- That being said, Eu Ddeum... - Yes?
You seem quite healthy to me.
Does it run in the family?
I doubt your family has had any medical issues.
No one in my family has been sick.
I see.
Meanwhile, my body isn't what it used to be.
They say your body starts to power down...
the moment you hit that 40 mark.
That must be what's happening to me. I ache here and there. Right?
That's not the case for me.
- No underlying illnesses? - No.
I see. That's good.
We're at an age where health is a touchy subject for us.
Hangovers aren't cured until the next evening...
and it takes two days to recover from an all-nighter.
So before we're hit with something bad,
we should check our health at least twice a day.
The doctor in me says that you have a liver problem.
You can't have a part of mine though.
It has hardened from all the liquor.
You're out.
Nice!
You two seem like real siblings.
How long have you been friends?
Unfortunately, since in utero.
Our moms were friends.
No wonder you two are like elementary school kids.
You're a polite one, aren't you?
You just bad-mouthed us while holding a smile.
I thought you were cousins.
His aunt's daughter.
You thought we were cousins?
I'm her friend. Her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend? Is he your boyfriend?
No, a friend who's a boy. Don't mix those two up.
Then why do you live together?
- Well, he's putting us out... - Who says we can't?
Especially when...
we're this close?
Yes, you're close enough to be smacked.
Goodness.
Anyway, it's nice to finally get to know you better.
Let's keep this up and gradually get to know each other...
even more.
Sounds good.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Cheers, everyone.
All right. Here you go.
(Episode 4: The Time One Needs to Understand Others)
Stop right there.
Follow me.
Get back here!
I'm sorry.
I know it's something to be frowned upon.
Didn't you know that?
I didn't think I'd get caught.
I understand how it can be frowned upon,
but I don't think what I did was that wrong.
Why should one's marital status make one's decision ethical?
Am I supposed to engage in a debate?
It's easy for everyone to accept how a married couple...
would want a baby.
What many can't accept is considered crazy.
Am I a crazy cow then?
Don't be too shocked by it.
I never once thought you were in your right mind anyway.
That's actually quite comforting.
If you're going to set off a bomb,
make sure the explosion's big.
Are you siding with me?
No. Let's just put it as me understanding how desperate you are.
Just make sure you deal with the mess yourself.
I doubt any harm was done.
Only our people would recognize me anyway.
Exactly. We all recognized you.
- It's her, right? - Yes.
So it's gossip over colleagues.
Ha Ri.
Please enjoy.
Is it true?
- What are people saying? - That it's not your first time...
and that it's how you got pregnant with your first child.
- Did I have a son or daughter? - Daughter.
- Who does she take after? - She's a miniature version of you.
Then she'll be cute.
Hold on. That I didn't hear.
Anyway, I hope that this unknown child of mine...
lives a great life without her mother.
You're going to let people say...
that you abandoned your child?
I can't believe she isn't taking this seriously.
Gosh.
If I don't get married?
If you're gone?
Should I live just for myself?
You say you live for me.
Should I live alone without any family,
living just for myself, and then die alone?
But you'll be too lonely.
When you're old, everything is upsetting.
If you have no one,
who will take care of you when you're sick?
Auntie, are you drinking?
- You shouldn't. - Shut it...
and get over here.
Jae Young.
What do you think of Ha Ri?
Mom. Can I call you that instead of Auntie?
You seem more like my mom these days.
What are you getting at?
Ha Ri and I have been friends since birth.
We're already family.
And all I want to do is make it official on paper.
Why won't you see Ha Ri as a woman?
She's pretty, kind, humorous,
and charming.
It's hard not to be attracted to her.
I know.
Of course I'm aware that Ha Ri's a catch.
It's why I'm not the man for her.
Come on.
Why would you want her to be with a single father?
She should marry someone...
who is better than me.
Of course she should.
Darn, it hurts.
My gosh!
It hurts.
Seriously?
Here.
Let's go.
We live together.
Then why do you live together?
- Well, he's putting us out... - Who says we can't?
Especially when...
we're this close?
How does this make any sense?
A man and a woman who has a close relationship...
are living in the same house?
Answer me.
Why won't you say anything?
Whatever. Forget about it.
Unbelievable.
You prepared a feast.
Anyway, thank you.
Everything smells nice.
- Do you want soup? - Yes.
Gosh, it looks delicious.
It sure does.
I'm not saying that I won't ever get married.
But realistically speaking, it's too hard to find anyone.
There aren't any decent guys around me.
I'm at an age where pregnancy is more urgent...
Mom, I...
Just how dense are you?
Come on.
Grandma's already upset as it is.
What are you doing by adding fuel to the flame?
Use your common sense, Mom.
There's no way I'd choose you.
- What do you mean? - Nothing.
What did you just mean?
Just get back to your meal.
I should eat.
(Jambi Studio)
Please put the kids in front.
- Gather round. - Okay.
- Look here, kids. - Look here.
- Look here. Okay. - Right here.
How cute.
Where did you find them?
They look just like each other.
With a little creative liberty, they're the genius father and son,
athletic father and son, and artistic mother and daughter.
He looks normal enough.
He's handsome.
He has a sharp nose and nice jawline.
And fair skin.
I hear he's Ha Ri's friend.
Yes. They've been friends since they were babies.
They grew apart when he got married, but they got close again recently.
He's married?
He adored his wife so very much,
that he was so very annoying from what I heard.
He got divorced and moved into her house with his baby.
- He has a baby? - Exactly.
He even has a baby.
He's perfect for her.
He's a doctor. They know everything about each other.
And he has a baby.
He's dangerous.
What?
He looks like a total con artist.
Look at him being jealous. You've been made.
When you feel anxious, you tend to make bad moves.
I'm saying this in case you date any guy because you want a baby.
What? Why?
Do you think I'll be immature and fall for a bad guy...
and hop on the express train to suffering?
No. You seem to be in a rush to get married and have a baby.
Feel free to make mistakes on me, though.
Whether or not I date a loser, it's none of your business.
Why would you date a loser?
Are you the type who gets love goggles?
Yes, I can't think straight.
All I see is love.
And once I decide against a guy, I never look back,
so don't worry.
- I'm getting dizzy. - Why?
It's so hard to carry on a conversation.
I need a sugar kick.
- My blood sugar level must be low. - What...
What's his problem?
- How about a punch with a "Yap"? - Yap.
Good.
Like this.
Hold on.
Mommy, I'm so hungry, I can't take it.
Can't I have a hot dog?
He's uncomfortable.
Next Wednesday is the anniversary of Father's passing.
Come. Mother's waiting.
Is it Paris this time?
Father gets to tour the world thanks to you.
Hey. Hey. Wait.
Your father drinks water...
before he eats.
- Here. Try this too. - Okay.
- You eat. - Eat up.
Anyway, aren't you going to have a housewarming party?
Set a date. Just the adults can come.
- What? - I Sang.
Our kids are well-behaved.
I have a baby at my place.
What? A baby?
Are you living with her?
No, Mother.
He means a statue made out of stone.
Stone?
Why are you living with a stone?
I bought it recently from Easter Island.
It's precious to me.
They say if you get attached to pets and figurines,
you won't get married.
That's not good.
Do you want to meet a manager from our company?
She's a successful single woman.
It's time to meet someone new.
No, I'm not very social.
Mother can't sleep well because she's worried about you.
How long will you act like a loser and act like...
you're the biggest victim in the world?
Hey. Hey. Don't.
- I'm done. - Hey.
You're not done eating.
- Hey. Hey. - Honey.
That kid.
Uncle. Aren't you marrying In Ah?
Byul, do you still remember In Ah?
In Ah bought me an Elsa dress.
Oh my gosh.
You're so smart. My gosh.
You must be happy that Byul is so smart.
We went to see Cinderella with In Ah.
Byul, shut it.
Uncle's wedding fell through.
In Ah ran away.
In Ah is banned, you stupid moron.
Mommy. He called me a stupid moron.
It's okay.
How could you say that to your little sister?
Watch it!
What did I do wrong?
Quiet down.
Hello. I heard you needed muscle.
We need to get the gift bags for the launch ceremony of "The Mom".
You'll need to make multiple trips.
Hyo Joo. Where are you going?
Excuse me? I have a meeting.
- I'll see you afterward. - No.
You don't have a meeting.
But...
There's a list of gifts there, so don't miss anything.
Don't go 3 times when 2 would've sufficed. Also.
Bring two more bundles of the magazines.
Excuse me?
Who pulls it like that?
Push it like me. It's easier.
Forget it.
I'd like to get it all so you don't have to,
but I know I may be being rude, rather than polite,
to a modern-day working woman.
Who says that?
My mom. She's a feminist.
She told me I shouldn't treat women like they're too weak...
to carry their own bags.
She probably said it because she couldn't stand...
seeing her son carrying his girlfriend's bag.
I'm fine, so pull it for me.
Hello.
Bye. I'll call you.
- Okay. Call me. - Goodbye.
- Have a nice day. - You too.
- Auntie, did you have a meeting? - Bye.
We picked an infertile couple.
- Are you going to the storage room? - Yes.
Are you going to die?
Yes. I think my clothes are going to die soon.
It's the first day it saw the light of day...
Okay.
The storage room is too rough a place for that dress...
I'll go.
Do you mean it?
We can't let the dress die. Let's go.
Okay.
See you.
I can't stand him.
Ms. Jang, should I take this down too?
Be careful.
Don't worry. I used to work at a warehouse,
so I'm used to this.
At a warehouse? You look like you didn't work a day in your life.
It was when I was looking for a job.
I'm glad I worked there. It's coming in handy.
What should I do with these?
Let's just take two.
Okay.
Yes.
The younger they are, the more fertile they'll be.
- What? - What?
Yes.
The younger they are, the more fertile they'll be.
- What? - What?
I was talking about strength.
I meant to say you must have great stamina.
You're young and healthy, so you're probably very active.
And that leads to a high success rate...
"A high success rate"?
I mean, there's a high probability that you'll succeed in life...
because you're healthy.
Both your body and mind.
Thank you, Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang, is there anything else you need me to help you with?
I'll gladly help you out with my healthy body.
Let's take a few more toys.
Toys? Okay. You got it.
People love that photo.
Do you think they'll keep working with you?
There's no reason not to.
You're right.
Whoever works with you always wants you back.
So I'm going to do the same and ask you to keep working with us.
Gosh, no way.
I'm sick of working with babies.
Excuse me. Sorry.
This is killing me. My entire body aches.
I'll go get you some medicine.
No, it's okay.
My body's just telling me that it's tired.
You don't need to take it too seriously.
You might feel okay right now,
but that might not be the case tomorrow.
It's better to take medicine at your age.
I'm not that old.
Gosh, your pain shows that you're a middle-aged woman.
Should I beat him up?
Wait here. I'll be right back.
Just a second.
Do you think you can take the elevator?
The elevator is packed.
Follow me, okay?
Excuse me.
Can you please make some space?
My mom is too old,
and her body is aching all over.
I may be young,
but my mom is old.
Please do us a favor and let us in.
I can't handle this kid.
(Nex Beer)
- You have to kick it properly. - Just eat.
Hey, kids.
Trash belongs in the trash can.
You sound like my dad.
Who are you to get involved?
Just let them be. They're not going to listen.
Let's just go.
What are you doing?
- Kids. - What are you doing?
Don't film us!
Who do you think you are?
Me? I'm an adult.
You're like an annoying uncle.
Gosh, I can't take this anymore.
Let's just go already.
Hey, just get lost.
Okay?
Kids, just pick up your trash and throw it in the trash can.
Let's give this video a nice ending.
What's his problem?
- What are you doing? - Hey.
"Kim Ho Jin".
- "Yoon Nam Joon." - Stop filming us!
Give it!
- Grab him! - Get his cell phone!
You punks! Soo Chul!
Soo Chul!
- Oh, my back. - Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I heard your first son got married.
I didn't know about the wedding.
Didn't I send you a big sum of congratulatory money?
Yes, it's fine. But what about your second son?
Oh, he's married already?
Your eldest son, the math teacher.
Did he get a divorce by any chance?
No?
(Jong Gu's mother, Hair salon...)
My gosh, when did I ever reject your son?
I said we should set them up once he gets a job.
He's still jobless?
(Jong Gu's mother, Hair salon...)
My gosh, there's no one.
What can I help you with?
I'd like you to help me...
do something for my daughter.
- Pardon? - I have a lot of money.
So I'm thinking of making a savings account...
or invest in some mutual funds for her.
Let me take a look.
You have a great first impression.
Are you married?
No, not yet.
Is that so?
Hello? Diapers?
Okay. See you.
You must have a niece or a nephew.
I have a son.
My wife gave birth before we could get married.
There's an investment that will guarantee a high profit.
Are you interested?
No, my business here is done.
One. And then,
two.
3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- 1, 2, - He's not...
- 3, 4. - so bad.
And use your thumb.
- 3, 4. - Or maybe I'm wrong.
Okay, that's it for today. Great job, everyone.
(Guitar Class for Residents)
Come in.
Excuse...
- The thing is, my daughter... - Yes, ma'am?
I'm sorry.
[VIU Ver] tvN E04 'Oh My Baby'
"The Time One Needs to Understand Others"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
My goodness.
Who are all these men married to?
When did I get a text?
Tomorrow is the day you receive your gastroscopy.
It's been three months already?
My gosh, you guys still have a lot of work to do.
No, we're almost done. Why did you want the magazines?
What's the use of keeping them all piled up?
We can send them to community service centers...
and postnatal care centers.
So Yoon, write up a list for me.
Sure.
We might end up giving too much away.
What do we do? They can't spare an extra vehicle.
They don't have any extras.
- Why not? - Due to waned photoshoots.
The magazine isn't as thick as it used to be.
We'll transport these ourselves.
Who's bringing their car tomorrow?
My husband took the car for his business trip.
Mine is at the auto shop.
Then I'll drive my dad's car to work tomorrow.
You have a license?
Yes, but I haven't been on the road yet.
Who's the photographer tomorrow?
Can't we call in a favor?
So...
he's the reason why your arm is busted?
Well, it at least...
I taught the kids to throw away trash...
in trash cans.
You...
are a grown-up who takes his responsibilities seriously.
Right?
So tell me about tomorrow's photoshoot.
You'll be taking photos of the event.
Is this not something you want to do?
All I'm doing is taking photos of an event.
What's there to like or hate?
I'm just flustered to work with "The Baby" again.
Why do you guys always need so many little favors?
I hate it when professional relationships get blurry.
Aren't we close enough now for me to ask these...
little friendly favors?
Are we?
I thought you didn't want to even look at me anymore.
You're unbelievable.
You took me in your arms when I cried the last time.
Why do that when we're not even close?
When did I take you in my arms?
All I did was pat you on the back while you cried.
I went from hating you to liking you which is even scarier,
but I guess the feeling wasn't mutual.
Only I thought we were friends.
(The Mom)
(Launching Event for The Mom's 10th Term)
(Do Rah)
(Ji Yul's Mom)
Mike testing, 1, 2, 3.
That's enough. We hear you loud and clear.
How about I sing a song?
I'd rather you make some phone calls instead.
Hasn't it been an hour?
My gosh, you're here!
Guys, what took you so long?
Let me show you to your seats. The others aren't here yet.
The other moms won't be here.
We came here to tell you where we stand.
- What do you mean? - You're her, right?
The woman who tried to buy sperm illegally.
How can a journalist for a baby magazine...
do such a thing? It's unethical.
We can't support the magazine...
when its journalist has questionable morals.
I thought...
that the moms would understand...
my desire to become a mom.
It's why we're taking a stand.
We want children to be raised in an upright environment.
We are aware that there are women...
who wish to raise children while still unmarried.
But what about the children who will grow up without a father?
Children aren't toys, you know.
Giving birth just because you want to...
is selfish if you ask me.
How could you do this to your own child?
If you want a family, try getting a dog or a cat instead.
Look here, ladies!
Get a dog instead?
How could you say that to dog lovers?
- Mind your own business. - The dog lover in me can't take it.
It's not your call...
whether or not she raises a dog or a baby.
What did Ms. Jang do anyway? She did nothing wrong.
I apologize for making you all uncomfortable.
I understand your worries...
and you can say that being moms yourselves.
However,
it wasn't my intention to do what you're thinking.
I've been working alongside moms for 15 years,
so I thought I knew how moms would feel.
But I guess...
I was clueless after all.
I wish to learn how it's like to be a mom...
and understand motherhood.
I truly hope I get the chance.
Hold on. Stop that.
What do you mean our supporters declared a boycott?
Where's Ms. Jang?
I ordered her to clean up storage.
We're about to call it a day, so you should talk to her tomorrow.
Ms. Shim, this isn't something you should defend her on.
Goodness. I didn't know I had the power to do that.
I want her in my office as soon as...
she gets to work tomorrow.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
("The Baby" Jang Ha Ri)
The person you have reached is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
You weren't at Jo Jo's.
People from work frequent there.
Thank you.
Why were you out looking for me?
Did you think I'd be crying like a kid?
Were you hoping to pat me on the back again?
It's because I needed a drinking buddy.
I have a lot on my mind today.
Why did you lie?
You don't raise dogs.
How did you know that?
You would've already talked about your dog if you had one.
My Ddol Ddol was clever, you know.
If only it came back after running away 30 years ago.
Will the moms ever understand me?
My parents always argued...
during mealtime.
My dad had to have a cup of water before eating,
but my mom would say that it'll hinder his digestion.
After my father passed away,
she has always served water during his ancestral rite.
She does that even after saying how she couldn't understand...
why he'd do such a thing for 40 years.
One must not understand at first to understand.
If you finally understand someone at one point in your life,
it'll mean that...
you've been thinking about that person throughout that time.
It's a human being, who can't even understand himself,
understanding someone else.
And if you really do understand,
your attitude would change.
Although it shouldn't take 40 years.
Why did you come?
I may need to be carried home today.
I have a wide back.
It'll be comfortable.
I don't know about that.
- How about a drink? - Okay.
Mr. Nam was right.
You're a good person.
What about me is good? I want details.
Let's just say you're an average person.
Mr. Average Person,
will you continue to stay single?
You seem like a pretty good guy.
I wonder if you plan to stay single.
I don't want to get excited.
Depending on someone and being disappointed,
hurt, and then liking them...
I can't handle being excited in love anymore.
If I fall after the age of 40, life won't be so kind.
I want to live as I do now.
Silently.
Without any happenings.
But...
why do you want to be a mom?
I just...
want to become happy.
You are very devoted to the company.
You did some incredible PR for the magazine.
I hear you turned the mom community upside down.
She said she was investigating undercover,
so we should write an article saying that...
to fix the situation.
She told the readers that she wants to have a baby!
- Yes, sir. - If we're going to play along,
we need to get our stories straight.
Yes, we do.
- I'll do what I can to fix... - Stay out of it!
Yes, sir.
You have no kids, so you can't figure out the readers' needs.
Even if you do well, I don't know about making you editor-in-chief.
All you do is make trouble.
That's why I plan to have a baby...
I knew from the get-go that you were an imbecile,
but I didn't know it was that bad.
We're going to hold a disciplinary hearing.
It's the first time in 30 years since we started,
so it won't be easy.
Given the situation, we will be very stern.
I'm sorry.
It was wrong to tarnish the company's image.
But strictly put, it's your personal life.
It's not like they'll take care of your life. Those schmucks.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Are you Lee Ok Ran's guardian?
This is Big Hospital.
Why aren't you coming. We can't discharge her without you.
Excuse me?
Lee Ok Ran's guardian.
- Yes. - She's still sleeping.
Wait here. We'll let you know when she's out.
- Okay. Thank you. - Sure.
Park Shi Ta's guardian.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm here for my baby's vaccination shot.
Okay. Wait here.
Okay.
Ha Ri. Where are we?
You're so sweet.
It's a sad realization.
Sit here.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
Even as I saw the growing wrinkles on Mom's face,
I was indifferent and only counted my age.
- Jang Ha Ri's guardian? - Yes, me. Me.
Oh no. How did this happen?
Oh no. You poor thing.
Because a Mom is a Mom,
I always expected to depend on her.
Does it hurt?
Why did I take it for granted that she was my guardian?
- Lee Ok Ran's guardian. - Yes.
- Okay. - Mom.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
Are you okay?
Yes.
That moment always comes...
when the child becomes their parent's guardian.
At...
that moment,
we have no choice but to become adults.
Did you two go somewhere nice?
Goodness.
So...
They let me go alone last time. That's why I went alone.
I didn't know the hospital changed its policy.
Why would you go to the hospital alone like you have no family?
I'm the only one who didn't know you had stomach cancer.
I get a call on the day of the surgery as if it's a picnic.
How...
You shouldn't do that to your daughter.
Why are you making me a bad daughter?
Did someone say you were bad?
Everyone knows you work long hours and can't even come home.
Don't mind me, and focus on your job.
How can I not mind you when you're sick?
I'm not sick. They said I'm fine.
You should eat and sleep properly as you work.
I... I'm always making you worry about me.
Can't I worry about you too?
Even if I act immature,
I can take care of you, so have faith in your daughter.
Why would you take care of me? I'm not terminally ill.
Save your nagging for your kids.
Get sperm or whatever. Have kids using whatever means you want.
It's so annoying.
No, that's...
I thought I could raise a baby well,
but I didn't think about the child who'd have to live without a dad.
I was being greedy.
I mean,
I was fine although I only had you, so...
I thought I could do well.
But I should've thought about the kid first.
I don't think I'm qualified.
Did someone say something?
No.
My gosh.
Parents have kids because they want to.
No baby is born out of their own will.
Do you think I gave birth to you because you begged me to?
What kind of nonsense are you talking about?
You don't study and take tests to become a mother.
You become a mother after you give birth.
There's no license for that. Don't say you're not qualified.
You're right. There's no license.
But if there was a license test for that,
you'd get the highest score.
So be good to your mom.
Anyway, I don't think this was a fight.
It was really nice to watch you guys reconcile and make peace.
Do Ah is crying. I'll leave you guys to wrap it up. I love you guys.
Do Ah.
What was that? My gosh.
Aren't you going to drink? Let's have a drink.
No, I don't want to become an alcoholic like you.
I'll sue you for slander.
Don't do that.
I'm sick of getting punished.
Are you serious?
What can you do?
You're just going through...
the adversities and hardships of becoming a mom.
Come to think of it, even you didn't ask.
What?
No one asked me why, but I Sang did.
He asked me why I want to become a mom.
What other reason could there be?
You want to become a mom because of your motherly instincts.
Yes, you're right.
But on my way home, I suddenly remembered...
my elementary school graduation day.
Don't be a scrooge and just get her a big bouquet.
And take a lot of photos.
Don't go anywhere else, okay? If you do, I'll get really angry.
Okay.
Dad, get me a big bouquet of roses.
Ha Ri, I need to get a film...
for the camera.
You should go without me.
- Do you know which class I'm in? - What?
I'm in class 6-5. It's on the 4th floor.
Can you find your way there?
Of course.
You go first. I'll be right there.
Wait for me!
(Ssanggang Elementary School, 23rd Graduation Ceremony)
(Congratulations on your graduation)
No matter how long I waited,
my dad didn't show up.
I was the only one standing there all by myself,
and I was embarrassed because it felt like all eyes were on me.
But I couldn't go home.
Because I knew my dad won't ever come back.
Ha Ri, what are you doing here?
Where is your dad?
I don't know.
Ha Ri, let's take a photo together. Come here.
Why?
- Stand there. - You guys are friends.
Smile.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
Let's take one more photo. Give me a bright smile.
You look really ugly right now.
Why you...
- Oh, gosh! - No, wait!
Ha Ri, stop.
- What's the matter? - Stop it.
- Stop it, Jae Young. - Ha Ri.
My goodness, what did you say?
Jae Young, stop it.
(Pig Skin)
- Mom. - Oh, dear.
Ha Ri, what's wrong?
Mom!
Where's your dad?
Is it yummy?
Yes.
It's all over your mouth.
You're okay without your dad, right?
Yes.
Eat some meat.
That's when I promised myself to become an awesome person...
when I grow up.
What kind of an awesome person?
A mom.
My mom is the most awesome person in the world.
A mother.
They'll probably cut her wage for about 1 to 3 months.
Do you think this is fun?
No, I'm worried.
The worst thing that can happen to an employee is not getting paid.
Did she really make such a big mistake?
She tarnished the company's reputation and credibility.
I should've just quietly dealt with those mothers.
What happened?
They suspended her for a month.
- What? - What?
Then she won't get paid for a month?
This is unbelievable.
They can't suspend her for this.
How are we going to meet the deadline for our project?
Where is Ha Ri?
Hey, Ha Ri.
I heard what happened.
Hey... Ha Ri, I'll... I'll see you.
She got suspended for a month.
She looks really angry, doesn't she?
This game is for two people. You can't play it by yourself.
Let's do this.
Over there.
To your left!
This is hard.
Shoot!
You were supposed to shoot that.
My gosh, no!
(You Lose)
You acted like a natural, so I thought you'd be a sniper.
What next?
Should we drink or go to the beach?
I'm no longer stressed.
I may have gotten suspended,
but I still need to meet a deadline.
This is fun, right?
Let me see you smile!
Over here! Look!
Give me a smile.
Smile, Yu Bin. Look here, Yu Bin.
Over here!
Yu Bin, give me a smile! He's laughing too!
Look! He's laughing too!
Yes, let's laugh!
There you go. All right.
I need him to cry this time.
What do I do?
Yoo Bin, roar.
Roar! I'm coming to get you.
He is a very bad man.
Look at me hit the bad man.
How nasty!
You naughty boy.
You naughty boy!
As if you stood a chance.
That's what I call talent.
- Can you check the photos? - Sure.
Let's see.
That one.
They're all good.
This should be the main photo.
Mr. Han,
I'm impressed.
(Good job!)
It's us grown-ups who really need compliments.
Good job, Mr. Han.
- Ha Ri, the baby's mom is leaving. - Okay.
Goodbye.
(Good job!)
This is bad.
(We thank Jang Gwang for his cameo appearance.)
(Oh My Baby)
You two were married?
A second marriage?
Right, the sperm donation.
I wouldn't have to be a father to your baby,
- so I'll do you a favor. - Really?
She's staying the night out?
Isn't she alone with Mr. Han?
You found the one place that only has one inn.
She'll get an earful from me once she gets back.
Is he the one that I shouldn't have let go of?
How should...
we spend the night?