(Episode 35)
His bronchial tubes
are quite constricted.
Oxygen saturation is low after
suffering from respiratory distress,
so he'll need some oxygen.
How long has this been going on?
My guess is several days.
I'm not sure.
When did it start happening?
His breathing was fine...
and he didn't have a fever
when I stopped by the workshop.
Right, he was fine back then.
I think it started after
his field trip three days ago.
I figured the fever
was due to a cold.
Bacterial pneumonia
can come along with a fever.
We'll check his blood
and X-ray tomorrow...
and give him antibiotics
as well as oxygen.
He had pneumonia, but
all I gave him was cold medicine.
Moms aren't supposed
to be medical experts.
Don't beat yourself up over it.
I'll get going then.
Sure. Thanks for everything.
Bo Young, have a seat.
I don't want you to pass out.
Are you done in there?
How's your patient?
He's okay.
Were you with Dr. Yoon
this evening though?
How so?
We went for some drinks.
So the patient's mother...
They used to go to the same church.
She's his first love.
What about the boy's father?
I'm guessing she's a single mom.
What a dramatic reunion, right?
It is, but you're being
very nonchalant about it.
You're saying it like
he's some friend.
It'd be odd to talk about him
like my ex-husband.
Anyway, we should get going.
Jae Seok.
Jae Seok!
Where on earth is he?
Where did he go
without turning off the lights?
Maybe the convenience store?
Jae Seok!
What on earth?
What are you doing?
You're home.
Why are you cleaning at this hour?
You never clean up
even when I ask you to.
Gyu Jin, I'm not cleaning right now.
I'm wiping my heart.
What are you talking about?
Well, I'm not in the mood
to argue with you.
Leave and let me shower.
Go ahead.
Stop joking around and leave!
Take your shower. I won't watch.
Why do you never listen?
Gyu Jin,
I'm experiencing a crisis right now,
so please let me be.
What's going on?
Have you been cleaning all night?
Jae Seok, you're scaring me!
Gyu Jin, I've come to a conclusion.
What do you mean?
I've been leading
too much of an honest life.
Instead of going out with friends,
I've been trying hard
to adjust to my new workplace.
Work, home, work, home.
The lack of stimulants in my life
has made me lose it.
Honest life? No. Insane? Yes.
Out of sight, out of mind.
I'll go back
to my corrupt lifestyle.
to being the old Yoon Jae Seok,
so don't try to stop me.
Hui Jae, it's me.
Let's meet up tonight.
Where? Secret Club.
I expect everyone to be there.
Especially Chang Ryeol.
He'd better not look old today.
Today, we're picking up women.
See? I'll now wash up.
What's gotten into him?
Has he lost his mind?
Jae Seok!
Did you clean the utility room too?
Gosh, look how shiny the floor is.
Just like I suspected,
it's bacterial pneumonia.
Thankfully, there's no
secondary infection.
His fever is subsiding,
so don't worry too much.
I want constant updates
on his oxygen level and fever.
Got it.
Si Hoo, how's your breathing?
It's good.
You'll keep getting better.
By the way, it looks like
you've grown a bit taller.
I'd say about 3cm.
And you lost some weight.
It's as if you've been trying to.
I haven't.
Does it seem that way though?
Yes, you also have
bags under your eyes.
My mom used to have them as well.
Si Hoo, please.
I see you're still
as honest as ever.
He's not like his mother at all.
I have bags under my eyes?
Dr. Song.
What's wrong?
Do you have more questions?
No, that's not it.
Things were too hectic yesterday...
that I wasn't able
to thank you properly.
Thank you for treating my boy
so late at night.
Please don't mention it.
I was just doing my job.
Also,
please know that
I was petrified last night.
Sense of relief washed over me
when I saw a familiar face.
I wasn't in my right mind.
So what I'm trying to say is that...
You don't have to
explain your actions like this.
I wanted to apologize
for making you uncomfortable.
Please don't.
This is actually
making me more uncomfortable.
Sure thing.
Then I won't from now on.
Sure. Good day, then.
That was kind of annoying.
Unbelievable.
Why does it feel
like I've been sucker-punched?
Darn it.
She seemed
so apologetic at first, but...
"Then I won't from now on."
That's one cunning cat.
Leave it to Gyu Jin
to fall for someone like that.
It was mycoplasma.
What?
What Si Hoo has.
His fever is down
and his breathing has stabilized.
I checked his nose for infections,
but the results came back negative.
I'll run some more tests
to rule out other suspicions I have.
Why are you telling me all this?
I thought you'd be worried.
I'm not.
Of course you do
what's best for the patient.
I always trust your judgement
as a doctor.
You must be chummy
with Si Hoo's mom.
You even have gone to her workshop.
Right, I did go there once.
Leathercraft is a lot of fun.
It clears your head.
How should I know...
when none of my friends
work at leathercraft workshops?
You have the hospital director
on your side instead.
Look at how sweet
Jeong Rok is on you.
- Is that so?
- Try to work it out with him.
He has a great personality,
and he's cool and attentive.
He sure is a catch.
Women adore men like him.
I should wish you good luck too.
Si Hoo's mom
seems to depend on you a lot.
Also, she's your first love.
It's why I consider myself lucky.
Men go head over heels
for someone like Bo Young.
- Exactly!
- Exactly.
Exactly.
We just don't work together.
My gosh. Ok Ja, stop!
Are you kidding me?
What now?
What's wrong with you?
You space out and then get angry.
Can't you see
you're bringing down the mood?
Go home
if you're going to be like this.
I wasn't in the mood anyway,
so thanks.
I'll get going.
What? Stop right there.
Why are you being so moody today?
Are you experiencing menopause?
Seriously?
How can you say that
to an unmarried woman?
Then what's the matter?
Honey, knock some sense into her.
Keep me out of it.
I'm scared of her these days.
Unbelievable.
- Hello.
- Hi, Mr. Song.
Are you off to your dance class?
- Yes.
- That's right.
We have more free time
during the day than in the evening.
Also, dancing in the evening...
makes me crave late-night snacks
which doesn't help.
We stopped by to ask
if anyone would like to join us.
I'm glad you guys are here.
Can you take her with you?
Ok Ja, don't mope around
and enjoy some dancing instead.
No, I'm not going today.
Why not? You were always against
missing even one class.
But you love dance classes.
I don't anymore.
Besides, I'm not
in the mood to dance today.
Ok Ja, don't be like that
and join us.
I'll buy coffee on the way there.
Come on.
The more the merrier, right?
Also, she offered to buy coffee.
- Come on!
- Let's go.
No wonder she's being criticized.
Anyway, this is supposed
to be a secret,
so you can't repeat this to anyone.
Oh, please. You know
I'm good at keeping secrets.
My lips are sealed,
so don't you worry.
Anyway, did you hear the news?
It's about Mr. Yang.
These days, he's been...
Hold on. Just a second.
Please watch your step.
Be careful.
I was fine walking here, you know.
It's not even that far.
But the weather's hot.
Why not save the sweat
for the dance class alone?
You're right about that.
Be careful.
Hello, ladies.
Please watch your step.
That's what I was just about to say.
Just to win over Ms. Kang's heart,
he's been wearing a leather jacket
and riding a motorcycle...
in this warm weather.
I can't believe it.
Incredible, isn't it?
Who knew that the manly Mr. Yang
would pine over a woman like this?
Unbelievable.
Cha-cha, spin, 1, 2.
Cha-cha-cha.
Good. After a five-minute break,
we'll move onto the next sequence.
- Sure.
- Got it.
Ms. Kang, you're sweating.
Yes, it has gotten warm.
My goodness, look at you sweating.
No, look at him sweating.
Gosh.
He's treating her like a princess.
It's as if she's a fragile being...
who needs constant protection.
It's disgusting if you ask me.
How hilarious.
Ms. Kang, just a second.
Could you come this way?
Ms. Jang, can you step aside?
What...
How is it?
Isn't it the best spot here?
You're right. It is the best spot.
- Gosh, that's good.
- Let me feel the breeze too.
It's as if I'm in Antarctica.
Conserve electricity, you fools.
- What?
- What's wrong with her?
Where is she going?
Ok Ja, are you leaving?
I used to work at Peanut Air.
Two years as a flight attendant
and a year working the desk.
And I'm qualified to perform CPR.
You seem over-qualified
to work the desk at our gym.
I always wanted to work someplace
that needed my service...
and I just knew it
when I saw the job description.
This place would definitely need me.
You're good with your words too.
I can start tomorrow
if you want me to.
Mornings or afternoons...
You're on the older side though.
(Resume: Song Ga Hee)
You're 38.
You didn't notice though, right?
As you can see,
I've been maintaining...
my young looks and physique.
You have a son too.
Yes.
(Fitness Center, Crossfit)
Those with children
tend to have family emergencies.
I'm sorry.
Darn.
If you're that sorry, just hire me.
What should a woman
on the older side with a child do...
after her career is cut off then?
Bow to the teacher.
- See you tomorrow.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
How about a game of soccer
before going home?
Soccer?
But I wore sandals to school today.
Hey, nerd.
Let's swap shoes.
No.
Don't be like that.
We'll swap again tomorrow.
I don't want to.
I know you won't give them back.
I wouldn't keep them
even if you told me to.
They look cheap anyway.
- Fatherless jerk.
- What?
Are you going to
come at me like last time?
It's not like
you can beat me anyway.
- You loser.
- Hey!
What just happened?
They're fighting.
What's up with him?
Hyo Sin!
Hey, is school already over?
Why did you come here
instead of going home?
I wanted to see you.
- What happened to your face?
- I threw him.
What?
I threw him over my shoulder.
Just like you taught me, wait.
I grabbed him here and here
and threw him over my shoulder.
It actually worked.
I got punched a few times too,
but I did well, right?
The kids in my class
were just as surprised.
So? You came all the way here
to tell me that?
Yes. I did well, right?
You did.
He's the third tallest boy
in my class.
He's really heavy too,
but I didn't feel any of his weight.
The technique was perfect then.
You did well.
Good job.
I'm going to keep working out,
you know.
Before you know it,
I'll be able to take him on fully.
You'll keep teaching me
until then, right?
I will.
Teach him what?
Mom.
What did he teach...
My gosh.
What's with your face?
Did you have a fight?
Why? Who did you fight with?
No.
- The thing is...
- He got hurt exercising with me.
Exercising?
What exercise did you do
to hurt him like this?
We were doing judo.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Don't even apologize to me.
What do you think
you're doing to my son?
He doesn't like to exercise.
Why would you want to teach him
judo when he was doing just fine?
What's the reason?
Why are you yelling at him?
I asked him to teach me.
What?
I wanted to learn judo,
so I asked him to teach me.
Ji Hun, you...
You've been coming home late
and going straight to bed.
Is it because you learned judo?
Why did you lie to me then?
- Because you wouldn't let me do it.
- Of course not.
Why would I let you do it
when you get hurt like this?
Don't do the judo thing ever again.
If you want to exercise,
I'll play badminton with you.
- Let's go home.
- No. I'm doing this.
Ji Hun.
I really need it.
And I want to learn it from Hyo Sin.
Why are you being like this?
What did you do to manipulate him?
Mom, please.
I want to do this.
I've never gone
against you before.
Please let me do
what I want this time.
Please.
Then just do exercise.
Safely.
And you.
Since I'm nine years older than you,
I'll drop the honorifics.
I will kill you if you teach him
anything dangerous. Okay?
Let's go.
Bye.
She's scary when she's upset.
I can tell she's a mom.
It's been only two days,
but I'm getting heat rashes already.
Gosh, it's so hot.
My gosh, how pathetic.
- What?
- What are you trying to pull off...
with the leather jacket
and motorbike at your age?
What a sight you are!
I'm just doing the whole thing
because I like it.
Whatever.
I don't know.
At least I admit
that you have the guts.
You blocked the huge
garbage truck and said,
"I'm a man who likes her."
That was just embarrassing.
Hey, why would you be
embarrassed by love?
You are so old-fashioned.
So what did she say?
Does she like you too?
She doesn't seem to hate me,
but she wouldn't give me a chance.
I guess it will take me a long time
to make her mine.
Actually I knew
she wasn't easy to deal with.
They say beauty is
in the eye of the beholder.
The old sayings are all true.
It's just mysterious.
Why? What's wrong about her?
Fine. You're the romanticist
of Yongju Traditional Market.
I admit it.
Is that a compliment or an insult?
It's a compliment.
It's not easy to be blinded
by love at your age.
Good luck. I'll do
what I can do to help you.
Are you serious?
Will you really help me?
How? What will you do?
Don't act charming to me.
Just do it to her.
What will you do to help me?
Tell me.
- Stop it.
- Hey, wait.
This is your check card.
It offers various benefits
of shopping.
You can use the card right away.
Thank you.
And this is an eco-friendly bag.
It looks pretty.
Please try using it.
I have bags at home.
I don't need it.
My gosh. I needed a bag like this.
I'll take it.
No, I'll take it with me.
You just said you don't need it.
Why don't you give it
to someone who needs it?
No. I need it too.
The clerk gave it to me
in the first place.
And you said you don't need it.
Why are you being so childish?
Did you not know
I'm always childish?
You haven't changed
at all, by the way.
You are such a freeloader.
That's so pathetic.
Excuse me.
I'll go get you one more bag.
Either of you can take it first.
Gosh, she's so nasty.
She's just ill-tempered.
That's why Na Hee couldn't
put up with her.
That sly wench.
She's so greedy, but she just
pretends to be generous.
We are just the worst enemies.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One. Time's up.
Darn it.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Hey, we have nothing to eat
at home. We should go to dinner.
Where are you going?
Gyu Jin, I told you this morning.
I will live a life of debauchery.
I will go astray tonight.
I'll come home late.
Don't wait for me and sleep first.
Bam.
1, 2.
Has he lost his mind?
This is serious.
Gosh, should I go grocery shopping?
Dr. Yoon.
Hey, Si Hoo.
Are you all right?
Can you move around like that?
Yes, I'm fine.
The nurse says his fever broke,
so he can go out.
Really?
Let me see.
Gosh, it's cold.
When did your fever break like that?
We were on our way to see you.
Me? Why?
Si Hoo wants to eat
packed dinner with you again.
You know I have an open hand.
I'm happy to join you.
Thanks to you, I'm getting
free dinner again.
(Mother)
Excuse me.
- Mom.
- You cold-hearted punk.
Do you not even care...
if I'm alive or dead?
Mom, are you drunk?
Mom.
That heartless rascal.
I've raised him with all my heart.
Mom, get up.
I know you're not drunk.
I saw you looking
through the window.
You should've said that sooner.
You sly punk.
This is embarrassing.
How could you pretend
to be drunk to call your son?
I had no choice.
Why did you not even call me
after leaving like that?
You silly rascal.
I was going to call you.
After you calm yourself down.
As if.
Do you even care about me?
Of course I do.
I've been feeling bad for you.
You're just saying that.
Were you waiting for my call?
Sure.
I waited for you to come every day.
I've been feeling so lonely
and empty waiting for your call.
I thought I've raised
my children for nothing.
Now I feel like I'm a terrible son.
Do you want me to stand there
holding up my hands?
Stop it.
Are you making fun of me?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I should've let you see
your son live happily.
I know I'm not a good son.
Don't say that.
I don't want to hear it.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You can start over.
She wasn't right for you
to begin with.
When I went to the market
earlier today...
Forget it. It's nothing.
Mom, did you eat dinner?
Do you want me
to cook ramyeon for you?
This place is so cool
even on weekdays.
I know. It's a beautiful world.
I was being silly.
Now that I'm here,
I don't think of her at all.
Hey, what is he mumbling about?
I don't know. He's not
in his right mind.
He just called us out
all of a sudden.
Stop chattering away
and order more drinks.
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
Do you need something, Mr. Yoon?
I...
I need another bottle of this.
This is crazy.
I'm seeing things now.
Hey, look over at the DJ booth.
Aren't they having fun?
The booth? Where? Where?
What? You'll go up to her?
Hey.
My gosh. What...
What? You're giving up?
Yes. It's best to not even try
when you'll only get jilted.
Forget about it.
Let's just drink. Cheers!
How strange. This is so weird.
Sorry. I wasn't feeling well,
so I left first.
Have fun without me.
I'll call you soon. Bye.
This is really confusing.
What's wrong with me?
This has never happened to me.
Oh? Mr. Yoon!
What's this? Is it
another apparition? It is.
What was that about, Mr. Yoon?
Why didn't you say hi?
It's real.
It's the real Song Da Hee.
What?
You appeared all over the place,
and now I finally see
the real thing.
This is just crazy.
This wasn't the plan.
What are you saying?
What's wrong? Do you feel unwell?
Yes. I feel unwell.
I'm so very, immensely,
disturbingly unwell.
Mom's such a drama queen.
Yes.
I closed up, so come home
when you're done.
Yes. Don't be too late. Bye.
Mother.
Hi. Did you...
visit your mother?
Yes.
Okay. I see.
I should get going.
Mother.
Mother. I'm so sorry.
You were so nice to me.
Forget it.
Don't call me that now. We're...
no longer family.
I'm not yet able to...
greet you brightly in the street
and ask after you.
I'm not yet ready to do that.
I should go.
Take care of yourself.
This is nice.
The weather's perfect too.
For some reason today,
I managed to concentrate so well.
So I studied without even
going to the toilet...
when I heard the closing song.
You know, the library's
closing song.
The feeling of hearing that
before leaving to go home...
That gave me quite a feeling of
accomplishment.
Must you be like that?
Yes. I like it over here.
Don't mind me and keep talking.
You're acting
really weird today. Why...
Are you very tired?
Now that I say that,
you look a bit pale.
No, no, stop. Freeze.
You stay over there. I stay here.
Don't cross that line, okay?
What? My gosh.
What line?
The line as in-laws.
Ancestors said it's better to stay
away from your in-laws' and toilet.
We got too close.
From now on,
we should keep a distance.
You're the one
who didn't keep a distance.
You asked me to be
your fake girlfriend.
But... That's why
I'm showing remorse for that.
Why exactly are you showing remorse?
Because I have my reasons!
You're actually the type to cling on
every word someone says.
It's because
you're suddenly being weird.
Are you angry with me?
Did I do something wrong?
Don't do that either!
That blank stare!
Just don't do anything!
Why should I just do nothing?
What's the matter?
What is wrong with you?
I said no crossing the line!
Hey, how dare you touch me?
It's your last warning.
Don't do that!
Hey, Mr. Yoon. You're leaving.
You're really leaving?
Mr. Yoon!
Mr. Yoon.
I need to know what I did wrong...
if I'm to apologize or something.
Mr. Yoon!
Don't follow me.
You didn't do anything wrong.
But you're angry.
You're angry with me right now.
I'm not angry.
I'm sorry.
I have a tendency to not
look to my side when I walk.
But that motorcyclist
was going a bit too fast.
Mr. Yoon.
Mr. Yoon?
I guess I lost.
What?
I lost.
To you.
Aren't you hungry?
Shall we have udon?
(Unnie's Kimbap)
I don't know, I don't know
Take all my candy, I don't know
Once you do that, I will
Ms. Ok Ja. We're closed for the day.
I know.
You know?
Do you have business with me?
Shall we have a drink?
A drink?
It looks like you want to
have a drink.
I'm sorry, but I have
errands to run tomorrow.
I can't drink tonight.
Just one glass.
I have something to say.
Okay, then. I can do that.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
(Episode 36)
No, it's fine.
I'm more accustomed
to pouring my own drinks.
I love drinking alone, you see.
A few drinks to wrap up the day...
leads to a good night's sleep.
Here.
So...
what did you want to say to me?
Earning my keep at an early age...
made me quite perceptive.
I doubt you wanted to drink with me
to swap meaningless words.
What is it? You can tell me.
Do you like Yang Chi Su?
Yang Chi Su?
Oh, you mean Mr. Yang.
So that's his name. I like it.
Answer my question. Do you like him?
I don't know why
I need to answer that.
Don't even think about
getting out of this.
You don't intend to
accept his feelings.
So what?
Why are you stringing him along
when you're not even interested?
What do you mean
I'm stringing him along?
You're getting
what you can out of him.
The free meat, the flowers,
and rides on the motorbike.
You're giving him false hope.
In other words,
you're being a gold digger.
What do you think
you're accusing me of?
Did you seriously
just call me a gold digger?
Let's say that I am
stringing him along.
Why are you getting upset about it?
Are you his family?
Are you like his little sister?
We're good neighbors.
That's right. We're friends.
I've known him for 10 years now.
That qualifies me as his family.
Is that so? I had no idea
that he had a family member...
who sticks her head in
where it doesn't belong.
I'm just sick and tired...
of the way
you've been treating him.
I wouldn't be this annoyed
if you were a stunning beauty.
But...
Are you saying that because
you think you're prettier than I am?
I won't deny it.
Unbelievable.
You're hilarious, Button Eyes.
What did you just call me?
Button Eyes?
I was only talking to myself.
Besides, you were the first
to judge me on my looks.
The liquor couldn't be sweeter.
I could drink for days.
Just so you know,
no one at this market...
can hold their liquor like I can.
One's alcohol intake isn't
something to brag about, old lady.
Old lady?
Besides, you're the one
who bragged first.
So tell me.
Are your eyes open or not?
They're open.
They're open wide.
Bottoms up.
Got it.
Anyway,
this is your last chance.
Just give up already.
Give up.
Darn it.
Give up?
I...
will never do such a thing,
Ms. Piggy.
What?
You're a resilient one, aren't you?
Fine, let's drink.
Drink it all.
Darn.
- Don't you dare drink it all.
- Go ahead.
- You drank all of it yourself.
- Bottoms up.
Bottoms up... Yes, bottoms up.
I won, I won
Gosh.
Being angry was a good look on you.
I can't believe you're old enough
to talk back to me.
Maybe...
you would've been better off
with your dad.
You could've exercised with him...
and go to the sauna together.
Maybe I shouldn't have
brought you with me.
That's not it.
I followed you out.
I wanted to live with you.
Wait, weren't you asleep?
You woke me by stroking my hair.
I see.
Sorry about that.
I like my life,
so don't even think that way again.
Really?
All right, I won't.
Ji Hun,
you're my everything, you know.
You're all that I have in my life.
Same here.
Can't you say
something sweeter than that?
Good night.
My charming little boy.
I love how chic you are.
Mom, stop it. I can't breathe.
No way.
This is how it'll be tonight.
I'll hug you all night,
so don't you stop me.
But you're crushing me.
All right. This is the morning
of a historic day.
What happens today will
make or break our action company.
- Please tell me you're confident.
- Sure thing.
Don't you worry, Joon Seon.
I had one sweet dream last night.
Really? What was it about?
Dreaming of girl groups
don't mean a thing.
This one's for real though.
In my dream,
we were eating ramyeon...
when a white tiger this big
bit down on my leg.
Is that a lucky dream?
Of course.
Don't you know what a tiger is?
The king of all animals.
The greatest creature of all.
And none other than
a rare white tiger chose me.
My gosh. No way.
Joon Seon, look.
"Your business will thrive
and fame will follow."
- It's the luckiest dream ever.
- No way!
What did I tell you?
The camera will get
a shot of my face today.
Jong Soo,
let me buy that dream.
No.
Come on.
Sell me that dream. You don't
have much to do today anyway.
Okay, fine.
I'll trade it for my tracksuit...
that you like.
It's the only big brand
tracksuit I have...
and it's the real deal.
I'm trading down,
but I'll let you have it
since you have seniority.
Okay, good.
Throw that dream of yours to me.
Got it. Here it comes.
Take it.
I got it.
- Take it.
- Got it.
- I dropped it.
Joon Seon, don't step on my dream!
- Got it.
- Here's another.
I got it.
You crazy jerks. Stop that already.
- Got it.
- Jeong Bong.
What you dropped is mine.
- No way.
- Hand it over.
- Wait.
- It's mine!
- But I bought it.
- Let me have some of it.
- Come on!
- Breakfast is ready!
Why does she want a bag
she has no use for?
She can be so childish.
Why did you try to take
what was offered to her?
I could've bought you a new one.
Why would you spend money on one?
She said she didn't need it.
Still. There's no need
to keep clashing into her.
Whose side are you taking?
Did you grow a soft spot for her
while working for her?
Of course not.
Ga Hee, is the soup ready?
Yes, I'm coming.
Gosh, it smells delicious.
Is it radish soup with beef?
- Good morning.
- Ga Hee, my gosh.
Please put that down.
Let me...
- What just happened?
- What's going on?
- How about this?
- It hurts.
- Here?
I think he fractured his bone.
You may not need surgery,
but you'll need to stay in a cast.
What? Then what about today's shoot?
Of course he can't do it.
He won't be even able to walk.
No, Joon Seon. I can do it.
Don't go to unnecessary lengths.
Your ankle will only get worse.
Oh, dear.
Now I feel terrible.
He was only trying to help.
Please don't say that.
I'm fine, Ga Hee.
You're not fine at all!
How can you shoot today's scenes
on that ankle?
Today is the most important day.
I can't believe this just happened.
You've got to be kidding me.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I shouldn't have
bought Jong Soo's dream.
What now?
Can someone else fill in?
There isn't anyone.
Everyone I know...
are members
of the company I worked at.
Our teamwork is one thing,
but we need someone athletic enough
to manage the moves.
Where do we find someone like that?
Wait. He's right here.
Hyo Sin, please.
Just help me this once.
You have a fit body
and are well-coordinated.
All you have to do
is walk around for us.
We'll do everything else including
all the kicking and punching.
I can't. I already told you I can't.
How can you say that
without even trying?
It's not that you can't.
You just won't.
- Then I won't do it.
- Hey!
Come on, don't be a jerk.
Have you always been
this cruel and cold-hearted?
Joon Seon, it won't work.
- He's bigger than me and...
- Shut it.
You're smaller than
the actor you're playing anyway.
We can make it work since
he'll be shot from afar and behind.
Hyo Sin, can't you do this?
Think about who we are to you.
We live here together
in this small crowded space.
That makes us family!
I'm not so sure about that.
Do family members...
scold you for taking
too long in the shower?
Who did that?
Him? This moron right here?
- Was it him?
- Joon Seon, please.
- It hurts.
- Whatever. I'm off to work.
I can't afford
to skip deliveries today.
I'll talk to my dad about that.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but that's how desperate I am.
Hyo Sin, please.
Just help me this once.
What if I got on my knees?
I'll do that right now.
- Joon Seon!
- Gosh, stop that.
Shut it and get on your knees too.
- Right now.
- Got it.
Please. Just help us this once.
- Will bowing help?
- Joon Seon, stop!
Fine, just do whatever you want.
You'd better get him back
before dinner time though.
If you don't,
I'll hold you accountable.
And make sure
he doesn't injure himself.
Be good to him. Unbelievable.
I can't even turn a blind eye
because he's my son.
Although, he's more like
an enemy most days.
- Excuse me.
- Hello, ma'am. Can I help you?
Are you perhaps Song Young Dal
who used to live in Yeongcheon?
Yes, that's me.
May I ask who you are?
My gosh.
It really is you, Young Dal.
Don't you recognize me?
I'm Ji Hyang Soon,
the second daughter
of the oil store owner.
Hyang Soon?
Hyang Soon with the pigtails?
- That's right.
- My goodness!
- Gosh.
- My gosh.
I can't believe it.
Here you go.
Gosh, hasn't it been decades?
Staying alive has its perks.
Tell me about it.
How did you recognize me though?
I bet I look nothing
like my old self.
As if.
You look the same
apart from the wrinkles.
Goodness.
Did you stay in Yeongcheon
after my family moved to Seoul?
That reminds me.
What about your little sister?
Is she well?
My mom suggested
she move to another city...
and work for her cousin
as a live-in babysitter, remember?
She passed away.
What?
She suffered from a high fever.
I went to see her,
but the family she worked for
had run off in the night...
and my sister
had already passed away.
Really?
My goodness.
Were you never able
to recover a body?
I don't know how she died
or how long she was ill for.
There was no way to find out.
My gosh. We had no idea.
By the way,
I visited my mother's family
a few years ago...
and I heard some news
about her cousin.
The family...
runs a shoe store in Dapsimni.
Dapsimni?
Do you know the exact location?
No, I don't.
Someone saw them
or heard about them I guess.
They were mentioned in passing
when we were exchanging...
news about each other.
What? What kind of errand?
All right. Ok Ja and I will
try to manage, so don't be too late.
Sure thing. See you later.
He said he'd be briefly
stopping by the office,
but now he has an errand to run.
Never-ending work
is the story of my life.
Anyway, where on earth is Ok Ja?
She should be here by now.
Ok Boon...
Why are you running
late this morning?
It's just the two of us,
so I need all hands on deck.
We need to fry the chicken
and sell them all ourselves.
Ok Boon, I think I'm going to die.
Actually, I'd rather die,
so kill me.
Gosh, you reek of alcohol.
Did you drink last night?
How much does one need to drink
to smell like a barrel of alcohol?
Stop overreacting.
I only drank a few bottles.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6 bottles.
How could you do this
when you have work the next day?
What's gotten into you lately?
Are you upset with me
or your brother-in-law?
Tell us if you are...
instead of being moody and silent.
That's not the case.
I'm lonely, that's all.
They say every shoe comes in pairs,
but I don't
which makes me feel broken.
My gosh.
Why on earth would you be broken?
You just haven't met
the right man, that's all.
You're quite charming...
and you'll someday meet a man
who treasures you.
So pull yourself together...
and finish making the batter.
I'll heat up the oil.
All right.
She only said that
to get me working.
Spoken like a true owner.
I drank too much
because of that Button Eyes.
Gosh, my head.
Getting fresh air isn't working.
If I drink again, I'm a brute,
not a human being.
Gosh.
Was the mountain always that high?
(Dapsimni)
If he buried her after death,
he might remember where it was.
But it's not like there are
few shoe stores in Dapsimni.
Are you sure you can find them?
- Excuse me.
- Welcome.
It's like looking for a needle
in a haystack.
Excuse me. I got the wrong place.
Excuse me.
Did you live in Yeongcheon
a long time ago by any chance?
No, I didn't.
Oh, I see.
Okay. Thank you.
Bye.
You can't just bring...
a new stuntman after the test shot.
Why would you have test shots
if you were being like this?
I'm sorry. He sprained his ankle.
He's new, but he's just as good.
And he has the build
that's more similar to the actor's.
If you don't like him, we can
replace him for the next shooting.
You should've been careful.
You do have a fine figure,
but are you sure you can do this?
I'm not sure...
He says he can do this.
You can rely on him.
You do sound determined.
All right. I guess
I don't have a choice.
Min Su.
You remember the moves I taught you.
Just make sure to stick to them.
Just try to imitate us,
and we will take care of the rest.
I'll do Jeong Bong's spinning kick.
Are you sure you can do this?
You do have a long moving line.
I have no choice but to do it.
Do you want me to give up?
And you. Don't dream
in your sleep again.
If you do it again,
I'll just kill you.
Okay.
Let's just make it through today.
Once Jeong Bong gets better,
we can change it again. Okay?
- Yes.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- All right.
Just go shoot a video.
Okay.
Ready.
Action.
What?
Did you just see him?
My gosh.
Cut. Okay. That was great.
You're amazing.
Well done.
- Gosh.
- Well done.
Nice work.
I like it.
This is pickled garlic...
I've been eating in secret
without the girls.
And this is pickled perilla leaves.
I brushed them with sauce...
1 by 1 yesterday.
You didn't have to do this.
I just had to.
You don't look as good
as you used to do.
I'm just getting old.
It's just nature taking its course.
I know. But you should
watch what you eat now.
Dad. I mean, Monk.
Without you, I'm like
a kite without a string.
When I went through
all sorts of things running a bar,
I could hold out because of you...
as I thought I had
at least one person on my side.
Okay. I get it.
I'll make sure to eat right.
Thank you.
Make sure to eat them
with your meals.
And don't share them
with other monks.
Okay.
I should give you
some nice tea in return.
I just picked some good tea leaves
a few days ago.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
I'll put these in the fridge.
Okay.
Hello.
Hello, sir. I've been seeing you
quite often lately.
I know. I just stopped by
to see my sister.
Okay.
If you have some time,
would you join me for some tea?
Okay.
I guess you have company.
Yes. She's the important person
I talked about before.
She wouldn't mind if you joined us.
Who knows?
She might become
an important person to you too.
No. I will just go
see my sister today.
- All right then.
- Okay.
(Song Young Suk,
Born March 19, 1967)
I'll come again. Make sure
not to skip meals.
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
- Dr. Yoon.
- Bye. See you tomorrow.
Ms. Song, where are you now?
What?
In the public library.
I'm studying hard.
She's studying hard.
Everything about her is so cute.
This is crazy.
"I'm studying hard."
Wait.
I don't like my hair.
Okay.
Gosh, Mr. Yoon.
Sorry.
What brings you here?
What did you say?
Here.
After I came back to Korea,
I found out dentists need
computer-related certificates.
So I'm preparing for it.
Did you study a lot?
Yes. With people
studying hard around me,
I can stay focused.
So that's how you feel.
I guess I should serve
as a model for you.
That'd be great for me.
It's almost time,
so I'm nervous again.
I'm studying math with Na Hee today.
I should prepare my lesson
if I don't want to get hit.
I can't believe her. Why would she
hit such a small person like you?
She doesn't even care.
She just slaps me in the back, arms,
forehead, and back of the head.
Do you want me
to help you with that?
I told you. I'm a genius in math.
If you get some lessons from me
before studying with Na Hee,
you will never forget it.
I'd love that.
But you should prepare
for your exam.
You know I'm smart.
I'll just teach you a little
while studying.
And I like to solve math problems...
to rest my mind.
Shall we meet
at this time every day?
Every day?
Isn't that too much? You have a job.
I'm a dentist, so I get off on time,
and my exam is just a month away.
What do you say? Yes or no?
It's fine if you say no.
No, I'll do it. Tutor me.
But in return, I'll buy dinner.
- In the basement cafeteria.
- Okay, basement cafeteria.
Then I'll meet you here
every day until the exam.
Yes, Mr. Yoon. Oh, no.
Teacher.
Do you mind if we start today?
I'm stuck on a few problems.
Okay. What are they?
Bring them all to me.
Now you can solve this
using this formula.
The one below that as well.
It gave you this number.
What do you do with it?
- Number two.
- Number two?
Correct!
- You're a fast learner.
- You're a great teacher.
This is the only time this is valid.
This formula here.
What does it mean?
I don't know. What does it mean?
Sit a little further away.
Write that down again.
Write it down.
Can't you test me again?
Didn't you learn it in high school?
- Gyu Jin.
- Bo Young.
It's late. You're leaving now?
Yes. I did some reading.
Why are you here?
To wash this.
Our usual toilet is busy.
Oh, I see.
Oh, how is Si Hoo?
His breathing is back to normal.
I owe it to Dr. Song.
She checked on him often.
What did I tell you?
She's better than me.
Let's go. I need to get something
from the convenience store.
- Let's go while Si Hoo's asleep.
- Okay. Let's go.
How are you...
Yes?
Are you done?
Yes. I'm about to go home.
Good. Let's have dinner together.
I was going to eat at home.
Eat out with me.
You said you'd be my buddy.
Not for dinner too.
Okay, then. Let's eat.
Good. I knew you'd say yes,
so I made a reservation.
The new restaurant
got some nice reviews.
Are you okay with steak?
Yes. I'm not craving
anything particular,
and I usually eat what I'm given.
It's good that you eat
whatever you're given.
I get that I'm the hospital outcast,
but why don't you have
any friends to eat with?
You're wrong. I have many friends.
No, I don't think you do.
You always want to eat with me.
You need to find a girlfriend.
Why waste money on treating me?
Treat the woman you like.
That's what I'm doing.
What do you mean?
The woman I like...
is going with me to eat dinner.
Hi, Si Hoo.
Okay. Mom will be right back.
Bye.
(Once Again)
Is there anything you want to do
after the exam?
Do you have a bucket list?
I want to do a lot.
What about dating?
Will you really not date?
- Will you bring him next time?
- What?
Hey, Hyo Sin. Work with us.
Hey. Hey, Hyo Sin!
How can I get to him?
That's how you confess your love.
Is the director in?
So, will you date him?
Why? Are you bothered that I might?
So will you see him or not?