(Episode 29)
It's freezing.
Can't I have my jacket back?
No, I'm still freezing.
Is she gone?
Yes, she's gone.
What is this mess?
I bet I'm the only forty-year-old...
to get kicked out of the house
by his mom.
What did I even do wrong?
Let's not unnecessarily
point fingers.
You're to blame as well...
considering how you started
the train of divorce.
I'm sorry about all this.
Don't say that. We're all to blame.
We shouldn't have provoked Mom...
- Someone's coming!
- What?
What on earth?
Why are the four of you
sitting out here?
- Dad!
My gosh.
Dad, my gosh.
Still, honey. You can't kick out
our grown-up kids.
The neighbors will talk.
You kick them out
when you're angry too.
Why don't I get to do it?
I still let them put on their shoes.
Just look at the state they're in.
Why would I have gone this far?
What Yun Jeong said to me
on the street earlier...
How is it that no one
understands how I feel?
Anyway, I don't want
to hear another word.
I'm done with them all.
I didn't realize it the last time,
but it's quite spacious.
Where do I sleep?
Just find a place.
The closet doesn't
seem like an option...
and joining you in
the master bedroom...
is unimaginable.
I should just crash on the couch.
It's not bad. All right.
Gyu Jin, don't sigh.
You brought this on yourself.
Why would you tell Mom about me?
I don't care how angry you were,
but that was careless of you.
You only added fuel to the flame.
You're happy to be
out of her house, aren't you?
"No" should be my answer,
but I can't lie.
I would've said something sooner
if this was going to be the outcome.
I do feel bad for Mom,
but saving myself
seems more important.
This is comfortable.
Darn it.
What's wrong? Are you stuck?
Gosh, are you still awake?
Sorry, I'll keep it down.
What are you stuck on? Math?
Yes, you know it has never
been my best subject.
The university I wish to get into
requires a math score,
so it's as if
I'm back in high school.
All right. Let me see.
It's all right. You're upset anyway,
so I'll deal with this on my own.
I've interrupted
your studies enough.
Come on. Let me help.
What? You?
You idiot. How is the answer "one"?
Is it zero then?
Or minus one?
This must be a joke.
Just guess instead.
I'll make some dice
out of your eraser for you.
My eraser? Right, my eraser.
I was just saying that.
It's not like I meant it.
You can't distinguish jokes
or even solve math problems.
Take a look at this.
All right. Where are you stuck on?
Well... Right here.
Hey, this is one of
the basic concepts.
You can't go on like this.
I'll help you study
at least an hour a day.
Every day?
Gosh, I'd be thrilled
to have a private tutor.
How nice. I'm the luckiest.
Focus.
How boring.
Slapstick comedy is so outdated.
I feel bad for Mom,
but this is paradise.
This is awesome!
Jae Seok,
you should clean up a little
after your shower.
There's soapy water everywhere.
Go and clean up.
Hold on. Stop snacking on the couch.
Do you know how hard it is
to get the crumbs out?
Clean up right now.
Okay, fine. I'll clean up later.
Not later. Do it now.
Get to it right away.
Fine, I will.
Get in there and clean up.
Hurry.
There's no need to get violent,
you know.
I'd like to keep the peace too,
so clean up already.
You're exhausting.
A man shouldn't be this nagging.
I finally get why
Na Hee divorced you.
- You little...
- My gosh.
Hey. Clean up already!
Fine, I will!
Get to it right away.
I will. I'm getting to it now.
- See? I'm cleaning up.
- Clean up.
- Okay, I'll get to it later.
- Right now.
Clean up after yourself!
- Stop hitting me.
- Clean up!
Here you go.
I hope the soup's not salty.
My taste buds have been off lately.
Gosh, Ms. Jang. It's delicious.
It's the best mallow soup
I've ever had.
He's right. It's truly delicious.
Really? I'm glad then.
Why aren't you eating with us?
You should get a bite to eat.
It's fine. I'll eat some later.
I'll get going first.
Stay and finish your meals.
Sure.
They should've
buried the hatchet that day,
- but that mean lady...
- Ga Hee, please.
What lady? Did something happen?
It's nothing.
Knowing will only upset you.
That reminds me.
Aren't you filming something today?
Yes, we're getting
our headshots taken today.
Headshots?
Yes, it's to hand them out
to TV networks and film studios.
We're thinking of a concept
that'll stick in people's minds.
So where are we taking these photos?
A studio in Gangnam?
Okay.
Awesome.
Seo Young will touch these up later,
so this is more than good enough.
Let's take some of you guys now.
How about a test-shot?
- Sure.
- Got it.
Wait.
What are you doing?
We don't have the time. Now, get up.
- Sure.
- Got it.
Look this way.
Smile for the first one.
Here we go. Smile, guys.
This isn't right.
How can you look
this scary while smiling?
Let's start with
no expressions first.
Go ahead.
Nice. This is way better.
Here we go. 1, 2, 3.
Okay, one more.
1, 2, 3.
Awesome, guys.
(Pediatrician Song Na Hee)
- Hello, doctor.
- Hi.
Dr. Yoon, can I get you some coffee?
It's fine. I'll get it myself.
Hasn't Dr. Song come to work yet?
I'm sure she has. Should I call her?
No, I can do that. Thanks.
(Bo Young)
Hi, Bo Young.
How's Si Hoo? Is he doing all right?
Yes, he's good.
You see,
I'm teaching a class
near your hospital later on.
Really?
You must be in high demand.
I really should swing by sometime.
You're always welcome here.
Could we perhaps...
meet up for lunch later?
Lunch?
If I'm free too then...
Sorry, Bo Young.
We'll have lunch some other time.
Are you here for a beverage?
Let me get it for you.
Here.
I'd like to apologize
for what happened yesterday.
My mom crossed the line.
Your mother has every right
to be angry.
It's fine.
My mom crossed the line too.
Should I...
call Mother personally
and apologize?
- That could ease...
- Why would you?
What?
My mom isn't
your mother-in-law anymore...
and you're no longer her son-in-law.
You calling her
won't appease her anger in any way.
It'll only provoke her.
Of course.
I should've known better.
We'll handle it separately.
I'll take care of my mom,
you take care of yours.
It won't be easy, but still.
Gosh.
Why are they together like that?
Guys, it's almost time
for the meeting.
We'll stick to what
we've been doing so far...
and make decisions
on community outreach later.
- Got it.
- Sure.
Then let's wrap up today's meeting.
By the way, should meetings
like this be held daily?
Normally, it's on
Mondays and Fridays,
but we meet up often
during presentation season.
I checked the logs...
and many meetings
didn't seem necessary.
Notices can be sent out to you
in different ways, right?
How about we stick to
one meeting per week?
- Nice.
- Sounds good.
Let's be flexible
with when we gather too.
We could meet briefly
before the afternoon shift.
Or we could meet
before we get off work.
Ms. Sim, I'd like you
to check the schedule.
Okay, I will.
All right. That's all for today.
I hope you all will have a good day.
- Thank you.
Gosh, Gyu Jin.
It took only 20 minutes.
I know.
Dr. Song,
do you want to grab a coffee?
Good. As long as you pay.
Okay.
Gosh, my head.
I finished a whole bottle of wine.
I wish I could detach my head
and have it sterilized.
Those punks.
Even if they call me,
I won't answer it.
You guys should try worrying
about me for a change.
Are they afraid to call me?
Still, I'm sure
they are feeling antsy.
I bet they can't even concentrate
on their work...
leaving their old mom all alone.
All right.
Yes, Director Lee.
Dr. Song. Did you have lunch yet?
No. I was about to leave.
That's good. Will you eat with me?
I have no one to eat with.
I'd rather eat alone though.
I don't want to eat alone.
And I don't want to look
like an outcast.
Can't you help me with that,
Dr. Song?
- What?
- Hey, listen.
I sound just like Lee Sun Kyun.
This is the first order for today.
- The first order for today.
What are you guys doing?
You've got a plan.
- What was that?
- Gosh.
- Darn it.
- Hang on.
Can I have stir-fried spicy pork?
That's Pengsoo.
- Peng-hi.
- Aren't I good?
- What?
They don't seem worried at all.
What are they so excited about?
Those punks.
Those rascals.
Gyu Jin.
About the new hospital director.
Isn't he great?
Maybe it's because he's young,
but he seems reasonable, smart,
and on the same page as us.
Tell me about it.
I'm sorry to say this,
but a certain someone didn't listen
and kept repeating himself.
Unlike the previous director
who used to torture us with words...
He's completely different.
I could see hearts
in the nurses' eyes.
I guess my best years have gone.
Shut it and eat your meal.
- What's that?
- Hello.
- Are they best friends or what?
- I know.
- What? You're right.
They seem quite close.
And they look good together.
Hey.
You have afternoon appointments.
Just finish your meal.
Let's sit over there.
Gosh, I feel better now.
So why did you cram your food
into your mouth like that?
Gyu Jin.
Be honest with me.
You were bothered, weren't you?
By the new director and Na Hee...
I mean Dr. Song.
I'm not bothered at all.
They were quite close
back in school too.
Is that true? Really?
Sure. That's true.
Let's just say it is.
By the way, Na Hee...
I mean Dr. Song...
seems to have chosen
the young director's connections...
instead of the old ones.
Can't I just call her Na Hee?
I don't know. I don't even care.
Hey.
You didn't fold the blankets
on the sofa this morning.
And why did you not put away...
the cereal bowl on the table?
Why are you talking about that
all of a sudden?
I told you before.
I will kick you out if need be.
There you go again with the nagging.
Oh, whatever.
- I can't hear you.
- Listen carefully.
If you keep acting like this,
you can't live with me.
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
- I don't know.
- Jae Seok. Jae Seok!
Gosh, that silly...
So... Do you want more soup?
It's okay.
Are you pressuring me to leave
because I'm done eating?
Gosh, no. That's not what I meant.
Business seems slow today.
It's usually very crowded.
That's because it's exam season.
I guess your customers are mostly
students and market vendors.
It must be nice to have
lots of regulars and pretty looks.
I'm so jealous.
Are you kidding me?
We're the ones who are
jealous of you.
Me? Why?
You have a good environment
to work in.
I mean the delivery guy.
Delivery? Are you talking
about Hyo Sin?
I guess his name is Hyo Sin.
Even his name sounds handsome.
He's totally our type.
We both like tall guys.
Height is what determines his style.
And we do care about looks too.
I don't care for tall guys
with ugly faces.
I easily get tired of them.
And I like taciturn guys.
That's the most important part.
Some guys are very talkative.
I just hate them.
So you don't like talkative guys.
- Of course we don't.
- I hate them.
- They are the worst.
What about age?
Do you not care about a man's age?
I prefer guys
who are younger than me.
I don't like old men.
Me neither. They stink.
So does the delivery guy
not have a girlfriend?
I bet he does.
I don't know.
He doesn't seem to have one.
Do you want me to look into it?
- Can you do that?
- That would be great.
If he doesn't have a girlfriend,
I will seduce him.
So you like guys like him.
You sweeties.
I'm just happy for you.
Let's laugh together.
Okay.
She's funny.
Dream on, Chi Su.
It's not going to happen.
Stop wasting your time
and just come to me.
Cho Yeon, this way.
Any store would be just fine.
They make sesame oil with seeds
they get from their in-laws' farm.
So it's much more flavorful.
It's on a higher level
than imported ones.
Ma'am, she will take some
Korean sesame oil.
2 bottles? Or 3?
I will stock up on some.
- I'll have three bottles.
- Okay.
- How much is it for a bottle?
- It's 20 dollars.
It's 60 dollars for 3 bottles.
Why is it so expensive?
Just take 55 dollars.
What are you talking about?
That wouldn't even pay
for the bottles.
That can't be right.
We're not just any old customer.
Will you be like that to members
of the merchant association?
Please stop it.
She should make some profit too.
- Here's 60 dollars.
- Thank you.
All right then. Give her...
some sesame seeds then.
Okay. I'll do that.
Happy now?
Honey, get her three bottles
of sesame oil.
See? It's good to have me around.
You should buy me sundaeguk today.
Okay. I will.
I will buy you sundaeguk,
so stop trying to act cute.
It isn't working.
I guess you like it.
You seem to like it a lot.
I said stop. I hate it.
Okay.
What was that? You startled me.
You're so naughty.
I'm upset.
Don't be upset.
You're funny.
Where's Hyo Sin?
Is he out on a delivery?
- Yes. Why?
- What?
I just have a few
questions to ask him.
Hyo Sin doesn't seem
to have a girlfriend, right?
I'm sure he finished high school.
Do you think he Is
from the countryside?
I don't know.
He rarely talks about himself.
I know.
Even a ghost wouldn't know what he's
up to if he doesn't say anything.
It's been a while
since he joined us,
but we don't know
much about Hyo Sin.
Forget about it.
Don't even try
prying into his affairs.
Why not? I'm just doing it
because I care about him.
I bet he doesn't talk
about himself for a reason.
Just don't ask him, okay?
Okay.
But what reason?
Do you know something?
- Oh, come on.
- Oh, come on. Come on.
Enjoy the food.
(Yuyoung Judo)
Park Hyo Sin?
You're Hyo Sin, aren't you?
My goodness.
How are you?
We haven't met in a while
and this is all I can offer.
It's fine. Thank you.
I coached judo for a few years
at a countryside high school.
My wife's family lives nearby.
I opened this gym here
about three years ago.
What have you been up to?
I heard you quit.
I just do whatever odd jobs I can.
I see.
Did you quit...
training altogether?
Yes.
What a pity.
It's hard to find talent like you
in your weight class.
If it hadn't been for
that incident...
Come by whenever
you want to work out.
You must be itching to train.
You don't have to pay.
Okay.
You're leaving on time.
Yes. My afternoon was pretty short.
You're leaving early too.
I have fewer patients now,
because of our scandal.
You must be pleased.
The new director seems to like you.
Jeong Rok?
We get along pretty well.
I guess you do. It shows.
Go ahead. I'm waiting for Jae Seok.
He stays with me now.
Mom kicked him out.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
As if you get along pretty well.
It must be great to have
a powerful backer.
What's taking him so long?
Darn him.
Hello? Hey, Gyu Jin.
Why aren't you here yet?
You have to clean up
the mess you made this morning.
Gyu Jin, I left work already.
Someone suddenly asked to meet.
I think I'll be home late.
See you at home later.
Drive safely.
Hey. I'll kill you if you hang up.
Darn him! Darn him!
I thought I could breathe
if I got away from Mom,
but why is he even worse?
Good.
Don't you think they look nice?
It's not nice at all.
It's so outdated, I can't stand it.
Why do they look so solemn?
It looks like this was shot
before they were executed.
And it shows that
you took it yourselves.
- Does it look that bad?
- Yes.
Why? I think it looks okay.
It's unique in its own way.
- "Unique"?
"Unique"?
- Is that a good thing?
- I think so.
Really? You really think it's nice?
Yes, it's not too bad.
And Dad, you have me, don't you?
You know me. I've been a hardcore
GOT7 fan for three years.
Even the webmaster
waits for my work.
Does that mean
she's good at tweaking photos?
Watch this.
First, I add a filter
that brightens things up,
then I accentuate your cheekbones.
A smaller face and taller body.
Then if I give you
broader shoulders...
- Tada!
- My gosh!
- Hey, is that really us?
- No way.
Let me see. Hey, this is fraud.
Ji Hun, isn't this too much?
Even kids do this much nowadays.
- Really?
- Yes.
Seo Young, do this with my photo.
I'd like a new profile picture.
- Make my face smaller.
- Okay.
Even she can't make you look pretty.
What's so funny?
- You're home?
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Welcome home.
Look at this, Auntie.
I worked wonders
on Dad's profile picture.
Wait.
Seo Young, shouldn't you be
in class right now?
What? Well...
I feel cold.
I feel like I'm coming down
with something.
I have a headache.
Today, I have no choice
but to skip class.
Really? Does your mom know?
Joon Seon, does she know?
No. I have to tell her.
I'll tell her later.
Joon Seon.
If your daughter is skipping class,
you should scold her.
Why are you hanging out with her?
If the parents have
different approaches to education,
the kid is bound to be confused.
- This is why Hyun Gyung...
- Na Hee.
What about dinner? Did you eat?
Not yet. I'll get changed.
Okay.
I told you to leave early.
I really didn't know
she'd come home early.
How does that brat
dare to lecture me?
I have my own philosophy.
Dad. Is she going to
stay here forever?
I feel uncomfortable.
So do I.
- Shall we go play in my room?
- Can we?
Seo Jin, shall we play in
the rooftop room? Yes?
Let's go.
Follow me.
You used your elbow? Your elbow?
Wait, wait. Time out. Time out.
This is unfair.
Didn't Seo Jin point at
Jong Soo and not me?
She pointed at him.
No, she pointed at you.
That's two penalties.
No, wait! Time out!
Sorry.
Seo Jin, earlier on,
did you point at him?
You did, right? Seo Jin, am I right?
Seo Jin, say something.
You jerk.
How dare you say that to her?
- Are you out of your mind?
- Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Seo Jin, I'm really sorry.
Seo Jin, they're so funny,
aren't they?
- Hyo Sin.
- Hi.
Why are you back so late?
What time do you leave work?
Do you eat dinner elsewhere?
What do you like?
Snacks? Korean food?
Right. What's your number?
Can I have your number?
Song Seo Young. Leave.
Why? Things were just getting fun.
Leave. You have math class.
Mom will be angry if you miss that.
Earlier, you said
we could play together.
Go already.
I have to go, Hyo Sin.
I'll see you around.
No, you won't. Get out of here. Go!
Okay.
Is the game over?
With me getting beaten up?
Hey, you. Get out of the way.
I was going to help her with math.
Why isn't she back yet?
- Hi, Na Hee.
- Where are you?
Why?
I'm waiting to help you with math.
Where are you?
Right now, I'm still at the library.
The district library.
I'm being so efficient today that...
I want to stay longer.
Until 10 p.m.
Is that so?
Okay. You should study when you can.
Good luck. Take care.
Okay. Don't wait up for me.
You must be tired.
I feel really bad.
Go to bed first.
Really, please don't wait up. Bye.
I'm starving.
Mr. Yoon.
Ms. Song.
I feel much better now.
All my friends had other plans,
and I really didn't
want to eat alone.
I was really hungry too.
What are we both doing here
when we have homes to go to?
Exactly.
So, I stayed with Gyu Jin
for a few days...
and realized
your sister was a saint.
I've never met a man
who nags so much.
Gyu Jin is the worst.
Don't say that when
you don't know the full truth.
You can't deal with my sister
unless you have a rock-solid will.
She's really gifted at
making people feel uncomfortable.
Why do you think I'm wandering
instead of going home?
My gosh.
My brother even hit me, okay?
Na Hee doesn't resort to violence.
Feel this.
Is that a bump? I felt another head.
She says she will teach me math
each night and...
Do you finally get how she truly is?
I see those two
were perfect for each other.
Couldn't they just have
stayed together...
instead of harassing
innocent civilians like us?
Tell me about it!
Shouldn't you
go to your mother though?
I walked by her cafe earlier
and it wasn't open.
No way. I should stay clear
since she's still furious.
It's best to stay away for now.
Still,
she gets lonely easily.
I'm sure she's waiting for you
to come home.
No way.
I bet I'm right.
She's too proud to call you first,
so stop by her place if you can.
Isn't it your job
to be a bridge between...
your mom and brother?
Mom?
Where is she? Mom?
What the...
Why on earth are you here, you punk?
Mom, what are you doing
on the floor?
You startled me.
Shut it and leave.
I don't need any of you, so go!
How much did you have to drink?
Your eyes are out of focus
and you're slurring your words.
Mind your own business!
Darn you brats.
I saw that you've been...
having the time of your lives
after abandoning me.
You darn punks.
Did you come by the hospital? When?
Shut it!
Leave.
- Get out. I'm done with you.
- Mom, wait.
- Leave!
- Fine, I will.
I will in just a second.
Don't drink too much though.
You're only ruining your health.
- Eat your meals instead.
- Shut it!
I don't want to hear any of it.
Just leave, okay?
- Go!
- Fine, I'm going, aren't I?
All right.
- I'm going.
- Go!
Just leave.
What?
He isn't coming back?
I can't believe he actually left.
Can't he read between the lines?
This is what I get for
listening to Ms. Song.
She still hates my guts.
I'm not comfortable
in my own house...
and Gyu Jin's isn't any better.
There is no place for me to rest.
I guess it boils down
to not having money.
Mom's kimchi jjigae?
Even the smell of it is to die for.
I love kimchi jjigae with pork.
Just so you know,
I've gained some weight.
It's all your fault.
Me too.
You can blame me all you want,
so eat up.
Those doing physical activities
shouldn't eat poorly.
Hyo Sin, you should eat up too.
I'm already enjoying a lot.
Ms. Jang, you should join us.
He's right.
You should eat with us...
instead of eating alone.
Yes, Mom, have a seat.
Mom, please have a seat.
Come on.
Here's your coffee.
Ga Hee, let me take that.
You didn't have to
bring this up yourself.
I was hoping to enjoy mine here too.
The tension between...
Mom and Na Hee
could freeze up the whole house.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- Thank you.
Joon Seon, have you healed from
the failed family dinner disaster?
Did you have to bring it up
when I've been trying to move on?
This is your biggest flaw.
You always try to catch both rabbits
when you need to make a choice.
Family or your career.
Sometimes you must choose one.
The director said
we'd be done by four.
Those jerks at TV networks...
act like they'll
keep their promises...
only to put us on the back-burner.
They couldn't care less
about our basic rights.
They're always in control.
I won't ever work
with that director again.
I won't even if it's a big role.
I won't agree to it
even if my character has lines.
Yes, Director.
Of course I got home in one piece.
A new project of yours?
What do you mean
by a significant role?
What? Of course, I'm on board.
I'll give it everything I have.
Thank you so much.
Guys, say you're grateful.
- Thank you.
- Once more.
- Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Hold on a second.
Let me bow down to you.
Guys, come on.
Please accept our bows.
- Thank you!
(Episode 30)
I know that I'm being
petty and childish.
I didn't say anything.
Yes, you were,
with that gaze of yours.
I don't want to be like this either.
I know no one's
more upset than Na Hee,
but my anger flares up
every time I see her.
Let's just get over there.
We need to divide zones
for today's general cleaning.
I'm not in the mood for that.
Couldn't he postpone it?
Being the president's wife
doesn't have any benefits.
All I have is a dense husband.
Where should we go?
That place seems nice.
- But it's...
- Good morning.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Good morning, Director Lee.
Have you had coffee this morning?
If not, I'm willing to buy.
We already had ours.
We're grateful for the offer though.
I wanted to talk about
today's team dinner.
We were talking about that too.
How about the galbi place
or the shabu-shabu restaurant?
Wouldn't a buffet
be a better choice?
Everyone likes different things...
and Korean barbecue means grilling
which could be annoying.
We're totally on board,
Director Lee.
Of course. It's the best ever!
So we'll go to a buffet
for our team dinner.
I'll look for a decent place
we can go to.
Also, it's not mandatory,
so you may skip it
if you have other plans.
Okay? Good day, then.
My gosh. How can one be this smart?
Doesn't he have a sweet voice too?
Yes?
I'm here to deliver a notice.
We're having a welcome dinner
for the new director at 6 p.m.
It's at a sushi buffet
and attendance isn't mandatory.
Will you be there, Na Hee...
I mean, Dr. Song.
Sure. It's not like I have
anyone at home waiting for me.
Okay, so you'll be there.
I have to make reservations,
you see.
A team dinner?
Why today? I have a research paper
I need to finish revising.
Just give me an answer.
Will you be there or not?
I need to see who's attending
and make reservations.
Is everyone else going?
You said attendance isn't mandatory.
But everyone is going...
including Na Hee...
I mean, Dr. Song.
Anyway, I'll ask you one last time.
Will you be there or not?
I'll be there.
I'll come back to this after dinner.
I still need to eat anyway, right?
Okay, so everyone will be there.
That reminds me.
I didn't tell you
because you were already asleep,
but I went to see Mom
just to be kicked out again.
She was totally drunk.
Really?
What the... What on earth is that?
Gosh, my head.
What time is it?
Jae Seok probably told him,
but he still hasn't called.
That brat.
Maybe I shouldn't have
kicked Jae Seok out last night.
Is it Jae Seok?
Yun Jeong, it's us. Open up.
It's us. Let us in.
Why on earth are they here?
How will they annoy me this time?
Unbelievable.
Try some.
It's abalone porridge
from a store in Cheongdam-dong.
Thanks. I'll enjoy it.
We were shocked
to read the news article.
What on earth happened?
I have no idea.
I must've sinned in my past life.
This is why one must be cautious
when welcoming a daughter-in-law.
Do you remember the girl that
I wanted to set Gyu Jin up with?
The second daughter of CEO Min.
She married an accountant
and has been a devoted wife.
Her in-laws couldn't
adore her any more.
They consider her their lucky charm.
That's something I regret too.
I should've never
approved this marriage.
Do it right when it
comes to Jae Seok then.
Jae Seok? That'll take a while.
He just got back to Korea...
and he doesn't seem interested
in marriage yet.
Do you want to be
stabbed in the back again?
Just set him up with women
when you can.
On a blind date?
As if that idiot
would ever go on a blind date.
It's why you should take action...
before he brings home some riffraff.
Do you want me
to set him up with someone?
How about the youngest daughter
of Mr. Hong...
whom you met at the fundraiser?
The one who's working
as a gallery curator...
after finishing her studies abroad?
Exactly. The family is looking
for a doctor son-in-law.
She seems perfect for Jae Seok.
Their ages are compatible too.
Really?
The family is looking
for a doctor son-in-law?
(Script by Park Hye Jin,
Directed by Bae Tae Jin)
So what's my role in this?
The protagonist
is a young mob boss...
and he has two trustworthy men
by his side.
You want us to be the stuntmen...
for the protagonist
and his two henchmen?
Yes, action scenes will continue...
throughout the series.
If you let us take on the role,
we'll give you everything we have.
Sure, then you're on board...
- Just a second.
- Sure.
Yes, sir.
I'm in a meeting...
Sorry?
Sure thing.
Got it.
So when does filming begin?
- I'm sorry but...
- Yes?
My boss is recommending
another stunt agency.
I'm afraid I'll have
to sit with him too.
I see.
I'm Jang Ho Beom from Action Art.
I look forward to working with you.
The situation isn't ideal,
but we need to hire
the best company.
We'll settle this with an audition.
How does next week sound?
Sure. Bring it on.
Sure thing.
I wonder if Jeong Bong
and Jong Soo have improved.
When they worked for me,
they normally stuck
to cleaning the floors...
because they weren't good enough.
They've improved so much...
that they can now lick ceilings
when they jump.
The leader can make a difference
in this line of work, right?
Joon Seon, don't try too hard.
There's no way you can beat us.
I know, which is why
we need to work harder.
It's not like I have
connections like you do.
Someone as clean as me...
can only work his butt off...
to beat the likes of you
in any capacity.
Sure thing.
Then work as hard as you can.
Good luck.
Hold on.
Here's my business card.
(Good Action, Song Joon Seon,
Don't call)
How childish.
See you!
- Get the trivet.
- Sure.
Hurry.
Here you go.
Seriously?
A sacred free weight?
How clever of you!
Good job. It's perfect.
Look. Isn't it perfect?
- Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food.
Stop right there!
That is why...
we'll begin a special
training program as of today.
Until the audition next week,
our goal is to be
as light and nimble as we can.
That punk, Jang Ho Beom.
Let's teach
that slimy jerk a lesson.
Can you do this?
Yes, of course!
We'll make it happen!
Yes, let's do this.
- 1, 2, let's go.
- Let's go!
We're just never in sync.
Gosh, over here.
- Goodness.
- Tell me about it.
All right, here we go.
Let's sweep.
- Hold on.
- Here you go.
- My gosh.
- Did you have to do that?
- Here we go.
- Sweep, everyone.
- All right.
- Here we go.
Pass one each
to the merchants at the market.
It's from the association.
Is there enough to go around though?
I think there is.
Gosh, it's nice and cool.
They must've been in the fridge.
Young Dal,
you're as sweet as always.
Would you Like one?
Open the cap for me then.
Gosh, it's hot in here.
You clumsy man.
You've got bits of tissue
on your face.
Why not help me take it off
instead of nagging me about it?
- Come on.
- What on earth...
I can't believe
you're asking me to do this.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome.
Cho Yeon, what brings you by?
I was wondering if I could borrow
a folding ladder.
Spiderwebs are all over
the top part of our sign.
I want to clean it,
but it's too high up.
Of course you can borrow it.
Let's go. I'll get it done for you.
Young Dal, where's the ladder?
I'll go with you then.
While we're at it,
we can clean the other signs too.
Really? Then bring the ladder, okay?
- Cho Yeon, shall we?
- Sure.
- Please watch your step.
- Got it.
He's treating her like a princess.
(Yongju Traditional Market
Merchant Co-op)
It's from the merchant association.
Quench your thirst.
- Thank you.
Thanks for this.
Thanks.
Get your beverages!
First come, first served.
Get one before they run out.
What do you mean
first-come-first-served?
They'll get here quicker this way.
We don't have all day.
- Hi.
- Can I get one too?
- Here.
- What's this?
- Is it from the association?
- Yes.
Can I get one too?
I was thirsty anyway.
Please form a line
in front of the president's wife.
You each get one,
so don't ask for more.
Gosh, thank you, Ms. Jang.
By the way, how have you been?
Sorry?
Oh, right. Yes, I've been fine.
Of course.
You should get over it
as fast as you can.
Your kids' lives
never go the way you want them to.
Anyway, hang in there.
Sure.
Ok Boon, I'll take three.
They're for the rice cake store.
Don't be too upset, okay?
She's pretty and good at her job.
What's there to worry about?
I'm sure she'll meet
someone special again.
Have a good day.
Ms. Jang, can I get one too?
You must be so upset.
Children are such nuisances,
aren't they?
We're always worried about them
no matter what.
Don't you think so?
You're right.
Hey, you take care of this.
- Gosh, Ok Boon.
- Ms. Jang.
- Gosh.
- Hey!
You silly thing.
Why are you so tactless?
What did I do?
- Just give me that. Don't drink it.
- Darn it.
Give it back to me.
Chi Su, sweep the right part.
- Where? Here?
- Yes.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
Okay. I guess it's done.
Right, Cho Yeon?
Yes. I think it's good enough.
Both of you are so skilled.
Young Dal. Young Dal!
What's wrong?
Is there a fire or something?
It's not like that.
I think you should go to Ok Boon.
What's wrong with her?
Did she get hurt?
She's hurt mentally, not physically.
- You should go see her.
- What?
Wait. What's wrong?
Why did Ms. Jang get hurt?
Just mind your spiderweb.
Are you done
cleaning the spiderwebs?
Yes. I was going
to give them some iced coffee,
but the president left right away.
Why? What's the rush?
I don't know.
He just took off
as he heard that his wife is hurt.
He doesn't seem like one,
but he's such a devoted husband.
You know loving husbands
can't be mean.
Look at you. You called him
a cold-hearted man before.
I know. You even said you hate
this neighborhood because of him,
and that you're so unlucky
with neighbors.
I know what I said,
which is why I'm correcting myself.
I should've borrowed
the ladder sooner.
I struggled with my short arms
without one...
and ended up covered in dust.
I'll go get changed.
Okay. Take your time.
My gosh. Darn it.
Why? What's wrong?
What are you doing?
You can't even drink.
What do you think you're doing?
Give me that! Without it,
I don't think
I can deal with this anger.
I feel like I'm about to burst!
What? It's empty already.
Gosh, I'm so frustrated.
I'm so angry.
Gosh.
Why? Do you need more alcohol?
Do you want to drink with me?
You're here.
Yes.
Gosh, that's not the right spot.
What are you doing?
I'm glad you're home.
Today's training session was rough.
Can you put this on my back?
Where's Jong Soo?
He's taking a shower.
And Joon Seon is downstairs.
- Is it here?
- Yes.
No, that's not it.
A little to the left.
Gosh, you should tell me
before you strip it off.
- So it should be here.
- Yes.
You moved it too far.
Move it to the right.
Slightly to the right...
Why do you keep
tearing it off so suddenly?
So it should be here.
I said left. It should go left.
It should be in the middle,
you stupid...
Hey. You're doing this on purpose,
aren't you?
You're trying to mess with me,
What's wrong, Jeong Bong?
He's trifling with me.
Bring it on.
Come on.
I was going to teach you a lesson.
Today is the day.
You should be grateful
that I have sore muscles today.
- You're startled, aren't you?
- Gosh, stop it.
Jeong Bong, you can't kill him.
Don't stop me.
It's bound to happen at least once.
Gosh, Jeong Bong.
- Turning kick.
- Jeong Bong.
- I'll kick you.
- Please.
What's going on?
Who told you
to make a fuss like that?
So you have the energy to do this.
Do you need more training?
No, it's not like that.
I just tried to stop them.
Gosh, what's wrong with me?
Enjoy your food.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
You didn't bring much food.
Aren't you hungry?
Not really.
Maybe we should've
gone to a barbecue restaurant.
Buffets are always like that.
There are a lot of dishes
to choose from,
but we don't know what to eat...
or how much to eat.
It just makes us hesitate.
It sounds like a happy hesitation.
You think? I guess you're right.
It's a lot better
than other kinds of hesitations.
Try this. It tastes good.
Have you not eaten in days?
What's with all the food?
I don't want to walk around.
Why do you even breathe?
That's a lot of work.
So I cram down air when I breathe.
By the way...
It has a strong flavor.
That's why I like it.
Thank you.
What?
Gyu Jin, there's something going on.
You know I have a good hunch
when it comes to these things.
That's more flirting
than being friendly colleagues.
At least one of them has feelings
for the other.
Don't be silly
and finish your mountain of food.
Are you sure
you don't care about it at all?
Of course I don't.
She's not with me anymore.
You're just trying to act cool.
Even I'm bothered.
What?
It's Mom. Why is she calling?
She yelled at me
and kicked me out yesterday.
Why is she calling?
Gyu Jin, what do you think?
Just answer it.
Then you'll find out.
Hello, Mom. Hang on a second.
If you are done eating, can we go?
The next round is on me.
That's great.
Gyu Jin, are you coming with us?
The director is paying.
Must we go to a second round?
Yes, Mom. I'm at a team dinner
and it was quite noisy.
I can talk now. What's the matter?
Is the dinner over yet?
Yes. We're almost done.
Why? You beat me up
and kicked me out yesterday.
What do you want to know?
Don't be silly and come home now.
What? Right now?
The dinner isn't over yet.
You said it's almost over.
Just come right away.
Within 30 minutes.
Mom.
Gosh, what was that?
She's so one-sided.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Why? I came right away
without going to the second round.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Mom, just say it.
You must've called me in
so urgently for a reason.
Do you want me to spy on Gyu Jin?
That's what I'm good at.
I want you to go on a blind date.
What did you say?
A blind date for marriage.
I've made up my mind.
I will never let you
choose your own wife.
I'll check her background,
personality, and everything...
to choose
a good wife for you myself.
Mom, in this day and age?
Who has arranged marriages
these days?
Besides, I don't even
want to get married.
I don't believe in marriage.
Okay. Don't be so sure about that.
Just meet the girl.
If you don't like her,
I'll find someone else.
Make a suggestion
that makes sense...
if you want me to accept...
If not,
will you come back home?
What?
You don't want to live here.
Don't you prefer to
live with Gyu Jin?
It's up to you.
Come back home,
or go on a blind date.
Dance with us, everyone!
Director Lee.
At all costs, at all costs
Why aren't you married?
When did you last have a girlfriend?
My last girlfriend?
It was so long ago,
I don't remember.
Has it been seven years?
No way. Why?
You must have high standards.
What do you care about?
What kind of woman do you like?
Why are you so curious?
You're all leaning in.
I guess I like someone
who's honest and funny.
Someone I get along with.
Personality over looks?
- That's a tough standard.
- It is.
You're picky.
Am I?
The love I have for you
Is a special, express kind of love
- At all costs
- Come on!
Next up is Dr. Yoon!
- Dr. Yoon.
- I said I won't sing!
16296.
I said I didn't want to sing.
What's the song called?
Yes, sure. Let's meet up next week.
Hey, I'll call you back later. Bye.
Do you not feel well? Are you okay?
It's a stomach thing.
I must have indigestion.
You didn't look well since dinner
and I forced you to eat.
Are you all right?
Get up if you can.
Stand up.
You look unwell. You're pale too.
Give me your hand.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital
and get an IV drip or something?
What's wrong? What's the matter?
Dr. Song has indigestion
and it looks pretty bad.
This doesn't work.
She has a weak stomach
and gets sick easily.
Na Hee, do you have
medicine at home?
I'll get you a taxi. Go home.
You need medicine
and sleep to get better.
I'll get your bag.
I won't be long.
Let's go.
Let's get you into the taxi.
Watch your head.
Take some medicine
as soon as you get home.
Get home safely.
To Jungang-dong, please.
Let's get back.
The others will be waiting for us.
I guess...
you're not completely over her yet.
What?
You look a bit on edge.
Wow, then it's a massive audition.
I'm impressed.
It's only impressive if he passes.
Attending the audition is nothing.
Do you have to put it like that?
I won't open you a nail salon
even if I make a fortune.
Da Hee, you can study abroad twice.
I'll pay for it.
- You will? Great.
- Sure.
How can you take that back?
It's Dad.
- Dad, why aren't you back yet?
- This is delicious.
Come over to the store right now.
The store? Why? What's wrong?
- Why? What's wrong?
- What's going on?
- What is happening?
- My gosh.
Shut your mouths and run. Mom!
- Mom!
- They're good for nothing.
- You're right.
I don't believe my rotten luck.
- I'm...
- Mom!
- Mom.
- Listen!
Mom!
- Mom, what's wrong?
- Mom.
- How much did you drink?
- Listen!
Get out of the way.
Why you darn scumbags,
sons of witches, jerks, and punks!
Wow, that was crazy.
Did Mom just swear?
Dad, what happened?
I have no idea.
She started downing soju
saying she was furious,
and I gave her a few more bottles
to put out the fire.
I had no idea your mom
was like this when drunk.
- Hey!
- No.
You darn good-for-nothing blockhead!
Shut your mouth.
Carry your mom home
before she wakes the neighborhood.
- What?
- Carry her.
- Mom, get on my back.
- How dare you?
Get out of the way,
you idiotic fool!
Hey, no, I feel sleepy.
I want to sleep, you scumbag!
- Mom, stop swearing.
- Hey.
- Get on his back.
- Hey! No!
What are you doing to me?
- What are you doing?
- Mom!
I don't care about anything.
I'm in this world alone anyway.
I've never heard Mom swear.
Her language is so colorful.
She never repeats a word.
Hey. Your face is bigger than big.
I'm your son.
- Is it my fault?
- I've never seen Mom drunk.
She doesn't even like alcohol.
Mom is such an elegant person.
Who made her like this?
You jerks.
I really don't care about
anything anymore, darn you.
- Joon Seon.
- Darn you.
How do you feel? A bit better?
It's stress-induced.
I'll feel better
once I have some medicine.
You seemed so fine.
You were pretending, weren't you?
I think so.
I can deal with everything else,
but I moved back home
and my mom won't look at me.
She has never
treated me like this before.
I see.
- That must be tough.
- Jeong Rok.
Sorry. I'll see you tomorrow.
- That hurts.
- Don't complain!
- Is Mom sick or something?
- Shoot.
No. She's just drunk!
She drank soju
straight from the bottle.
What?
Mom, are you all right?
Hey, isn't this the traitor?
Hey, put me down.
I'll walk from here.
- Mom!
- Darn you.
- Darn you!
- You'll fall over.
- Mom.
- Stop it.
- Hey, you.
- My goodness.
You can barely stand straight.
- Carry her in.
- Okay. Mom.
Hey!
I hate everyone so much,
but I hate you the most, you jerk!
Dad!
Mom!
My gosh.
(Once Again)
You fell over again.
Do you want to play a sport?
Keep it a secret from my mom.
She'll just worry.
Ms. Song! I mean... Ex-in-law!
What did you want to talk about?
Be my girlfriend.
What?
I thought about it at home.
Is that really it?
I have nothing to say to you.
How long will you be like this?
Don't ask me. Sort it out yourself.
Did you ever ask for my opinion
before doing something?
I'll move out, Dad.
I'm sorry.