Get away from me.
- Honey, hold still.
- Get lost.
You can't sleep with your socks on.
Gosh, my tailbone.
I can't believe I was
kicked by my own wife.
It hurts.
Does it hurt?
Well, I'm hurting too.
It...
It hurts right here.
- Honey, hold on.
- Yes?
- Hold on a second.
- What is it?
Let's...
move...
to a foreign country.
Let's leave the kids behind...
and move to another country.
Sure, let's do just that.
We will,
but I'm exhausted right now.
So go to sleep for now.
Get some sleep.
Darn you.
Darn this!
Goodness.
Get some sleep.
Gosh, it hurts.
Unbelievable.
Gyu Jin,
I'm in the middle of a crisis.
I think I made a huge mistake.
Mom wants me to go on blind dates.
Either that
or I'm supposed to return home.
What should I do?
It's like deciding whether
to burn to death or drown.
Na Hee's temper makes it
easier for her to get indigestion.
All she needs to do though is
take some medicine and sleep it off,
but Jeong Rok was rubbing her hand.
It annoyed me so much...
that I stuck my nose in
where it doesn't belong.
An arranged marriage
in this day and age?
All we would do is try to dig up
information on the other's family...
and flash fake smiles.
These so-called blind dates
couldn't be more archaic.
Someone with indigestion
should be given medicine...
or sent home.
Why was he hovering
over her like that?
Gyu Jin, must you be this way?
Don't you care about my life at all?
As if you cared about mine.
And besides,
I'm in enough trouble myself.
But this is different.
I'm in this mess because of you.
Mom's being this way
because you failed.
You're to be blamed for this too.
It's why I'm letting you live here.
What more do you want?
I don't know. What do I do?
A blind date?
I can't believe
I acted the way I did.
Do I have to apologize for this?
Unbelievable!
Mom, what are you doing out here?
I was going
to set the table for you.
It's fine.
I'm feeling too queasy
to lie down anyway.
Did you make it from scratch?
Yes, it's your famous
hangover bean sprout soup.
Actually, Da Hee made it
and I just seasoned it for her.
- Would you like some?
- Maybe later.
I drank so much last night
and now I have a killer headache.
We all have one of those days.
I bet it relieved
some of the stress though.
Maybe next time,
you can join me for a drink.
I'm a much better drinking buddy.
Save it.
I'm never going to drink again.
Na Hee won't have breakfast.
She has indigestion from yesterday.
Really?
No wonder her face was pale.
What happened though?
I know this is hard for you, Mom,
but it's taking a toll
on Na Hee too.
She has indigestion
even though she doesn't eat much.
So if you could
take it easy on her...
What do you mean?
What on earth did I do anyway?
It's not like
I've been yelling at her.
Fine, Mom.
I won't say anything more. Sorry.
Da Hee, can you set the table?
I'll call down the guys upstairs.
Breakfast is ready!
Doing cardio on an empty stomach
is the best way to lose fat.
The director wants lean muscles like
Bruce Lee, so what else can we do?
We need to meet his criteria.
- Sure thing.
- This is nothing, Joon Seon.
Why is it so hard
to get into shape though?
Maybe I've been
eating too much these days.
Hey, you're quite fit.
I can tell you've been working out
for a while.
Are you an athlete?
- No.
- Don't be ridiculous.
He only built muscles
to look good for the girls.
Isn't it obvious?
This isn't just for show.
Check out his body.
I bet he's some sort of athlete.
Look at his tight butt.
Guys, breakfast is ready.
My gosh.
You're in the middle
of your morning workout.
Good morning, Ga Hee.
Good morning.
Sure. Come down for breakfast, guys.
The table is set.
But we need to manage our weight.
Guys, stick mainly to vegetables...
and eat only half a bowl of rice.
Got it, Joon Seon.
I'll only eat half.
Sure, just half a bowl.
Instead of walking,
jog on the spot as you take steps.
- 1, 2, 1, 2...
- 1, 2, 1, 2.
- Drama queens.
- Hyo Sin, you should also...
- Sure.
His looks couldn't be more my type,
but his attitude is far from it.
Too bad.
Good morning.
Yes, good morning.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
What for?
I thought about it at home...
and it could seem
like I was on edge.
Anyway, I sometimes cross the line
when I'm inebriated.
Although I didn't drink
that much yesterday.
Maybe my tolerance for alcohol
has gotten weaker.
Really?
Is that it?
Sorry?
You acted that way
because you were drunk?
That's it?
What other reason would I have?
I'm just asking.
I wanted to be sure.
I forgot about what happened anyway,
so don't worry.
Have a good day.
It wasn't this bad
when Joon Seon was around,
but now I feel like
the only moocher.
Should I do something too?
Hi, Ji Soo.
What are you doing this evening?
What else? I'll probably be home.
Why do you ask?
Hye Soo got promoted,
so she's buying.
You're welcome to join us.
Really? That's great news.
Of course I'll...
Wait. Don't tell me
that Yoon Mi will be there.
Of course not.
We won't tell a fly this time.
You don't have to worry.
Sure then. Yes, I know the place.
I'll see you later.
Nice! I'm going out.
Hold on.
I sold all my purses though.
What am I supposed to wear?
Coming in.
Let's see.
Gosh, she has some nice stuff.
My goodness. Leave it to her
to always be meticulous.
Thanks, Na Hee.
I'll enjoy wearing these.
Gosh, these are so pretty.
Wait.
My gosh.
Darn it. What now?
Did you tell the teacher
that we were bullying you?
It wasn't me.
Don't think about lying.
We know it was you.
I'm not the only one
you've been bullying,
so check again. It wasn't me.
- Darn it.
- What are you looking at, loser?
You live with your mom
at your grandpa's house.
It's because your parents
are divorced.
I can't believe
you're living off her parents.
You jerk!
Darn it.
Hey!
You...
You jerk!
Stop...
I don't want to interfere
with your business,
but it's 6 p.m. already.
Do you know that?
Isn't the date at 6 p.m.?
Did you cancel it?
No, I'm going.
But?
I'm being late on purpose.
Come to think of it,
I just have to be dumped.
There's nothing
Mom can do about that.
I worried over something
that had an easy solution.
Just go out there
and ask for her understanding.
This is rude, you know.
That's rich coming from a person...
who got temperamental
with Jeong Rok for no reason.
I wonder which will hurt the most.
Hey, it was just a joke.
Put them down.
Gyu Jin, look at me.
Which side of my face looks better?
I don't like them both.
The left one? I knew it.
If she wants to slap me,
I should stick out my right cheek.
Okay.
I'm ready.
I'll off to get slapped then.
See you at home.
What a dork.
You acted that way
because you were drunk?
That's it?
Sorry?
I'm just asking.
I wanted to be sure.
Welcome.
Can beginners join this class?
I'm all fingers and thumbs though.
Sure. Please come on in.
You're home late.
Yes.
You fell down again, didn't you?
Do you want some ice cream?
It's good, isn't it?
Not really.
I don't like this ice cream.
This was the only
"buy 1, get 1 free" deal.
That's why I'm just eating it.
I guess you've
been falling quite often.
Don't you think you're too weak?
Mom says I was born weak.
But that's something you can
overcome with acquired strength.
Do you want to play a sport?
How is it? Does it fit?
It's a little too big for you.
The length fits you,
but you're too skinny.
Come here.
That's better.
Can I exercise here?
Yes. My friend runs this place,
so it's okay.
What do you say to working out
for an hour every evening?
Okay.
Keep it a secret from my mom though.
If she finds out,
she will just worry.
Okay. I won't tell her.
Are you ready?
Shall we begin?
Okay.
You said you're ready.
You're not supposed to let
your guard down when you're here.
You never know
when I'll throw you down,
so keep your guard up.
The goal is
for you to throw me down.
Got it?
Yes, I got it.
Let's go.
We should stretch out first.
Ms. Seo Yun Hee?
I'm sorry.
Have you been waiting for long?
Well, I can't exactly say no.
I guess the traffic was bad.
No. The traffic was fine.
Actually, I forgot about this.
I drank a lot last night.
Am I being too honest
when we just met?
No. I like honest people.
I just hate pretense.
Shall we order something to eat?
It was my dad who made me
go to Harvard.
It was actually nice.
I became more open-minded.
I see.
All right.
And that's why I came here today.
My dad always makes
the right choices.
Okay.
I want things to go well between us.
How about you?
You're very straightforward.
Now that you said it,
I should be honest with you.
I came here
because my mom forced me.
I'm a non-believer
when it comes to marriage.
I'm not even interested in
these kinds of meetings or marriage.
But I am.
I've never seen a guy
who's so indifferent to me before.
So it makes me want
to get to know you better.
Well...
Actually, I have a girlfriend.
You do?
You said
you don't believe in marriage.
But she is the one who made me
change my beliefs.
I promised to marry her.
I couldn't tell my mom about her yet
because of certain reasons.
But if she finds out
that I'm on a date with you,
she will be so upset.
When I think of her,
my heart aches.
I think this is true love.
Then let me see her.
- See what?
- Your girlfriend.
I think that's the only way
I can give up on you.
No, it's...
This is on me.
You pay next time.
Well... Wait. Yu Mi.
I mean, Yun Hee.
Ms. Seo Yun Hee.
Ms. Seo Yun Hee!
I have two quick turn flights
in this month's schedule.
Me too.
I have one layover flight in Paris.
That's the only comfort I have.
When are we ever going to
become service directors?
Hye Soo, is it nice to become
a senior service director?
The money and welfare are
even better than I thought.
You guys should work hard
to earn points for promotion.
Don't even think about taking leave.
It's all over
once your career is stalled.
Excuse me.
Can I get some water please?
Okay.
I'm sorry
we kept talking about work.
It's okay.
It's nice to hear it after a while.
It reminds me of the old days.
By the way, why didn't Gyu Ri come?
Is she working?
As soon as she got promoted,
she got scouted
by a foreign airline.
She got a house and a car
from the company.
I checked her social media.
She travels a lot on her off days.
She's in Spain now.
Really?
All my colleagues are successful.
I'm so proud of you guys.
Oh, right. Yeon Hee is
looking for an instructor...
at her flight attendant academy.
Do you know anyone
you can recommend?
I heard the pay is pretty good.
I don't know.
I can't think of anyone.
Hey, me. I can do it.
That's my area of expertise.
You guys know that I got top scores
during my interview.
But the thing is they look at
your career background.
You haven't been working
for quite a long time.
I see.
That's understandable. I get it.
I hope you're not offended.
Of course not.
Why would I be offended?
I just wanted to try it
to pass the time.
If I really were to do it,
I'll have to prepare a lot.
I can't bother with all that.
I won't do it. I take that back.
Those girls have no regard...
for the feelings of others.
Those nasty wenches.
Do you think
you guys will work forever...
with no breaks in your career?
You never know
what will happen in life.
They used to crawl before me
back in the day.
So now you're just getting prettier?
Is that it?
What do you think? Is it going well?
Yes. It's fun.
As you said, I don't get
any distracting thoughts,
which is even better.
I did it.
Do you want some coffee?
Sounds good.
What color is this anyway?
I'm doing as you said,
but I have no idea
what this color's called.
Giraffe poop.
Its real name is evening shadow,
but Si Hoo calls it giraffe poop.
That's what everyone here calls it.
It really is that color.
Si Hoo is quite observant.
Isn't he?
The color grows on you
and doesn't even tarnish.
Just like you, giraffe poop.
Wait, what are you saying?
Is that a compliment or an insult?
Mom.
Si Hoo.
Dr. Yoon.
You look even cooler
in your uniform.
Why are you here?
Do you live with us now?
No, Si Hoo, he's just visiting.
I don't think I can live with you.
How about I show you around Seoul?
Let's go. Let's look around Seoul.
- I'm scared.
- You can see Seoul from there.
- Mom!
- Look around.
Go ahead.
Massage your arms
and legs before bed.
I will, Hyo Sin.
Can I call you by your name?
You already did.
Get some rest.
Hyo Sin.
You just got back? You're late.
Yes. Did you have a drink?
Oh, my. Does it show?
Gosh. That's not good.
If Mom and Dad notice,
they'll chew me out.
Do I stink?
Oh, no.
I think even my clothes smell.
What should I do?
Na Hee will nag me as well.
This won't do.
What's that look about?
"What a pathetic woman."
That's what you're thinking.
I can't exactly say no.
What?
I guess not all older people
are mature.
Bye.
How dare he?
I liked him because he's cute.
Is everyone being nasty
to me today or what?
Darn it.
That...
You have no idea how scary I am.
You're dead meat.
You're so dead!
Are you leaving now?
Yes, I had a lot to learn.
You?
I read a few papers.
I'll give you a lift. It's late.
No, it's fine.
My ankle is fine today.
Let me drive you.
Consider it staff welfare.
You worked hard
until this late hour.
There's so much to
running a hospital.
Sitting at my desk all day
doing nothing...
makes me think I'd rather
work full-time doing surgeries.
You loved surgery.
I did.
What papers
were you reading this late?
Was it because
you didn't want to go home?
You got me.
If it's that bad,
wouldn't you rather move out?
It's too uncomfortable for
you and your mother.
Tell me if you want to move out.
My sister plans to spend
a year in Fairfax...
and a year in Korea
for her kid's education.
She's looking for someone to
watch her place while she's away.
It would be perfect if you move in.
That's a bit...
It's fine. It's better than
hiring a stranger.
It's near my place,
so we can carpool to and from work.
Thanks for the offer,
but I'll bear with it a bit longer.
If I move out now,
it'll take way too long
to reconcile with my mom.
You can drop me off over there.
Okay.
Thank you, Director Lee.
Your staff welfare is the best.
Not at all. You're my best employee.
I could take you to your front door.
No, I appreciate the lift
this far. Goodbye.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Are you just coming home from work?
Yes. Our meeting ran late.
Who was that?
A senior from medical school.
He's our interim director.
It must be nice to have
a senior as your director.
He even drove you home.
Let's go on inside.
You just got back?
It's quite late considering you only
went to get slapped in the face.
Gosh. Don't even ask.
You're pouting,
so I guess it didn't go your way.
Your cheek looks fine too.
Gyu Jin. The woman is so resilient.
I glanced around
to make her ditch me,
but she said I'm the first man
to act indifferent to her like that.
She's curious about me.
She wants to date me.
I was so flabbergasted.
Are you free on Saturday?
I'll invite you to my gallery.
Darn it.
What's wrong?
Hey, she's really into you.
It's rare for a woman to do this.
What else did she say?
"I won't accept excuses.
I'll wait until you come."
Hey, she's so cool.
I don't like women like this.
She's more like Mom than Na Hee.
I'm so scared of women like that.
How can I get rid of her?
I said I have a girlfriend,
but she didn't believe me.
Then visit with a fake girlfriend.
Are you kidding me? Who can I ask...
- What are you doing?
- Don't talk.
I'm recruiting a fake girlfriend.
Ms. Song! I mean... Ex-in-law!
Over here. I'm over here.
- Hi.
- Don't run. You'll trip.
Am I late? I'm sorry.
Did I make you wait?
You're studying for an exam.
I feel bad for disturbing you.
You didn't. The district library
closes at 10 p.m.,
so I was just about to leave.
Why did you call me out so late?
Is Gyu Jin in trouble?
No. Gyu Jin is doing
annoyingly well.
I need to ask you for a favor.
You do? What is it?
Be my girlfriend.
What?
No, I mean, not for real.
I'm in this situation
where I need a fake girlfriend.
You're the only person
I could ask for help.
Oh, right. My goodness.
Your reaction kind of hurt.
Why were you so horrified?
Enough to back away from me.
No, I mean, you know.
Our relationship is
a bit complicated.
I guess. If we were to date,
the number of people who'd faint...
1, 2...
There would be at least 4, right?
Why do you need a fake girlfriend?
It's a long story.
Because of Gyu Jin,
Mom wants to handpick a wife for me,
and I went on a blind date.
But the woman is a bit persistent.
She won't give up easily.
I said I have a girlfriend
I've been seeing for three years.
And you want me to
pretend to be that girlfriend?
- Yes.
- Gosh. I can't.
I can never do that.
Just this once. Please.
Don't you remember you owe me?
For slamming the cafe door
on my foot and hurting it.
You teased me and we called it even!
Do you always have to be so exact?
Just give and take? That's cold.
Are you that kind of person?
I never took you for that type.
Say anything you want,
but I can't lie or act...
to save my life.
Just thinking about it...
makes me nervous.
I can't do it. Never!
I'm an expert in the field,
so you just have to sit next to me.
Can't you see how desperate I am
to be asking you this?
Please, Ms. Song. Please.
Ms. Song, please!
No, I can't.
I'm sorry, Mr. Yoon.
Ms. Song!
- Ms. Song!
- I'm sorry.
Ex-in-law!
Sorry!
How can she be this cold?
Maybe I shouldn't have
taught her how to say no.
Unbelievable. So what now?
Yes, it's me.
Do you know what the daughter said?
Really? She's fond of Jae Seok?
Gosh, she has good taste in men.
He's the type that ladies love,
you see.
Really?
They already agreed
to another date?
My gosh. When?
At the gallery on the weekend?
No, I didn't hear the news.
You know how boys
never speak about these things.
He must be embarrassed.
I really hope this works out.
Of course.
Sure thing. Thank you so much.
My gosh.
Physically, this team seems to be
closer to our actors.
You three aren't muscular enough.
They may seem that way,
but you'll be surprised
when you see their bodies.
Besides, it won't show
when they're running around.
I'm not sure about that.
Viewers these days are so keen.
I mean it's not like you can make
grown men taller, right?
Let's see you in action then.
Let's begin.
Guys, get ready.
- Sure.
- Let's do this.
Come on.
He's like the guy from
"Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon".
They want to intimidate us.
They're just being flashy.
What matters are the basics.
When it comes to basics,
no one can outdo us.
You trust me, right?
- Yes, Joon Seon.
- Of course.
Next up is Good Action Company.
Sure thing. Come on.
They're not that bad.
They're all on point.
You can tell that
they practiced a lot.
We'll see.
It's all about the end results.
Sir,
I think these were swapped with
the ones that were partly sawed.
What?
They were swapped?
Are you kidding me?
What are you going to do?
These weren't sawed in advance?
Joon Seon,
- these are the real deal.
- Don't waste our time.
- These weren't sawed in advance.
- I'm fine, so just do it.
- Trust me.
- But these won't break.
It's fine. Just come at me.
- Joon Seon.
- I gave you an order. Come on.
That's how you do it!
What did I tell you?
Are you guys all right?
You can get up now.
That was awesome!
He's just full of spite.
Attention, bow.
Guys, that was amazing!
(Episode 32)
Again. This time,
throw your body at me.
Sure.
Again.
Loosen your shoulders
and add weight to your legs.
This is all about your strength.
Got it.
- That's it. Good job.
- Really?
Yes, you'll get better at this
in no time.
Can I go again?
Bring it on.
Okay, go.
What did I tell you?
I told you to trust me.
Joon Seon, you're the best.
You're amazing!
Ho Beom, how was it to witness...
the gap between our abilities?
Don't just stand there.
Go and bring the car around.
Your scenes were too flashy.
I suggest you go back
to practicing the basics.
Good luck, Ho Beom.
See you next time, Ho Beom.
I mean, Mr. Jang.
I bet that stings.
It would, considering his pride.
By the way, Joon Seon.
Are you okay?
You endured the pain
of those square bars.
Of course.
You know how thick my bones are.
That was nothing.
- Joon Seon.
- Joon Seon!
Really? Dad, that's awesome!
My gosh.
Smiley, Dad's going
to be in a TV series.
He's the stuntman
for the main actor. Awesome, right?
Right?
Seo Jin says you did well too.
She's proud of you.
Dad, you're awesome.
Mom? She's right here.
Yes, I'll put her on. Just a second.
It's fine. I'm driving, aren't I?
Mom can't talk
since she's driving right now.
A party? Of course I'll be there.
See you later. Bye!
Couldn't you at least
pretend to be excited?
He's in a great mood today.
You're always so cold.
Anyway, there's a party later.
Seo Jin and I are going,
so don't stop us.
Really? Joon Seon got the part?
Yes, you know how he achieves
what he puts his mind to at times.
If only he's like that all the time.
Right. He's like that sometimes.
He must be super excited.
Gosh, you have no idea.
He's already gathering people
for a barbecue.
So when will you be home?
I don't know.
Wouldn't it be best
if I went home late?
Mom will be in a good mood...
and I hate to bring her down.
That's all the more reason
for you to come home early.
You should use this chance
to get on her good side.
So you'll be home early, right?
I'll see you later.
I heard the news. Congratulations.
(I heard the news. Congratulations.)
Yes, ma'am. What a surprise.
She won't be able
to fit me in then?
No, of course she needs
her math classes.
I'll try and accommodate her
later in the evening then.
How about 9 p.m.?
Of course I should. Sure.
Thank you.
Attention!
Are you all enjoying your food?
- Sure.
- Of course!
Thank you so much.
Please tell me
you're considering it.
I'm sure you're all aware of it,
but you're here today...
to congratulate...
the successful TV debut
of my company,
Good Action Company.
My awesome dad.
Give it up for my dad!
Gosh, thank you
for the thundering applause.
That's enough.
We're good.
He can never play it cool.
Let him have his moment.
It's a great day for him.
First, Jeong Bong and Jong Soo.
You guys did well.
Since it's an honorable day,
I'd like...
to express my gratitude.
I wouldn't be here today
if it weren't for these two people.
Even though I lack in so many ways,
they have always supported me.
First,
it's my mother. Mom!
Stop it. You're embarrassing me.
Good for you, Ok Boon. I'm jealous.
Also,
I haven't been able
to say this often,
there's someone I love...
and truly admire. It's...
my aunt who's sitting
next to my dad.
Me?
What on earth
are you thanking me for?
Mom, I'll just tell everyone.
You see,
Auntie invested her money...
- She invested what?
- What's going on?
Joon Seon means...
that I've been
supporting him mentally.
I bought him a few drinks...
when he needed a friend to talk to.
- Right?
- I see.
I thought otherwise.
Anyway, enjoy until you're too full.
- Let's enjoy.
- Thanks.
Mom, do you want some soda?
Na Hee, pour Mom some soda.
Mom, here you go...
Na Hee, there's some behind you.
Sure thing.
Let me pour you some.
I'm good. I'll stick to water.
But I already brought you some.
Just drink some.
I'm fine, all right?
I don't want any.
Must you be this petty over nothing?
He's right.
Just let her pour you a glass.
You're embarrassing me, Mom.
Here you go.
- I said I'm fine!
- My gosh.
Mom, gosh.
I said I didn't want any.
Na Hee?
Da Hee, no.
We need to talk.
I don't have anything to say to you.
I know I disappointed you...
and I'm truly sorry.
But...
how long will this go on?
Until when...
will you avoid me?
Why?
Are you upset by
how I'm treating you?
Does it hurt to be ignored?
No, I just can't
assess what's going on.
Should I be living with you
in this house...
or should I disappear
from your sight?
Mom,
I didn't move back in
to torture you.
What a tear-jerking thing to say.
You have a funny way of showing
how much I mean to you.
You think you're so smart...
and you think you rule the world.
So don't ask me
and do whatever you want.
It's not like you ever
ask for my opinion first.
What about this upsets you the most?
Is it because you've become
a laughing stock at the market...
or is it because
you feel bad for me?
What?
The decision wasn't
easy for me either.
I tried to keep our marriage
for as long as I could.
I knew what I meant to you.
I know how much you count on me.
But...
my life was just too miserable.
I was dying out of loneliness.
I wanted to live my life too.
Why? Why were you miserable?
Why were you so lonely?
You got married because
you were head over heels for him.
I had a miscarriage.
I lost a baby...
about two and a half years ago.
Wait.
What?
It was my fault.
I stubbornly overexerted myself.
At first,
I just thought of it as bad luck.
We could always get pregnant again.
But...
I couldn't let it go.
Due to guilt,
I wanted to force a pregnancy.
And Gyu Jin found it
too hard to bear.
We kept arguing.
We argued every second
that we were awake.
The arguments led to scars...
and we kept hurting
each other even more.
I didn't want to let it continue.
Mom, I...
didn't think
my life should continue like that.
That's why...
You...
How could you...
hide such a huge deal from me?
How could I tell you?
How could I when I knew
you'd be heartbroken?
You were upset enough
because of Joon Seon and Ga Hee,
so how could I add on to that?
You should have told me though!
If you thought of me as your mother,
you would've told me.
Even then, you thought little of me.
Normally, kids seek their parents
when they need comforting,
not when they want
to share good news.
Have you ever thought of that,
you brat?
Mom...
Mom, I'm so sorry.
I guess I'm too selfish.
I'm sorry.
Na Hee...
Na Hee?
Her eyes were blotchy.
I'm sure she was crying.
My gosh. Mom must've hit her.
No way.
I'll go to her.
Na Hee?
Are you okay?
Don't be too upset.
She just counted on you
so much that...
Da Hee.
Can you turn off the lights?
I'd rather go to sleep.
Sure. All right.
Don't think about it
and just get some sleep.
You will feel better
after a good night's sleep.
Hey, you're up.
Yes, Dad.
I have something to tell you.
Okay. I have something
to tell you too.
I'll move out, Dad.
I'm sorry.
Okay. You can do that.
I thought it would be better
for you to keep seeing each other.
But perhaps
I didn't think this through.
Don't resent your mom though.
I don't.
I have no right to be resentful.
You should get more sleep.
You didn't sleep a wink last night.
Na Hee wants to move out.
And I said okay.
I should go check the meters.
The weather has become warmer,
but the heating bill is still high.
(Hospital Director Lee Jeong Rok)
Yes.
Do you have a moment?
I have something to ask you.
Sure.
All right.
What's the matter, Dr. Song?
I'm here as your friend,
not as an employee.
Really? I'm even more curious.
What is it?
You mentioned
your sister's house yesterday.
The one you're hiring
a house sitter for.
Is the offer still valid?
Of course.
But why did you change
your mind in a day?
Is something wrong?
No. I just think it'll be better
for me to move out.
But I don't have much money to spare
at the moment.
So I'd appreciate it...
if I could stay at your sister's
until I sort things out.
You don't have to be sorry.
It's empty anyway.
So when will you move in?
This weekend?
Can I move in today?
Here is your large
sweet and sour chicken...
and two fried chickens.
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
- Bye.
Ok Boon.
You startled me. What?
I just thought you've been
spacing out the whole day.
I have a lot on my mind today.
So don't bother me
and leave me alone. Okay?
Okay.
Gosh, I'm just like
everyone's punching bag.
Maybe I should move out
and stand on my own.
- Joon Seon.
- Auntie.
I'm at the cafe
where we met that time.
Come over here
without telling Mom and Dad.
Discreetly.
Okay.
Auntie. Ta-da.
Gosh, what is this?
It's my gift for you.
It's a cosmetics set.
It's expensive,
so don't share it with anyone. Okay?
You know Mom isn't
in a good mood now.
So I couldn't bring it to the store.
You didn't have to do this though.
It's nothing
compared to what you did for me.
I wish I could get you
something better,
but this is just the beginning yet.
I'll give you something huge later.
And I will pay you back
every penny for sure.
Okay.
Joon Seon.
Yes?
The thing is...
About the investment money.
Are you moving out again
just like this?
Give me the coat over there.
Na Hee,
can you reconsider just once more?
You should at least wait for Mom
and see her before you leave.
If you leave like this,
you might never make up with her.
Ga Hee, don't just stand there.
Do something.
What can I do?
It's not like she wants to do this.
Do you have a place to stay?
Yes. I asked my friend a favor.
I'm sorry.
This is when I'm supposed
to help you as your older sister.
But I'm in no better position,
so there's nothing I can do.
I feel so ashamed.
It's okay.
I've never helped you either.
Give me that. Let me carry one.
I don't think this is right.
Are you leaving now?
Yes, Dad.
I saw a taxi in front of the house.
I was wondering why,
but I guess it's for you.
Do you have a place to stay?
Yes.
I'll send you my address.
See you, Dad.
Mom.
I'm leaving.
I should go.
You don't have to walk me out.
Bye, Na Hee.
Be careful.
Make sure to call us.
Who said you could move out?
Mom.
Are you running away like that
after breaking my heart?
What am I supposed to do?
You brat.
You...
You can't leave.
Come back in.
You can't go.
I'm not letting you go.
You're not going anywhere.
You should've told me.
You should've cried
your eyes out in my arms.
It must've been so hard.
It must've been so painful.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry, Mom.
You're so cold-hearted.
What do you think
you have your mom for?
Why did you put up
with the whole thing by yourself?
How could you do that?
You brat...
- Mom.
- You silly thing.
- Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
What are you doing? Get off me.
Just stay still, Dad.
Just for a minute.
No, just five minutes.
Let go of me.
Mom, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
You silly girl.
You poor thing.
(Transfer Exam Academy)
(Good morning.
The weather is nice today.)
Good morning.
The weather is nice today.
It's a perfect day
to do a good deed.
How many messages has he sent?
He's so tenacious.
I'm really desperate.
Can you please help me this once?
Please, Ms. Song.
It's not something I can do for you.
You're making me feel bad.
No, no.
I can't do it.
- Hold on tight.
- Everyone!
Will you see who's here?
- My gosh.
- Hey!
Ok Boon, it's you.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Is your stomach... How do you feel?
I feel fine.
Did you learn a lot?
What if I can't keep up?
Don't miss any more classes.
Attend them all.
Our instructor said that
if we get good enough,
we can even enter
amateur competitions and such.
My gosh, look who's here.
It's our president and his wife.
It's been a while since I saw you.
- You too, Ms. Jang.
- Yes.
Why did you two come in together?
We met on the way here.
I was leaving my store
when Mr. Yang passed by.
I see.
- Will I manage?
- You'll do fine.
This time, we'll learn
the turn and embrace.
1, 2, 3, and 4. Okay.
Ready, go.
1, 2, 3, and 4.
My gosh. Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Will you concentrate, Mr. Yang?
Okay, I'll concentrate. Concentrate.
My gosh.
Why is there always more trash?
Are we done? I'll tie up the bag.
There's still room for more.
While we're at it,
let's clean Cho Yeon's room too.
My gosh.
Is this the expiration date?
Throw this away too.
Wow, how many years
did she keep this for?
Throw it away. Toss it.
I'll finish up here.
You check her closet.
Throw away
everything she doesn't wear.
Really? Without asking her?
If we ask, will she let us
throw anything away?
She'll say she'll wear it later.
I bet she has a stash of
underwear and socks with holes.
Don't hold back.
Throw everything away.
Okay.
My goodness.
There's more to throw away
than she can wear.
What's this?
What should we do about her?
Throw this away.
Put this in there.
And this too.
I bought this piece myself.
It's a good piece
considering the artist is new.
I liked the untypical
sense of adventure.
It's just my style.
Like you, Jae Seok.
What?
Well, I'm not that adventurous.
- Excuse me, Ms. Seo.
- Yes?
I don't think you and I
suit each other.
I'm not that classy a person...
Do you feel uncomfortable here?
Next time,
we can meet where you like.
I don't mind a game of bowling,
or drinking at a cart bar.
I'll accommodate you.
No, it's not a matter of that.
It's a lie that
you have a girlfriend.
Right?
Sweetie.
Did you wait for a long time?
Hello. I'm Jae Seok's girlfriend,
Song Da Hee.
- Cheers.
A glass of lemonade
after cleaning up...
brings back memories.
I used to feel so good
when we had...
a shot of soju with a tray of fruit.
Me too.
I feel so relaxed these days.
There's so little stress.
Right. I even feel healthier too.
- Cheers.
Are you two still slacking off?
Couldn't you chop up
some vegetables in your free time?
Cho Yeon. We didn't slack off.
Don't nag and go on inside...
and get changed.
Yes, get changed.
Okay, I will.
You two nag more than I do.
- Cheers.
Cho Yeon will be shocked
when she sees her room.
Of course. She'll wonder if her room
was always that big.
I feel so much better
since we cleaned it up.
Hey.
Who... Who cleaned up my room?
What? I did...
with Ga Yeon.
Are you angry
we didn't ask for permission?
My clothes.
The clothes wrapped up in a cloth.
Where... What did you do with that?
Where's the wrapping cloth?
The wrapping cloth?
Was there something like that?
Some old clothes and makeup...
Things you don't use...
We threw them out in a trash bag.
What?
My gosh.
What's the matter?
What was inside? Cho Yeon!
Stop! Stop!
Stop, misters. Stop the truck!
- Stop! Mister!
- Stop the truck.
Stop for a moment. Stop.
- What's the matter?
- Sorry, mister.
I threw away something
I shouldn't have.
The trash bag... I need to get it.
Can you help me?
How are we to know which is yours
out of dozens of bags?
Give up. We have to get to
the next area before 40 past.
No, mister, please. I need it back.
Go back home.
- Please, sir. Let me look.
- We're busy too.
- Please.
- You can't do this.
What's going on now?
Isn't that the kimbap lady?
- What's up? Are they fighting?
- It's really important.
Hey, Chi Su.
I just need to look inside.
- We're busy too.
- Mister.
It's really important to me.
Just 10 minutes. No, just 5 minutes.
You just took it,
so it'll be in the back.
I'll just take it out.
Please, mister.
You can't, okay?
- Move or you'll get hurt.
- Mister!
Mister.
What's the matter.
My clothes... My clothes...
The girls threw them out.
My mom's handkerchief was in there.
I need to get it back!
What should I do?
I need to find that trash bag.
What am I to do?
Mister, what are you doing?
You can't go.
Cho Yeon asked for just 10 minutes!
She said it's important!
What's wrong with you people today?
We have work to do!
Who are you?
What are you to her? Her husband?
No!
I'm...
a man who likes her!
I like her, okay?
What?
So just give her 10 minutes!
My goodness.
What's wrong?
- What's the matter?
- What's wrong?
(Once Again)
Has it been that long already?
Jae Seok?
Tell me if there's any place
you want to go.
There is just one place
I'd like to go to.
Ok Ja, come here.
You know Mr. Yang's...
Ok Ja, I was just
on my way to your store.
I have a feeling
this will go really well. So...
Can't you let me keep
my promise to Seo Young?
I like Na Hee, you know.
But...
I'm not asking for your permission.
I just wanted to be honest.