What's wrong with you people today?
We have work to do!
Who are you? What are you to her?
- Her husband?
- No!
I'm...
a man who likes her!
I like her, okay?
So just give her 10 minutes!
- My goodness.
- What's wrong?
- What's the matter?
You've been with Jae Seok
for four years?
Has it been that long already,
Jae Seok?
Yes, that sounds about right.
I see. It's already been four years.
We hit a rough patch
when he was in Turkey though.
I thought about
ending the relationship,
but I just couldn't
live without him.
Right, I see.
I wasn't sure about
coming here today,
but I mustered up the courage.
Until we get his mother's approval,
I figured it was up to me
to stay strong.
Seriously?
That's right.
Gosh, my heart nearly
jumped out of my chest.
Are you sure
you were nervous in there?
You seemed like
a professional actress.
Are you kidding me?
My heart was racing
throughout the whole time.
I was worried that
she'd see right through us.
Was I okay though? Did I seem off?
Not at all.
Where did you get
that outfit though?
Don't tell me you bought it.
No, it's Na Hee's.
Jeans and a hoodie
didn't seem appropriate.
- This doesn't suit me, does it?
- It's better than I expected...
Anyway, thank you for doing this.
Ms. Song, you are one loyal friend.
I mean it.
Stop that.
Just know that
I won't ever do this again.
Sure thing.
And to express my gratitude,
I'll treat you to
a full-course meal.
Tell me where you want to go.
A hotel buffet? A wine bar? A club?
Forget it. I'm a student
studying for an exam, remember?
It's only a one-time thing.
Besides, you need to
blow off some steam now and then.
You're right, but...
There is a place
I've been wanting to go.
Where?
I'm a man who likes her!
I like her, okay?
My gosh. I can't believe it.
Who knew he had feelings
for the kimbap lady?
Unbelievable.
Honey, did you know?
Know what?
Stop gossiping
and get the chicken batter ready.
Why her though?
What about her does he like?
He's always been picky
with high standards...
when it comes to women.
Why on earth
are you so curious about it?
Now, where's my chicken batter?
I'm mixing it right now.
See? My hands are moving.
Ok Ja, you've been
awfully quiet all this time.
Ok Ja?
Who would've seen that coming?
I'm shocked!
How could he fall for a woman
that reminds me of a barrel?
Mr. Yang sure has
weird taste in women.
Actually, there's something
intriguing about her.
In what way?
- I heard this at the salon.
- Yes?
Rumor has it...
that she's the girlfriend
of a notorious gangster...
and a former high-stakes gambler.
Don't underestimate me
and my fat lower belly.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would a gangster's girlfriend
be selling kimbap at the market?
This is what I heard
from the rice cake store.
Rumor has it that
she was a big player...
among loan sharks.
A 24 percent interest
with your car as collateral.
Okay?
So she seduced Mr. Yang
with her money?
Yes.
That's absurd.
Mr. Yang has quite the fortune too.
You're right.
Ok Ja, over here. So Mr. Yang...
What on earth?
Ms. Kang,
I shocked you earlier, didn't I?
Yes, I guess you did in a way.
Well, I'll say it again.
I like you, Ms. Kang.
Actually, I think I love you.
Please accept my love.
My gosh.
He seems driven.
Right.
Well, I'm sorry to tell you this,
but I don't feel the same way.
Sorry?
You're not my type.
I like those who are handsome.
I'm not as bad
when it comes to my looks though.
People say I seem manly.
Exactly.
I like men
who are on the prettier side.
I prefer young and fresh
over old and rich.
So don't bother with me anymore
and take your affections elsewhere.
No can do I'm afraid.
I won't.
What do you mean you won't?
Do you plan to
kidnap me or something?
I might have to
if you won't accept my feelings.
My gosh.
The fire in my heart
won't ever go out...
and I won't sheathe
the sword I drew.
Just you wait and see.
I will woo you eventually.
That being said,
I wish you a good day today.
Have a good day, Mr. Yang!
My gosh.
What's gotten into him?
Gosh, now I'm scared.
Unbelievable. It wasn't one of us...
but you who he had fallen for.
My gosh.
Exactly.
We're the ones
who are young and pretty,
so why would he fall for you?
Has he lost his mind or something?
Shut it, you two.
I never said this out loud,
but I have a sex appeal
that draws men in.
Call me a femme fatale if you want.
Once hooked,
men can't seem to think straight.
Really?
Gosh, this is news to us.
Anyway, this could be
quite bothersome for me.
He really isn't my type, you know.
I tried so hard not to get
caught up in romance here,
but it still happened.
What a big mess.
If you ask me
Even though she said...
- she's annoyed by all this,
- If this is
- she seems pleased if you ask me.
- Love
- It's quite obvious.
- I will say
It's the seed
that leads to a breakup
Unbelievable.
How does this make any sense?
Does he carry his eyes on his feet?
How can he fall for
that woman of all people?
Ms. Jang, I was on my way
to Young Dal's store.
Is she insane?
What has gotten into her?
Gosh, it hurts.
Let me see though.
What exactly does she mean
by a pretty boy?
How can I be like one
when I don't know what they're like?
It's not like I can be
reborn from the ashes.
Hey...
Hyo Sin, you must be
making a delivery.
Be safe on the road!
Like always,
the tall young man emits light.
It sure is good to be young.
Of course.
Bingo.
Young, fresh, and pretty.
Noted.
1, 2, 3.
In one motion. Squeeze your core.
A strong core.
- 1, 2, 3.
See? Your legs were wobbly. Again.
1, 2, 3.
That's it. Good job.
Do it just like that 50 times. Go!
What?
50 times. Go.
Got it. All right.
- 1, 2, 3.
My gosh. Really?
Mr. Yang confessed his feelings
in public?
To the stout lady
we saw at Dad's birthday party?
No way. I can't believe it.
I didn't peg him for a romantic.
The people must be gossiping.
Of course they are.
How could they not...
when this happened
in our small market?
Why would this be a big affair?
What's the big deal about
one person liking another?
They're both single,
so it'll be nice for them to date.
I, for one, am jealous.
There's love in the air
for those who are old,
but here I am
wasting my good looks.
Gosh, unbelievable.
- It's so good.
- I'm home.
- You're back.
- Ji Hun, you're home.
- Hi, Ji Hun.
- Son, you're late than usual.
Come and have some dinner.
Here. I saved a drumstick for you.
I'll wash my hands first.
Aren't you hungry?
Why were you held up today?
Gosh, it's so pretty.
I had no idea that
I lived in such a pretty city.
I can't believe that
a woman who had a fiance...
has never been
to Seoul Tower before.
Tell me about it.
He spent most of his time
studying for the state exam...
and I packed meals for him.
If he had a break,
we'd go to the movies,
but he'd fall asleep beside me.
Enjoy it to your heart's content.
Just capture everything in your eyes
until you get sick of Seoul.
Okay. I will.
There are a lot of locks though.
I guess all the couples
in this country have been here.
How are there so many locks on here?
I think there's a catch here.
Some people overlap.
They put locks here
with many different people.
Look. Think about
the buildings in Gangnam.
There are many buildings, but none
of them belong to me or my friends.
That's because owners overlap.
It's like the rich get richer
and the poor get poorer.
I guess you're right.
You are so smart.
Thank you for recognizing it.
When would I be able to come here
with a guy and put a lock here?
Why? Are you envious?
Let's just do it.
Fortunately, I happen to be a guy.
- No, that's not right.
- Where?
- Here? This looks good.
- Okay. I'll put it here.
Thank you for today, Ms. Song.
My pleasure.
I guess I'm the only woman
who does this with her in-laws.
Why? I'm doing it too.
This is fun.
This is really nice.
Stay here.
I'll take a picture of you.
Since this is your first time here,
you should have your picture taken.
Then please take it focusing
on the night view, not me.
Okay.
- I'm a great photographer.
- All right.
That's not good.
Move over here.
Okay. It's good.
The background is nice.
I'm taking it now.
In 1, 2...
What kind of pose is that?
- You know it's Mount Nam.
- Just stand straight.
Good. I'm taking it now.
In 1, 2, and 3.
Try to look taller. In 1, 2, and 3.
Gosh, my back hurts.
Okay. I took it with the background.
Now I'll take one from up close.
A close-up shot.
1, 2...
Gosh. Stop it.
Ms. Song, sit here.
Sit there.
No. I told you to sit.
Okay.
I'm taking it. In 1, 2, and 3.
Stay still. Lower your hands.
Stay put. I'm taking it now.
In 1, 2, and 3.
Hang on.
Gosh, I'm such a good photographer.
This one looks good.
She's pretty.
That's enough.
Stop taking pictures of me.
Mr. Yoon.
Mr. Yoon?
Yes? What did you say?
I said it's enough.
I'll take pictures of you now.
No. I'm okay.
I've been here a lot.
I'm not saying I came here with
a woman. Anyway, I don't need it.
It's Mom.
It's my sister.
- Song Da Hee.
- Na Hee.
I didn't expect you to do this.
Where did you go in that dress?
The transfer exam is
not far off now.
How could you go out
all dressed up like that?
It's not like I went out for fun.
It's you who wore the dress
I ironed a few days ago, right?
Did you think I wouldn't find out
if you had it dry-cleaned?
No, Na Hee. This is my first time.
Seriously, this is my first time
to wear your clothes.
I don't buy that.
You are so busted. Come here.
No, Na Hee. I didn't do it.
Please trust me.
This is my first time.
The longer you hold out,
the worse things get.
- Just tell me the truth.
- It's true. Please believe me.
- This is my first time.
- You, Da Hee.
How dare you wear my dress?
Gosh, Na Hee.
Seriously, it wasn't me.
I didn't wear other dresses.
- My goodness.
- It wasn't me.
I'm sorry, Da Hee.
I will remember your sacrifice.
I won't forget it.
- How dare you...
- Gosh, she's so spiteful.
What's the big deal
about sharing clothes?
What is she talking about?
Is it really true?
Is it true that
you're seeing someone?
Yes. I have a girlfriend.
What?
How could you...
Who on earth is she?
What is her family background like?
Why did you go on a date
when you have a girlfriend?
Mom, ask one question at a time.
I can't tell you who she is.
I started dating her
before I went to Turkey.
And I didn't tell you about her...
because I knew
you would want to see her.
Of course I do.
Bring her home tomorrow.
See? I knew you'd be like this.
You can never do that.
Why? Why can't I see her?
Well...
She's still a student.
What? A student?
My gosh. What a jerk.
You're dating a girl
who's a lot younger than you.
She's not that young.
Who on earth is she?
How could she captivate
your heart like that?
Well... Let me tell you
what she's like.
Excuse me. Is this yours?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
She's so nice like a fool.
- She's diligent.
- Thank you.
Sometimes she's whimsical.
And...
- Here? This looks good.
- Okay. I'll put it here.
In 1, 2, and 3.
Again.
Stay put. I'm taking it now.
In 1, 2, and 3.
She's pretty.
What?
I said she's pretty.
Mom, what did I just say?
Did I say she's pretty?
I take it back. She's not pretty.
What's going on?
Is she pretty or not?
She's just average.
Anyway.
Bring her home first. Show me.
I'm telling you again.
You can't date anyone
without my permission.
I'll pick a girl I really like.
I will never back off.
We can do it later.
We're not that serious yet.
If I married all women I've dated,
I would've gotten married 10 times.
I'll date her a little more.
Mom, do you want to drink something?
I'm having beer.
What?
You said you'd just show your face,
but you came home late.
Why?
Did you change your mind
after seeing her?
Was the gallery that fancy?
How dare you ignore
your older brother?
Gyu Jin.
Have you ever thought
Ji Yeon is pretty?
Or Ms. Oh.
What?
Nothing. Never mind.
Keep cleaning.
Gosh, he's just hopeless.
What should I do with him?
She is pretty.
This is strange.
Why does she look pretty?
She's definitely not pretty
on my terms.
She's pretty again. This is crazy.
What's wrong with me?
No. It's not like
I have feelings for her.
I haven't dated a woman for a long
time. It's just testosterone.
It's just a reaction...
of the pituitary gland
to visual stimulus.
It means nothing
more than that. Sure.
(Ms. Song)
That's right.
You're a healthy
average man of Korea.
No, that's not true.
You're more than that, Jae Seok.
I made another batch of jangjorim.
I'm not sure how it tastes.
Try it.
Eat your fill. You need to
eat meat to gain energy.
Thank you so much, Ga Hee.
You're the best.
What are you staring at?
Is there something on my face?
Yes. Dried seaweed by your mouth.
Mom, if you're not too busy,
will you come out for dinner?
A sushi restaurant
opened by our hospital.
You like sushi.
I would love to,
but am I allowed to
leave the store before closing?
Go. Go ahead.
Can we not do business without you?
There's your sister and Hyo Sin.
Just go.
Yes, Mom, come out for dinner.
Ga Hee and Da Hee, you too.
A girls' night out.
Really? I'd love it. I'm in.
Me too.
I'll wait by your hospital
after class. At around 7 p.m.?
- Okay.
- What about our dinner then?
Don't you worry, Ji Hun.
Uncle will cook.
Why don't we all get together too?
Dad. Your eldest son
will prepare dinner for you today.
Expect something good, okay?
Take care, son. Study hard.
- See you later.
- Bye.
What's this?
It's the jerk's motorcycle.
What did you just do?
Jeez.
Why did this fall over?
Is it a jerk, just like its owner?
Gosh.
Director.
You're here early.
So are you.
I guess you sleep less at your age.
When I heard you'd be
our new director, I was pleased.
But you play favorites.
I want to be your favorite too.
You tend to look out
a bit too much for Dr. Song.
I'm envious.
You're the jealous type.
Or is it because it's Na Hee?
Oh? Good morning.
Hello. Morning.
Hi.
I was going to see you
in your office.
You can't speak because of me.
Okay, okay. Go ahead.
I don't think...
I have to move out.
I talked it out with my mom.
Did you? Did you and
your mother reconcile?
We didn't exactly reconcile,
but we worked things out.
Good for you.
I feel let down, though.
It would be fun to carpool
to and from work.
You did well.
- Ju Ri, to the side.
- Here?
Wipe harder.
Did you skip breakfast?
Move. I'll do it.
Give me that. Rub hard, like this.
- You do it, then.
- Can't you even do this? What?
- You do it.
- Hey.
- Good for you.
- Let's do it together.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
What's this?
I found it on the way.
You're more of a flower, though.
See you.
What was that about? Did he...
pretend to be
the chicken delivery guy?
Because you like pretty boys?
It looks like it. Wow.
I think he's
really into you, Cho Yeon.
Try and make it work!
Forget it. He's not into me.
I'd rather he bring meat
like last time.
Why would he
give me something I can't eat?
They smell nice, though.
Where should I put these?
Do we have a vase?
My goodness.
She's playing
hard to get, isn't she?
Her swaying hips mean yes.
But she says no.
She's definitely playing
hard to get.
She is.
Let's go inside.
It's just practice,
so don't hurt yourselves.
Today, we'll just test
the camera angles...
and practice the moves,
so don't get too nervous.
Yes, sir. Don't worry.
Bye.
Relax. Why are you so tense?
You'll become stiff
and mess up everything.
It's just that
the suit is a little thin.
- Joon Seon.
- What?
You should relax.
Your face is too pale.
- Is it?
- Yes.
Did I put on too much makeup?
Standby!
Okay! Okay.
Ready.
Action!
Cut! That's fine.
Stunt doubles. Take your places.
Go!
Cut! Okay! Wow.
I'd like you to do just that
for the shoot.
Yes, director! Thank you!
Yes.
Come with me.
You did great.
Why isn't anyone else here?
It's almost 7 p.m.
Don't be silly.
Oh? Ms. Song?
Mr. Yoon.
Ms. Song!
It's so nice to see you here.
- Why are you here?
- I'm waiting for my sister.
The women of the house
are eating out.
With mom and Ga Hee too.
Wow, your family gets along well.
Ours is still a bit icy.
How did you manage that day?
After your mother called.
We got over it somehow.
What about you?
Did your sister yell at you?
I managed too.
You should go.
Your colleague's waiting.
Okay. See you.
Eat something nice.
- I will.
- Bye.
Bye.
Na Hee.
- Da Hee.
- Na Hee.
I was about to call you.
Mom and Ga Hee just got off the bus.
We can meet them nearby. Let's go.
Let's.
It's so good.
How is it, Mom? It's nice, isn't it?
Yes. I love this place
because I don't smell any oil.
And the fish is fresh.
Eat a lot. Ga Hee
and Da Hee, you too.
I'm stuffing my face as we speak.
Don't make me talk.
The tempura is so crunchy.
I just love this.
Eating good food
with Mom and my sisters,
and chatting and giggling.
Yes. We should've
been like this before.
Things were too gloomy between us.
Yes. I had to
tiptoe around you two...
and could barely breathe.
- Right, Ga Hee?
- That's right.
Those two are mocking us, Mom.
They are. You're nasty brats.
Anyway, let's all
forget about the past...
and go back to being a tight group.
Shall we toast to that?
Sure.
To the friendship of
the four ladies of the Song family!
- Cheers!
Excuse me. I'm sorry to bother you.
Yes? What do you want?
I work at
a nearby securities company.
I'm here to have dinner
with some colleagues,
but then I saw you four having fun.
If it's not too much trouble,
how about you join us for a drink?
My gosh.
Goodness me. Really?
Are you sure
my age won't be a problem?
Sorry about that. Excuse me.
There's no need to apologize.
It's fine.
You could stay for a chat.
Unbelievable.
I guess I'm still attractive.
Look at him blushing.
We must've shocked him.
Good for you, Mom.
A young man just asked you out.
You must be pleased with yourself.
Being with my daughters
has its perks.
I wonder if the men of our house
have managed to cook dinner.
I'm sure they're already
enjoying theirs. Cheers.
- Sure.
- Why not? Cheers.
- Cheers.
I'm loving this.
Gosh.
Joon Seon, when will we have dinner?
It's almost done, Dad.
What's taking you so long?
All we needed was a simple stew.
Look forward to it, Dad.
Just so you know,
we'll be having spaghetti vongole.
What? Vongole?
Ji Hun, what on earth
did he mean by that?
It's a spaghetti dish
made with clams.
It's quite delicious.
Something's wrong with the clams.
They won't open up.
What? Let me take a look.
Joon Seon gave you an order,
so open up!
Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
Bring it on.
- Let me try.
- We don't have the time.
Let's just cook them.
I'm sure they'll taste the same.
Hurry up, guys.
My dad must be hungry.
- Sure.
- Get cooking.
What else should go in here?
What's up with the spaghetti?
It's stringy.
It must be because
we cooked them for so long.
Wait, shouldn't it get mushy?
Joon Seon,
this doesn't smell like oil.
I think it's a plum extract.
What do we do?
What now?
I knew it.
This place serves
the best jajangmyeon.
Right? Isn't it to die for?
Yes, it's delicious.
The fried dumplings are the best.
Everything tastes good
when you're hungry.
It's way past dinner time.
- Shut it.
- Seriously?
Let's eat in peace.
I don't want to hear another word.
- Sure.
- Got it.
What a luxurious evening.
I enjoyed sushi
and an expensive bottle of sake.
I feel like I missed out though.
We should've drunk
with those group of men.
Seriously?
I'm going to tell Dad, you know.
That's not what I mean.
I should've for the sake
of my three single daughters.
A securities company
means stable and secure jobs.
It's too bad.
Why do we suddenly
feel like sinners?
We are, aren't we?
We're the reason behind
Mom's growing wrinkles.
I'm sorry...
for adding wrinkles
to your pretty face.
It's fine, so shut it.
Take me out like this sometimes
if you're that sorry.
Of course I'd love for you
to find love again,
but it's not something
you can force.
That much we can do.
How about once a month?
It'll be on me.
Don't be ridiculous.
Aren't I the older sister?
I'll at least pay 10 percent.
You don't have a job,
so all you have to do is attend.
I'm thinking of changing that.
I'm going to look for a job.
- Really?
- Yes.
I wouldn't mind the extra money...
and it's a shame to waste
my beauty and brain.
That's something pleasant to hear.
So this came to mind just now.
I might get busy starting tomorrow,
so how about another round?
This cart bar serves
the best rolled omelet.
I'm already tipsy though.
Another drink might
interfere with my studies tomorrow.
Come on.
Leave it to tomorrow
to worry about tomorrow.
Besides, you need to recharge
in order to study.
Let's get another drink.
- Sure, let's go.
- Nice!
- I'm in!
- Girls, it's too late.
Your father will be waiting for us.
Mom, come on.
- You're a free woman today.
- Let's go.
- Okay, fine.
- Come on.
Over here.
All right. Fine, I'm coming.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Here.
- Come on.
Watch your step.
What's with the ruckus?
It's not like
they own the neighborhood.
(Episode 34)
My darn sons.
I should've at least
had one daughter.
Seo Jin, you're here!
I'm always so sorry about this.
I know it's you
who watches her the longest.
Don't mention it. I'm jobless,
so it's the least I can do.
Seo Jin, we'll have fun today
like we always do, okay?
Here you go. It's for kids
two grades above Ji Hun,
but he won't find it that hard.
Hyun Gyung, thanks for
always looking out for him.
Goodness.
What?
Go.
Get inside.
Seo Jin, let's head inside.
- Bye, Hyun Gyung.
- Bye.
I feel like this new series
will work out for me.
We rehearsed yesterday...
and the director was pleased.
I feel good about it too.
Really? I'm glad.
So I was wondering...
if you could let me
keep my promise to Seo Young.
Let us go out for dinner
as a family.
I wanted to treat the kids
to something delicious.
Could you allow that?
Sure. Let's go out for dinner.
Really?
Let me know when and where.
Just so you know,
Seo Young's craving cream spaghetti.
Cream spaghetti? And you?
What about you?
What does Seo Jin like?
I'll buy everything you want.
How many of our patients
are booking in advance?
We're allowing 60 percent
of our patients to book in advance.
What do you all say
to increase that...
to about 70 percent?
Patients have been complaining...
about having to wait too long
on the spot.
Increasing the number
to 70 percent...
will help us be more efficient.
It sounds like a good idea.
I have been receiving
many complaints too.
Then let's give it a try
and see how it works...
I don't agree, Director Lee.
Go ahead, Dr. Yoon.
Many kids in this neighborhood
are being watched by grandparents.
They'll find it difficult
to book for our service in advance.
Isn't an increase in 10 percent
a reasonable compromise though?
Actually, that's a large number.
Especially children
from lower-income households...
who come to us because
of our welfare program...
might not have access
to the Internet at home.
Then we'll allow bookings via phone.
I'm sure they can
at least make calls.
We already have
that system in place.
It's just a given fact that
people of the older generation...
prefer to come in
instead of booking appointments.
They find the entire
booking system to be foreign.
Wouldn't it be better
to educate them on the system then?
For the long run, I mean.
Why is this something
we must push through?
Then we'll think about it some more.
That'll be the end
of today's meeting.
What Dr. Yoon said earlier
applies specifically...
to the nature of this district.
Of course it's more efficient to
increase the percentage of bookings.
However, once you deal
with the grandparents,
you get to understand
where they're coming from...
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
I'm just amused by...
how passionately
you're speaking up for Gyu Jin.
I didn't want you
to be bothered by what he said.
Well, I'm not.
We don't have to agree on everything
so I understand.
Then I'm glad.
I'm more worried about
eating lunch alone today.
You'll join me, right?
I'll call you later.
Are you kidding me?
Gyu Jin,
don't you think you overreacted?
What do you mean?
With Director Lee.
It's not like you to get emotional.
As if. You're the one
who's making it a big deal.
I'm your brother, Gyu Jin. By blood.
I can tell when you're not yourself.
It's because of Na Hee, right?
Something's up between them.
I don't know.
But so what if there is?
It's none of my business now.
Gyu Jin.
Apologize when you
get the chance, okay?
I'm sure he was bothered by it.
You talked back
in front of his subordinates.
An interim director is still
a director of this hospital.
I'll get going.
Unbelievable.
I'm going.
- Have a good day.
- You too.
- Sir, can you sign this?
- Sure.
Got it. Have a good day.
- You too.
- Sure.
Sorry about that.
It's nothing. Have a good day then.
Thank you.
My gosh.
Again? But you got
me flowers yesterday.
Just because you eat today
doesn't mean you shouldn't tomorrow.
Roses keep reminding me of you.
Just you wait and see.
I'll fill up the store with roses
in no time.
What use does a kimbap place have
for all these roses?
Aren't you hot though?
It gets sweaty in leather items.
I'm not sweating at all.
Anyway, here's to another good day.
Young and fresh!
I could see him sweat,
but he says he isn't sweating.
What now?
You should tell him, Cho Yeon.
Wearing a leather jacket
and riding a motorcycle...
doesn't make you a pretty boy.
Let him be. I can't tell him
to stop what he enjoys.
There's an adorable side to him.
Hello,
I'm here to bring you
words of wisdom.
Dad!
The room's too small, isn't it?
The rest had to be allocated
to the diner.
It's big enough
for just one person.
Also, the flowers smell amazing.
I moved to a fun neighborhood, Dad.
Who knew that flowers
could blossom on a dead tree?
Some guy has been bringing
me flowers because he likes me.
Is that so? That's nice to hear.
How do you feel about him then?
He's not that bad...
and he's quite down-to-earth.
There's a manliness
to his good looks too.
Then you should make it work.
I'm seeing how it plays out for now.
You know I'm skeptical
when it comes to men.
I've dealt with
my fair share of morons,
so I'm taking my time for now.
Also, it's not charming for a woman
to accept one's love so fast.
You need to play hard to get.
Goodness. What if he gets tired
and moves on?
Don't worry, Dad.
Your daughter is an expert
when it comes to men.
I see that spring
has found my daughter's face.
It must be a good sign.
You said that last year too,
remember?
All you do is lie.
It's all part of the journey.
Life may seem tough for you,
but it'll deliver
a gift to you someday...
just like it led me to you.
You keep getting better
with your words, don't you?
If you weren't a monk,
you'd have broken a lot of hearts.
Here you go.
Sir?
- My gosh.
- Goodness, it's you.
I can't believe I ran into you here.
- What brings you by?
- Well...
I'm here to meet a friendly face,
but I didn't expect
to run into you too.
I was able to meet
two precious spirits today...
which can only be categorized
as an extraordinary event.
Goodness.
- Have you been well?
- As you can see, yes.
I'll see you around then.
Sure thing.
Please have a safe trip back.
He looks like he lost weight
every time I see him.
This won't do.
I should make
the perilla leaf pickles he likes...
and take it to him tomorrow.
I feel awful.
Are we taking the day off then?
In your dreams.
We'll need to prep the ingredients
before she comes in.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello, Mr. Song.
- Hi.
What brings you by?
I'm here to get your approval...
for the eco-friendly
food waste disposer.
Should I sign it?
Just a second.
Did you have a visitor?
The tea smells nice.
My dad stopped by a few minutes ago.
I see.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
You're working hard like always.
I hardly think that's true.
Hold on. Hasn't Chi Su
been by today?
He already came by!
He bought her
a bouquet of 100 roses.
One yesterday and one today.
It's true how one falls harder
later in their years.
Give my friend of 10 years
a chance, okay?
I can't speak for everything else,
but he's truly a decent man.
Well...
Anyway, have a good day.
- Bye.
- I'll see you around.
- See you.
Have a good day.
Gosh, why is everyone trying
to pressure me?
Anyway, let's open up the diner.
Stop that, you two.
Ju Ri, blanch the spinach.
Ga Yeon, chop the carrots.
Okay. I will.
Let's go.
Here. This is your favorite,
cream spaghetti.
Have some steak too.
I'll cut it for you.
Dad. I forgot to bring oil paints...
for the art class today.
Really? What did you do?
So I went to the stationary shop
in front of the school.
And I found photo cards
of GOT7 there.
What can I do? I'm a big fan.
So I had to buy them.
I just braced myself for scolding
and bought them.
You know my friend
who sits next to me.
I told you about him before.
He's Oh Jae Min.
Oh, right.
He brought extra oil paints
for me. Isn't that amazing?
Gosh, he sounds very sweet.
You should have some steak.
You've lost weight recently.
And he gave his pastels to me.
That's when I realized it.
He has feelings for me.
Why would he give me art supplies
when he doesn't like me?
You're right. He really does
have an eye for people.
My daughter is pretty.
If he takes good care of me,
it means he likes me. Right?
Stop talking and eat your food.
You said you wanted
to eat out as a family.
Are you here to chat away?
Yes. This is what I wanted to do.
Sit around together
and have a chat over a meal.
So how do you feel?
Do you not like Jae Min?
Well... He's not bad,
but he's not my type.
I like tall guys.
I don't like it that I'm short.
And I like guys with single eyelids
who are chic.
There's no need to explain more.
I like a guy just like him.
Hyo Sin.
Hey. You said your ideal type is me.
I just said it...
- to make you feel good.
- Gosh.
Is he doing well?
Did he not ask you about me?
He didn't. He's not
interested in you at all.
You're just jealous. You're so cute
when you feel jealous.
Gosh.
Excuse me. Can you take
a picture of us?
Our family is eating out together.
Okay.
- Please come closer.
- Okay.
Mom, come closer. Come here.
I'm taking it now. 1, 2.
Dad, thank you
for dinner today. Bye.
- All right. Text me, Seo Young.
- Okay.
Good night, Seo Jin.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye.
Hyun Gyung.
What? Do you have
anything to say?
Well... It's nothing special.
Like I said yesterday, I'm feeling
pretty good this time.
To be honest, I was worried...
if I wouldn't get any work
after starting my own business.
Once I do a good job,
it will go viral quickly.
So?
Well... I mean...
I think I'll become
financially stable soon.
And we should think
about Seo Young and Seo Jin.
If things go well,
- we might...
- Joon Seon.
Yes, ma'am. I mean, yes.
I don't want to talk
about what's already over.
I just want you to do things...
that you should do
as Seo Young and Seo Jin's dad.
I should go then.
Joon Seon is coming home late.
I guess the dinner is over already.
I know. It's past 10 p.m.
Is it that Joon Seon
went home with them?
Are they having a great time
as a family?
I hope things go well
and they get back together.
He's still in love with his wife.
Sure. He's such a romanticist.
I know it. And the sky knows.
By the way, I think we should lose
some weight to wear a suit.
Shall we try intermediate
fasting or something?
It's intermittent fasting,
not intermediate fasting.
Right. Intermittent fasting.
I said intermittent fasting.
You said intermediate fasting.
He's right. I heard it too.
Hey.
I'm sure I said
intermittent fasting.
Are you deaf or what?
Stop accusing an innocent person
and go pick your ears. And you...
You're home, Joon Seon.
They didn't pick their ears.
So I was going to pick them.
Joon Seon, did you enjoy the dinner?
It took a long time.
I bet things went well.
Joon Seon, what did you eat?
Did you go home with them
after dinner?
Did you get to talk to your wife?
Joon Seon, tell us about it.
We were really curious.
Let go of me. What? Why?
Gosh, I'm feeling nauseous.
Ga Hee forced me
to drink soju with beer.
I just wasted the whole day
without studying.
I can't do this.
I should go take some pills.
Hello. I need
some hangover relief pills.
Ms. Choi. My gosh.
Gosh, it's cold.
What?
I'm sorry.
- Please enjoy.
- Thanks.
Please eat, Ms. Choi.
You're not feeling good,
so you haven't eaten all day.
Here.
I've never tried
ox blood soup before.
You should try it. It's good.
Ox blood soup is great
for a hangover.
Ms. Song, with you...
No, we're not in-laws anymore.
I'm not sure if it's okay
to sit here with you.
But I like you. I have
no hard feelings towards you.
I know. I'm sorry
about Na Hee and Gyu Jin.
I have no one to talk to,
so I'm just frustrated.
My first son is now a divorced man.
And my second son is no different.
I wanted to set him up
with a woman I like,
but he showed up there
with his girlfriend.
It turns out he had a girlfriend.
I don't know who she is though.
I heard she's still a student.
What does he want to do
with such a young girl?
I wish she wouldn't be
a selfish wench.
Oh, it's okay.
I know Na Hee has that side to her.
That's how the elders feel
about her.
I know. Even her sister knows that.
I knew it.
Right.
Anyway, I just can't get
my way with my children.
Life is so vain and empty.
I see.
When are you going home?
If you need a ride, come running.
Gyu Jin, I'm having dinner
with Gi Yeong.
You go home first.
You should've told me sooner
so I didn't have to call you.
I'm hanging up.
That fool.
Are you getting off work, Dr. Yoon?
Yes.
If you have some time,
will you go out for a drink with me?
Well... Okay.
Isn't it nice here?
I come here a lot.
I see.
Earlier on, I think I went too far.
I apologize.
Leave it. I went too far myself.
I've worked here for a few years,
and the hospital means a lot to me.
It wasn't anything personal,
so don't get the wrong idea.
Really?
It was a bit personal for me.
I like Na Hee.
I have feelings for her.
I want to make things work,
but I think she needs more time.
So I'll approach her slowly,
bit by bit.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I think you caught on.
Isn't that why
you opposed me so hard?
No, that was...
I'm not asking for your permission.
I just wanted to be forthcoming.
Why are you buying me dinner anyway?
Why even ask? It's not a big deal.
Also, talk freely now.
You're my university senior.
I can't do that.
We're in different departments
and I came to the hospital later.
Don't you say that.
Just speak freely.
Treat me comfortably.
Can I do that? I will, then.
Speaking casually
does make us feel closer.
Right, Gi Yeong?
- Eat some more.
- Thanks.
So, that person we met yesterday.
Dr. Song's younger sister.
Who? My in-law?
Yes, your sister-in-law.
No. Technically,
she's your ex-sister-in-law.
Yes. What about her?
Could you...
set me up with her?
- What?
- The thing is,
she's totally my type.
I can't handle strong women.
But she looks sweet and docile.
She's my type.
I feel really lonely these days.
I see.
But even if my life depends on it,
I can't ask Dr. Song to
introduce me to her sister.
If you arrange a date
as if it's a coincidence,
I'll do whatever...
She has a boyfriend.
What? She does?
Yes.
It looked like
they're going to marry.
You got excited over nothing.
Is your car parked at the hospital?
Yes. I'll call for a driver.
What about you?
I'll take a taxi from here.
I'd rather not walk back.
- Okay.
- Bye.
(Bo Young)
- I'll call you...
- Where are you?
Si Hoo... My son...
What's wrong? What's the matter?
39, heart rate 105,
white blood cell count is 18,000.
Respiratory rate is 40,
indicating tachypnea.
Chemistry results?
We're still waiting.
I'll get the shot ready.
Doctor. Si Hoo's okay, isn't he?
Is he okay?
Yes. Don't worry.
It could be pneumonia. I prescribed
an antibiotic, so he'll be fine.
Bo Young.
Gyu Jin.
It's okay. He'll be fine.
Thanks.
- I enjoyed the meal.
- Good.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
Bye.
What was that about, Jae Seok?
She has a boyfriend?
What were you thinking?
Do you...
Thanks for everything today.
I feel much better now.
I enjoyed dinner too.
Don't skip any meals.
Find a part-timer soon too.
Okay, I will. Take care.
Bye.
- Sleep well.
- I will.
Lock up.
See you.
Bye.
Yes.
That's the only answer.
I like...
Ms. Song.
(Epilogue, The day before)
Let's be honest. I'll say this
only because I have liquid courage.
Why are parents never okay with
their kids' divorce?
Look at Americans, for example.
My life is my own.
My kids' lives are their own.
They acknowledge everything.
Why... Why can't you
let your kids be independent?
Jeez...
Yes.
There's a difference in mentality.
And culture as well.
Hey, imagine Ji Hun was divorced.
Would you be cool with that?
I can't.
Gosh, no. Never.
This can't happen to Ji Hun.
- How could you?
- See? You brat.
Ga Hee!
Mom!
My gosh. What's up with her?
She's drunk.
Her pupils are dilated.
Have you ever been to Mount Nam?
Have you?
Mom. Have you been to Mount Nam?
I...
I have been to Mount Nam.
She's out of it.
Why did she mention Mount Nam?
She must've gone.
Who did she go with?
No!
- No, no.
(Once Again)
I'm not cleaning right now.
I'm wiping my heart.
I'll go back
to my corrupt lifestyle.
to being the old Yoon Jae Seok!
My gosh!
- Mom.
- What happened to you?
- Well...
- What did you do to him?
I'm sorry. I was careless.
I was so afraid yesterday.
No, don't say that.
It'll only make me
feel uncomfortable.
Then I won't do that from now on.
- Are you...
- Who are you?
It is you, Young Dal.
Oh, right. I visited my mom's
a while ago...
and heard about my cousin
once removed.