What do you mean?
The woman I like...
is going with me to eat dinner.
Hi, Si Hoo.
Okay.
Mom will be right back.
Bye.
Yes, sir.
Really? Is it urgent?
Okay, got it.
I'll be right up.
Sure thing.
That was the administration office.
There's an issue with
the contract we signed...
with a pharmaceutical company...
and it needs
to be solved immediately.
Can I take a rain check on dinner?
Sure thing.
Sorry about this.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We should go too.
Sure.
So that's how
you confess your love to someone.
Who knew? I guess I was schooled.
He told her how he feels
all so casually.
It was sophisticated.
Right.
Are you all right?
Doesn't it bother you?
Of course not.
Besides, it's none of my business.
I knew in advance though.
He kept hinting at it.
Really?
He's not the patient kind though,
is he?
I thought he'd wait a little longer.
Hold on.
What's taking the elevator so long?
Is something keeping it up there?
Cut! Okay.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
Have a good day.
- Mr. Song.
- Yes?
- That was some great work.
- Gosh, thank you.
I liked your new stuntman.
His punches and kicks were sharp...
and his figure
matches his double more.
Right? What did I tell you?
I said you'd be fond of him.
Where did you find a gem like him?
He has a fresh face too.
If he can act,
he might even make it as an actor.
My gosh. He's not on that level yet.
Anyway, thank you
for thinking fondly of him.
He'll be here
for the next shoot too, right?
Sorry?
Yes, of course. He'll be here.
- Thanks, Mr. Song.
- My pleasure.
By the way, what's his name?
His name?
A good person
It's Park Hyo Sin.
You were incredible today.
How can an amateur...
look even sharper than Jeong Bong
who's been at this for five years?
Jong Soo, you're overreacting.
His performance just now...
can be done by anyone
who's athletic and nimble.
Well, the landing was great.
I give you that.
The rest seemed sloppy though.
As if.
Every move he made was sharp.
Is that so?
Let's go then.
Sorry about that. My bad.
Jeong Bong.
The night air sure is refreshing.
Maybe it's because
I studied hard today.
It could be...
because you're with a decent guy.
But that decent guy
isn't my boyfriend, but my in-law.
- How sad is that?
- Seriously?
I'm grateful for today though.
Na Hee won't have any reason
to hit me today.
You're the best math tutor ever.
Didn't I mention that I competed...
in the Mathematical Olympiad?
And you proved it.
Hold on a second.
This isn't
the fastest way home for you.
I'm trying to walk more
to lose the weight I put on.
What? That's absurd.
You're still just as slender.
As if. You'd be surprised
by the weight I put on.
I really need to work out more.
You're not bad at that.
You have good a good stance too.
Left hook, right hook.
- Jab, jab.
- Jab!
- Like this.
Light punches.
So my house
is just around the corner.
It's late, so let me walk you
all the way.
That's all right.
It's only a short walk.
You should...
head that way over the uphill road.
There's a running track
so you can squeeze a jog in.
An uphill road? I see.
I'll get going then. Good night.
I'll see you tomorrow if I can.
Bye.
If only she stayed longer.
I miss her already.
What?
You miss her? Unbelievable.
Are you insane?
Well, I miss her.
Taxi!
Nice.
Gosh, look at you all
flying across the room.
That's so cool of you.
You don't look like the guys
I see every morning.
Joon Seon, is this you?
No, Dad. That's Jong Soo.
- This is me!
- I see.
Right, it seems like your figure.
- That's right.
- Still,
I think Hyo Sin looked the best.
The landing was awesome.
- Thanks.
- Right?
Ji Hun, you have a good eye.
It's not easy to land perfectly
without any training.
You could end up busting your knees.
It shows that Hyo Sin
has natural talent.
I only copied what I saw on TV.
Yes, that's right.
It only looks good
because he's tall and fit.
You could've
badly injured your knees today!
Don't be ridiculous.
He didn't hesitate at all today.
You did well.
I don't know much
about stunt performances,
but you did well for a beginner.
You're nimble and well-coordinated.
I guess. You look good.
That reminds me. Ga Hee,
didn't you have a job interview?
How did it go?
What?
Oh, I'm going to take
a pass on that one.
The gym didn't seem
like my cup of tea.
What's the place that
works for you then? Your room?
Dad, must you
kick it where it hurts?
Now I know where
Na Hee gets her tendencies from.
- I'm home.
- Hi, Da Hee.
- Welcome home.
- Have some strawberries.
Strawberries!
Where's Na Hee? Is she home yet?
- I'm home.
- There she is.
- Hi.
- Have some strawberries.
Did you just get home? Me too.
Na Hee, I'm ready.
We can begin our session.
I'm sorry,
but can we skip today's session?
I'm tired.
But I solved all the math problems.
Are you that tired?
Yes, I'd rather go to bed early.
We'll study tomorrow.
Sure. I guess I have no choice.
The woman I like
is going with me to eat dinner.
He sure has poor judgement
when it comes to women.
"That's what I'm doing."
Are you kidding me with that line?
Could his words be any cheesier?
Who emptied the can? Unbelievable!
Gyu Jin, I'm home.
So what if you are?
What am I supposed to do about it?
Why are you in a sour mood again?
Is something up?
A sour mood? As if.
I'm in a good mood like always.
Why are you throwing
a temper tantrum?
Living with you
has made me realize...
just how temperamental you are.
I seriously suggest
that you seek out a therapist.
A sudden change in one's life
releases cortisol...
which prevents you from
thinking clearly, right?
- People these days...
- Seek out a therapist yourself.
I hate everything about you,
especially how chatty you are.
Actually, I loathe it,
so just shut it and...
Stop kicking me here and there.
It's disgusting!
Let go of me.
If you don't,
I'll kick you with my other leg.
Why would I let go
when you'll only kick me again?
I'll hold onto them all night.
I dare you to try!
- Take that.
- What...
Darn it!
Joon Seon, I was already...
Hyo Sin, have a seat.
Let me put some ice on your knees.
Your muscles can go into shock...
if it's not used to being worked
in a certain way.
You need to ice them.
But my knees are fine.
Just hold still.
How about you tape your knee
before the next shoot?
That'd be better.
The next time?
That's never going to happen.
There's no need to
flatly reject the offer.
My goal was to only
have you fill in for today,
but you have natural talent.
Why let it go to waste?
Besides, this is
a good opportunity for you.
This will give you more of a future
than delivering fried chicken.
It's not something I want to do,
so give up on the idea.
But Hyo Sin... Hey, wait.
Come back here. Hyo Sin!
He sure is a tough nut to crack.
How do I get him on board?
He clearly isn't fond of the idea.
It's not like you can
force people to do things.
I'll work on a speedy recovery.
Actually, I've already recovered.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
I'd rather work with you too,
but it's Hyo Sin
that the director wants.
How can I persuade him?
Darn it.
A jog early in the morning...
sure is different
compared to our training sessions.
How refreshing.
Hyo Sin, wait for me.
Do you mind if we work together?
Our faces may not
be shown on the screen,
but we can also still become
someone like Chad Stahelski.
Do you know the movie
"John Wick" and "Captain America"?
He's the director who
designed the action sequences.
Is it because of your day job?
Don't you worry
and let me tell my dad.
He may not show it often,
but he's my biggest supporter.
Trust me, okay?
Hyo Sin, wait!
This isn't me falling behind.
I'm giving you some space
to rethink my offer.
Come to a wise decision!
Gosh, he's fast.
What can I do to persuade him?
Darn, my heart. It's about to burst.
- Darn it.
- My gosh.
Wait, are you here
to take a nap too?
I thought I get some shut-eye
before I see my patients.
What about you?
I didn't sleep well last night.
Da Hee studied until
late in the night...
and you know I can't sleep
if the light is on.
That's right.
Should I leave you to your nap then?
It's fine. I don't think
I'm in the mood for one anyway.
Should I leave the room
for you instead?
No, I'm not as sleepy anymore.
Why don't I sit down then?
Lucky you.
A man confessed
his feelings for you.
Oh, that. Tell me about it.
Who knew that'd happen to me?
Right.
So... What will it be?
Will you date him?
I don't know.
Why? Are you bothered that I might?
Does it make you uncomfortable?
What?
Why would it bother me?
It's more like this.
Well, Jeong Rok...
is a sweet and considerate guy.
But he's quite flirtatious
if you ask me.
His eyes are always smiling.
He's the type of guy...
that might string women along.
It could be annoying to date him.
Why the sudden change of heart?
You once wished me luck with him...
and said that he's a decent man.
Well, he is. Of course he's decent.
I'm just stating the rumors...
and what I have observed
to help you decide.
Sure, I'll consider your advice.
Good.
Anyway, I wish you luck with
your first love. You two seem close.
Me? Wait, with Bo Young?
- You see, Bo Young and I...
- I'll get going.
When will she learn
not to cut people off like this?
I doubt she'll ever be able to.
My gosh. Hold on a second.
So is she going to date him or not?
Unbelievable.
Na Hee.
I was on my way to see you.
Is that so?
- Today, for lunch...
- Jeong Rok.
I don't think I'll be able
to join you for lunch today.
I was coming over here
to tell you that too.
Something came up.
I see.
Then I'm glad.
Your shift begins soon, right?
Have a good one.
What on earth is going on?
Didn't he say he liked me yesterday?
Why is he acting like
nothing happened?
8, 2, 3, cha-cha-cha.
2, 3.
That's right.
It's not over until it's over.
I, Jang Ok Ja,
have yet to make my move.
Cha-cha-cha.
Okay, that'll be all
for today's class. Good job.
Can I get your attention
for a second though?
I have an announcement to make.
In two months,
the borough will hold...
an amateur dance festival.
It's a big event
with many prizes to win.
I thought it'd be a good idea...
for a couple in our class
to enter it.
I doubt we're good enough
for a competition.
What about me?
It's probably better...
to have our two best dancers
enter it.
So Ms. Kang and...
the always enthusiastic Mr. Yang.
What do you say?
I'd be honored! I'd love to.
And Ms. Kang?
I'm not sure.
It may not work out since
I'm a better dancer than he is.
I have a store to run too,
so I need to think about it.
All right then.
I'll wait for your answer.
Me! Let me enter instead.
I want to give it a shot.
He's my partner,
and we are nearly equal.
With you
Dr. Yoon, is there something
good going on today?
Sure.
I'm having a date.
A date?
Gosh.
Are you seeing someone?
Well...
It feels like she's mine
But she's not quite mine
It's like that.
Oh. 3, 2,
and one. Time's up.
Bye. See you.
I bet he's got a girlfriend.
I just lost one more guy.
When did you come?
I just got here.
Why isn't it here?
It doesn't say 64 here.
Why do you think is that?
Because it's wrong.
Let me see.
F of x plus y equals...
f of x plus xy plus four xy.
Then it's limit from h to 0.
And it's f over h.
So the answer is...
What is it?
What's the answer?
The answer is...
Isn't it Na Hee over there?
Na Hee?
It's not her. I was mistaken.
She looks just like Na Hee.
You startled me.
Why would Na Hee be here?
All right. Look.
Put these in
and calculate the answer.
What is it then?
It's number 2, 80. Okay?
I put in the numbers
the wrong way earlier.
So you're an Olympiad
contestant indeed.
This is just nothing.
Do you want me to solve it
using my foot?
You don't have to. I believe you.
All right then. Let's go in.
Already?
Do you not have
any other problems to ask?
I'm almost finished.
And you have some work to do.
I'm fine.
I excel in memory work,
so I can memorize it all
once I read it.
Still, I don't want
to take up your time.
Let's go.
I can't do this.
I should just get it over with
and make myself clear.
I might feel bad for the time being,
but this is the right thing to do.
(Director's Office)
- Na Hee.
- Hey.
Is the director in there?
No. He's having a meeting
with hospital directors.
I just left reports in his office.
Did he leave already?
What? He shouldn't
have brought it up.
He's making things awkward.
Na Hee.
Mom, Dad.
Hey, did you have dinner?
Not yet.
You are coming home early tonight.
Yes. The chicken sold out
earlier than usual.
Things have been like that
since we started delivery.
I told you we should've
done it sooner.
Why would you not listen to me?
It's just good that we started it.
Don't be so greedy for profits.
What? Look who's talking.
It's you who always
talk about money.
I just try to economize
and save money.
It's nothing like being greedy.
That's enough.
If you keep being like this,
you might start fighting.
This is what we do all the time.
It's no big deal.
I guess your mom can't
do otherwise than nag me...
every single day.
Let's just go home
and eat. I'm hungry.
Let's go.
What?
I should get going.
Do you want to stay and study more?
No, I should go.
I was about to leave.
My pen.
Are you making
a detour again tonight?
You must be tired.
I still need to stick to my words.
A person's lifespan is inversely
proportional to his waistline.
You're not even fat.
It's good for me though.
I'm not bored this way.
Do you like it?
Me too.
We can talk and exercise.
The exam is not far off now.
I'm nervous already.
Is there anything you want to do
after the exam?
Like a bucket list.
There are a lot of things
I want to try.
I want to go to eat
something delicious.
I want to go on a trip.
What I want to do most is
getting a driver's license.
I don't have it yet.
What about dating?
Do you not want to date a guy?
You know what I went through.
I don't want a guy in my life
for the time being.
I'll just focus on my studies.
I should pass
the transfer exam first though.
Don't speak so hastily.
You never know
what the future holds.
I'm pretty sure.
I will never date a guy.
- No.
- Why not?
You can't be like that.
Why would you bar up
your heart like that?
You can't resist love
after one failure like that.
It's just so foolish of you.
Why are you yelling at me?
Well... I wasn't yelling at you.
I'm just worried...
you might not recognize a good guy
because of one failed love.
I'm just saying this
for caution's sake.
I guess I should go this way.
Bye. I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye. See you.
Thank you for today.
Cha-cha-cha.
- My gosh.
- We can't do this.
It's not working.
Why not?
I didn't get the hang of it yet.
And you're just as bad as I am.
We can't enter a contest like this.
It will be just humiliating.
So what? Do you want to quit?
That's not what I'm saying.
I might be able to pull it off
with someone better.
Who? Cho Yeon?
She said she isn't interested,
and however much you cry for her,
the reality is that Jang Ok Ja,
I am your partner.
So, will you practice hard
for 30 more minutes,
or shall we practice all night?
30 minutes.
30 minutes?
Okay. Let's start
from the beginning.
- Stay alert.
- Okay.
Here. The starting stance. And go.
1, 2, cha-cha-cha.
3, 4, cha-cha-cha. Pose.
Mom, I'm home. Dad, I'm back.
- You're home.
- Yes.
How do you feel today?
I feel fine. Let's study.
- Let's make up for yesterday.
- Okay.
Wow, you got it right.
This question
is about differentials.
Good for you. You got better at
solving the complicated ones.
My tutoring is working.
See? You're improving
because you have a great tutor.
Yes. You're right.
It's all about the tutor.
That's right.
I'm an expensive tutor.
Next question.
F of x is...
Na Hee said I'm doing well.
Why did she send
such a cute emoticon?
This is crazy.
Congratulations. Good luck.
I owe you. Night night.
What was that for?
Why did she say "night night"?
How cute!
"Night night."
My goodness.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm cleaning the bathroom.
Why are you doing that for?
I cleaned it already.
It's great for when you want to
stop thinking about something.
You should've told me so!
Stop thinking about what?
Did something happen at
the hospital today?
- Move.
- Wait, I want to wash my hands.
- Get out.
- But I want to...
Yes, director.
He's a newbie and not ready yet.
Can I bring the other guy...
What? Why would you say that, sir?
You'll hire another stunt team?
You know how hard
I worked to get here.
How can you say that?
Then I'll do what I can
to persuade him,
and bring him to the shoot...
And this is not the right time
for someone to call me.
Okay.
I got your point.
Let's do this instead.
Joon Seon.
I think I'm almost healed.
I jumped rope 100 times.
Good. Congratulations, Jeong Bong.
Don't overdo it.
You. Let's talk.
What's going on? Why did they
go out when they could talk here?
Exactly. Do you think
they're discussing a secret?
A secret? Like what? What secret?
What secret?
What secret could Joon Seon
possibly keep from us?
Sorry. I'm not angry with you.
Fine. You take 30.
- What?
- Your pay.
Stuntmen sign with a team
and share the profits.
I take 50, Jeong Bong takes 30,
and Jong Soo takes 20 percent.
But especially for you,
you can take 30.
But honestly, shouldn't we
give Jeong Bong 10 percent?
He got hurt too.
That means I get 40 percent.
I'll take that.
It's not about the pay.
Okay, fine. 40.
You can take 40 percent.
It's not just for a few days.
Let's say I'm investing in you.
This is an exceptional deal
for a rookie.
You can't tell Jeong Bong
and Jong Soo, okay?
- Joon Seon.
- What? Talk freely.
Don't hesitate. Share your opinion.
I'll say it again. I'm not
interested in doing stunts.
Nor will I strike a deal
with my pay.
Give Jeong Bong
whatever stunts he can handle.
Hey, hey. I want to
do that if I could.
But you're the one
the director wants.
I told him you're our newbie
and I can't take it back now.
Tell him the truth.
What truth? This job is
all about trust and credit.
Should I tell the director,
"It's a lie that he's our newbie"?
Hey, Hyo Sin. Come on.
I'm off to work.
Na Hee, wait for me!
Where are you going?
To a job interview.
What?
The clothing store
asked me to come in.
You didn't say so earlier.
What if I did
and didn't get the job?
I'll never survive Dad's scorn.
I smell cigarettes.
Who the heck smoked here
so early in the morning?
- Jerks should...
- Wait. Ga Hee.
Isn't this mine?
Gosh, look at the time.
Let's hurry. I might be late.
Ga Hee! Did you wear
some of my other clothes too?
- I'm late!
- Is it your second time?
(Resume)
Managing a clothing store
is hard work.
Even more so because
we deal with men and women.
You need to be tactful
and it helps if you're young too.
Oh, I see.
But then younger people
are bad at dealing with customers...
and quit for no reason.
Give it a go.
You're a mom,
so you must be responsible.
Did I just get the job?
Yes. You can start tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
Did I tell you that
you're beautiful?
I didn't, did I?
I wanted to say so for a while.
You're so beautiful.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Sure.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Hi, Mom.
Ji Hun! I passed the interview.
Mom got a job!
You did? Congratulations, Mom.
Thanks.
Now I'll get you
everything you want.
I'll dress you in designer labels
from head to toe,
and send you to violin lessons.
I don't need designer clothes.
And I'm not interested in
learning the violin.
You're not? Then think about
what you'd like to do.
Let's meet up after your class.
I'll treat you to celebrate.
What do you want to eat?
Shall we eat lobster?
No, that's hard to digest.
Bring some tteokbokki.
What, just tteokbokki?
Yes. I want tteokbokki.
The bell just went. Bye.
Bye.
He's so thoughtful.
Yes. Mom got carried away.
I wasn't paid yet.
I can't afford lobster.
Yes. Today, we'll have tteokbokki!
(Episode 38)
(Song Joon Seon)
Hyo Sin, help me this once.
My body's aching all over.
We're both inept dancers,
but we're forcing ourselves...
to practice for the competition.
It's killing me.
It would've been better
to team up with Ms. Kang.
Exactly!
She would've agreed to it
in a few days,
but your sister-in-law
can get greedy at times.
She might even make you
hand over this store for free.
I will if that's what she wants.
It's not like I can run it forever.
Are you serious about that?
What about Joon Seon or Ga Hee?
Ga Hee's too lazy for the job.
And Joon Seon thinks that
being a stuntman is his calling.
Who am I to stop him
from doing what he loves?
Still, he's starring
in a new TV series...
and he showed us
a video of it last night.
Really?
Your son is on a roll then.
There's no need
to worry about him anymore.
Gosh, he still has a long way to go.
- Would you like to see it?
- Sure.
My grandson sent over this video.
Here we go. There.
He has a lean body just like me...
and is quite athletic.
Look at him go!
Is this Joon Seon?
No.
This guy flying across the room.
What do you mean he's flying?
He only jumped.
He jumped over another person.
- That's flying.
- Let me see that again.
All right. Watch closely this time.
Did you see him fly just now?
- Was that Joon Seon?
- Yes!
What? You're in?
I'm super glad to hear that.
I'll make sure you never regret it.
Thank you so much, Hyo Sin.
I'll do it if Mr. Song allows me to.
He will, so don't you worry.
Why would he say no
when my career's on the line?
I'm talking about
my job as the delivery guy.
What?
So...
I'm supposed
to let you have Hyo Sin...
and use this delivery app instead?
That's right.
I'll pay 30 percent
of the commission.
And how much would that be?
I looked into it...
and based on our sales,
the commission
will be twice my salary.
It may be more
when sales go up in the summer.
Then 30 percent is not enough.
50 percent.
Dad, please.
You're being calculative.
I haven't even received
my first paycheck yet.
How about 35 percent?
I can't cut you slack
because you're my son.
40 percent.
Seriously?
Joon Seon,
- agree to the 40 percent...
- What?
Or I'll turn down your offer.
Okay, fine. 40 percent!
You mean business,
don't you, Mr. Song?
Do we have a deal then?
- Here.
- Just do your job properly...
and don't put Hyo Sin
through the wringer.
A good job is what I'm trying to do.
Here.
It's only for this show though.
The handshake wasn't meant for you.
Joon Seon, let's do this.
Sure thing!
Here are the doctor's notes
and medical records you requested.
The doctors at the other hospital
can conduct basic tests again.
Yes, thank you.
It's her mom, right?
The child abuse victim
that Dr. Song reported.
Yes, the girl's dad is out on bail.
- Really?
- Yes.
She was staying at her sister's, but
now she's moving to the countryside.
They're switching hospitals too.
Gosh, how terrifying.
I knew he was terrible
from the start.
That dragon tattoo on his arm...
Your coffee is out.
Aren't you getting it?
Oh, right.
Go ahead.
What now?
Is there anything else
you want to give me advice on?
Not exactly.
Did you hear that...
the child abuse victim's dad...
made bail recently?
I did when printing out
my notes for her.
The law is lenient, if you ask me.
What about the kid and her mom?
A restraining order?
How can that ensure their safety?
Instead of worrying only about them,
worry about yourself more.
You're the one
who reported him to the police.
There's no need to worry...
because thugs only go after
those weaker than them.
You should've seen him cower
in front of the police.
Still...
You must have
a lot of free time on your hands.
First, you're giving me advice
on my love life...
and now you're worrying
about my safety.
It's not because
I have a lot of free time.
You know how considerate I can be.
Guys, hurry on over
to the conference room.
Gi Yeong's mom sent over dinner.
Her pork cutlet restaurant
is a big hit these days.
- Hurry.
- Pork cutlets?
Perfect timing.
She's too gutsy for her own good.
Too gutsy.
My gosh. What is all this?
Guys, come quick.
You have no idea
how crunchy they are.
They're to die for.
It looks delicious.
What about Dr. Yoon?
Did he head home?
He left a while ago.
He's awfully busy these days.
Anyway, thanks, Gi Yeong.
- Please enjoy.
- Thanks.
Did I hear, pork cutlets?
Is there some for me too?
Yes, right here.
Let's sit.
Thanks to Dr. Han,
we're enjoying a great treat today.
Where's your mother's
restaurant again?
Hanam, sir.
If it were close by,
I'd go there often.
Hanam isn't that far though.
We should go there for
a team dinner sometime to thank her.
Sure.
Sorry about that.
How unilateral of me.
I should've asked
for your opinions first.
- No, it's a great idea.
- I love the idea too.
Sounds good to me.
Okay, let's eat then.
Enjoy, everyone.
Sure.
Director Lee,
can we eat later...
and talk for a bit first?
Dig in, guys.
We should talk.
We should,
but here?
Right.
It's not something to say at work.
Should we take it outside then?
Sure.
We were about
to get off work anyway.
We'll take my car.
Did she get off work or not?
What on earth did
she and Jeong Rok talk about?
Unbelievable.
It's none of your business,
so don't even be curious.
Gyu Jin,
didn't you leave yet?
Right.
Well, I was thinking
about engaging myself...
in a medial discussion
with Dr. Song,
but maybe I'll do it tomorrow.
Bye, guys.
- We didn't ask.
- What's up with him?
Gosh.
I thought I needed
to stay fit to be a medical student,
so I came out here
to shoot hoops every night.
I liked how the bouncing ball...
sounded like my heartbeat.
All right then.
My heart-rate is up,
so say what's on your mind.
Jeong Rok, I'm not in a state...
where I can afford
to date anyone right now.
But...
now that I know how you feel,
I don't think
we should eat and talk...
like we once used to.
I don't want to give you
a sense of hope...
when I'm in no position
to handle the fallout.
I'm not so sure.
It doesn't seem that bad to me.
Keep giving me hope, I mean.
Our emotions move...
in different directions
at different speeds.
The one who developed feelings first
can wait...
for the other
to realize their true feelings too.
Giving hope to the one waiting...
is like the food we live on.
Without it...
To be honest,
I blurted out my feelings
and wanted to gain time to think.
I didn't know what to do next.
But...
now I do.
Bulldozing my way in
is not the answer.
Jeong Rok...
Leave me...
some hope, will you?
It'll be what I hold onto as I wait.
It's too bad
if I can't at least have that.
All right then. Here.
Want to give it a try?
Running around a bit
helps you sleep at night.
Over here.
Shoot.
- That was close.
- You almost scored.
Okay, that's good.
And here.
I'm buying to celebrate
my finding a job,
so eat up.
You never go big, do you?
A celebration dinner...
should at least involve
tangsuyuk and jajangmyeon.
My son's the one
who wanted tteokbokki.
Isn't that right?
Yes, I was craving it today,
and it's delicious.
Who cares if
it's tteokbokki or sundae?
What matters is that
she got herself a job.
Who'll look after Seo Jin
now that Ga Hee has a job?
Don't worry.
I can take her to work with us.
It's not like
she comes over every day.
I guess you're right.
Anyway, it sure is
a good day for our family.
Ga Hee found a job
and I signed a deal with Hyo Sin.
What? Really?
Is Hyo Sin
a member of your squad too?
Of course. We're brothers now.
No way.
He's too handsome
to be part of your team,
but this is good for you.
Every team needs
a visually stunning member, right?
If only he wasn't
the obvious choice.
Don't exhaust him
for no particular reason...
and look after him.
Hyo Sin, do your best
since you agreed to do it.
Sure, Mr. Song.
Don't worry, Dad.
All I'm worried about
is how successful we'll be.
Now that you mention it,
I don't see Chestnut.
Did he go somewhere?
He was tired, so he turned in early.
What? It's Mom!
She'll be mad
when she finds out I'm here.
But I told her you were here
when she called earlier.
Seo Jin, your mom's here. Let's go.
She's going to kill you.
Seo Young,
this is your last warning.
Don't you dare skip classes again,
or I'll kick you out of the house.
Sounds good to me.
I can stay at Grandpa's.
Don't get cheeky with me.
Sorry, Mom.
I won't skip my classes again.
Also, starting from
the day after tomorrow,
head to Grandpa's chicken place
after studying.
Take Seo Jin home and babysit
until I get home.
Why?
Your aunt has a job now.
Your grandma and grandpa
have enough on their plate,
so how can I ask them
to watch Seo Jin all night?
I'll get home as soon as possible.
But then I can't hang out
with my friends.
Help me out here, Seo Young.
You can hang out with them
some other time.
Whatever. You're so annoying.
I can't believe them.
They know how much
I love tteokbokki and sundae,
but still...
Jeong Bong, are you asleep?
I stole some sundae for you.
Have some, okay?
Gosh, I know
you're upset about this...
and it breaks my heart
to see you sit this one out.
Did you know that?
Besides, this isn't
our last project together.
I'll snag another gig for us...
and make sure
you get your chance to fly.
So get over it and have some sundae.
You're disappointing me
by being this way.
- Joon Seon.
- All right.
I brought liver, your favorite,
so have some.
Here.
- Joon Seon...
- Get in here.
I know how you feel
and I'm sorry about it.
I thought...
that you had abandoned me.
You only seemed
to care about Hyo Sin.
Are you seriously
comparing yourself to him?
You guys are all I have.
Hyo Sin's standoffish attitude
makes it hard for me to like him.
I'll use him for this project
and kick him to the curb.
Why on earth are you crying?
Now, eat up. You too, Jong Soo.
Sure.
The tteokbokki...
- Tteokbokki?
- I wanted some.
Hyo Sin, good luck.
I might not be around the gym
as often though.
Is that all right?
It's fine.
I'll keep training on my own.
Good. I'll let the trainer know.
He'll look after you.
Ji Hun!
How dare you touch my child?
Mom, please.
He's my son, okay?
You should head inside
and do your homework.
Clean up the rest then.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be at practice?
I haven't had dinner yet,
so I thought I'd grab a bite to eat.
Don't be ridiculous.
We can't waste a second of our time.
Now, stop this nonsense
and lead the way.
We need to practice. Come on!
You'll ruin my sweater.
It's expensive, you know.
- Come on!
- Fine, I'm going.
Mr. Yang hasn't been around
that much lately. Is he busy?
He's entering
that dance competition.
He must be busy practicing.
Still, he's not one
to not stop by the place.
Could he have fallen
for someone else?
Really?
Will we no longer
receive free beef then?
Gosh, that's too bad.
I'm weaker now that I haven't had...
my daily fix of beef.
Shut it, you two.
Will you be scrubbing all night?
Anyway, make sure you scrub well.
The surface was sticky
even after cleaning up yesterday.
Sure thing.
(Chi Su's Butcher Shop)
He's not here.
Where could he be?
He must be upset about everything.
Maybe I should've just caved in
and agreed to be his partner.
Why did I play hard to get?
I thought I'd get him smiling again
with a few rolls of kimbap.
Where is he anyway?
Gosh, I'm hungry.
It's so good.
These look good. Go ahead.
I thought you were dragging me
toward the dance studio,
so what are we doing here?
You said you didn't have dinner yet.
How can we dance
when you lack the energy?
Also, shouldn't we
build our teamwork more?
For better or worse,
we're stuck as partners.
Sure thing. Let's eat.
Here.
I'm staying away from alcohol
for the time being.
You see, I got wasted recently.
Cheers.
You shouldn't be drinking so much
at your age.
One should only drink until
you're in the best mood.
Gosh, that's good.
Sweet on the tongue.
I mean, look here, Ms. Ok Ja.
Let's be honest.
Do you think I'm that unattractive?
Am I just unlikable?
No, you're not unlikable.
I know. I'm not that bad, right?
Then why is Cho Yeon...
not interested in me at all?
What's wrong with me?
Ms. Ok Ja.
I want some food.
She's just unbelievable.
I've given her a lot of beef so far.
You know what?
It wasn't just beef.
It's from my heart.
For me, that's what beef means.
If I gave her beef,
it means I gave her all my heart.
Mr. Yang.
Are you crying?
I'm just frustrated. I'm so upset.
Stop crying.
Will you stop crying?
What's the big deal about her?
Why are you being so pathetic
because of her? It's upsetting.
Are you a fool?
Are you a moron?
Why would you cry
because of a woman...
who doesn't even care about you?
With a woman who has a huge
crush on you sitting right here.
What do you mean?
Just think about it.
What would that mean?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Well... Ma'am.
What should I do first?
Do I have to tell you
what to do every time?
Just try to be more tactful.
Okay. Be tactful.
All right.
What should I do?
Ga Hee, I just organized them.
I just thought it'd be better
to arrange them by color.
I'm quite picky about colors,
so I tend to move to colors I like
when I shop for clothes.
- I think, this way...
- Ga Hee.
Are you saying I just arranged them
randomly without thought?
Pardon? Gosh, no.
That's not what I meant.
Customers prefer products
arranged by styles.
I appreciate your positive attitude,
but you should ask things
you don't know.
It's not like
organizing your closet.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'll make sure to ask.
We're not having customers yet.
Just go straighten up the warehouse.
Carrying-overs inside
and new products outside.
Yes, ma'am.
Darn it.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
She is such a wench.
She's even younger than me.
"Just go straighten up
the warehouse"?
She could've asked me
to work on it.
This isn't feeling good.
I guess I will explode
with rage pretty soon.
No.
I took the plunge
and started this job.
I should hold myself back
thinking about Ji Hun.
All right. I've had it too easy
the whole time.
I need to keep
my temper in check.
I'm so sleepy sitting in here.
I should go get some fresh air.
There's Mr. Yang.
I guess he's coming
to our restaurant.
I knew it.
I thought I haven't seen him...
- for the past few days.
- Hello...
He's leaving.
Where is he going?
You're right. Where is he going now?
I don't know. What's going on?
How adorable.
You're so sweet and lovely.
I guess she takes after her mom.
I think so.
I don't think
she takes after her dad.
She has well-defined features.
You're so pretty.
It's not that Joon Seon is
not good-looking.
I know. He's not bad-looking.
It's not like
he's good-looking though.
So?
Did your first daughter
go to work today?
Sure.
As soon as she made up
her mind, she got a job.
She used to work.
Hey, you guys are here.
You're here.
My husband just went to the office.
You missed each other on the way.
No. I just stopped by
to give this to you.
It's good for beef tartare.
My gosh.
It's for beef tartare.
You're so lucky
to get stuff like this.
Gosh, you don't have to do this.
Ok Ja.
It's for beef tartare,
your favorite dish.
Oh, really?
I didn't know
Ok Ja likes beef tartare.
Gosh, my eye.
Ms. Song, are you in the library?
I got off work early today.
Yes, I'm in the library.
See you soon.
I should be there soon.
Hey, Jae Seok.
Gosh. Jae Seok!
What?
Where is he going in such haste?
Is it that he is...
I'm sure that's it.
He seems carried away. I'm sure
he's going to meet his girlfriend.
I got you.
Where did he go?
What?
A library?
He said his girlfriend is a student.
Are they meeting here?
- Mr. Yoon.
- Ms. Song.
Where did he go?
- You're here.
- Yes.
Are you going to the restroom?
No. I'm feeling sleepy,
so I need some coffee.
It's Da Hee.
Da Hee.
Jae Seok.
Mom.
I'm on my way. I just got off work.
You just came without calling me.
Why did you...
Excuse me.
Well...
You go on in. There must be
a lot of restaurants there.
Okay.
A seafood soup restaurant?
Sounds good.
You go on in.
I'll be there in five minutes.
I knew he was terrible
from the start.
That dragon tattoo on his arm...
No.
Oh, my gosh.
Why won't you pick up?
(Yoon Gyu Jin)
Nurse, are we done for the day?
Who are you?
Who are you? Why are you here?
You don't get it.
This is what I'll put on the form.
"Conclusion. Child abuse
at the hand of the birth father."
You're out of your mind.
You recognize me.
But then, you ruined my life
and I'd be disappointed...
if you didn't remember me.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
What do I want? Here's what I want.
I did time because of you,
and since then,
my wife and kid moved.
Where did they go?
You must know
if they kept coming here.
I don't know.
They haven't been here recently.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Do you have a death wish?
Darn you! Tell me.
Tell me if you want to live!
I don't know. I really don't.
- Doctor, you can go home...
- Darn.
Darn you!
Be quiet! What?
What? What?
If you want to save her,
bring my wife and kid!
Now!
Sir. Calm down first.
I'm no sir.
Hey. You go.
Get my wife and daughter!
- We can't share information...
- Be quiet!
My gosh.
Don't just stand there. Go!
- Gyu Jin, what's going...
- Go!
- Get them now.
- Sir.
Get them!
Do it!
- Get my wife and daughter!
- Na Hee!
Who are you?
What do you want, you fool?
Are you okay?
(Once Again)
Ga Hee, you're still
hanging up the clothes?
I'm coming.
Isn't that Ga Hee?
This is what Song Ga Hee does now?
You're so sweet sometimes.
Not just sometimes.
It doesn't feel real. I'm trembling.
Right now?
Darn it.
Shoot.
Are you sure it didn't hit a nerve?
It's not your fault.
I didn't move fast enough.
I want you to be happy, Na Hee.
That's why you went through
the tough breakup.
You help out at an orphanage?
2 or 3 times a year? We go as well.
That song you always sing.
- Sing, sing.