RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 16
Did you gather the test subjects?
Or was Choi Geun-cheol behind that?
Han Tae-woong.
I thought only Kang Gi-beom
was the crazy bastard.
No wonder he locked you up as well.
Just answer my question.
Who's responsible? You or Choi Geun-cheol?
Have you heard of competitive bidding?
The people's safety is at stake.
I ought to do my due diligence
to choose the best investment
for the country.
Surely, you'd understand
why I had to test it out.
You guys are much more capable,
but managing Rugal...
At least, Hwang Deuk-gu's products
don't bite the hands that feed them.
-"Products"?
-Han Tae-woong.
Do you think you're human?
You have a huge ego for a test subject.
Choi Geun-cheol didn't teach you properly.
He decided to dump you all for a reason.
You're telling me Choi Geun-cheol
and Hwang Deuk-gu are connected, right?
And it was Choi Geun-cheol's decision
to put those test subjects, right?
A bastard like you
shouldn't be a cop.
Were you the one
who sent those test subjects?
I had to allow it
in order to protect Rugal.
Right.
You're willing to do anything
when it comes to Rugal.
So
is that why you killed Gi-beom's wife,
gouged out his eyes,
and even killed my sister?
Was it all
part of your plan?
"No matter what happens,
one will not hold Rugal responsible."
Did you forget that?
Answer me!
That was a big job.
She had it coming.
Why did she rat us out to the police?
Let's go.
A member of Argos was betrayed
by other members of Argos.
BACKGROUND CHECK RESULT
I needed an element of surprise
from the fallout.
Right after they cut my arm,
you showed up to save me
at the perfect timing.
Because I needed you!
Have you already forgotten
what you had done
and who you used to be?
Just because I buried your past,
it doesn't mean you should forget it.
You probably know they run crazy
experiments here on people they kidnap.
So how does it feel
to be kidnapped yourself?
Their screaming almost drove me insane.
Don't sound so indifferent.
You could have been one of the victims.
Why don't you wait
over there in place of me?
That might be the best way
to get rid of Hwang Deuk-gu.
Do you think getting rid of him
would solve all the problems?
-Wouldn't it?
-Don't you want to weed out
the root, turn it upside down,
and turn over a new leaf?
Are you telling me
to leave Argos?
That's how you got yourself in this mess.
Look at you. Hwang Deuk-gu kidnapped you.
Gwang-cheol.
What's the matter with you?
Leave now.
Dr. Oh!
Mi-na.
I'm so glad you're okay.
You guys risk your lives for Rugal.
And I did the same.
Dr. Oh, Hwang Deuk-gu
kidnapped Gwang-cheol.
He must be somewhere in there.
I'm sure Gi-beom will find him.
Mi-na!
Gi-beom.
Gwang-cheol.
Mi-na.
Mi-na is in trouble. We need help.
Dr. Oh?
What did they do to you?
It can be turned on and off remotely.
There's a pressure sensor,
which means
he was able to control the voltage.
By pressing this spot right here
like this.
Wake up, Gwang-cheol!
Gwang-cheol, are you okay?
Gi-beom.
Get up.
Hey, are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I don't feel like myself.
I adjusted the voltage. You'll be fine.
We'll have Dr. Oh treat you.
Did you find Dr. Oh?
Yes.
Darn it.
Mi-na!
Mi-na...
I'll continue to be on the lookout.
Then, I'll trust you guys
and get some sleep.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
You're so good at it.
With you?
Take my word and trust me.
My body won't last long.
Dr. Oh can take care of you.
Quit talking nonsense.
I was always anxious.
I was always insecure
because I'm not special like you guys.
I was always lonely because I thought
no one approved of me.
So you know that you are not special.
Just focus on getting recovered
and living a diligent life.
Hwang Deuk-gu could see through me.
I didn't have
a presence in Rugal, either.
Why would you listen to that thug?
Despite that,
I managed to beat you, land
a few punches, and fling you down.
I scored a big one before I die
although dying sucks.
If you keep saying you're dying,
I'll really end you.
Keep up.
Are you okay?
Hang in there.
Are you okay, Tae-woong?
I can perform emergency treatments
for the time being,
but to properly treat them,
we must go to the HQ.
I want you to go to a safe place now.
Once we finish here, we'll come to you.
We have unfinished business here.
Call Susan and Bradley for me.
I'll try my best to keep them alive.
Yes, sir.
Be careful.
By the way, are you really okay?
What happened?
It was just as you expected.
You and I became part of Rugal
just like Choi Geun-cheol planned.
What will you do now?
I will
kick him out of Rugal.
I'll go take care of Hwang Deuk-gu first.
Dr. Oh took Mi-na and Gwang-cheol.
-You should go help him.
-I will. I'm getting my stuff now.
By the way, I think Gwang-cheol got
the same shot their test subjects got.
He got really strong all of a sudden.
That might be a similar drug
we used on Ko Yong-deok.
Once we dilute the drug, he'll be okay.
Okay. Take good care of him.
But Susan hasn't come back
when she left to meet with the chief.
-Should I get going first?
-Yes, hurry.
Okay.
I just left the building.
-Hold on.
-What is it?
Seol Min-jun...
His dead body is abandoned
in front of the HQ.
What?
I'm on my way to destroy the crazy bastard
responsible for that.
Gi-beom.
I really want you to kill that scumbag.
Don't worry. I'll put an end
to this today no matter what.
Guess what they are.
When Ko Yong-deok failed to open
Bong Man-cheol's vault
with his iris,
his eyeballs burned down.
The key to the ledger
of the political slush fund
Ko Yong-deok left behind is gone.
How does that feel?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
In life,
some are destined to work like a dog,
and some, to enjoy the luxury.
I would like to check something.
What are you doing?
If Ko Yong-deok couldn't open it,
you must be able to, then.
If you were dying to check it,
you should have killed me in the lab.
That was my plan, but you managed to
get Kang Gi-beom here before I knew it.
Did you let him go
because you were scared?
I prepared a grand event just for him.
As for you...
Wait here.
You will be the last.
UNKNOWN CALLER
ACCEPT, DECLINE
Did you have a nice funeral
for your dead wife?
Did you come to my turf
after sending her off?
Was it to see Choi Ye-won or me?
Why were you hiding like a rat?
What are you scared of?
Isn't it nice to keep the suspense going?
Shall we meet now?
You're finally asking to meet.
I guess your time has come to an end now.
I feel bad that
people from your side keep dying.
Fine. I ought to pick out
a burial site for you.
Where should I bury you?
It looked like you already have
a lot of bodies to bury.
I don't want to add onto that.
Where are you, you asshole?
I snatched up a new lab.
Try to keep up. You're good at that.
Locate Hwang Deuk-gu.
Don't go to the HQ
until I give you a green light.
Mi-na. Gwang-cheol.
Focus on your treatment.
Everyone, get some rest.
I'll put an end to this.
What were you going to do
after abandoning Gi-beom and me?
I
devoted my life to bringing down Argos
and forming Rugal.
I should get rid of any obstacles
that may get in my way.
"Obstacles."
Gi-beom went berserk
and I ended up where I am now
because of what you did to us
in order to fulfill your goal.
I'm going to continue making
human weapons after you all.
I will make tons of them if I need to.
I don't think so.
No one is here.
It's a shame to waste all that money
and people's lives just to bring me down.
Answer me!
The toy you created, Rugal.
They were pretty useful to me, too.
Don't you dare run your mouth.
Why not?
I know a bit about how it all began.
If I knew you'd be a monster,
I should have stopped you, then.
You still think you call the shots.
Kang Gi-beom's gun which used to point
at me is pointing at you now.
And you brought it upon yourself.
You just worry about yourself.
I'll handle him.
Like you didn't know what I'd do,
you don't know Kang Gi-beom.
I wish Choi Geun-cheol was here
to see this with me.
We should have a showdown.
Rugal
versus Rugal.
Shut the fuck up. You can blabber away
all you want when you go to hell.
You're such a weakling.
I'm disappointed.
Good.
That's the Han Tae-woong I know.
Dr. Oh.
I'm so glad you're alive.
I'm glad to see you guys again.
Why can't we go to the HQ?
-Where's Tae-woong?
-Well...
Tae-woong went to speak with Chief Choi.
Why?
What's going on?
Ask Tae-woong directly later.
Gi-beom probably met
with Hwang Deuk-gu by now, right?
I should go.
Please...
If you die here,
I'll give you a proper burial.
And I'll take your eyes to the burial,
so that you can see it yourself.
You...
Thanks to you,
I had fun.
Kang...
Gi-beom.
-What the hell?
-Hands up.
-Hey, go.
-What's going on?
-Get them!
-What the fuck?
-They're not here!
-Fuck off!
-Damn it!
-Get them!
-Freeze!
-Don't move.
-You bastards!
-What the hell is going on?
-Let go.
-What the fuck!
-Let go!
-What do you think you're doing?
-I said, let go!
-Don't push me!
-Let go!
-Hey!
-Are you all right?
-Help!
-Stay with us.
-Gosh...
119 RESCUE SERVICE
I can't even ask you to forgive me.
I started it to save you and Yeo-jin.
No.
Regardless of the reason,
I should've never done that.
As your friend,
I should not have done such a thing.
And I feel terrible
for what happened to Yeo-jin.
I hope where I punched you
isn't still sore.
I deserve to get beaten up.
You had no choice.
I understand now.
So just forget everything.
Stop wallowing in guilt
and move on with your life.
I'm sure that's what Yeo-jin wants too.
Take care of Hwang Deuk-gu though.
I'll see you around.
Detective Yang.
It's all over now, for real.
But I must say,
it doesn't feel that great.
I feel the same way.
I'm relieved.
But at the same time,
I feel like it's still not over.
I guess
that feeling will stay with us
for as long as we're alive.
Tae-woong.
What are we going to do now, by the way?
We'll think about it
once everyone recovers.
Will the world accept us back?
In order to go back out in the world
without feeling ashamed,
I should turn myself in.
I need
that time.
The extent of the evil deeds
committed by Argos behind the facade
of it being a legal corporation
was finally revealed today.
Argos had always denied
all the allegations
that it might have been the culprit
behind various cold cases.
But now that Vice Chairman Hwang Deuk-gu
has been arrested,
conducting human experiments
and reaping illegal profits
off the victims
will all be brought to justice.
The drug seeped
into your artificial organs,
so we have to flush them out
for a few days.
It will be painful,
but you can handle it, right?
Yes, I'll get through it.
Good.
Gosh, how did you hold out?
You must not move for the next few weeks.
If you do, the wounds will open up.
Okay.
Susan and Chief Choi
passed away.
RESTRICTED AREA
We will follow the police funeral customs
for Susan and Chief Choi.
I wonder who killed Susan.
Talk about odd timing.
A lot of the files related to Rugal
are gone.
Bradley is trying to track down
who did it.
They were probably planning
to start something new.
But someone figured it out
and stole the files.
Who'd be interested
in something like that?
Let's just hope
they won't be put to bad use.
It's not like I wasn't mentally prepared,
but I still feel betrayed and dejected.
And even Susan...
Now that I'm actually faced with it,
it is hard to endure.
RECENT CALLS
MADAME JANG
Ko Yong-deok...
Do you know who killed him?
DELETE THIS NUMBER?
DELETE
BONG MAN-CHEOL
You--
DELETE THIS NUMBER?
DELETE
Please...
CHOI YONG
DELETE
HWANG DEUK-GU
One.
Two.
DELETE THIS NUMBER?
DELETE
It'll take a while,
but I will pay you well
for getting rid of Hwang Deuk-gu
as I promised.
That's not necessary.
Choi Ye-won.
Personally, I don't hold
any hard feelings against you.
But as long as
you're the chairwoman of Argos,
you'll have to bear the weight
of responsibility that comes with it.
I will.
Argos without Hwang Deuk-gu
will be very different.
To do that,
you'll need this.
Why didn't you kill him?
By any chance,
is it because you feel guilty about
what you did to Chairman Ko?
Choi Ye-won, you're so funny.
"Guilty"?
Me?
You're the one who killed him.
At the reservoir. Don't you remember?
One, two...
Bang!
He's totally out of it.
Are you okay?
Wake up.
Who knows?
Thanks to Ko Yong-deok's rotten corpse,
you might be able to catch
a gigantic fish.
Ms. Choi Ye-won? You're under arrest
for the murder of Ko Yong-deok.
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
What the hell are you doing?
You need to pay
for the crimes you've committed.
You can turn over a new leaf later on.
Do you actually think
you can get me locked up?
Absolutely not.
All your higher-ups
are under my thumb.
-Take her.
-Yes, sir.
Fine.
I'll cooperate,
so don't you dare lay a finger on me.
I guess this is it.
Take care.
Mr. Lee Gwang-cheol?
We have to ask you a few questions.
Can you tell us what Rugal used to do
in detail?
Are Rugal and Argos Hunters
the same organization?
There's something
you should take care of first.
When I was taken to the lab, I heard that
the test subjects and the victims
whose chips got swapped
might experience side effects
even after the chips are removed.
That's dangerous.
I think that's more of a pressing issue
than your interest in Argos Hunters.
Right. Thank you.
My gosh, Rugal saved all these people?
You're realizing that just now?
These people should all get tested, right?
Did you not hear about the side effects?
They'll turn into monsters.
-Call all of them.
-Yes, sir.
All right. I guess we should go
our own separate ways now.
It's really over now.
You're the one who said
that we exist to vanish.
This day has finally come.
Frankly, I didn't think it'd ever come.
The government doesn't acknowledge us,
so we can't really hide.
But being together
will be even more uncomfortable.
-Did you all decide what to do?
-I feel daunted.
I was much happier
when I had regular paychecks.
I'm too old to be jobless.
Gosh, I don't even know
why you guys are worried.
You're strong, and you're nimble.
Well, you're a tricky one.
But you can just go work part-time
at a convenience store. You're young.
Be adventurous.
If an adventurous spirit
is all you need to live,
who'd be worried?
Gosh, I'm cut out for this job.
I knew you'd say that,
so I prepared gifts for you guys.
Don't be too touched.
This is for you, Tae-woong.
And this is yours, Mi-na.
Thanks.
Where's mine?
What about me?
You're the youngest one.
I want a gift too!
I got you one, of course.
It's the thing you always wanted.
Oh, nice.
It's gold.
My, this is so cool.
-Happy now?
-I am happy indeed.
I want to take some photos.
Hey, do you work here?
-You opened your eyes.
-Do you know me?
We're on the same team.
Please get out of my way.
You'll regret this.
Do you think
everything he told you is true?
The police officially confirmed
how Kang Gi-beom was framed by Argos
to be a ruthless killer
who took the life of his own wife.
They apologized for the traumatic shock
Mr. Kang had to suffer from.
A retrial of his case
will clear him of all allegations
and the case
will be reopened to investigate
and capture the true murderer.
KANG GI-BEOM, FALSELY CHARGED
I'll go this way.
Then I'll go that way.
We sure are different, aren't we?
Brother.
I just
wanted to call you that.
Well, your brother is all ears
if you have any requests.
I have nothing to ask.
All I want to say is that I'm grateful.
I was happy being on the team.
Me too.
And I mean that.
I'll get going then.
Jeez. I almost mistook you for a threat.
Why are you following me?
I'm not.
We're just going the same way.
And which way is that?
-Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
So Bradley the Quack,
what will you do for a living now?
Beats me.
This quack still has skills though,
so I'm more worried
about how you'll make a living.
You're worrying about me?
I can't help it.
It seems like you're asking me
to take you in or something.
-Really?
-Yes.
Like I said,
I'm not interested in men that way.
You'll be helping me
put these eyes to better use.
What do you say?
I guess that sounds nice.
But just so you know, I don't come cheap.
I didn't even tell you the details,
but you're already
talking about your paycheck?
Since you're the one with the skills,
you should be bringing in the bread then.
I already knew it,
but you truly are a con-artist.
A con-artist?
You think you're a smart ass, don't you?
Anyway, dig in.
Go on.
A FEW YEARS LATER
R DELIVERIES
Unbelievable.
How could you walk all the way here
when I was waiting for you
at the detention center?
Did you wait a long while?
It's nothing compared
to the years I had to wait.
Who knew that your service at Rugal
would put you up for early parole?
Tell me about it.
I guess we were really famous.
Is that so?
It's been a while since we talked,
so tell me all about it.
Is that your ride?
I bought one. Sweet, isn't it?
Let's ride.
Are you sure it works?
It may not seem like it, but it's new.
What are your thoughts on forming
another black ops program like Rugal?
Black ops programs are dangerous
by just existing.
And agents with artificial body parts--
We have other crimes surging
in our metropolitan areas.
It'll decrease the pressure
on our police officers...
Thank you, Mr. Han!
I told you to call me Tae-woong.
Oh, right.
Got it, Mr. Tae-woong.
I mean, Tae-woong.
-Let's get back to work.
-Sure.
Are you taking selfies, boss?
Tae-woong,
how are we supposed to manage
when we keep hiring
ex-Argos members to help them
on a limited revenue?
Should we ignore them, then?
They're trying to
straighten out their lives,
so of course we should help.
Then at least cut back on food expenses.
Do you even know how much they eat?
It's like I'm feeding elephants.
I'll work extra shifts then.
You just have to make me
look like the bad guy, right?
We're done for the day,
so let's grab a beer.
Deal.
Cheers.
I remember
how we used to play pool
as well as the fun I had with you all.
-Rock-paper-scissors.
You need more than
just your strength to play pool. You know?
When will that stop?
Nice!
We had our fair share
of pain and heartache too.
I know.
Does being the muscle
ever get old for you?
I have to keep at it
or the arm will get rusty.
And that includes getting
the bad guys from time to time?
That's right.
That's what you've been doing too.
I miss Gi-beom and Mi-na.
They don't answer my emails
and they haven't been in touch.
I wonder what they're up to.
I'll be back
when I finally am brave enough
to forgive you.
Thank you, Chief.
There are a few conditions
that promise the perfect brew.
The temperature of the water
and the amount of coffee
can all affect
how your brewed coffee tastes.
Like I mentioned in my earlier class,
you shouldn't
pour water on one spot
which is what some of you did.
Pouring in your water
in a slow spiral motion
is what makes
the coffee taste good
up until the third brew.
Please watch the steps.
That was nice.
I'll see you all next week.
Thanks. Have a good day.
Hold on.
Why were you back there?
You fucker.
Fucker?
That's rich coming from a druggie.
You shithead.
What the hell? He died?
It seemed like
you wanted to kill him, so...
Are you kidding me?
Get rid of it.
I didn't think
it'd knock him out cold though.
What a wimp.
Hey, you.
Here.
What's that?
You don't know?
Then I'll just throw it away.
Do you have any idea
how expensive this is?
Let go...
So you're the dealer.
Bastard.
Not again.
Why are the kids these days
all a bunch of wimps?
Jeez.
Sons of bitches.
How high up the food chain does this go?
RECENT DESTINATION
HEAD OF PRIVATE SECURITY KANG GI-BEOM
SINCHEONG SHOPPING MALL
SPECIAL ROBBERY CASE
Mr. K, my sister hasn't
been in touch for days.
Please find her.
Drug deals at Yuyeon Intersection.
I'm worried that the kids might see it.
Please punish them.
May I report school bullying?
My parents argue whenever they drink.
-What should I do?
-I think my boyfriend
is cheating on me.
Talk about a truck load of work.
Gi-beom, I hope you're well.
Gi-beom, I miss you. I really do!
Get in touch with me.
It's been a while, Gi-beom.
Have you been well?
New message.
Located former the goons of Argos.
Street on Dongeun-dong, Yangjeon-gu.
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son
THANK YOU WATCHING RUGAL