RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Did you change your mind?
Mi-na, what's wrong?
Mi-na?
Mi-na!
Damn that punch of yours.
Why didn't you dodge it?
I need to
erase Yeo-jin from my memories.
What do you mean?
If I do,
I may be able to forgive the chief.
I never said you should.
If I don't,
I won't be able to move on.
Rugal
can go on without me...
No, never without you.
Come back home with me.
I'm sorry.
This was
the only way.
Gi-beom?
Gi-beom!
EPISODE 15
-What if he doesn't wake up?
-He has to.
The shutdown was nothing.
He could've died.
I can't believe he pulled it out.
He can't even walk or move without this.
-Right, I have to put in a new one.
-Any side effects?
It could cause memory loss,
and his body might reject the new chip.
It sounds like everything is risky.
-Gwang-cheol, can you move Mi-na?
-Sure.
-Susan, let's get ready for the surgery.
-Okay.
Are you sure this is your first experiment
of this kind?
This is a type of stimulant.
It stimulates the body to instantly
produce a great deal of energy.
-It can even make paraplegics jump.
-Hwang Deuk-gu!
You asked for a pain reliever, so
I gave you a dozen-fold dilution of this.
But most people would be wiped out
for days even with such a minute amount.
Well, people tell me that I'm strong.
How did you come to have
such a high tolerance?
Tolerance...
How come Dal-ho is nowhere to be seen?
He's dead.
What?
Who whacked him?
CHOI YE-WON
Did you kill Dal-ho?
He's dead too?
Oh, no. This breaks my heart.
-Did you kill him?
-We'll all die one day, you know.
There are some who deserve
to die sooner than later, like yourself.
-Put Choi Ye-won on the phone.
-She's still alive.
I'm sorry though.
She said she wanted your head
for her birthday,
and I just couldn't say no.
I should be there
to wish her a happy birthday.
Good. Come join us
if you think you can handle it.
You know where my villa is.
Get the car ready.
You know, I trusted you.
But I guess
you didn't trust me.
Ye-won.
Let me explain.
It's not like I wanted to do it.
He harshly threatened me.
I understand.
Some people even sell their children
when pressed and cornered.
We don't share a single drop of blood
after all.
I must've been out of my mind.
I mean, to you of all people...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Ye-won.
Ye-won!
Let go of me. Let go!
Ye-won.
Ye-won!
You said you just wanted to see her.
Who knew you'd actually shoot her?
You deceived me?
Ko Yong-deok...
Do you know who killed him?
Why listen to her bullshit?
Are you ready to catch Hwang Deuk-gu?
What makes you so sure
that he will come for you?
Just make sure you finish him
once and for all when he does come.
What's going on?
Gi-beom came by again last night.
I think he and Tae-woong had a big fight.
-And?
-Tae-woong is okay,
but Gi-beom pulled the chip
out of the back of his neck.
Tae-woong said
Gi-beom stirred him up to do just that,
saying he wants to erase everything.
Problems with the chip
affect Mi-na as well.
Yes, they received treatment together.
My head feels like it's going to explode.
What will happen to Gi-beom?
A new chip means he'll forget it all?
The memories that are closest to the point
in time when the chip got damaged
will be hardest to restore.
And his artificial eyes
have been initialized,
so his visual memories
have been wiped out too.
"Wiped out"? Until when?
That I don't know.
Isn't this too cruel?
Remaining a member of Rugal
without any memories or emotions.
It is.
But people on the Internet
are looking for Rugal at the moment.
We have our own lives too.
Or should we not? Like robots?
If we aren't seen for a while,
they'll think Argos killed us.
Whatever, I don't care.
Forget Rugal.
I want to forget everything for a while.
Kang Gi-beom.
"Kang Gi-beom"?
That's your name.
Who are you?
Han Tae-woong.
Han Tae-woong?
HAN TAE-WOONG
-I don't remember anything.
-Your memories will come back.
I'll help you with that.
You got a new chip, so your eyes
might experience some side effects.
You need to recover quickly
so that you can do what you're good at.
What am I good at?
Catching the bad guys.
It was your specialty.
Then why am I in this mess?
Who attacked me?
No one.
As if you'd let that happen.
The harder the task was,
the more you excelled at it.
Then what about you?
Me?
I feel like I've done a lot of things.
Gi-beom!
But I don't think
I excelled at any of them.
Well, I don't think that's true.
-How do you know?
-I can just tell.
Are you all right?
He can already move around,
so I don't think we need to worry.
-What about his memory?
-Who is he?
Chief Choi Geun-cheol.
CHOI GEUN-CHEOL
I'll show him around
to help him retrieve his memories.
All right.
How come Madame Jang isn't here?
She'd never miss an occasion like this.
I guess she caused trouble and got busted.
That woman, Madame Jang.
I know I called you wishy-washy.
I take it back.
Where did it all go?
Beg me to spare your life.
Spare...
Spare my life.
Louder!
Please spare...
Spare...
I'd like to put all of Rugal's activities
on pause for the time being.
-Is there a problem?
-No just for maintenance purposes.
You can't keep Kang Gi-beom under control?
I mean, he's the one
who got Hwang Deuk-gu out.
Some are saying that Argos Hunters
are actually instigating crimes.
If he's a self-destructive weapon,
there are many ways to tame him.
Han Tae-woong and Kang Gi-beom.
Why don't we just lose them
if they can't erase their pasts?
If we get rid of them,
Rugal can officially become a department
within the National Police Agency.
And if you make an appearance
at a few national events,
all the criticism will be gone in no time.
Are you all right?
I just fainted. That's all.
Don't give me that. I saw you in pain.
I'm really okay now.
Did you say
Tae-woong stepped out with Gi-beom?
Yes.
He said he felt cooped up.
But if he woke up...
I would've known, but I felt nothing.
Maybe it's because the chip was switched.
It's a good thing then. I'm relieved.
Is it really a good thing?
That much pain I could easily endure.
Over my dead body.
The police are here.
-What?
-How?
It's like someone let them in.
Where's Han Tae-woong?
A douche with no manners, I see.
You can't just barge in here unannounced.
POLICE
-Lee Gwang-cheol?
-So?
And you're Song Mi-na.
You know who we are,
so I guess there's no reason to play nice.
We're not here for you two,
so just tell us where Han Tae-woong is.
I'm right here.
Being a cop doesn't give you a free pass.
Where's your warrant?
Explain yourselves.
I authorized it.
Chief?
Why?
As of this moment,
Rugal will be closed indefinitely.
What is he saying?
You're closing us down?
Why? What did we do wrong?
That's not the reason.
Then why are you already
waving the white flag?
-Chief?
-Will the two of us being arrested
-solve the issue?
-I must be arrested too?
The rest will be commended
and compensated for your service.
As if we'd want that.
I won't let anyone take them.
How does any of this make sense?
Chief!
Guys, we knew this was one of
the scenarios that could play out.
I was never informed of this.
Trust me and the chief
and let them take us.
Why would I agree
to an obvious trip to prison?
Besides,
do you trust him that much?
We should trust him blindly?
Even though we could rot in prison?
Thanks to that,
obstruction of justice charges were added.
So what'll it be?
Take care of the chief.
We won't wait long.
So we should trust
how the chief said he'd get them out?
It's impossible. Once they're booked...
I hate seeing them behind bars,
but Rugal closing
without a fight is worse.
Also, Gi-beom isn't even
in perfect health.
He needs to be treated first.
Let's wait for the chief's orders.
When has waiting worked out for us?
We need to take action right now.
Tae-woong and I had a hard time
getting Gi-beom out the first time.
That's only because
you had to fake his death in the process.
It'll be way easier this time.
What? Why?
Gwang-cheol.
You too?
What? Why? What's going on?
You said it'd be way easier.
Yes, compared to back then,
it'd be way easier.
It'll be even easier
since they'll only be in a holding cell.
So get working on a plan.
What the hell are you talking about?
Unbelievable.
Are you both insane?
That's right. You've both gone mad.
I won't do this.
Such insanity. Count me out.
How is it that you have
zero doubts about this chief?
You were about to take them all out,
so why did you change your mind?
What good would taking on the police do
when the real enemy is still out there?
Have your memories come back?
No, it's just a feeling I have.
We're under special care.
-What does that mean?
-Some may view us as threats.
We're better off being scrapped
when unmanageable.
What about the others?
The police will use them as mascots.
Are you saying this was foreseen?
I'm sure the chief has a contingency plan.
So they'll be on the third floor
of the annex building?
Yes, it's where
the temporary holding cells are.
The place dubbed as the torture chamber?
Isn't that where you worked?
What do you remember about the security?
Perps who are a higher flight risk
are placed there.
Can't we subdue the guards
while Tae-woong busts his way out?
There's no need to make a commotion.
-I can open the doors for you.
-How?
Just take me to the building
and I'll do the rest.
This seems like a big task
for just the three of us.
It'll be easier
if we had help from the inside.
We know who can help.
Let's go then.
What the hell?
What's wrong with these guys?
Tae-woong.
Your memories are back.
Yes.
Tae-woong, are you okay?
-Gwang-cheol.
-Yes.
This is crazy.
Where should I shoot first?
Your brain isn't a robot too, is it?
Goodbye,
Kang Gi-beom.
The devil behind all this.
Then why did you never tell me
that she was alive?
If everything went as planned,
we wouldn't be having this conversation.
Why didn't you tell me?
The past doesn't matter.
You're a part of Rugal now.
Don't forget your duties.
All that you have believed in
will start to crumble.
The one I need to take my revenge on
is you,
Choi Geun-cheol.
And the one who concealed it.
Only one would send these men after us.
But how did he know we were here?
Choi Geun-cheol and Hwang Deuk-gu.
We'll beat the answers out of them.
We'll begin right away.
Bradley, I said you didn't have to hide.
Is this really necessary?
Hey, unlike you, I need extra precautions.
You just never take risks, do you?
He's gone.
-Is he?
-Yes.
It was getting stuffy back there.
-Let's begin.
-Sure.
Would Detective Yang be all right?
I heard he was reprimanded.
He's somewhat part of Rugal anyway,
so who can he complain to?
It seems as though
you're talking about me in a way.
I wonder why you think so.
Just do your job, okay?
I'm Bradley, aren't I? I never mess up.
All right, then.
Let's get the guys out.
Has Rugal really been dismantled?
Does it make me a bastard
for being relieved
of Gi-beom's memory loss?
It's only temporary.
His memories will come back to him.
Of course...
and they should.
I'm sure you heard
about Yeo-jin.
Yes.
He'll never forgive me now.
Mun-bok,
are you willing to do anything
to help Gi-beom?
Chief Choi should've told me
about what he did to me
when I escaped the hospital,
or at least when I had recovered
from my surgery.
The same goes for
how Yeo-jin was still alive.
I was only used to serve his purpose.
Your story
might be just that as well.
Did you actually see
who killed your sister?
I know it's hard to believe,
but something went down that day.
Revenge is what brought me this far too,
but you heard him.
We could've been used in the same way.
ARE YOU READY FOR YOUR SECOND ESCAPE?
I'm being asked if we're ready to escape.
By the chief?
IT'S ME, BRADLEY
No, by Bradley.
I'M HERE WITH THE MEMBERS OF RUGAL
Mi-na and Gwang-cheol are here too.
Things are going to get fun.
CAN'T PROVIDE AUDIO
SO FOLLOW THE ESCAPE ROUTE
Shall we? I'll guide the way.
What the hell?
Nice. Good job.
The doors will keep opening,
so don't make any pit stops.
Oh, dear.
-Can't open the door?
-It's not that,
but they can take a detour.
Gi-beom.
Gwang-cheol, they're coming out the back.
Not the front?
No, so move.
Got it.
-Don't tell me that--
-I'm getting Gi-beom out of here.
-What?
-This is your chance.
Over there. Get them!
-There!
-Get them!
Let's go.
Move!
Open these doors.
-Let us out.
-Move!
Where are Han Tae-woong and Kang Gi-beom?
Where did you hide them, damn it?
What are you talking about?
It wasn't just me.
You wanted them arrested too!
Han Tae-woong was to be tamed
and Kang Gi-beom punished!
If this is such a pressing matter,
issue an APB out on them.
What's going on?
Was it just the three of you?
Yes.
Do you still not see
who threw us to the wolves?
I want to ask the chief face to face.
Me too.
Then do so. I'll look for Dr. Oh.
I'll come with you.
I have another request
for you and Bradley.
Me too?
Tae-woong and I are fugitives
from here on out.
I won't be able to hide if Choi Geun-cheol
brings Rugal back on line
which is why I need you to keep me hidden.
You want us back in the lion's den?
How's the chip?
Do you need any medical assistance?
No, not yet.
Do you have Gi-beom's phone?
Yes.
You'll need it.
This is where we separate.
I'll be in touch.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
Got it.
Give me your phone.
I can't do that, ma'am.
It's for an important business deal.
Do you want to be accountable
for tens of billions of won?
Tell me who it is and I'll make the call.
Do you think they will take your call?
It's still a no, ma'am.
Then I'll send out a text.
That much is all right.
It'll leave a trace,
so you won't be in trouble.
You must stick to texting.
It's urgent,
so I'm ordering a case by case.
MESSAGES
IT'S URGENT,
SO I'M ORDERING A CASE BY CASE
Hello?
You there. Can't you hear me?
What the hell?
I'm planning to kill them
even if you tell me not to.
So how dare you use my private
military company for their lives?
I'm hanging up.
There are so many photos.
When I almost died because of Gi-beom,
Mi-na told me
that I am the target after you.
That's when I thought you had died.
I wondered, "Who'd take care
of their families from now on?
What will happen if I die as well?"
So many thoughts crossed my mind.
But the most ridiculous thought
was that I was the one
who added Gi-beom to this list.
You did nothing wrong.
If anything, it's my fault.
And it's up to me to correct this.
I helped him escape.
I thought that was my way
of asking him for forgiveness.
HAN TAE-WOONG
We'll go in first.
The number you have called is unavailable.
Leave a message.
I can't reach him.
Do you think
he is really trying to abandon us?
He won't do that.
I know that he cares about Rugal
more than anyone else.
But it's true that Rugal can go on
without us.
Who can replace us?
Perhaps,
Rugal is what he wants to protect,
not us.
I've been having that thought.
It doesn't matter who the members are.
Let's not talk more about this
until we can ask him face to face.
And
there is someone I need to meet
before that.
It could be dangerous,
so I'll meet the chief alone.
-No, I'd like to--
-This is an order.
Okay.
Hey!
Come here.
Damn it.
Who the hell are you?
I'm here to see Chairwoman Choi.
Where is she?
Do you want to tell me now
or after being beaten to a pulp?
RESTRICTED AREA
Where's the key?
Dr. Oh!
Gi-beom!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I truly am.
No, don't be. I'm all right.
How did you know I'd be here?
I came because Choi Ye-won
had contacted me.
I think Hwang Deuk-gu got to her.
I'm certain
she's somewhere in this building.
I'm not sure where, though.
But I know you can find her.
Let me escort you out first.
Where's your everyone?
Why do I only meet a pawn?
How did you get in here?
I was looking for something.
You were so bold back at the holding cell.
But now, you look petrified.
I'm just disgusted
by everything you've done.
Bring it on.
Hey, did you get it?
The police shouldn't know about this.
We are the only ones who know.
I'll meet you there later.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Tell me.
How did you escape?
When we were in custody,
the guys who looked like
Hwang Deuk-gu's test subjects
attacked Gi-beom and me.
Do you know about this?
Is that why you're here?
Did you even consider
the consequences our team would suffer
due to that rashness of yours?
Please help me understand.
I want to know
what your intentions were.
Those who are a threat to Rugal
will be punished.
Are you saying that Gi-beom
and I are included?
Yes, you can speak.
Okay.
Gi-beom has found Dr. Oh.
Had he been in custody,
he wouldn't have found him.
Do you still think
we were reckless?
Where's everyone else?
I cannot
tell you.
Please wait here. Mi-na is on her way.
Don't worry about me
and look for Choi Ye-won.
Will you be okay?
Of course.
By the way, I received a new chip.
I'm not sure if it's working properly.
It feels all right, though.
May I take a look?
Yes, please.
Gwang-cheol.
BLUE CAP DELIVERY SERVICE
Pick up the phone.
-Hey.
Hwang Deuk-gu has Gwang-cheol.
-What?
-He came
to our headquarters.
We need to save him.
What? What's going on?
What's going on?
Was I too late?
Thanks for saving me.
We need to carry out our mission now.
I've been waiting.
Where is Hwang Deuk-gu?
Were you the one
who sent those test subjects?
I had to allow it
in order to protect Rugal.
Right.
You're willing to do anything
when it comes to Rugal.
So
is that why you killed Gi-beom's wife,
gouged out his eyes,
and even killed my sister?
Was it all
part of your plan?
"No matter what happens,
one will not hold Rugal responsible."
Did you forget that?
Answer me!
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
We should have a showdown.
Rugal versus Rugal.
Locate Hwang Deuk-gu.
You and I became part of Rugal
just like Choi Geun-cheol planned.
You got Kang Gi-beom here
before I knew it.
What's the matter with you?
What did they do to you?
It's a shame to waste all that money
and people's lives just to bring me down.
Wake up, Gwang-cheol!
If you die here,
I'll give you a proper burial.