(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Mackerels, octopuses...
Bring that here!
(Episode 1)
Chef Park.
Hello.
I can breathe now.
I'm serious.
I think you can read my mind better than my colleagues...
that I've been working with for four years.
You said getting your mouth ready...
with cool beer before drinking soju was the best.
Chef Park, I'm going to drink hard liquor today.
Hard liquor?
I guess you had a tough day.
Yes. Today was infuriating.
I see.
What's my side dish of the night?
Well,
there's a perfect side dish to have...
on a day when you're infuriated.
Here you go.
It's fun...
to pick at the shells.
I'll show how it's done.
It's good.
Taurine in the Manila clams...
will promote the liver function.
This is the best pairing for hard liquor.
This hits the spot.
Did you have dinner?
This is a late dinner.
(Access Pass)
Isn't this really petty?
They put names for people with permanent positions.
It only says "Access Pass" for contract workers...
instead of our names.
It's so petty.
Putting names on the card isn't that hard.
Right?
My gosh. I've been working there for years.
But no one calls me by my name.
What's your name?
It's Kim Ah Jin.
This is on the house for Director Kim Ah Jin.
Please dig in.
This is for your quiet and long career at the TV station.
Thank you.
This is so good.
Hello.
Hi, Chef Park.
You're coming here often.
I ought to, you know.
My goodness.
Soju, please.
Sure.
The glasses are in front of you.
Okay.
I wonder what he's serving tonight.
I can't wait.
Chef Park, we'll look forward to your food tonight.
Sure.
(Cup Park Apartment Complex 4)
- In other cities... - That's so cheap.
- At home... - Seriously.
- That guy is unbelievable. - I totally agree.
- Don't be ridiculous. - I'm not lying.
There aren't many restaurants.
What should I do?
- Because I live alone... - You're lying again.
- No way. - How could they do that?
Why?
Dad!
You're intruding on my territory.
Why are you here? I told you not to come.
How could I not? I have the most important job.
You're exaggerating.
No, I'm not.
It's super important to make sure food is properly seasoned.
Not everyone can do this. It's too hard.
- I thought this... - You should just...
Gosh, that's way too bland.
It needs more salt.
Since I was young...
- Dad. - Yes?
- Can you hand me a vest? - Sure.
- This is all because of you. - No, it's not.
Wait, Dad.
This is a strong young man's job.
I'm still a lot stronger than you are.
You want to show off your strength? Is that it?
What?
- You're blushing. - Come on.
Is it fun teasing your dad?
- Why did you come to my house? - Why did you come to my house?
- Are you here to look for... - Are you here to look for...
Dad.
Try them on.
Why did you buy them?
I don't want you to wear worn-out shoes.
You have neither a wife nor a girlfriend...
who buys shoes for you.
Do you?
I know a cheapskate like you would never buy a new pair of shoes.
And you always spend all your money on others.
So, what can I do? As your son, I have to buy you new shoes.
White shoes get dirty easily.
They look great on you.
Try walking in them.
Do they fit well?
Absolutely.
How did you know my size?
(The Purpose of the Program)
(Program Introduction)
("A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies")
(Characters)
Wait, what?
What's wrong?
Wait, what happened?
No! Please!
What's wrong?
Contract employees don't get computers.
Pardon?
Then what should I do?
There's a document I have to submit soon.
Actually, permanent employees recently got new computers.
You might find some used computers in storage.
Used computers?
Okay, thank you.
Dad.
I packed some food for you.
Don't skip meals.
You should eat well too.
Just because you're young, doesn't mean you don't get sick.
Dad.
Let's get a new car.
I'll pay for half of it.
Come on. Just take a look.
This car is still perfectly fine.
We bought it when Mom was alive. It's at least 20 years old.
But it still works well.
You need a nice car...
to get a girlfriend and go on dates.
There you go again.
I'm just worried.
This car is too old.
What if it breaks down on the road or something?
Hey.
Why would you worry about such a thing?
Fine, I get it.
Next time,
I'll tell you which model I want.
Are you happy now?
All right.
This is my favorite song.
Father, your son is all grown up now
I look a bit better than you did, don't I?
With my small hands, I pour you...
Both permanent employees and contract employees...
work for the broadcasting station.
Why do they have to discriminate against contract employees?
If they had bought me a new computer too,
I would have been so touched and worked even harder. Idiots.
Seriously...
Gosh, I'm so relieved.
("A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies" Proposal)
Ah Jin.
Mr. Nam wants you to bind these.
Me?
Yes.
Why can't you do it?
He specifically said that you should do it.
I'm just delivering his message.
What's that?
"Sweet Munches"?
You're submitting a proposal too?
Can't I?
Can contract employees...
submit proposals?
I thought they couldn't.
What about you?
You didn't prepare anything because you're a permanent employee?
Or...
is it because you have no ideas to propose anyway?
I mean...
"A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies"?
Goodness.
If you have time to do this, just focus on your basic duties.
We're out of coffee and green tea in the pantry.
Okay?
Here.
What are you waiting for?
A hot Americano with an extra shot.
The cup has to be washed first.
Bring the coffee to my desk.
Answer me.
Yes.
See you around.
("A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies" Proposal)
Mr. Nam wants these bound as soon as possible.
Good luck.
Gosh.
That jerk.
Well, Mr. Nam.
Hello, Ms. Kim.
I'd like to submit a proposal.
Sure, give it to me.
"Sweet Munchies".
I like the title.
- Really? - Yes.
Good job. Let's have some meat at the team dinner tomorrow.
Is there a team dinner tomorrow?
No one told you?
Oh, it must have slipped my mind.
7pm, the pork place.
The pork place.
Gosh, is it pork again?
Can we go for beef instead?
Why is the Variety Show Team so obsessed with pork?
Did you pull another all-nighter?
No. I just came.
I really like the water pressure here.
I feel a lot better now.
Here's my proposal.
By the way,
Confirm the team dinner menu with me from now on.
The director knows nothing about food.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Mr. Park.
You must've been busy. You weren't answering your phone.
Yes, I'm planning something.
(Contacts)
(In Deok)
The person you have called cannot be reached.
In Deok,
why is it so hard to get a hold of you? You don't even come by.
I'm worried,
so give me a call.
(Bumpy Road 33)
(Winter at Home)
(Special program, Happy Weekend)
(Variety Show Team 1 Minutes)
Kim Ah Jin.
Are you still here?
I just completed my manuscript.
Ah Jin.
Do you want to get a drink?
That sounds good.
Should we go to the place you're a regular at?
Not there.
Why not? It's time for them to open.
It's a place I want to keep to myself.
You're weird.
Why?
Is the chef hot?
Is he my type?
Are you worried we'll end up fighting over a man?
(Bistro)
Chef Park!
What's this? Are you closing already?
It isn't 4am yet.
I didn't have many customers today.
Gosh. I was hoping to get one more glass of beer.
Just one glass.
Right.
It's nice to be a regular.
I get to open closed doors.
You're a VIP customer.
I feel weirdly strengthened...
when I come here.
I also like talking to you.
I do too.
Really?
You're buried under work...
and I imagine it must be tough,
but you're always bright and strong.
I like that.
Thank you.
Cheers.
How did you become a regular here, Ah Jin?
Didn't I tell you?
No.
I think you were drunk that night.
I wasn't that drunk.
I wasn't drunk that day.
You see...
Are you taking me home by any chance?
No, I'm not.
You aren't, are you?
No.
- Good night. - Good night.
Do you live here?
What floor?
What about you?
How did I never see you?
You live right upstairs.
I know.
- How could this... - How could this...
I hope we get along.
It's nice to meet you, neighbor.
Since we're neighbors,
I'll have to give you side dishes on the house.
Nice!
Let's go in.
Come on.
- This is weird. - I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
I really can't believe it.
Are you not coming
Or can't you come
You, who isn't here
Late at night When there is no one outside
What's going on?
What's this?
Hi, Dad.
Yes, Park Hyung Soo is my dad.
Who is this?
There was bleeding in the endocranium...
and we had to urgently perform surgery.
Luckily, the bleeding has stopped...
and we haven't seen any additional bleeding yet.
- There you go. - It's mine!
Wait, my father didn't have car insurance?
"Liability insurance"? What's that?
Does it mean he won't get compensated for the damage?
(Balance: 442 dollars)
- Hey! - Kick it. Hey!
Hey, it went in.
Go over there.
Over here!
(Call)
(In Deok)
(The person you have reached is unavailable.)
(We're giving out a lot of presents!)
Chef Park.
Chef Park, we'll look forward to your food tonight.
- Hello. - Are you here to take out a loan?
Well, I wanted to find out how much I can take out for a loan.
- Can you give me your ID? - Okay.
- Here. - Okay.
You have a student loan.
Do you have any collateral? What about the lease for Bistro?
Well, I didn't sign the lease under my name.
Then,
how about your house? Do you own it? Or is it a deposit-based house?
I pay monthly rent.
How much is the deposit?
5,000 dollars.
But I've been using this bank for several years now.
Can you take my record into consideration for the loan?
How much do you need?
Well,
how much can I borrow?
We cannot...
give out any loan for you.
In Deok, why didn't you answer my calls?
Where are you? You're not at the restaurant.
Are you there?
In Deok.
Hey, you're here.
I couldn't reach you for days. Where have you been?
Sit down.
By the way, what's going on?
I'm pulling out from this place.
What are you talking about? Why would you do that?
It just happened.
Wait. But you didn't even tell me anything about that.
How could you tell me...
such an important decision on the day you're moving out?
- I'm sorry. - In Deok.
Why are you doing this?
I need this place.
My father was in a car accident, so he had emergency surgery.
What?
Is he okay?
The surgery went well,
but In Deok,
can you reconsider?
I don't have any assets. Where could I get a job?
You know that all I can do is cook.
Jin Sung.
I'm really sorry.
I know things are tough for you more than anyone.
I'm in a tight spot too.
(The link between you and me)
(Hideout)
(Immediate cash loans are available.)
- My gosh. - Come on.
- Hold on. Give me that. - Let me do that.
- Okay. - This looks great.
- Let me pour you a drink. - Right.
- This is good. - Exactly.
- Look at your shirt. - My gosh.
- Hey, drink up. - Okay.
- What is it? - Yes.
Now that we've had some food,
let's talk about our jobs.
How can you eat meat right now?
Did it taste good?
When I read the proposals you guys submitted,
the thought of other people reading them...
embarrassed me.
So I put them in the paper shredder and destroyed them.
That's how awful they were.
Ah Jin.
Yes?
"A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies"?
Do you know how many cooking shows...
the other TV stations have?
Eight.
Our industry is saturated with cooking shows.
You want to run another cooking show?
Don't you think about the viewers?
But this isn't just a regular cooking show.
The gay chef will give them advice.
Why?
Do you think this will get high ratings...
because the presence of a gay chef will be shocking?
Did you think about...
how these gay chefs will be perceived by the viewers?
You need a clear agenda for a program like this.
If you're not careful with this subject,
you'll end up getting criticized by everyone.
Do you get it?
Okay.
My goodness. I'm sorry I'm late. I had a meeting.
- Hello. - Hello.
As always, the seat in front of you is empty.
- Next, No Jae Soo. - Yes?
Why is that shocking?
Besides, should we pretend they don't exist...
because we're scared to be criticized by people?
What?
Ah Jin, what's wrong with you?
You know what?
I've given a lot of thoughts and time into this proposal.
I didn't treat this subject lightly.
Go on.
The thing about people is...
when they don't know someone,
they consider that person to be a different species.
And they'd be uncomfortable and scared to talk to them.
I want to show the viewers that the way they live...
and all the feelings they have are identical to...
our way of life and our feelings. I want to show they're just like us.
Only 4,000 dollars?
Can't I borrow any more than that?
No one would lend you more without security.
What's the interest rate?
47 percent?
Give me a chance.
If you do,
I'm confident I can do a good job.
I guess CK didn't recognize our future star director.
They haven't even given you permanent employment yet?
All right.
I'll give you a chance.
Really?
But only on one condition.
Your chance lasts only for a day.
Bring a gay chef who meets my standards within 24 hours.
How could I do that within a day?
Let's say a live show guest has an accident...
and doesn't show up.
Would you say you don't have enough time to find a replacement...
and not air the show?
As a director, you should be able to find the people you need...
within the time limit.
What?
I just gave you a chance, and you want to give up?
No.
I can do it.
Really? That's great.
But one more thing.
What if you fail?
Pardon?
If you fail to bring the right person,
you'll lose not only the show...
but also your position...
at CK Channel.
Okay.
It's a deal.
All right.
I must be out of my mind.
Hey.
Ah Jin.
You surprised me.
How could you say those things in front of someone so high up?
Is it because you're a temporary employee?
Because you're not going to work with her for a long time anyway?
Mr. Nam.
- Mr. Nam, we're leaving. - Okay, let's go.
Hey, come to your senses.
You can't say whatever you want to say.
You completely ruined our team dinner.
Unbelievable.
Do you not understand the hierarchy?
Let's go. Gosh.
- See you. - See you.
Why did this guy drink so much? Hey.
- Come on. - I'll take him home.
- Come here. - Mr. Lee!
Good night!
They all left.
But I can have another drink with you.
Forget it, that's what you want.
Hey.
Do you think you can brag because you have a company card?
Gosh, there you go again.
Hey, let's have another drink!
Please!
You eat so much.
How can you eat all that?
You'll understand if you live alone.
Oh, you do live alone.
By the way, why did you give Ah Jin a chance?
Were you convinced by her words?
M Channel is already airing American reality shows.
I know.
But they're being criticized a lot.
They still get high viewer ratings.
People love watching the shows they hate.
That's what being in a high position does to you.
Viewer ratings come before anything, right?
Anyway, if you were going to give her a chance,
why couldn't you give her more time?
Why do you have to torture her like this?
Because I want to.
Of course, because you want to.
Did you read my proposal?
Everything was garbage, including yours.
Hey! Please support me.
Why do you keep saying that?
Why would I support you?
Hey! Please.
Jin Sung.
Dad.
Are you okay?
Isn't...
this hospital expensive?
Dad, you almost died in an accident.
And you worry about your hospital bills?
I don't think this is covered by my insurance.
So why...
Don't worry. It's not that expensive.
Don't worry about a thing.
All you have to do is recover.
But you don't have any money.
If you're so worried about money,
you'd better get well quickly.
I'm sorry.
Why would you say that?
You know how mean she can be.
Why did you have to go against her?
Then should I have remained quiet?
"I apologize for coming up with..."
"and proposing such an absurd idea."
"I'm such an incompetent person."
Should I have said that?
You're an idiot.
I can do it.
I have a whole day ahead of me.
You're crazy.
Sung Eun, where should we start digging?
I doubt there are many chefs who came out as gay.
Also, it has to be someone competent, right?
You started this.
Why are you dragging me into this?
Help me, please.
You could say I'm on the verge of losing my job,
but at the same time,
this is my chance to become the main director.
You're one ambitious girl.
- Gosh. - Hurry up.
You're scaring me.
I'm so lucky to have you.
You put me through so much trouble.
I love you, Sung Eun.
(Job Openings)
What's this?
What is this?
Who changed the lock?
(Contacts)
(In Deok)
- Isn't the collection nice? - Yes.
It's ready.
This looks good.
Go ahead and try it.
I knew it.
You were born with amazing cooking skills.
It's really good.
You'll be a huge success.
Thank you, In Deok.
It'll be thanks to you if I become a success.
I won't ever forget that and pay you back.
Just make sure you pay the electricity bill...
and treat me to a drink often.
Drinks are always on me.
What else do you want to eat?
Me? This time...
Do you have any noodles?
(Special Chef Wanted)
I'm not after this tiny access pass.
(Post)
I just want to be someone useful.
We're all alone.
We're infinitely incomplete.
Come to me
Are you happy now
A corner of my heart feels empty if I do nothing.
I feel like...
I'll fall into an endless pit.
That's why I want to become useful to someone...
and be together.
Am I asking for too much?
Chef Park?
Chef Park!
Where are you, Chef Park?
I have to talk to you!
(Lottery ticket)
Chef Park!
What are you doing here? Why is Bistro closed?
Hi.
I was at Bistro, but it was closed.
Why are you drinking soju?
I'm sorry,
but I'd like to be alone.
Yes, of course.
Chef Park.
I know you don't want company,
but I'm in a rush right now.
Do you know any...
gay chefs?
What?
I can explain.
I'm planning a TV show.
If you take a look at this...
A gay chef cooks and...
Later.
- I can't right now. - I'm tight on time.
Could you introduce me to anyone?
I can pay the chef a good amount of money.
Does it pay 10,000 dollars?
It could... It depends on who the chef is.
What does the chef need to do?
Just cook.
- Cook? - Yes.
The chef just has to cook on the show.
I even have a script. It isn't that complicated.
I only have a day, Chef Park.
Could you introduce me to anyone?
Please.
("A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies")
(Program Introduction)
No...
No one is here.
Not a single person?
I'm on my way to Rainbow Organization.
I'm going to ask if they can recommend a chef.
Yes, I'll be right there after visiting a few places.
Okay, bye.
You can take your time and look around.
Are you done? What do you think?
This looks nice.
- It's well-maintained, right? - Yes.
Who are you?
Is this place for sale?
Yes. Who might...
you be?
I'm a regular here.
There are cockroaches everywhere,
not to mention rats.
You shouldn't buy this place. It'll be your loss.
Who are you?
Who are you to say such ridiculous things?
Are you the owner of this building?
Yes, I am.
I asked who you are.
Please help me out.
Who are you and why are you doing this?
Get up.
I used to work for In Deok.
You can't sell this to anyone else.
I worked on every corner of this place.
This place means everything to me.
If you give me some time, I'll come up with the deposit.
Please.
You must have had at least 15 chefs so far.
Right?
Did not a single person show up?
Look.
I gave it some thought.
I'll clean out your desk for you.
What do you think?
Have a nice day.
- Gosh. - It's cold here.
It's cold.
I can't just sit here. I'll go out and look for someone.
Go where?
Then what am I supposed to do? I have to do something.
Excuse me.
I'm here for the audition.
- Yes. - Yes.
- Over here. - Come this way.
Wait. Ms. Cha.
Why can't I cast him?
What are you doing?
I know that I didn't have a shot, to begin with.
But this isn't fair at all.
Do I seem like I have time for this?
Do you think I'd do this just to torture you?
Then, why can't I cast him?
He wasn't that bad.
Must I tell you why you can't cast him?
His hands are too chubby.
What?
You didn't think about...
the close-up shots you'd need when he's cooking, right?
He's supposed to win over women's hearts.
Will you use a hand double?
Move.
You should beg me to give you...
one more day.
Doors are opening.
Ms. Cha, can you give me one more day?
If you need one more day,
it would mean that you're admitting...
that your ability to cast and your credibility,
which are important qualifications of being a director, are lacking.
You don't...
need to give me more time.
You have four hours left.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Hey.
Chef Park?
What?
Starting now,
I am not myself.
I must hide my identity completely.
You know what?
I can just do this once.
This is the only way I can survive.
Starting now,
I'm a gay chef.
(Sweet Munchies)
His looks and his culinary skills.
Isn't he what we've been looking for?
I really want to launch this program with him.
Show me what you had in mind.
There's a thin line between fashion and costumes.
If it's too much, you'll look ridiculous.
Are you saying that I look ridiculous?
- Is he famous? - He's really popular nowadays.
That jerk. I'll meet with him.
Can you help me out just this once?
Can I ask you...
why you want to be a gay chef?
Why don't you join me?
Watch me. I'll make a great show.