It's good.
It's delicious.
His looks and his culinary skills.
Isn't he what we've been looking for, Ms. Kim?
Yes. Right?
I agree. I mean, look at his hands.
He has such nice hands, doesn't he?
He does have really beautiful hands.
Ah Jin.
Come to my office.
Oh, Chef Park. I'd like to speak to you in my office as well.
Me too?
All right. We're rolling.
Cue!
Gosh, there he goes again.
What's wrong? Is he doing that again?
Like always.
I guess he has a lot on his mind.
All right, we'll take a quick break!
Who do you think...
made this model so depressed?
When you wear clothes, you don't just wear fabric.
You wear emotions.
Evoking emotions.
That's what fashion is all about.
You guys ruined the model's mood...
as well as mine.
If one person on your team were to be disqualified,
who do you think should be sent home?
Actually,
he's slow and doesn't have the basic skills.
That made it hard for all of us.
But the design was yours.
I think the wrong choice was made...
for the material, the first step.
You all liked it at first.
- I said you should change it. - When did you say that?
You worked as a team for a few days.
However,
no one is using the word "we".
If you want to clothe many people in my clothes,
you have to get used to working as a team.
You can't work alone.
It's the same for everything.
Wait.
(Script)
You all...
are disqualified.
Excuse me.
Ms. Cha,
I really want to launch this program with him.
Do your parents know about your sexual orientation?
They may...
or may not know about it.
Does that mean they know or not?
I think they might pretend not to know even if they did.
Short clips of the show will be everywhere.
Ms. Cha.
We don't know what people might start picking on.
Your family or friends could get hurt.
Are you still okay with this?
Everyone...
gets hurt one way or another.
Ms. Cha.
He has made up his mind and...
Ah Jin.
Yes?
Leave us.
Excuse me?
Why is that?
Okay.
All right.
I'm divorced.
I have a daughter who is all grown up now.
She puts her boyfriend...
and her dog before me.
I'm not interested in men.
I know they're all the same.
All I have left is work,
but it's starting to get boring too.
Comfort me.
Even better if you have a solution.
You want a solution?
Yes.
Say something.
How will you win the viewers over when you can't even get to me?
(Rejected, Revised)
(Monthly Schedule)
Then you should...
just quit.
There is nothing worse than keeping a boring job.
Some of my customers...
always talk about quitting their jobs.
They are frustrated...
at even the thought of going to work in the morning.
It might be the right choice...
for them to quit...
rather than waste their lives like that.
It's such a waste.
But interestingly,
some of those who say their work is boring...
are workaholics.
When they are on vacation,
they pack their laptops instead of swimsuits.
Nature doesn't impress them at all.
People like that always return...
to what they love.
So,
you should try quitting.
If you want to figure out what matters to you,
losing it first is an option.
I ran into you earlier, right?
Are you okay?
I'm sure you're here since you're okay.
I stand out because of my flashy outfit, right?
I can explain.
There's a thin line...
between fashion and costumes.
If it's too much, you'll look ridiculous.
Excuse me.
Are you saying that I look ridiculous?
I didn't expect this, Ah Jin.
That wasn't bad for someone you found within a day.
Show me what you had in mind.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
Seriously...
Thank you so much for giving me this chance.
I'll make a great show by all means.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Thank you, Ms. Cha!
Isn't that what you've been thinking too?
- Pardon? - You've been self-conscious...
the whole time.
As if you're wearing someone else's clothes.
There's also a thin line between over-the-top and fancy.
It's all about balance.
Mr. Kang, are you ready?
See you.
Why...
are you looking at me like that?
Well...
How did you persuade Ms. Cha?
Did I pass?
She said I can make a pilot.
- Really? - Thank you so much.
Thank you.
- Ms. Kim. - Yes?
When can I...
When can I get paid?
When can you get paid?
I did it! This is unbelievable.
My goodness.
Sung Eun!
- Sung Eun! - Hey!
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- Can you make the show now? - I can't believe this.
- Really? - Can you believe this?
Great job, Ah Jin.
Hey.
By the way, do you know the chef?
It looked like it.
He runs Bistro I often go to.
It's him?
Then you could have cast him from the beginning.
Why did you go through all that trouble?
I had no idea.
How come?
You go there all the time.
I know.
Then again, how would you know if he doesn't tell you?
Hey, what's with that disappointed look on your face?
It's not like that.
Don't tell me...
you asked him out and he turned you down.
Don't be ridiculous.
By the way, I don't have enough budget.
What should I do?
Let Director Kim Ah Jin take care of it tomorrow.
- Tomorrow? - Today...
is your last day as an assistant director.
We should drink.
Buy me a drink.
- You're a director now. - Okay.
Ah Jin, you finally did it.
Congratulations.
Shouldn't we go for a drink?
Where should we go?
- What's with him? - No idea.
Right. Guys, the whole hallway...
smells like fried food.
How about we go for some makgeolli?
Makgeolli sounds amazing.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Kwang Su, your styling has been pretty good so far.
It's sophisticated, and I like the way you use accessories.
It's always controlled.
Dad.
- He's my favorite designer. - I wanted to be bold this time.
Really?
It's my dream to walk the runway in his clothes.
- I'm here. - Hi.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
You didn't have to come. What about Bistro?
In Deok is there.
- Did you eat? - Hold on.
I don't want to miss this part.
It's that jerk.
- Do you have anything to add? - Hey.
Is he famous?
Yes.
How famous?
Famous enough to host a show like that alone at his age.
He's a huge star.
Please go back.
Gosh.
Thanks for taking good care of Dad.
Jin Sung, make some food for me.
At this hour? Are you hungry?
Yes, I'm starving.
Gosh.
All right. I'll go change first.
Yes!
What is he doing?
Come here.
Wow, that looks delicious.
Jin Sung, how do I look?
I have an audition soon.
That's why I bought this.
Are you auditioning for a nightclub?
What do I know?
You're right. You know nothing about fashion.
- Jin Woo. - Yes?
How...
did you know you were special?
You're going to nag me, aren't you?
I'm not. I'm just curious.
I just found out naturally.
I realized what I liked,
and it was different from what most people liked.
Can you tell...
just by looking...
whether a person is gay or not?
Not if that person hides it well.
Take Tae Sik, the pride of our neighborhood, for example.
No one knew before he came out himself.
No one knew?
You know passion is never enough.
She'll be out of here once her contract is up. Am I wrong?
Let's face it.
Think of Park Sin Ho, Kim Hye Jeong, and Ko Seung Ju.
None of their contracts got extended.
They can't even negotiate their salaries.
They have no reason to stay here.
Who knows "Sweet Munchies" will become a hit and she'll make it big?
You never know.
No way.
There's no way that's going to happen.
What about the assistant director?
I don't need one.
What do you mean?
If No Jae Soo is going to be my assistant director,
I'd rather not have any assistant director at all.
He'll look down on me because I'm not a permanent employee,
and he'll ruin the whole atmosphere.
If you only want to work with people you like,
start a club instead.
You can't make a show alone.
You always need other people.
Still, I couldn't force him to work on this show if he doesn't want to.
Make him want to.
That's also a director's job.
This is a jungle.
How many people do you think will recognize and support you...
before you become successful?
Will there even be any?
What are you waiting for? Get out.
Seriously, don't be like this, okay?
Ah Jin is working on a show about gay guys.
Lesbians?
Goodness.
Hey.
When one thing takes off,
dozens of other shows with similar concepts get produced, you know?
Ah Jin is working on a show featuring a gay guy.
"A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies".
"Sweet Desserts by a Lesbian".
Gosh, isn't it such a great idea?
You want to produce a mere remake of the show?
Don't be like this, please.
My face is all red and hot because I'm so embarrassed for you!
Gosh, seriously.
You think it's that lame?
Yes!
Be it a remake or a third-rate show. I don't care.
I just want to produce a show. That's all.
Gosh, why am I getting teary-eyed?
- Bring the paperwork. - Yes, sir.
(Instant Loans 365, Get Cash Today)
I think the amount is wrong.
You said it'd be 4,000 dollars,
but the amount is...
That is the correct amount.
That's what you get after deducting the interest in advance.
You deducted the interest in advance?
Goodness gracious.
Sang Young, spare me a moment.
What is this?
Why do I see my name on the staff list?
Let's work on "Sweet Munchies" together.
I know why you don't want to work on "Sweet Munchies".
First off,
we're the same age,
but I joined the company a year earlier,
so you have to use honorifics.
You probably don't like that.
Just talk to me casually. Let's be friends.
But be polite and call me "Director" when we're on set.
Gosh.
Secondly,
your position is permanent, whereas I'm on a contract.
Right. As you said, I'm like a short-lived mayfly.
But whether I'm a mayfly or a mosquito,
we all have one life, you know?
Goodness.
And you know how this industry works.
When a show takes off,
your pay goes up drastically.
I'm going to do a really good job with this show.
What's the third reason?
Is there a third reason?
You don't trust me, right?
If that is the case,
just think that you're there to build experience.
"I shouldn't do what Kim Ah Jin is doing."
"If I were in her position, I'd do it this way."
Real firsthand experience, you know?
Such experience can't even be bought with money.
You get drunk fast when you drink during the day.
I'm scared of what you'll do when you're drunk.
Hey, eat something.
Am I...
a thief?
What?
Are you dating someone half your age or what?
I feel as though I'm not doing any work and just stealing a salary.
Gosh, that's why...
I told you to just get a managerial position.
If I get a chief producer position, I'll just sit at my desk...
from 9 to 6 and pick on the juniors all day long.
And I'll have to tiptoe around the higher-ups...
and fight to keep my position.
Hey, that won't be fun at all.
You see, I...
I like being on set.
This time, I'll have the camera operator pour me one.
What? Are you already bossing us around?
Gosh, no.
You know,
I'll do my best and work really hard.
You're thorough, so you'll do a great job.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- Hey, Director Jang. - You made it.
- Our Lighting Director! Hello. - Hello.
- I'm so happy you made it! - Hi.
- Hello. - What's going on here?
Are you guys wrapping up already?
- Gosh, no. - Of course not.
We're just getting started.
Right? Let me pour you one, Director Kim.
"Director"? My gosh, I'm not used to being called like that.
Gosh, all you directors here.
I'm counting on you.
All right.
Directors.
This is my first show as a director,
and I'm so honored to work with all of you!
I look forward to working with you.
- Here's to her first show! - Cheers!
Cheers!
Jin Sung.
Why are you still up?
Hey, don't mind me.
Go back to sleep.
Hey, pull up the blanket.
(Show Appearance Agreement)
This is just wrong.
Oh, I'm home!
Kitty, did you have a good day?
Kitty!
Here, kitty.
Kitty.
Where are you?
Don't hide and come on out.
Here, kitty. Where are you?
You're there, right? Kitty?
Chef Park!
Chef Park, Chef Park!
You must have had a lot to drink.
Yes, I had a drink with the directors.
I see.
What are you doing out here?
Were you... waiting for me by any chance?
What?
No, it's not that.
I have something to tell you.
You do? To me?
Yes.
I see. I have something to tell you too.
Chef Park,
if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be able to do this show.
You're...
my savior.
My savior. I'll do my best.
I'm home, I'm home.
- I'm totally fine. - Yes, go on up.
I'm so drunk, aren't I?
I'm so drunk.
I'll go home now.
Your house is upstairs.
Good night. Go ahead.
No, I'll see you go in first.
- Really? - Yes.
Gosh.
- Go on. Go in. - Okay.
I have the money.
This is a contract with CK and it's basically money.
This isn't money.
Well...
Could you give me a week?
If you give me a week,
I'll bring you the money.
I've worked hard all my life.
(Note! It's better to use crunchy fruit or vegetables.)
(Shrimp carpaccio)
(Shrimp salad)
(Salmon flower salad)
If you just give me a few days,
I can wire you the money.
Please.
I'm giving you exactly a week.
Thank you, Grandma. Thank you so much.
Why do you keep calling me "Grandma"?
Are you my grandson?
Excuse me?
I'm not a grandma.
I don't even have grandchildren yet.
I see.
Wait, isn't this the outfit...
that was in "Cooking Class"?
You're right. That was intentional.
It looks good in the kitchen.
I see.
This doesn't seem to have anything to do with the kitchen.
I think it does.
It wasn't on TV that often. It's a nice outfit.
This is something I prepared.
Could you take a look?
You're working hard.
Yes.
I gave it some thought. What do you think about...
Yes, I know.
That's what I put up on those hangers.
I think it's totally different.
Ah Jin.
That's because you have no idea.
I want to add fashion to munchies.
It will be better if you have more to talk about.
Add fashion to munchies?
- Then the food would be the model. - Yes.
Eating munchies will make you gain weight.
You get fat.
I'm serious.
I am too.
Ah Jin.
How long have you been working here?
I can tell you're fairly new...
and want to focus on the packaging.
But you should be worrying about the content.
This is more than enough.
The packaging?
Then are you in the packaging business?
What? What did you just say?
He's gay and will be coming out for the first time on this show.
It wouldn't be enough to dress him in delicate and beautiful clothes.
But this?
It would be better to get clothes off the street market.
Street market? Hey! Is that all you have to say?
No, I'm not done yet.
I'm not working with you.
What?
I'm not working with you!
- Wait. - Hey, hey!
My goodness. You're fearless, Ah Jin.
What are we going to do?
Gosh.
I want to help you.
You were the nicest to me.
However, if I work on this show,
I'll be branded for life.
I even got a written notice...
to boycott you.
This is so childish.
Aren't they going too far? They're playing dirty.
You probably won't find any stylists that will work with you here.
I have to get going.
What? Yes, of course.
- Have a nice day. - You too.
Thank you.
Ms. Kim.
Chef Park.
It's a struggle, isn't it?
You're lying.
I'm really not struggling.
It isn't right to say I'm struggling.
I'm doing something I've always hoped for.
By the way, what were you doing at the broadcasting station earlier?
Oh, that's...
I was just...
passing by.
Well, did you say I'd get paid...
after the shoot?
Yes.
So when is the shoot?
Well...
As soon as the outfits are ready.
The wardrobe department is still working on it.
But as soon as they're ready, we can shoot. I'm sorry.
Please wait just a little longer.
I see.
That jerk.
Pardon?
I mean...
Kang Tae Wan.
What about designer Kang Tae Wan from "Changing You"?
Can I ask you something?
Why does it have to be a gay chef?
Well...
As it says here...
I want to hear it from you.
Think about it.
Why not a five-star hotel chef?
Why does the chef have to be gay?
It's because I want to talk about people.
A gay host...
wouldn't take sides...
between men and women.
He could talk about people...
from his own special perspective.
Have you ever considered...
if that idea could be based on prejudice?
I don't want my clothes to be contaminated by such prejudice.
Mr. Kang.
Well...
This will be your chance to attract more female customers.
Every woman dreams of having a gay friend.
By targeting women...
You can't become friends with someone just because you want to.
Friendship is not a thing you buy like you buy a bag.
I mean... I'm an idiot.
Why did I say such a stupid thing?
Gosh, what should I do?
Seriously.
Chef Park, I'm sorry.
Gosh.
How about...
I talk to him?
Pardon? You want to do that?
We've met, right?
I'd like to ask you to take charge of...
the outfits for "Sweet Munchies".
I just told Ms. Kim that I can't do it.
You told me the other day...
that there's a thin line between fashion and costumes.
What's your point?
I don't want to look ridiculous.
That day,
when you told me that,
it hurt my feelings, to be honest.
But after some thought,
I realized that you were right.
So...
can you please...
help me this once?
You're reckless.
If I had a choice,
I wouldn't have come this far.
By that, do you mean...
Coming out?
You don't want to look ridiculous?
But before that,
have you thought about how much ridicule...
you might bring upon yourself by coming out as a gay chef on TV?
Why?
What's so wrong about being gay?
I don't see why...
I should be ashamed of being gay.
But at the same time,
if you have a prejudice against gay people,
I guess there's nothing I can do.
I believe...
no one should ever be ridiculed...
for any reason.
I'm so proud of you. Great job.
From Ms. Cha to Mr. Kang...
You saved my life.
- Ms. Kim. - Yes?
I have a favor to ask.
Sure, go ahead. I can do anything for you.
It's about my appearance fee.
Is there a way I can get it before the shoot?
Well, I don't think there's anything I can do about it.
But I'll try to find a way.
I owe you so much.
- Really? - Yes.
- Are you sure? - I'm positive.
- Ms. Kim. - Yes?
I'll work really hard.
That sounds great.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
We can do this!
Mr. Kang, Chef Park, I brought some snacks.
I think I'll go get some coffee too.
Turn around.
Well, this makes me...
nervous for some reason.
You have a nice body.
Red looks good on you.
I'll leave everything up to you.
I don't know much about anything other than cooking.
What?
I see that you can smile.
What's your shoe size?
265mm.
I see. That's perfect.
Hi, guys.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Yu Jin, I'm counting on you.
- Director, hello. Hello! - Hi.
- Hello, hello. - Hey, you're here.
Okay, we'll do that.
Lighting Director, can we have more light over here?
Why does he look so nervous?
He does seem nervous.
Right? Let's go talk to him.
Chef Park.
Your lips look all purple. Are you all right?
Chef Park, just follow the script.
Right, yes. Don't worry.
Why don't you take a deep breath?
- Breathe in through your nose... - Sorry?
and breathe out through your mouth. Take a deep breath.
In through the nose and out through the mouth.
Yes, that's it. Don't be nervous. You're okay?
- I'm not nervous. - You're okay, right?
- I'm fine. - We'll get started, then.
- Okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
You're good, right?
We'll begin now.
Let's begin!
- Let's start rolling. - Okay.
We'll begin now.
All right, we're rolling.
Rolling.
1, 2, 3.
Cue!
Ta-da!
What is this?
It's our seven-year anniversary.
We're the same age, and we've been together for seven years.
- Even just a month ago, - This is so beautiful.
he wanted to get married as soon as possible.
But I found out that he's been cheating on me for two months...
with a girl who's 10 years younger than me.
After that day, I can't even eat tripe, my absolute favorite.
I've just been crying every day since then.
I can't do anything.
What can I do to break this off?
("A Gay Chef's Sweet Munchies")
Do you think...
I can be in love again?
What kind of question is that?
It seems like you're the only one...
who doesn't know how attractive you are.
Gosh. Hold on. Hold on a moment.
Chef Park, be natural.
Just think that you're having a conversation with her.
Okay?
- Be natural... - Yes.
Okay, got it.
We'll try that again.
We'll do it again.
- Okay. - All right.
Rolling.
It seems like you're the only one...
who doesn't know how attractive you are.
We'll try that again.
Don't worry.
It seems like you're the only one...
who doesn't know how attractive...
Again.
We'll try it again.
(Park Jin Sung: Don't worry.)
Don't worry.
Everyone is born...
with their soul mate's name written on...
One more time.
Don't... Don't worry.
Again! One more time.
With their soul mate's name...
Again.
written on the sole of their feet.
One more time.
You'll meet...
Do it again.
- You're... - Do it again.
How attractive you are.
We'll try that again.
Director Kim, I have another shoot.
I'm sorry.
I've never done this before, so I was nervous.
I'll...
do better.
Chef Park.
Do you know why...
I became a regular at Bistro?
Sorry?
"I've done more than enough."
"I can't put up with this anymore."
"I'm just going to quit."
It was...
one of those days.
I was on my way home after working 15 hours straight,
getting yelled at all day long and skipping all three meals.
I suddenly noticed a sign that was still lit up.
(Bistro, 10pm to 4am)
I thought, "My gosh, there's a restaurant that's still open?"
I was so glad to see that it was still open.
So I went in and ordered soju.
Do you know what I got as an accompaniment to the soju?
Can you believe it?
That I was served a home-cooked meal at a bar...
I happened to stumble upon at 2am?
You probably need a proper meal more than soju on a day like today.
"Gosh, I miss Mom."
"I want to eat..."
"a hearty meal made by Mom."
The food you made that day...
reminded me of my mom's hearty home-cooked meals.
I want to make a show like that.
A show that can comfort the hearts of those...
who are going through a rough patch.
A show that's like a hearty, wholesome meal.
Just be yourself.
Just think that there are no cameras around.
And think that the guest is a customer at Bistro.
You don't have to follow the script.
Gosh.
Ah Jin.
What did you say to Chef Park to keep him from coming?
Did he go home? Is he quitting?
What's this?
Isn't that tripe?
Hi.
Are you making fun of me?
I told you tripe makes me want to throw up.
Take this away.
Let's try it without the tripe.
How will you get over him...
if you can't even eat tripe?
You said you want to get over him.
Try to remember.
Not him,
but the things you really love.
(Sweet Munchies)
"Sweet Munchies" forever! Cheers!
Come on, Chef Park.
Let's try being friends first.
Nice to meet you, Park Jin Sung.
Same here, Kim Ah Jin.
Thanks to your heartfelt words,
my clothes looked special.
You were impressive today.
People won't stop posting comments and the viewer ratings are high.
"Sweet Munchies" will get a regular slot.
Was this your plan from the start?
You are inexperienced and can't handle it.
Please don't do this to me.
What does "Sweet Munchies" mean to you?
It means everything to me.