[ TEAM BULLDOG: OFF-DUTY INVESTIGATION ]
[ All characters, locations, organizations
and incidents appearing ]
[ in this film are fictitious. ]
[ Episode 2 ]
[ Ido Pharmaceuticals ]
[ Murderous company, Ido Pharmaceuticals,
bring my son back. ]
[ "Ido Pharmaceuticals Enters
the EU Market" ]
"Kim Min-seok".
You're Mr. Kim Min-seok, aren't you?
You can't be here.
Wait.
- Who are you?
- Director Kang Moo-young of Fact Check.
I have some questions
about Lee Jong-dae who was murdered
at a park in Guchon in 2007.
Why would you ask me that?
You use the screen name,
Dr. Caligari's Cabinet,
don't you?
Hey, get rid of her.
The IP address of that user ID came
from your house.
You uploaded a video of killing
a cat on the dark web too, right?
What?
What are you talking about?
Director Kim!
Hey... You told me
the new drug test came out clean.
But my son fell
into a coma after taking that drug.
What are you going to do about this?
Gosh, this old man.
Get lost!
This little...
Let me go!
Are you insane? What are you doing?
You all must be out of your mind.
Goodness, you're so tough.
Do you have a license
for beating people up?
Who on earth are you, punk?
Get this off me now.
Me?
I'm a cop who arrests punks like you.
Sir, are you hurt?
Are you all right?
Can you get up?
What do you think you're doing?
What do you think?
I'm arresting you
for murdering Lee Jong-dae
and Gu Hyeong-jin.
Did you say I killed somebody?
How will you handle this later?
How else? I'm sure the law will handle it.
And let me give you a piece of advice.
Why don't you try disinfecting your life
for once?
Your life is full of germs, you know.
Hey, you can leave.
And bring the Chief of Police instead.
Is he a friend of yours or something?
Why would I do that?
Goodness.
[ TEAM BULLDOG: OFF-DUTY INVESTIGATION ]
My gosh, I'm here, Director Kim.
Oh, you're here.
Chief, what is going on?
I just got a call from your father.
I think we made a mistake.
Please forgive us.
I'll take care of it quickly.
That won't do.
The Legal Team from my company
will be here soon.
Let's talk then.
Since the law says so,
I'll let you keep me here for 48 hours.
But after that, you should be prepared.
Hey, you. Get out here now.
My gosh.
Gosh, this is hurting my ego.
What?
You little punk!
Have you lost your mind?
His dad is a member
of the Police Development Committee.
So what? Are we supposed to bow down
since he gives us financial support?
Shut it.
I'm sorry, sir. I should've stopped him.
Stop what?
Have you ever seen me let go of a suspect?
You need to know whom you're dealing with.
You need to stop acting up like this.
You don't even have evidence.
I have evidence right here.
Check if his fingerprints
match the ones we found
on the weapon
that was used to kill Gu Hyeong-jin.
But it was an unidentified fingerprint.
Do you think they'll match?
He could've forged the data
and got away with it.
But this definitely belongs to him,
so I'm sure it'll be a match.
- Hurry up and check.
- Okay.
- If the two don't match...
- My gosh.
Can we talk about it
after we get the results?
It hurts!
We're from Ido Pharmaceuticals'
Legal Team.
Where is the director?
What a big group.
This is delicious.
Do you finally realize
that you're in big trouble now?
I bet you're getting the chills, right?
I'm not sure. I don't think so.
Do you want one, too?
How much do you get paid a month?
I make more than you.
Should I buy you something delicious?
Stop bluffing.
It's probably about
2,000 to 3,000 dollars.
And you got yourself in this mess
just to earn that much?
You should call your mom
and tell her your career is over.
Should I call her?
I haven't called my mom in a while.
This will be nice.
Hey, Mom. Some rich guy's son
keeps looking down on me saying I'm poor.
So can you tell me how much money
I'll be inheriting later on?
You're still that loaded?
I've been spending money like water.
And you still have that much money left?
My gosh, that's unbelievable. Okay, Mom.
What a crazy punk.
Hey, my mom says I should just ignore you
because our family still has
a lot of money left.
I'll let you video call her
if you don't believe me.
You bluff way too much
for a smalltime cop.
I'll sue you for psychological damage,
slander, and libel.
So you'd better brace yourself.
- Sue him as soon as we leave.
- Yes, sir.
This is why it's important to teach kids
their manners.
What? "Manners"?
They say you should always avoid
taking things to court.
My next-door neighbor was just like you,
and he ended up going broke.
I just feel really bad for you.
You're only humiliating your parents
by behaving this way.
My goodness.
Gang-ho, can we talk?
Wait right here.
It's him, right?
What? What is it?
[ 98 percent not a match ]
What... What the... Are you sure?
Darn it.
I'm sorry, sir. I don't know what to say.
You should know
how to manage your subordinates.
I'll make sure my dad hears about
what happened today.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Sorry, pal. Your career is over now.
You'll get to experience how terrible
the Korean legal system is.
I wish you a safe trip back, sir.
Don't forget to eat some tofu
on your way back.
Bye, sir.
Gang-ho.
Darn it.
This is the first time
we never got to use this.
He's a big fish.
Hey.
Kim Min-seok. What... What's going on?
Why is he leaving? He's the culprit.
Why didn't you go home?
You're being so annoying.
I did all the work for you.
You just had to wrap things up.
Why arrest him and then tank it like this?
I couldn't even film anything.
Are you serious?
- Do you think I wanted to tank it?
- Well, that's what you did.
Look at you.
You never listen to anything we say on TV.
And I did all the work for you,
but you just ruined everything.
Why do you think I stepped up
and tried to catch him myself?
You make it sound like
you had a huge sense of duty.
- But you only did it for your ratings.
- What?
That's just what follows along.
My main purpose was to create
a just society.
Leave that to us. That's our job.
You should just focus on the ratings.
You even said you owed me
when we met in front of the NFS.
Didn't the documents say
the two unidentified fingerprints
from the two murder cases are a match?
Then you just had to compare them
with his fingerprints.
If they were a match,
he wouldn't have gotten released.
- What?
- Do you get it now?
We have to start all over again.
Gosh, you're so loud.
What? Seriously?
Why?
What kind of show does she direct
to know so much about the case?
I don't know. I think it was Fact Bomb
or something.
I guess that's why she was going on and on
like she was bombing us.
Oh, right. The section chief
wants to meet in the chief's office.
Do you think you'll be okay?
What?
A three-month suspension?
For something like this?
You should be grateful for this.
He wanted to sue you and have you fired,
but I barely talked him out it.
Tell him to sue me.
I'm not scared at all.
If I get suspended for three months,
I won't be able to investigate.
Shut your mouth!
You better not do anything.
Just stay quiet for the next three months.
Sir, please.
I'm a cop, too.
I'm not doing this for money.
I know his dad is a member
of the Police Development Committee.
But if he's guilty, he should go to jail.
But if you really wanted to catch
a big fish like him,
you should've brought conclusive evidence.
Okay, fine. I'll bring you evidence.
My gosh, that hardheaded punk.
Do you finally realize
that you're in big trouble now?
You'll get to experience how terrible
the Korean legal system is.
You think money is stronger than the law?
But I'm too crazy for you to handle,
you punk.
Minus 20?
It's another deficit.
Did I spend too much on food?
Gosh, will you stop it already?
You've been doing that for an hour.
You must also be sad about the deficit.
Should I cut down on meal expenses?
It's just simple math.
It's not that complicated.
The answer to life isn't that simple.
[ I have some questions about... ]
I'm sure Dr. Caligari's Cabinet
is the culprit.
[ Why would you ask me that? ]
I wonder why Kim Min-seok's fingerprints
weren't a match.
Because he's not the culprit.
- What?
- Right there. Stop.
- Here?
[ - Get... ]
[ Get lost! ]
Look. He hit him with his right hand.
The culprit is left-handed.
The stab wounds
are all tilted to the right.
The suspect is left-handed.
What?
Then are you saying
Kim Min-seok is innocent?
But he seems way too involved.
He seems somewhat familiar.
What's this?
It's from my heart.
You're drinking soju in broad daylight.
Your life seems great.
I get to drink in the afternoon.
Now that I'm suspended,
my quality of life improved a lot.
You know what? Cause some trouble.
You and I should hang out together.
Oh, right. Here.
It's the isotope analysis result
of the hair we found at the scene.
[ Isotope Analysis Result ]
[ Conclusion ]
"Zinc, sulfur, calcium carbonate,
chromium oxide"?
They said these are isotopes
people mix in paints.
The victim, Gu Hyeong-jin,
was an ethics teacher, so it can't be his.
Then, it means it's highly likely
the culprit handles paint at work.
That must be it.
"Cross Section of Death".
[ Painter Kim Min-soo ]
What?
[ To my number 1 fan, Tak Won ]
Before coming here, just in case,
I checked out
Kim Min-seok's family registry.
And
take a look at this.
"Kim Min-seok". "Kim Min-soo".
He was born on March 14, 1991.
He was also born on March 14, 1991.
They have the same birthdays.
[ Painter Kim Min-soo ]
- Twins?
Where have you been all night?
I was looking for you.
I was painting in my studio all night.
You must have had a tough day yesterday
because of me.
Cleaning up your messes
is driving me crazy.
It's time for you to grow up now.
I don't know.
So the culprit isn't Kim Min-seok.
It's Kim Min-soo.
If they live in the same house,
they would have the same IP address.
And what if the nickname,
Dr. Caligari's Cabinet,
belongs to Kim Min-soo, not Kim Min-seok?
My gosh. If I play this right,
I might get the ratings up to 4.5 percent.
Shall we begin?
My jawline looks sharper from this angle.
- Come on. Let's just film.
- Please.
Goodness. Fine. The jawline?
I don't know anymore. Action.
Why do you think Kim Min-soo
is the culprit, not Kim Min-seok?
In 2007 when the incident took place,
I analyzed the culprit as a profiler.
And a significant part of my analysis
matches Kim Min-soo.
I found out that
the culprit was left-handed.
All right. This is a painting
by Kim Min-soo.
It's called "Cross Section of Death".
As you can see,
the direction of the brush strokes
goes from left to right evenly.
This means that he's left-handed,
just like the culprit.
Hold on. I have a question.
What is it?
I looked up Kim Min-soo's filmography.
He was born in 1991.
Then, when Lee Jong-dae was killed...
Right. He was 17.
So it was before his fingerprint
was registered.
Then, what about the recent incident?
His fingerprint must be in the system now.
Why did he leave the murder weapon
that had his fingerprint on it?
[ No weapons, gas fittings, or heating
appliances allowed in interrogation room. ]
When I was scouring this footage,
you told me to use my brain.
Look at you now.
This is why you have a long way to go.
The basic rules of investigation
are determination and persistence.
You must double-check
and check for any leads
you might have missed. Don't you know?
Oh, right.
You're suspended. Can you be here?
I can be here as long as you stay quiet.
I already checked all the footage.
I didn't find anything.
That's not true.
Right here.
This guy coming out of the club
isn't Kim Min-seok. It's Kim Min-soo.
You know?
Is there something there?
Why do you keep watching the same part?
What?
I knew it.
- Kim Min-soo, you'd better wait for me.
- What?
Did you make plans to meet him?
Hey, I'm talking to myself.
To use a technical term, it's a monologue.
My goodness.
[ I couldn't throw out
my son's belongings. ]
[ - You can't be here.
- Wait. ]
[ Who are you? ]
[ - Is that why you killed him?
- No. ]
My goodness. I got his bottom.
That lousy cop.
Why did he have to sit down right then?
I can't believe this guy.
Why did you crouch down there?
Come on, he ruined the audio track too.
Why haven't you reported a new topic?
Don't tell me this week's episode is...
No. No way.
You'll be surprised when you watch it.
What? What did he do with his bottom?
Why would I be surprised?
You saw it.
This is too bad, you know.
I think this will surprise you
more than me.
What is it?
Your junior, Director Hong,
brought a proposal for a new pilot show.
Goodness, I've never seen that kind
of format before.
It's bound to be a hit.
All right. Keep wasting your energy here.
My gosh, that sly geezer!
I'm going to get the highest ratings.
Darn it.
What is it?
Moo-young, someone is here to see you.
[ "The Bible" ]
Hey. What's wrong with you?
Are you a hybrid Buddhist-Catholic?
If you keep this up, believers of
both religions will stone you.
On my way to the temple,
I met an old priest.
What's wrong with him?
I'll skip my long story.
You should make a donation.
As if.
Why? You're dressed like a priest.
Right.
- How about an offertory?
- What kind of priest pays a home visit...
I mean, a personal visit
to collect donations?
Based on that, you think of the TV station
as your home.
That must be why you exposed me,
your only brother, on TV.
And that's why I'm broke.
I see.
Hey, I don't have cash.
Sister.
What will you do
with your mobile banking app?
How much?
Let me tell you
that my balance is 320 dollars.
Just give me 320 dollars.
[ I analyzed the culprit as a profiler. ]
[ And a significant part of my analysis
matches Kim Min-soo. ]
[ I found out that
the culprit was left-handed. ]
[ All right. This is a painting
by Kim Min-soo. ]
[ It's called "Cross Section of Death". ]
[ As you can see,
the direction of the brush strokes ]
[ goes from left to right evenly. ]
[ This means that he's left-handed,
just like the culprit. ]
What do you think? Can you see it?
It kind of got weak in the end.
I'm not sure.
We're not cops.
We can get it started first.
It's a reasonable doubt.
And it's up to the viewers to decide.
In our industry,
getting the scoop first is important.
But, Ms. Kang,
a lot of people are left-handed.
To say there's a reasonable doubt
with this,
isn't it unreasonable?
Why not?
We have his nickname and IP address.
"It was stolen. I was hacked."
If he says that,
we have no rebuttal.
She has a point.
Besides, this is Ido Pharmaceuticals.
If we make claims
without any hard evidence,
they might sue us.
Gosh, that will be a hassle.
My gosh, you and your words.
Mr. Never-Had-A-Girlfriend.
How can you launch your own show
if you're such a coward?
Last month, you aired an episode
that AX Group rigged stock prices
to succeed the management rights.
And AX Group filed a lawsuit.
Your trial against them is still ongoing.
I should have stopped you to the end.
It's all right.
I would've done it
even if you didn't approve.
Why bring that up?
What about you?
We definitely need more than this
to narrate a story.
Do we have any visual materials
that could shock the viewers?
So far, we only have suspicions.
Something shocking
that would make the viewers believe
that he really is the culprit.
Visual materials that
would be shocking to the viewers?
Let me see.
I might be able to find it.
I'm so thirsty.
Hey, Dae-jin.
Are you sure Kim Min-soo is home?
Yes, he's home according
to his cellphone signal.
But how come he never comes out
once all day?
Don't you think he left his phone at home?
[ You said the basic rules of investigation
are determination and persistence. ]
Then a stakeout is
like the highlight of investigations.
- Detective Min.
- Yes, coming.
I hope you become the highlight
of determination and persistence.
My goodness.
That is some annoying support.
Darn it.
What? What's that?
What?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Why are you covering your face?
- Do I know you?
- No, I don't know you.
You can just keep going.
What's wrong with her?
What are you modifying your voice for?
What? Director Kang?
Just pretend you didn't see me.
It'll be over soon.
Look at her.
You must know that this is illegal, right?
Where did you get this tall ladder though?
I borrowed it from the construction site
over there.
You think I stole it?
Okay.
You're filming here illegally
without permission.
I got you. As a guardian of the law,
I will make you pay for your actions.
Gosh, it's Kim Min-soo.
Hide!
Forget it.
Fine, then.
- Darn it.
- Gosh.
You just did that on purpose, didn't you?
So, that's Kim Min-soo?
He's the twin brother of Kim Min-seok.
No way. That's Kim Min-seok.
How can you tell which one is which?
My scientific gut is telling me.
I haven't just been slacking off as a cop,
you know.
How can your gut feeling be scientific?
You're joking.
Hey, one second.
- There. That guy who just came out.
- Where?
That's Kim Min-soo. Record it now.
On what grounds are you saying that?
Let's go.
Who's there?
Who is it?
What in the world...
It's just a horse.
A horse? Hey, wait!
- Hey, there's someone out there!
- Gosh.
Are you crazy? You're insane. You must be.
How can you think to mimic a horse
right then and there?
And why are you so good at it?
I was so startled that it just came out.
- Let's hurry and run.
- Gosh, I was so shocked.
What were you thinking, seriously?
- Hey, hey.
- My goodness.
- Hey, go!
- What's wrong?
- Who are you?
- Why are you getting in this car?
Mine is over there.
Let's just go first. Drive.
Hey!
Who are you anyway?
- Hey, you don't need to know.
- Okay.
This is that shared car
from the other day, right?
You're overspending
when you're on a budget.
I needed it to investigate the story.
What? Then should I drive
a lousy car to Guchon
when it would only stand out?
I'm just saying.
Let me have your number.
What's with you? It's not what you think.
- Excuse me, I have a boyfriend.
- She doesn't.
- Hey.
- I get that you don't have one.
Just share the video of Kim Min-soo
that you filmed earlier with me.
Why should I?
Are you trying to steal this too?
I've filmed you filming illegally,
all right?
So? Should I issue a warrant?
Is this a threat?
It's called a negotiation.
I can tell that he's a cop.
Why don't you just share it?
There.
I sent you my email address,
so please make it quick.
Now, please drop me off over there.
And take care, Pony.
- Let me off, please.
- Gosh.
Good work.
He's a total thief.
So this is the solid proof that the guy
who followed Gu Hyeong-jin
at the club was not Kim Min-seok
but Kim Min-soo.
That's what you're saying?
The gap between each individual's shoulder
and pelvis is different.
So is their stride and joint movement.
We can analyze such data
to find out the real culprit.
You can see the example
of the circumduction gait here.
Both of these guys kick their left legs
while walking.
And the right foot is an out-toed gait.
It means the right foot points outward.
It is extremely rare
that these two cases show in one person.
Which means, it's highly likely
that these two are the same person.
Seriously, that's amazing.
How did you figure this out?
It's not that I analyzed it
so scientifically...
This is what years of experience
looks like, you know.
Look up to me all you want.
Oh, right. We should report it
to the section chief.
No, don't.
Why not? We have the perfect evidence.
What if he says he only followed him
but didn't murder him?
Let me make sure of one more thing.
Okay, let's compare these two photos.
This mansion that belongs to Kim Min-seok
was owned by three generations
of Ido Pharmaceuticals owners.
Look at this place in the video.
What do you think? It's the same, right?
Is this the perfect evidence or what?
Now, he can't say
- his IP was hacked or stolen.
- Exactly.
The dirty secret of the twins
of Ido Pharmaceuticals.
That'll work.
I knew it, Director Kang.
You nailed it eventually.
No, no. There's something more important.
All right. These two men
who were at Kim Min-seok's house.
Doesn't one of them
look familiar to you?
I think we might have interviewed him.
Isn't that Kang Pil-du,
the Director of KFDA?
We interviewed him
for the humidifier case before.
He was a professor
of Pharmaceutical Sciences back then.
Right, he lied that there was no issue
with the product.
Bingo.
It's three days before Ido's new drug
gets approved by the KFDA.
And the Director
of Ido Pharmaceuticals secretly met
with the Director of KFDA at his home.
The time and place seem suspicious, right?
That's enough for reasonable doubt.
But that man
always sues people. Will it be okay?
Goodness, that's fine.
Let's put it out there
and worry about it later.
Those two men could be our key.
So please dig up some dirt
on them quickly.
Hey, I'll go and interview Kim Min-soo,
so you go ahead and meet with the victims
of the new drug test.
There's got to be something.
- Yes, sure.
- Gosh, you get on my nerves.
- Let's go!
Okay.
[ Mom ]
Mom, please stop calling.
He already got 320 dollars from me.
My gosh!
What are you doing here?
How did you know I'd get off here?
It looks like you're off
to Kim Min-soo's house.
What?
Did you wiretap me or something?
How did you know? Tell me.
You weren't calling me,
so that had to mean you found something.
And I figured you'll go see him
to do the prepping.
You're exactly correct.
It's as if you scanned my brain.
Let me go with you.
This might be the last time I see him,
so I want to go, too.
Is that really necessary?
I also solved the puzzle.
The mystery behind
the unidentified fingerprints.
What?
Seriously? What are you guys doing here?
That's what I want to ask.
I have to ask him something first.
So count to 100 before you come in.
Where are you going?
We get to ask him first this time.
Really? Do you have something?
I'm not going to tell you.
And just go home
if you're going to tank it like last time.
Don't get in our way.
Gosh, why would I get in your way?
I know you worked really hard
to get this far.
Make sure you film this
if you don't want me
to beat you to it again.
All the paintings in the gallery
were painted by my little brother.
This is creative.
He was very talented from a young age,
unlike me.
Your paintings always give me goosebumps.
Your last piece was
"Cross Section of Death",
and now, "The Dark Side of Death".
We all die one day.
And that is a very beautiful thing.
You think it's beautiful?
Death is the only thing
that's fair and peaceful to everyone.
In other words...
Hey, Min-soo!
What? It's them again?
Stop right there.
You should leave.
I'm from "Fact Check"!
We have a question for you,
Mr. Kim Min-soo!
If you don't leave, we'll call the cops.
There's no need for that. I'm a cop.
I came just in case you might call.
Now, get lost.
Hey.
He got suspended, so just kick him out.
You punk.
That's my privacy.
You can't just tell them that.
Listen. I'm not a cop, and I don't work
at the broadcasting station.
I'm just a big fan of Mr. Kim Min-soo.
So will you let me through?
I guess not.
Mr. Kim, do you remember me?
Do you know him?
How could you not remember me?
- You called me your number one fan.
- My gosh.
You can hold your fan meeting in prison.
But before that, you need to sign
a few things in the interrogation room.
Come on.
My gosh, you punk.
You darn punk.
Why won't you listen to me?
What?
Where are the others?
"The others"?
They probably won't make it here.
My gosh!
You startled me!
My goodness.
Don't come near me! Just don't!
You guys! We have a lot of time!
So let's make this a work of art!
Put your arms up properly.
Let me make this clear.
If you use physical violence
to stop us from investigating,
it's considered
an obstruction of business.
That's enough.
Shouldn't you be filming something?
Do you understand?
Mr. Kim Min-soo.
Did you upload a video of yourself
killing a cat on the dark web?
You're that lady from last time.
I'm Kim Min-seok.
Gosh, you punks.
You guys should be wearing name tags.
You know Lee Jong-dae, right?
The culprit's fingerprints were
on the weapon that was found at the scene.
And the same fingerprints were also found
on the weapon that was left
at the scene of a recent murder.
You solved the mystery behind
the unidentified fingerprints?
Yes.
Here is a possible explanation.
What are you doing?
Don't interrupt during the shoot.
It's my turn to talk, so hush.
Twelve years ago,
when Mr. Kim Min-soo found out
that he had left the weapon at the scene,
it was too late to go back for it.
[ But his fingerprints weren't
registered yet since he was only 17. ]
[ So he came up with an idea. ]
[ Something only twins could do. ]
[ Kim Min-soo ]
[ Left four fingers, Right four fingers ]
[ Right thumb ]
That is how he was able to leave
his weapon behind
after he committed the recent murder.
Because his fingerprints
aren't registered.
Is this all true?
I noticed
that you guys registered
the same fingerprints.
If you're not the culprit,
there'd be no reason for you
to forge an official document like this.
Kim Min-soo.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Lee Jong-dae and...
Okay, cut.
I'm not done talking.
You put handcuffs on him.
What more do we need?
I need to tell him his Miranda rights.
That's the main part.
Okay, fine. Go ahead.
Shoot it properly.
Kim Min-soo.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Lee Jong-dae and Gu Hyeong-jin.
Are you kidding me?
- You have the right...
- What are you doing?
- My gosh.
- You dare to bring up a ten-year-old case?
Do you really think
you can do anything to us?
We're above the law!
My goodness.
You may be above the law,
but I'm above you.
Do you think
I'll let you get away with this?
My goodness, what a nice cushion.
Who was kind enough to put a cushion here?
Are you allowed to do this?
People are watching.
What did I do wrong?
I sat down because I saw a cushion.
Up! Raise them up!
Let's go to the police station.
Let's go there and see who's right.
Are you reckless or just plain dumb?
Exactly.
Why would you leave the weapon
at the murder scene?
- I personally think you're just dumb.
- What?
It's best not to respond
to everything he says.
He has no evidence,
so he's just trying to provoke you.
You're worried for nothing.
He'll never be able to put me in jail.
You're just as rude as your twin.
You guys have the same personalities.
Let's see if I'll be able
to put you in jail or not.
I'll go ask my mom what she thinks.
Wait.
Let me give you a refill.
Why? So you can collect my fingerprints?
I'm sorry to tell you this.
But I work with my hands a lot.
So my fingerprints are worn out.
- You little...
- This is evidence.
You were suspended. Don't you know that?
This is an illegal investigation.
Yes, I know.
This is going to be my last try,
so just give me 44 hours.
If I'm wrong, I'll just quit.
I'll take full responsibility
for what happens.
- Get out of the way.
- Sir.
He may be reckless at times.
But he doesn't talk nonsense.
Let's see how it goes.
Whatever.
Just know that your entire team
is in deep trouble in 44 hours.
My Section Chief.
I'm holding evidence.
If you're wrong this time,
I will kill you before you get fired.
Darn it.
Gosh, he's so soft-hearted.
Gang-ho, do you think
we'll get it right this time?
- This is the fifth attempt.
- Just go already.
Okay.
Hey, how did it go?
Nothing?
All right, go.
[ Interrogation in progress ]
I'm sorry.
What are you doing? Apologize.
What's this?
There's no use in begging now.
Get ready to take off your uniform.
I feel shy that everyone's asking me
to take off my clothes.
Do you want to see me naked that badly?
Should I take them off for you?
The 48 hours of detention is over now.
- Move aside, please.
- I don't want to.
We finally got your fingerprint.
Here. And this is
the report saying your fingerprint matches
with the one on the murder weapon.
[ Assessment Report ]
- How did this happen?
- I'm not sure.
[ Fingerprint Identification ]
[ The fingerprints are a 98 percent match. ]
This can't be.
You've seen one too many movies.
Apparently, you can't just damage
your fingerprints
and get rid of them completely.
Your damaged skin healed
over the 48 hours you were here,
which means your fingerprints reappeared.
Let me have that.
- Show him the way to lockup.
- Sure.
Okay, Mr. Kim Min-soo, let's go.
Come on.
Goodness, I should get some sleep.
[ The twin brothers,
Kim Min-seok and Kim Min-soo. ]
Our team at Fact Check got to the bottom
of these brothers' secret
who dreamed of the perfect crime
while hiding behind their power.
[ Even if these unrepentant brothers
get punished by the law, ]
[ we are still left
with a problem we must solve. ]
[ Even at this moment,
dozens of people who were victimized ]
[ by the clinical trial are fighting
for their lives. ]
[ I hope they and their families
will be able to smile again soon. ]
[ After a certain show was broadcast, ]
[ over 100,000 people signed
a nation-wide petition asking for ]
[ a thorough investigation
of Ido Pharmaceuticals. ]
- [ The police who have been... ]
- [ Today, the prosecution ]
[ carried out a search and seizure
of Ido Pharmaceuticals. ]
[ The black cartel between a pharmaceutical
company and the KFDA was revealed, ]
[ which led to the arrest
of the current director of KFDA. ]
[ As unfavorable factors continue
to be revealed, ]
[ Ido Pharmaceutical's stock prices
collapsed and have become worthless. ]
I don't know how to repay you.
Thanks to you,
my Jong-dae will rest in peace.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
No, ma'am.
I'm just glad we found the culprit now.
You're here, detective.
Director Kang Moo-young was just here too.
That Pony is so nosy.
So, is he doing better?
I thought my precious son might die
like this without proper treatment.
Thanks to you two, he'll be okay.
Thank you so much.
Things will be harder from now on.
We can't underestimate
the people of Ido Pharmaceuticals.
And...
Although it's not much, please use it
for medical and legal expenses.
Thank you.
10, 100, 1,000... 100,000?
[ Fact Check ]
Are you laughing right now?
[ Bureau Chief Myung Gi-chul ]
So the TRP was 3.1 percent?
It is far less than the 4.5 percent
which you promised.
I wouldn't say "far less".
If we raised it about this much in a week,
I think we did quite well.
And we still have three weeks left.
More importantly, we are now sponsored
by Ido Pharmaceuticals' competitors.
That's why I let you off the hook
for last week with only a written apology.
You can go now.
Goodness, when was the last time
we had this many sponsors?
My gosh.
Are you sleeping?
- I wasn't sleeping.
- You've got to be kidding me.
[ Written Apology ]
[ Suspension Termination Notice
Jin Gang-ho ]
If not for the suspension,
you could've been promoted.
"Killing two birds with one stone."
You've solved two cases at once.
Well, we got the guy
without using tools this time.
That's what matters.
What? Why are you making that noise?
I know you're happy too.
Oh, right. Should we
go get some drinks to celebrate?
Gosh, no.
I don't want to do that with you.
Why not? What are you going to do then?
I have somewhere to go.
Mr. Detective, it's been a while.
I thought you wouldn't come back now.
Why?
Are you already getting an urge?
It has been ten years already.
You wouldn't believe me
even if I say that I won't.
Next time, wear dress shoes.
I'll shine them for you.
Ten years already?
It's only been ten years.
Think about the people who died.
So,
sit right there and don't do a thing.
Don't go anywhere.
Get home safely.
[ Inmate 6001, Jang Min-gi.
Come out for transport. ]
[ Emergency Transport, Ministry of Justice ]
Jang Min-gi.
Hey. Jang Min-gi.
[ Emergency Transport ]
[ Breaking news.
A dump truck crashed into a bus ]
[ that was transporting prisoners
at the intersection near Sanok Station. ]
[ Two of the prisoners
have escaped from the crash. ]
[ A prisoner that's on the run
is accused of murdering four women. ]
- Excuse me. Sorry.
[ - His name is Jang Min-gi, ]
[ the serial killer
who was arrested in 2013. ]
[ And Kang Soo is known as the second
most powerful member of a gang. ]
[ - Their escape is leaving people in fear. ]
- A serial killer escaped?
That jerk, Jang Min-gi.
He murdered a woman
as soon as he escaped?
[ TEAM BULLDOG: OFF-DUTY INVESTIGATION ]
It's him. That's the culprit's signature.
Butterfly.
[ I get that he's a killer. ]
[ But how can he kill right away? ]
[ I can feel it. This will be huge. ]
I'm here to collect the bowls.
I'm here to clean.
[ What are you plotting? ]
[ Don't cross the line.
Don't make me take over. ]
There's an accomplice?
"Tak Won"?
- He's the accomplice?
- Wrong.
[ I'm sure there had been
more killings somewhere. ]
It's a hidden crime.
Stop trying to look cool.
Can you say that I was right too?
It just doesn't feel right.