(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
(3 weeks ago)
Here.
Are you sure you want to stay at your current school?
I'd rather just take the bull by the horns...
than to try and adjust somewhere new.
It looks like you've mustered up your courage.
And for that, I'm grateful.
- Hey, Dad. - You're home.
Hey, guys. Gosh, it smells delicious.
My goodness, it's grilled fish, my favorite.
I'm starving.
Wash your hands first.
I'll scoop the rice for you.
Gosh, why can't you do a better job?
How is that you're always getting scolded by Mom?
That's just because your mom loves me way too much.
- Whatever. - Yes, he's right about that.
See?
Look at his face.
- Let's eat. I'm hungry. - Okay.
It's good.
Did anything special happen in school?
- School is always the same. - How was your day, honey?
I'm going on a business trip to China next Tuesday.
Really? Can we expect some good news?
I have a really good feeling about this one.
I guess he really might get the deal this time.
What are you going to get for me in China?
What do you want? What should I get for you?
All I need is you, Dad.
I'm impressed, Joon Young.
All I need is your mom.
I'm done.
Okay, go and get some rest.
(Move to trash)
(The album is empty.)
Hey, Ye Rim.
I called after I saw that the lights were on.
When did you come back?
Are you okay, Sun Woo?
I'm relieved that Joon Young is hanging in there.
I think it's finally over now.
How about you? Have you been well, Ye Rim?
Mom.
(Final episode)
Do you want some pocket money?
Sure. Why not?
- Who are you meeting? - That's a secret.
Don't be late. Come home for dinner.
Here.
I'll call if I'm late.
This one will be easier for you to understand.
There are lots of drawings.
Are you looking down on me?
You skipped a lot of classes.
You'll have to study hard to catch up with the others.
What did you get?
("Strategies to Enter College")
How annoying.
I helped you pick out that book, so treat me to some ice cream.
Hello.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Hi.
Dr. Ji.
I heard you came back.
Have you been well? Is Hae Kang also doing well?
Yes, of course. I hope you and your son are also doing well.
- Bye then. - Hey, wait.
Do you still find me uncomfortable?
That's nonsense.
The kids made up. Why would I be uncomfortable?
If you were offended by what happened last time,
let me apologize.
Thank you.
Let's let bygones be bygones,
and act like how we used to, okay?
Bye now.
Hello, ma'am.
Should I congratulate you...
or commend you?
Regardless,
I like your unbending spirit.
If you're referring to my return, you're being way too kind.
All I did was decide to stay because that's what my son wanted.
No need to be modest.
I know who played the biggest part in Chairman Yeo's family...
leaving Gosan.
I'm sure all the women in this town are being very careful...
not to upset you.
Still, wouldn't it have been better to leave it alone...
and let it follow its natural course?
Whatever the relationship, people are bound to get hurt...
if they are too passionate about it.
I hope that doesn't happen again.
I'm sure you've experienced it enough.
What do you think? Do you like it?
I'll pick them out next time.
You don't like it?
Do you know who's the worst dresser in school?
- Who? - The kid whose mom shops for him.
You punk. You're all grown up, is that it?
- I'll return them. - It's okay.
These aren't so bad.
Fine. I'll just give you my credit card next time.
I want to go back to the academy starting next week.
You don't have to push yourself.
You can rest as long as you want.
I think it'll be better than being bored.
Some kids are preparing for college already.
Okay.
I'll register you.
Aren't you leaving?
Joon Young.
Look.
(No Eul)
What are you up to?
Sorry.
Good night.
- Another. - Okay.
How have you been?
Have you had dinner?
Why haven't you called?
Why aren't you getting a place?
How long do you plan to stay here like this?
Did you come to nag?
At this hour?
You're mad for way too long...
just because I said no once.
So?
I'm annoyed...
- that you gave up already. - And?
I was worried that you may be sick.
Is that all?
And I missed you.
I've missed you too.
- I'm sorry. - You don't have to say anything.
Let's just stay like this for a little while.
Joon Young.
Are you ready?
(1 week ago)
My son looks so handsome.
Your lipstick is too dark.
Really?
Should I wear something more neutral?
No. You look pretty.
- Congrats on your remarriage. - Congratulations.
Congrats.
You're embarrassing me.
Why did you plan this? I said let's not make a big deal out of it.
What?
Next is a banquet.
But my sweetie's too embarrassed, so we'll pass.
It's an amazing feat...
to overcome that hardship together and forgive each other.
You deserve to be congratulated.
So enjoy it, Ye Rim.
Thank you.
Thank you...
everyone.
Congrats on your return too.
I'm glad.
All that remains is for your lives to get easier.
Thanks for your concern everyone.
We'll be well, if not for any reason other than to make it up to you.
Joon Young agreed as well.
Let me know if I can help in any way.
You too, okay?
Excuse me for a minute.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
It's okay. It'll all be fine.
Have you heard from Tae Oh?
No, not at all.
I'm sure he left Gosan.
He wouldn't show up again.
True. No one has seen him.
What's the matter?
No. It's nothing.
The food here is great.
Order as much as you want.
Come on. Stop joking.
- Isn't this place delicious? - It is.
The three of us should get together soon.
All right. I'll invite you guys to my place soon.
That sounds good.
Joon Young, see you soon.
- Bye. - Bye.
The single lady is leaving first. Bye.
- Take care. - Bye.
Bye.
Should the rest of us go for another round?
The guests should know to leave now.
You two should enjoy some time on your own.
I had fun today.
- Let's meet again soon. - Okay.
Take care. You too, Joon Young.
Take care.
Get in. I'll drive you home.
Our place is close. We'll walk home.
See you next time, Dr. Kim.
Okay, then.
See you next time, Joon Young.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Shall we get going too? - Yes.
The air's so fresh.
- Isn't it? - Yes.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Let's go.
Tonight's dinner was so nice. Thank you.
I never imagined I'd be able to walk with you like this again.
I thought it would just end there.
The weather's nice today.
Without you,
I would've lived a broken life.
You're my savior.
You saved me.
I won't ever let go of these hands again.
Don't make it a huge deal. No one saved anyone.
One is responsible for saving their own life.
I only realized...
after you disappeared too.
I found out I love you a lot.
That's why I want to try it.
They say you regret it whether you get married or not.
Since I already did it once, why not try it twice?
My wife is so cool.
I think Dr. Kim is a good guy.
It looks like he's interested in Sun Woo.
Actually, I think I saw Tae Oh recently.
What?
It was only in passing so I'm not sure.
That's why I thought it'd be better for them to not know...
than to get worried about it.
Perhaps I should've told them.
I'm not sure.
What is it?
It's nothing. Let's hurry and go inside.
- Sleep tight, Joon Young. - I will.
I'm late, I'm late. I'm so late.
- Honey! - Yes?
Coffee. Take your coffee.
- Thank you. - It's hot, so be careful.
I'll be back.
- Drive safe. - Okay.
Joon Young.
Hello.
I'll get going.
Why did you come? I can walk home.
Why did No Eul leave?
I was going to buy you guys some tteokbokki.
It's okay.
What is it?
What?
Gosh.
You should let me drive you for the next little while.
I don't think you have to worry anymore.
I'm just bored staying at home all day.
All right.
I have to go to the washroom.
Mom.
Yes?
Don't ever call him.
Don't try to find out where he is or what's going on with him.
Don't get swayed by this and just ignore him.
If he does this again, just report him to the cops.
A vow renewal?
We don't need to do that.
Wouldn't it be bothersome for you?
My gosh, I had absolutely nothing back then,
but I rushed things because I didn't want to lose you.
We didn't even get to have a proper wedding.
I bought this dress at the department store...
on a three-month installment plan. I bet it's still here somewhere.
Do you know I bought this veil from an online shopping mall?
That's exactly my point. Let's do another photoshoot.
I know you look pretty in anything,
but I've always wanted to get you a proper wedding dress.
- Should we do that? - Let's do it before it's too late.
It's not even that big of a deal.
We could've done it earlier. I don't understand why we didn't.
Then I'll have to get some skin care before we do the shoot.
You don't need to get skin care.
While we're on the subject, let's do a photoshoot every 10 years.
Joon Young is getting older every year.
So let's take photos...
of how we age together.
We should keep a record.
Every moment with you is precious.
Even after Joon Young gets married...
- and has children? - Of course.
I bet you'll be beautiful even when you're a grandma.
- What? - I guess...
I did a really good job of turning you into fine a man.
Are you serious?
Come here. How dare you treat your husband this way?
Sun Woo, we really enjoyed the meal.
I ate so much.
Why did you cook so much?
I didn't know I'd end up cooking this much.
Thank you for enjoying the food.
It's because she's bored all day.
She even asked if we should make our own kimchi.
Can you believe that?
I think I like doing housework.
Maybe I should just get a new job.
I should quickly make you work so you don't get another job.
Yes, please.
I'll be off now.
- Bye, Joon Young. - Goodnight, Joon Young.
Let's drink.
Okay, sure.
I'm really glad to see how bright he's become.
I think he has a girlfriend.
Really? That's so cute.
You must feel a bit sad.
I'm just glad he's doing okay.
I hope things stay this way.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
He has you as a mother, so there's nothing to worry about.
You just need to make sure you stay strong.
Yes, of course.
I actually have something to tell you, Sun Woo.
Je Hyuk told me that he thinks he saw Tae Oh a few days ago.
Where?
At the bar Je Hyuk usually goes to near his office.
He wasn't completely sure when he told me,
but I thought you should know.
Tae Oh must be drinking every day.
Do you think he might end up ruining his life...
just like how his father did before he passed away?
Do you think he went there on purpose?
He used to go there often as well. That's probably why he was there.
He wouldn't have gone there to start a fight with Je Hyuk.
Yes, you're right. Plus, it might not have been him.
What matters is that he isn't in Gosan.
- Right? - Right.
Hey, don't let it bother you.
I'm sure he'll get by on his own.
But of course, it might take some time.
I hope so.
I really hope he gets to his senses and finally lives a decent life...
so that we'll never have to see each other again.
Trust me. You don't need to worry.
Hey, I need to go now.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, bye.
- Did you have fun? - Yes.
- Who was that? - A friend from college.
We weren't even that close, but he suddenly called me.
- Aren't you going to bed? - I'll sleep after I read a little.
Would you also like a glass?
Sure.
What are you reading?
Honey.
Why aren't you in bed?
I thought I'd be okay.
It's all in the past.
And I know you'll never cheat on me again.
I do, but...
But the truth is,
I'm not okay.
It won't get better.
I keep suspecting you.
I'm nervous.
I try not to, but I keep thinking about it.
I just can't forgive you.
I wish I could hate you instead.
Because I love you... Because I know I love you...
it kills me inside even more.
What if I keep doing this?
What if I can't forgive you,
can't let it go,
and keep tormenting you like this?
I said I'm fine.
You won't go out, right?
No. Don't worry. Just go.
If you want to hang out with a friend,
bring them over.
Stop worrying about me. Worry about yourself.
Are you going to be unemployed forever?
Don't worry and start working here again.
We left your office empty all along.
Stop making the director feel so anxious.
Thank you.
By the way, about Tae Oh...
I don't think he left for good.
Remember Woo Ho Sang?
My high school friend you met last time.
He told me he saw Tae Oh pretty recently.
- Where? - In Gosan.
He looked all haggard...
and was fighting a street bar owner for not having paid properly.
My friend felt bad for him, so he offered to pay instead.
But once he looked back, he was already gone.
When was that?
About a week ago.
Why don't you look for him?
I'm worried he might get himself in trouble.
Why should I? He's probably thinking clearer now.
Mom?
- Are you home? - Yes.
Is everything okay?
It is.
When are you coming home?
I'll stop by the grocery and head home.
Okay.
Joon Young. I'm home.
Joon Young?
(Son)
I'm taking Joon Young.
(Tae Oh)
The person you have reached is not available.
Tae Oh?
Sun Woo.
I'm sorry.
Did you take Joon Young?
Yes.
He's with me.
Where are you?
I missed Joon Young.
I wanted to be with him, that's why.
That was all, Sun Woo.
I'm sorry.
I know. I understand.
He's okay, right?
Everything's okay, right?
I'll go to you.
Let's talk in person, okay?
Should we eat together?
Let's do that. Let's all eat together.
The three of us, with Joon Young. And we can talk.
Tae Oh.
Are you there?
Hello?
Will you...
really come see me?
Of course.
Definitely.
I'm sure Joon Young would like that too.
He's...
with you, right?
I'll ask him.
Can you put him on the phone?
Hello?
Tae Oh?
Tae Oh!
When I was your age,
my dad left home.
He never came back.
Not until he died.
I didn't want you to turn out like me.
I wanted to keep you by my side.
Because if we are apart,
you'd think that I abandoned you.
I just couldn't do that...
because I never abandoned you. Not even for a moment.
That's all I wanted, Joon Young.
Are you okay?
He asked me to stay with him just for a little while.
He wasn't sure what he'd do if he was by himself.
That's why I came with him.
There was something I had to tell him,
Sun Woo.
I didn't mean any harm.
Please don't misunderstand.
Get in.
Mom.
We should go eat.
We said we would, right?
Did you drink?
Yes. A little.
Enjoy your meal.
Go ahead.
Let's eat, Joon Young.
Okay.
How have you been doing?
I'm sorry.
I saw you and Joon Young...
eating here...
a few days ago.
I should've been there too.
I should've been the one sitting next to you.
I should've been with...
my family and my friends.
What's the point of saying that now?
You're the one who ruined it all.
Joon Young.
Why did you suggest to come here?
Now I only feel more disgusted.
I think you should give Dad some time to get himself organized.
That's the only way to start over again.
I mean that for all three of us.
Yes.
Let's start over.
Let's forget about all the mistakes we made so far.
I'll forgive you, so you should forgive me too.
- What? - Let's do it for Joon Young.
Let's do our best as Joon Young's parents.
It'll be hard at first,
but he'll become stable if we all try hard.
We can go back to how it used to be.
- No. - We'll become a family again.
You know it can't happen.
I even wrote a new script.
I think I could even get someone to invest.
If you don't what me to do that,
I'll stop writing scripts and get a different job.
Let's yield for each other so we can have a better future.
Stop. Stop it.
It's over, Tae Oh.
We're done.
Ever since we first met,
you were my everything.
But I realized that way too late.
Can you please take me back, Sun Woo?
I know you also want that. Isn't that why we're here?
Is that what this is? You're going to take him back?
No way.
No, that's not what this is.
You kept lingering around us instead of getting to your senses.
And I figured you needed to stop living such an unstable life.
So I'm giving you a chance to finally settle things...
in front of Joon Young.
But you're even going to ruin this, too?
Tae Oh, you're unbelievable.
Is this really the best you can do?
I have absolutely nothing left. I lost everything.
Please give me one more chance.
Isn't that what families do?
If you're going to keep doing this, just go and kill yourself.
I'll help you financially until you settle down.
I'm not here to beg you for money.
Don't make me look more pitiful.
This might be your last time seeing Joon Young.
Is this really how you want to end it?
You need to stop living so shamelessly...
for Joon Young's sake.
That's the last thing you can do...
for Joon Young.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go already.
Say goodbye to your dad.
Joon Young.
Don't ever turn out like me.
The most precious person in the world...
is the person that stands by your side.
But if you forget that,
you'll end up making a fool of yourself just like me.
If you forget...
who cares and loves you the most,
you'll end up losing everything.
Don't ever forget that, okay?
Just forget about me.
I won't ever show up again.
This is really...
the end.
If you're done, we'll go now.
Dad!
The person who tore my heart into pieces.
The enemy I killed.
My other half whom I utterly resented...
and also loved from the bottom of my heart.
He was both my foe and comrade.
He was both my best friend and archenemy.
My husband.
What choice...
should I have made?
Did I even have a choice?
Was there at least one opportunity...
to undo the wrong?
Joon Young!
Everything I had been clinging onto...
were worthless.
By the time I realized it,
it was too late.
I lost...
what was most important to me.
(1 year later)
Thank you.
- Please tell him I was here... - I will.
- Okay. Thank you. - Sure.
(In front of the house)
Any word...
on Joon Young yet?
Dr. Ji, your patient is here.
- What? - Your patient.
Okay.
Long time no chat.
How have you been?
Have you not heard from Joon Young yet?
I'm getting pretty settled down now.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I have more regulars now. - How have you been?
- Good. - What would you like?
Do you want a cake?
No. I was just looking.
Let's go home.
Okay, let's. I'm hungry.
I don't regret my decision.
(Managing an Art Gallery)
To be more honest,
I'm trying not to regret it.
Since your life is a result of your decisions.
Pick up your prescription on your way out.
I hope you'll be more at peace...
by the time you get this email.
She's almost ready.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Would you bring me her chart? - Yes, doctor.
Let's go.
I have a seminar at a school on the fourth.
Would you check how many appointments I have?
Okay.
You have two. Choi Soo Kyung and Jung Nam Shik.
Pull up their appointments to before the seminar.
Yes, doctor.
- Send in the next patient. - Okay.
It's been a while, Dr. Ji.
Oh my gosh.
You look much better.
Appearances don't tell the whole story,
but I was better for a while.
But...
I realized I can't do it alone just because I try hard.
The moment you relax, you get sucker-punched by life.
Life is continuous anxiety.
Don't you agree?
I do.
Have a nice day.
I have a patient waiting for me.
It's a brief life that you live for yourself.
People aren't interested in other people's misery.
You've regretted and blamed yourself enough.
Is Ha Dong Shik here yet?
Mr. Ha Dong Shik?
I hope you've forgiven everything by now.
Above all else... Yourself.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(Runaway Children Counseling Center)
(Street Teen Counseling)
No matter how hard I try,
I don't think I could ever say the word "forgive".
(Back into the Arms of Your Loving Family)
(We will all work hard to reunite you with your son)
Because I learned...
that to forgive someone...
was as arrogant as judging someone.
I simply...
endure the time allotted to me, and stay where I belong...
waiting for my son who will return someday.
Holding onto that uncertain hope.
Enduring that anxiety.
Setting aside my arrogance...
of thinking that I set the rules, judge, and take responsibility,
is probably the best I can do.
Cutting out your spouse with whom you've shared...
most of your life...
is like cutting away a part of your body.
And that pain continues to haunt both people.
When it comes to married couples,
there are no assailants...
nor completely innocent victims. Such things can't be established.
While dwelling on the painful mistakes we made...
or...
while enduring each day without letting the pain dominate us...
Perhaps...
a moment of redemption might come.
The moment I can finally forgive myself.
You're here.
(A World of Married Couple)
Subtitle by VIU
Resynced by IG @mad.yudi.subs
(A World of Married Couple)
Subtitle by VIU
Resynced by IG @mad.yudi.subs
(Thank you for watching A World of Married Couple.)