It goes all the way back to my father.
I got a call when I was in the army.
That my father had taken his own life.
After being tormented by false accusations that...
he had betrayed his colleagues,
taking the lead in the destruction of the labor union,
and acting as the informant on the company's side.
He sued the company...
for unfair labor practice.
And we stopped that, didn't we?
Yes, the prosecution worked things out...
and laid the dissolution of the labor union...
and the layoffs to his charge.
Because of that, the executives of the dissolved union labor...
and the employees who had been laid off...
all ended up suing him.
So all the charges on the company were dismissed,
and he was the one charged for illegal destruction...
of the labor union.
He committed suicide sometime after,
and we just confirmed that...
he was Han Jae Hyun's father.
It was the most lonely funeral.
No one came.
(1996)
It was as if...
my father had been abandoned.
Why he took his own life,
both Mom and I...
had no idea at all.
Until we found...
all the complaints issued against him in his bag.
Those who didn't attend the funeral...
were named in the complaints.
They blamed him for the broken union.
They blamed him for their lost jobs.
They were sure he embezzled from the company...
and demanded there should be a thorough investigation.
The path my father had taken his whole life,
the path that I was following,
disgusted me.
How I should live and what I should live for.
That's when I made up my mind.
How could we only realize that now?
For fear that our company would be connected to his death,
we made it look like he'd resigned...
and deleted all his files.
When we ran Mr. Han Jae Hyun's identity,
nothing showed up.
I apologize, sir.
And Jae Hyun.
Since when did he know?
Did he know when he approached Seo Kyung?
I don't believe so.
According to IT,
Mr. Han first accessed...
the files on the labor union five years ago.
But five years ago,
a union member called Kwon Hyuk Soo killed himself.
The old man's son?
His death reminded me of my father.
What began with a belief...
turned into foolish naivete,
and the colleagues' resentment and hatred...
sent him to his death.
It was the same.
That's when I started to search for the truth...
and found out that Chairman Jang was behind...
both the deaths.
The days I'd spent as his loyal hound...
became too much to handle.
That is why...
I didn't turn down the four-year stint in prison.
It must've hurt so much.
Being alone for so long.
While I was behind bars,
I thought a lot about my father.
The resentment and fury...
I felt after my father had died...
was actually my guilt and yearning for him.
As time went by,
I felt more guilty...
and missed him even more.
Dad...
Dad.
It's nothing.
Why can't you drink it?
It's delicious.
Jae Hyun.
Your father...
will miss you a lot too.
Just like him,
you're warmhearted and sweet.
You may have lost out,
but you always sided with the weak.
I also think he'll be very curious about you.
About how you will live...
from now on.
And what you will live for.
(Noodles in Anchovy Broth)
We are so very connected in a twisted way.
(Fall of 1995)
Excuse me.
Did the family here move away?
I haven't seen anyone leave in a while.
I don't know if they moved.
FM Music City's last song of the day...
is from Light and Salt.
"Do Not Leave My Side".
Jae Hyun.
Hey.
You're out on break?
Did Ji Su ever come by?
Would she come here?
You said she left on purpose.
But still. Just in case.
She's not at home or on campus.
Hi, this is Yoon Ji Su's boyfriend, Han Jae Hyun's pager.
If you're a guy, press 1 or 2.
And if you're a girl, just hang up. He's taken.
Besides, his girlfriend has a bad temper.
What are you doing? I'll scold you.
Hi, this is Yoon Ji Su's boyfriend, Han Jae Hyun's pager.
If you're a guy, press 1 or 2.
And if you're a girl, just hang up. He's taken.
Besides, his girlfriend has a bad temper.
What are you doing?
Hi, this is Yoon Ji Su's boyfriend, Han Jae Hyun's pager.
If you're a guy, press 1 or 2.
And if you're a girl, just hang up. He's taken.
Besides, his girlfriend has a bad temper.
Did you have to get discharged on such a hot day?
Did you have to come here when I told you not to?
I did out of pity.
You have no dad or girlfriend.
Did you look for Ji Su?
Thanks to you, I became great friends with the music majors.
They grew up wanting for nothing,
and they're so naive.
You got their pager numbers...
instead of looking for Ji Su.
You're talking about pagers?
Hey. The day after tomorrow, I get my new phone.
- Landline? - Cellphone.
You hold it like this and go...
"Ideal for Korea's geography".
- "Any"... - Stop talking nonsense and walk.
You should get one too now that you're a civilian.
I need to save money.
Don't you need to have money to save?
- I'll make some. - Doing what?
Anything.
Will you not take the bar exam?
I have no time for that.
I'll graduate fast and make money.
My mom's weaker and can't work much longer.
My dad's friends and colleagues...
are all gone.
What'll you do with money?
I have to repay a debt.
You're in debt? To whom?
- My dad. - Your dad?
Did your dad lend you the money for your tuition?
That's totally the American way.
My dad gave me the money he made by working day labor.
You just kept it?
I couldn't spend it.
So I want to return it.
With a million times in interest.
Do you miss your dad a lot?
I don't know.
Why don't you know?
I don't remember him.
When I was out on break,
I last saw him outside my house.
It was late and dark.
I don't remember him.
Why is it like this?
No one lived as tough as you have.
To Ji Su who will be somewhere.
I plan to turn into a different person.
If we meet again one day,
even if I'm very different,
please recognize me.
Will that be enough?
He'll come at us with all he's got.
According to Legal,
there's nothing he can find fault with.
They say the prosecutors are likely to go after him instead.
Did he not know that?
What is he up to?
I'm on the lookout as nothing has surfaced yet.
- The problem is... - What's the problem?
The ledgers we prepared...
in case of a search and seizure,
the prosecutors took without much of an issue.
It bothers me that they took the past 10 years' worth of...
electronic banking and shareholder meeting minute books.
From our subsidiaries too.
You should've doctored those in advance as well.
It's too much work...
to make sure that the subsidiaries' records correspond...
Why do you make so many excuses these days?
Everyone dies for a reason,
but you have too many reasons.
Mr. Han. The chairman wishes to see you.
I heard you had a busy day yesterday, but you're here early.
You came in early yourself.
I wish the sun would rise earlier each morning.
The joy of work is the joy of life.
What? Do you want me to get to the point?
But then,
I guess our current relationship isn't the kind...
where we exchange niceties.
How far do you want to take this?
Is there no point in asking when we both know the answer?
Do you want to replace me as Hyung Sung's chairman?
All the investigations...
has turned you very silent.
Let's start with the most recent issue.
A prosecutor you became very close with...
searched Seo Kyung's and my offices.
Is it because of Hyung Sung's slush fund and dividends?
They are not Hyung Sung's.
They are your slush fund and dividends.
That is your bare face.
I like this. I enjoy such conversations.
Your words are so pungent and pointed.
But...
do you know the law of exception between family?
The dividends and slush fund...
from your borrowed name accounts.
Even if it goes to me or your wife,
none of us can be held legally responsible.
Theft between family isn't legally theft.
The law of exception applies only to those related by blood.
That literally means people who share blood.
Unfortunately for you, sir, we are not related by blood.
As you never failed to stress,
you and I are from different blood.
You want to come after me and leave Seo Kyung out of this.
I didn't take a single cent.
Everything went to Seo Kyung.
You can tell the prosecutors it's my money,
but I'll say it's my daughter's.
You know that...
how much I loathe going to prison.
Even if I have to sell out my daughter,
I won't ever go to prison.
Yes.
I know very well that you will never let that happen.
It's the same for you too.
She's the mother of your son.
You can't let her get locked up in prison.
On top of that, the money she has...
will be your son, Jun Seo's money.
You know that, right?
I'll handle it myself.
Since we're talking about Jun Seo, let's talk about this.
I heard Yoon Ji Su's son physically harmed Jun Seo.
I was asked how I wanted to handle this.
The news reached me too.
What are you getting at?
Don't ask me questions...
you already know the answers to.
Jae Hyun.
Can you spare some of your time today?
I need to talk to you too.
Let's meet there tonight.
Where we started.
So tell me whom you lost.
I told you my story,
but why won't you share yours? It's not fair.
I definitely know what you have lost.
Do you remember it?
Your sanity.
Is that funny?
I like you very much.
Let's date.
What? Gosh.
That's the only ride I cannot go on.
I can ride the scariest rollercoaster here...
with my eyes open and my arms upraised high.
But I just can't ride that one.
Why is that?
My mother...
left me here.
I was only seven years old then.
I'm cruel because I take after my mother.
You must face it to break it.
Break what?
Your trauma.
Do you think I'm really scared of this ride?
It's just boring.
I'm not a little kid.
I'll make it so that the last person...
you saw on this ride isn't your mother.
If you were going to leave me,
you should have disappeared that day.
What is this?
In the end,
I'm being abandoned again.
Let's go back to that time.
I'll leave Se Hwi, be nice to you,
and love only you.
It's not that I wasn't capable of doing these.
I just chose not to.
It got a bit boring.
So I thought I wanted to give you a wake-up call.
I was looking for something fun and new.
But I don't like any of them. It's all boring.
I'm sorry,
but it will feel like we're putting together a broken glass window.
I should apologize to you.
I will never let you go.
A broken glass window? Why can't I piece it together?
Since I broke it, I'll put it together.
I can put it together...
flawlessly.
What are you doing, Ms. Yoon?
Ma'am.
I'll find a way.
Can you give me some time?
I didn't want to waste your talent,
so I might have been a bit rash.
What does "rash" mean?
Because I wanted something badly,
I ran, but I ended up falling.
Do we have to take some time to want something?
Right.
We should take our time to want something,
but once you want something, it's hard to stop.
I think I was that too.
I was rash.
I bragged to Yu Bin that you were going...
to teach me how to play the piano.
That's not your fault. It's mine.
It's natural for you to want to brag about it.
Trying to do this secretly was my mistake.
What will we do then?
I should open up my own piano academy.
(For Rent)
Don't let anyone see you. Hide here.
I'll bring some money.
Hello, ma'am.
Hello, Ms. Yoon.
Yu Bin's mother...
found out that you didn't graduate college.
You know that Yu Bin and Byeol are in the same class, right?
You gave Byeol a free lesson.
That caused trouble for your job here.
(Jae Hyun)
Then, does it mean you're unemployed?
No. I have a lot of private lessons.
Will that do?
What do you mean?
To make ends meet?
I should make it work.
I can make it work. I don't spend much money.
So losing my job at the academy won't be any problem for me.
Here. This is my personal card, not the corporate card.
The company can't track it. And it doesn't have a limit.
Are you testing me?
"Will you say no to this too?"
I want to help you.
I can't think of any ways to help you except for financially...
to make up for the past 25 years. It's torturing me too.
I didn't know that I lacked imaginations.
Then, you should improve on it.
Use that money to take lessons or go to an academy.
She hasn't changed.
Is it you, Hye Jung?
I didn't order anything.
Aren't you Ms. Yoon Ji Su?
Yes, I am.
My gosh, what's all that?
I see. Will a war break out tomorrow?
Gosh, is this a house or a supermarket?
Do you want to take some of it?
Where did you get all of this?
There's no way you'd buy this much food.
You're a cheapskate who buys rice by the bag.
Hey, did you get registered as someone in need?
Is this from a charity or something?
It's from Jae Hyun.
You're still meeting him?
Sit down. I'll cook you something delicious.
Forget it.
How can I eat here? It's too disturbing.
Let's eat out.
Shall we?
I thought you quit drinking. You haven't been here for a while.
I couldn't come because I'm busy trying to make a living.
I won't charge you. Just come.
Does your liquor fall from the sky?
I'm sure you use your cards to buy the liquor and ingredients.
How could I drink it for free?
Anyway, credit card statements scare me the most.
I hope the 25th of the month doesn't exist.
It could go like this. 23rd, 24th, and 26th.
Then, you won't get paid either.
I should change the date of my payment then.
Why aren't you drinking?
It's just because.
How will you break this awkwardness? Did you two fight?
We didn't fight.
Do you fight with your fingers?
- Fingers? - Fingers I can't hurt.
Be careful. She might be your middle finger.
In that case...
Don't do that.
My gosh. Don't smile at me. You look gorgeous.
This is why he can't give you up.
Thank you for everything, Young Woo.
And I'm sorry.
- Hello? - Hi.
This is the sanatorium.
I see. Hello.
By the way, I was wondering if you could come by today.
What is this about?
Mr. Yoon is asking for you.
Did something happen to him again?
No. Actually, he's doing better.
He's lucid.
I see.
Sir.
I heard you asked for me.
Do you want...
some fresh air?
Don't...
forgive me.
I'll be okay...
if you push me...
from this cliff now.
What are you talking about?
Ji Su didn't do anything wrong.
So...
you should punish me for everything.
I can't let my daughter...
be in any more pain.
The one who prosecuted...
your father for illegal labor acts...
was me.
(May 1995)
The summer that year...
That was the summer when my life had stopped.
When you ran away with Ji Su,
your father reported the management of Hyung Sung Group...
to the Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office...
for disbanding the labor union.
As soon as I heard about it,
I knew he was your father.
That time, I was utterly enraged against you and Ji Su.
And your father showed up in front of me.
And so did Chairman Jang San.
Chairman Jang asked me to quash...
your father's report against Hyung Sung Group.
But instead of doing so,
I made them prosecute your dad.
I used the evidence your father submitted...
to report Hyung Sung Group's crimes...
and framed your father for those crimes.
Your father was in despair.
Chairman Jang was happy.
And I was satisfied.
Chairman Jang...
promised to support me so I could become a politician.
I felt as if the deeper my rage for you and Ji Su became,
the bigger my reward became.
I told myself that I was livid,
but I was smiling.
And that summer, my life came to an end.
I had lost...
a house and a family to return to.
I lost my job and career.
I didn't know the meaning of the scale...
Lady Justice was holding in front of the courthouse.
And I had forgotten...
the warning of the sword which she held in the other hand.
That summer,
it only took a moment...
for me to lose everything.
Ever since then,
my clock stopped running.
Now,
my body wants to stop running as well.
I am truly sorry.
The crime I have committed against you...
is too grave and deep.
Please...
accept my apology.
Did something happen at the sanatorium?
You don't look good at all.
Jun Seo.
Do you want to go on a trip with me?
We can go camping, like last time,
or we can go night fishing.
Or we can go hiking.
There's a beach in Gangneung...
and other fun things to do.
There are more exciting things to do...
outside that small world in your hand,
so give it a thought.
Dad.
You're late.
You must have a lot of plans since it's your first leave.
Why are you out here?
And why are you smoking again?
I was just having a hard time falling asleep.
Let's go inside.
He left this so you can get something to eat before you go back.
I guess that's why he's working.
What kind of work is Dad doing?
He won't say,
but he always comes back with his hands all dirty,
so it can't be anything easy.
It looks like he gave me...
his whole daily pay.
(30 dollars)
How are things going?
Nothing special.
I played several parts, but I'm not getting any leads.
Why do you keep seeing me?
Obviously...
because I like you.
Me or my money?
What's up with you today?
Did something happen at home again?
You don't want me to get a divorce, do you?
That way you can toy with me for a while...
and then move on elsewhere.
You're right.
I don't want you to get a divorce.
Because I think you'd have a hard time.
I know you still love him a lot.
Your husband.
I'm sorry. I'm practicing this these days.
I have a lesson, so have the lunch box...
and fruit when Grandpa wakes up.
What if Grandpa gets mad?
He doesn't even remember me.
You'll be better off, then.
He doesn't get mad at strangers.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Hello.
Yes.
You should put on some weight.
You're so scrawny, just like your mother.
What grade are you in, again?
Eight grade, sir.
Right.
Do middle schoolers play with these?
I brought these for you because I thought you were younger.
I don't have anything else to give you.
It's okay, sir. I like these.
Is that so?
Then take this.
And this too.
And this.
Take this as well.
But this isn't for free.
Sorry?
I'm giving these for you to listen to your mother...
and always take her side.
Yes, sir.
Your mother has gone through so much,
so you need to make her happy...
by supporting her...
and taking her side.
The two of you need to live...
happily ever after...
for a long long time, okay?
Are you sure you won't regret it?
Quitting school.
Yes.
And you won't say why you got into that fight?
I'm sorry.
But Young Min,
you are in the worst situation...
when it comes to childcare.
That means I can win you back 99 percent...
if I file a lawsuit.
So you'd be better off telling me.
Why you got into that fight, and why you decided to drop out.
If it's a financial reason,
I have no other choice but to bring you back.
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
But I think I will like living with you as well.
(Caregiver)
- Yes, ma'am? - Ms. Yoon,
your father suddenly showed difficulty in breathing,
so he was taken to the ER.
His pneumonia symptoms worsened,
so he currently can not breathe on his own.
(Intensive Care Unit)
Ji Su.
I got a call from Hye Jung. She told me to hurry ahead.
I see.
What's going on?
He had pneumonia, and it worsened.
Were you surprised to get my call?
Yes, a bit.
We don't know how long your mom will have to stay at the hospital,
so she said you can spend the night at my place...
and come to the hospital tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Oh, and my husband may look a bit threatening,
but he isn't a bad guy, so don't worry and eat with him.
Then, you can watch TV...
or study if you'd like to.
But is Grandpa okay?
Hey.
Your grandpa is a strong man.
You may not know it,
but he used to be one of the top three...
strongest men in the country.
He looked skinny.
Not strong like a wrestler,
but like taking in bad guys and so.
That power.
Okay.
(Dong Jin)
What?
What do you say we go to Young Woo's bar tonight?
I landed some extra cash.
Goodness, you.
This is not the time for that.
- Yes, Dong Jin. - Aren't you going to the hospital?
- Hospital? - I knew it.
Of course, Ji Su didn't tell you.
What are you talking about?
Ji Su's father is in the ICU right now.
(Intensive Care Unit)
Are you Mr. Yoon Hyung Gu's guardian?
Do you have any other family members heading over?
Not anymore.
He does have a young grandchild, though.
I think you should come in and spend your final moments.
Doesn't he need to have the ventilator on?
He signed the papers saying he will forego...
any life-sustaining treatment.
I'm sorry, Ji Su.
If you're really sorry, then you need to get back up.
I never...
gave you a proper hug.
No, it's okay.
I will take...
all the wicked things I have done...
and the burden...
I had given you with me,
so that...
you will only be left with the good things.
Make sure...
to live happily, Ji Su.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
Dad.
Make sure to tell Mom and Ji Young...
that I'm sorry.
Okay?
Dad?
Dad!
I don't want...
anyone to leave me anymore.
(When My Love Blooms)
The one your father hated the most was me.
I couldn't dare say it to you,
so I'm leaving this letter.
The chief prosecutor is who?
The people may be dead, but the facts live on.
I really don't want anyone to leave me anymore, but...
It's all right.
Everything will be all right now.