- What's wrong? - What's going on?
- Call the conductor. - What's that sound?
- Why is the light off? - What's going on?
- Goodness. - I can't be late.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will be stopping momentarily due to a problem with the generator.
The train will start again as soon as we finish maintenance.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
It's okay.
It's raining. I need to go find my daughter.
My daughter will be cold out in the rain.
Ji Young!
Honey!
We're going to the department store to fix the clock today.
Should we get the strawberry cake there?
Dad told me to come to his office right away.
I should still hurry up and go. I'm sorry.
(Halt)
Ji Su.
Excuse me.
We might be late.
What do I do...
No.
I need to go.
Please open this door!
I...
I was too late.
I told them I would be early.
What will happen to Mom?
Please open this door.
Ji Su.
Ji Su?
I don't remember.
I remember everything...
that happened that day,
but I can't recall...
the last moment I saw Mom and Ji Young,
no matter how hard I try.
Ji Su...
Ji Su!
Ji Su.
(Episode 10)
I hoped it was the emergency room.
I prayed it was the emergency room.
That they were somehow alive.
I prayed and prayed.
We're going to the department store to fix the clock today.
Should we get the strawberry cake there?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
We're going to the department store to fix the clock today.
Should we get the strawberry cake there?
Whatever you want.
Get back early. Your dad will get mad again.
Yes, ma'am.
That brat. Look at her leaving without a proper goodbye.
I barely remember your face now!
Mom.
Ji Young.
Ji Young!
Mom!
Mom! Ji Young! Yoon Ji Young!
Mom! Look over here!
Mom, I'm... Will you look over just once?
Ji Young!
Look at me just once.
Just once.
Show me your face just one time.
Please, let me see you.
It's always the same dream.
However hard I scream,
Mom and Ji Young never look at me.
I should've looked at them more often.
She said she could barely remember my face.
I should've looked at them every day...
and told them that I loved them.
I have changed so much.
What if they don't recognize me?
I miss them so, so much.
What if I never see them again?
That's what I always think.
How could they not recognize you?
They'll be watching you every day.
I bet they noticed your white hair too.
"Ji Su has white hair now." That's what she'll say.
Your mother and sister...
will laugh and worry together,
and then discuss what you should do.
I bet they'll scold me for...
worrying about the afterlife when I have enough to worry about.
Very much.
It's possible that...
I haven't yet taken...
a single step away from what happened that day.
Do you have to?
That day might not be something you must...
overcome or leave behind,
or get away from.
A deep wound also means a deep longing.
You hurt because you miss them,
and miss them more because you hurt.
It's not about how...
you get through it but how you accept it.
If you keep facing yourself and looking inward,
then one day, your mother and sister's face...
will come back to you.
Was it like that for you?
In Dong Jin's words, you bet.
I put on a brave face, but I'm a long way off.
I'm about halfway there, I guess?
My daughter. Help me find my daughter.
- Please. - Get off me.
Please help me find my daughter.
Ji Young.
Help me find her.
Please, doctor. My daughter.
My daughter and wife should be here.
- What? - Find her for me.
- Please. - Did they call to say they're here?
They should be here.
They were hurt. They'll be in bed with injuries.
Sorry.
Please, help me find my daughter.
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
Hey!
- What will you do? - Let go.
I just heard them talk. I said I'm not sure!
I don't care. I'll kill them all.
- Han Jun Seo! - Jun Seo!
I said I didn't like you from the start!
I want you to die! Just die already!
What now? What's this about? What did I do wrong?
I just hate everything!
I hate you and your darn mom!
Why are you cursing my mom? Why?
Because all this is your mom's fault!
I was waiting for you.
You both came at the same time.
Jun Seo.
Young Min.
Young Min hit Jun Seo again.
Didn't I tell you last time that we should've taken full measures?
A thief becomes a robber.
Old proverbs are never wrong.
Do your bruises hurt?
Do they?
What happened?
Young Min.
Look at Mom.
Will you really not tell?
Shall we let it go again?
Then I can't help you this time.
I said last time that...
this would never happen again.
Are you...
angry with me?
Neither of them will say what it was about.
Rather than that, the important fact is that...
Young Min hit Jun Seo first.
Isn't the reason more important than who started the fight?
Ms. Kim.
Were there any students with them or who saw the fight?
Speak up.
I was told you were there.
If you don't talk,
you'll be called to the School Violence Committee,
and it'll go on your record.
Who hit whom first?
Jun...
I mean, Young Min lashed out first.
There must be a reason.
Because Young Min's mom and Jun Seo's dad...
are up to no good.
Young Min.
Mom heard everything.
I know why you refused to see me.
It really...
breaks my heart.
Mine too.
Is it true what Jun Seo said?
Young Min.
I don't know what you'll think of it.
It might make you angrier,
or it might make you feel better, I don't know.
But I'll tell you what happened long ago.
Jun Seo's dad...
was Mom's first love.
The two people...
that got along the worst were left with each other.
Dad!
Where are you going?
They're gone.
They're really gone.
She hasn't gone!
Why has Ji Young gone?
If you say that once more,
I will kill you myself!
Why are you here?
Will you not come back to university?
I think I'll quit.
I get why,
but there's no need to quit.
Take some time off, and when you're ready...
My dad was fired.
For abusing his authority and taking bribes.
And he admitted to everything when he was questioned.
It's as if...
my dad is slowly dying instead of living.
The department store is a five-minute walk from my house.
I think every day that my dad could die.
That's why I want to leave this place.
What about Jae Hyun?
Thanks to those moments that were as pretty as flowers,
I think...
I can go on.
Sorry and thank you.
Jae Hyun.
(To Jae Hyun)
There you are.
Yoon Ji Su.
(To Jae Hyun)
(Thanks to those moments that were as pretty as flowers,)
(I think I can go on. Sorry and thank you. Jae Hyun.)
She isn't anywhere.
She moved away.
She quit university too.
Young Woo.
Did she tell you anything?
No.
What about her friend?
Ji Su's closest friend who studies engineering.
Hye Jung?
Do you think she's in the dark too?
If I were her, even I wouldn't want to see anyone.
I do feel really bad for her,
but she should fight.
Why did she disappear on her own?
The brat.
I will keep looking...
until I must return to my base.
Once I go back,
can you guys keep looking?
It'll be so hard on her and she's on her own.
If something bad were to happen...
I can't survive that.
I was physically healthy and mentally stable,
but there was nothing I could do for her.
The woman I loved with all my heart was crumbling.
But the only thing I could do was watching her crumble from afar.
So throughout my life,
it had broken my heart and tortured me.
Do you understand where I'm coming from?
But I always wished that she would lead a good life.
And by chance, we met again.
She was struggling just like before.
So it felt like I was transported back to the past.
It had pained me.
But you have Mom, Dad.
I had...
no choice but to leave.
After that day,
I felt as if...
I didn't deserve...
to be happy...
from loving someone or being loved by someone.
You're so little,
but I gave you such a big burden to carry.
I'm sorry, Young Min.
- Yes? - Hello.
I'm calling from the sanatorium.
Is this Mr. Han Jae Hyun?
Yes, it is. What is this about?
Mr. Yoon Hyung Gu's daughter isn't answering her phone.
The patient had left the sanatorium and hasn't come back.
His mother isn't like the other mothers.
Other moms are willing to cover up anything for their children...
and trying to make a good impression.
But she isn't interested in doing so to the point...
that it bothers me.
I'd expect that from her.
But for now, I did make this...
into Young Min's fault, not Jun Seo's.
But I'm a bit worried about...
how Young Min and his mother will handle this.
Their claim won't do anything. They don't have any proof.
That's true.
By the way, if a student violates the school policy...
and causes serious trouble,
can't you expel the student with your authority as the principal?
Yes, I can do that.
Even if the School Violence Committee is held,
expelling him would be the highest degree of punishment.
And they don't make such decisions to middle school students.
I'm concerned that people might question it.
So what? I'm sure the gossip won't last long.
Do you think people are interested in other people's lives?
You're right. They are not.
Then, I'll call you again as we proceed further.
Sure.
(Three-way Supermarket)
You didn't answer your phone.
It's been off.
The sanatorium called me.
Your father left but didn't come back.
Do you know a place he might go?
It's raining. He probably went there.
What are you doing here again? You're breaking my heart.
What if something really happens to you?
(Emergency Center)
Ji Su.
Isn't it a relief...
that we found your mom and Ji Young?
I heard a lot of families couldn't even find the bodies.
We should be grateful.
But still,
I...
miss them a lot.
Dad.
Do you have a minute?
You said you were curious...
about why I left.
It wasn't your fault.
And I knew it too well.
But I was scared that I might resent you for it.
If I weren't leaving to see you,
I would have turned back to see them that day.
And Mom and Ji Young wouldn't even have been at the department store.
We would have been together and spent a peaceful evening.
Resenting myself wouldn't probably have been enough.
I would have found someone else to blame.
And that would have been you.
I thought that after resenting you,
I might even end up hating you.
I thought we might hurt each other...
and that would be more painful.
But this time, Young Min got hurt.
Of course, it's not your fault again.
But I'm confused.
It makes me wonder...
if my talk with him wasn't enough after the last incident.
I understand that a mother can have a big influence,
but a son would be scared of his dad.
When it crosses my mind,
I stop myself.
I think to myself that...
I'm blaming you again like a fool...
and I'm making the same mistake...
now and 25 years ago.
Jae Hyun,
the kids are emotionally and physically hurt.
They need time to heal.
Perhaps, we do too.
Okay.
You might be right.
(Homeroom Teacher)
Yes.
Yes. Okay. I see.
The School Violence Committee will be held.
Mom.
Are you still sorry?
Yes.
Then,
can you let me do what I want?
Yes.
Sir,
you cannot change your mind and must proceed...
even if he comes to you and tries to talk you out of it.
Okay.
- Will the committee be held? - Do you think it shouldn't be?
He attacked my son twice.
I won't let it slide this time.
What will you do?
I will publicly humiliate him and get him expelled from school.
But I hit him too.
Is what you told me yesterday the whole story?
About what?
Did he really just hit you? Without any reason?
There was a reason.
He said I looked down on him and bullied him.
Forget it then. Have your meal.
You can tell your side when the committee is held.
Why did you come now?
Young Min has something to tell you.
Young Min.
I will listen to both sides with impartiality.
If I listen to one side of the story and make a decision,
it will be partial.
I know that you will only believe Jun Seo.
What do you mean?
When did I only believe Jun Seo?
I did not hit him first.
But I was mad and hit him back. And that was wrong.
I will face my punishment.
That's why the School Violence Committee will be held.
I don't want to face the punishment from the school.
The school didn't do anything for me...
when I was bullied at school.
So...
I'm going to leave this school.
Okay. Just cry.
You can cry.
I know how that must feel.
It's all right.
Does it mean I'm an elementary school graduate?
I'm a high school graduate.
I know that you love me, but you shouldn't follow the same path.
Young Min.
You can transfer to another school. Why did you quit school?
I thought that would end this quickly.
That way, it will hurt you less.
Don't you hate me?
I was angry that there was a rumor about you and Han Jun Seo's dad...
of all people.
I'm sorry.
You might think I don't mean it because I say it too often.
But I'm really sorry.
By the way, what will happen with you and his dad?
Will you not see him...
if I don't want you to?
Yes.
That kid quit school. Did you tell him to do that?
He did?
It was his mother's doing then.
She wanted him to leave school before he got kicked out.
Isn't this petty?
What's your point?
I'm telling you the divorce you want won't be easy.
Do you think you can raise another man's son...
after abandoning your beloved son?
Dad, do you remember Young Min?
Hello.
It's okay.
It's Saturday.
It would have been better if Jae Hyun was eating with us.
He goes to work on Saturday too. You know that he's a workaholic.
I didn't mean it in a bad way.
I didn't tell him that you were coming over on purpose.
I just wanted to talk to you in private.
Did something happen?
Jae Hyun does everything you tell him to do.
He loves you dearly.
If you tell him that you like me,
I thought he might not leave me.
Something is...
going on between you two.
Can you stop Jae Hyun, Mother?
When did you get here?
Why are you here alone?
Did something happen?
I should ask you that. What's the matter with you?
Seo Kyung asked me to stop you.
You said you met her.
Did something happen between you and her?
I know the life you had led after she left.
If I were to only think about you,
I would tell you to divorce her.
But when I thought about your son,
I can't bring myself to say that.
What a surprise. You came out to greet me.
Did you drink?
After you asked my mother to come?
I told her everything I wanted to tell her.
Seeing your reaction,
I guess you won't listen to your mother either.
It's between you and me.
There's nothing my mother can do.
That can't be.
I'll do everything. I'll use everyone.
It's a pity that your father passed away pretty early.
He would probably be on my side.
I just need you to make your decision.
I can't.
How could I make a decision like this so easily?
Nothing in life was easy.
I had to risk everything I had on every decision I made.
(Bada Piano)
- Bye, Yu Bin. - Bye.
- Is that your friend, Yu Bin? - She's not my friend.
Are you here for a lesson?
She doesn't have any lessons.
I can play it better even if I don't get any lessons.
That's ridiculous. How can you play it...
when you don't get any lessons?
I can play.
You don't even have a piano at home.
I can still play.
Then would you like to try?
Ms. Yoon.
Mom said I need to be home for dinner.
All right, Yu Bin. Go on home.
Good-bye, ma'am.
Byeol, how did you play that?
Are you sure you never had lessons?
Then can you play anything else?
Are you sure you never had lessons, Byeol?
- Yes. - And you can't read notes?
But you can tell how to play as soon as you hear it?
Yes.
Would you like to take classes, Byeol?
Mom says we don't have the money, no matter what.
I can teach you for free if you come around this time.
But I don't have any money.
I won't be taking any.
I just want to hear you play.
Go on.
Ms. Yoon.
Thank you.
(For Rent)
I know you're a busy man,
so I'll just verify a few things and get it over with.
The plaintiff's main argument is that...
the suicide of Kwon Hyuk Soo...
was due to the malicious destruction of the labor union,
and that you were in the middle...
of that case.
Do you admit to it?
That is not true.
Yes, I can tell too.
The reference material the plaintiff submitted...
were all circumstances and speculations...
and had no proof, except that...
you were the director of the Strategy and Planning Department.
There was illegal destruction of the union.
Sorry?
What I meant earlier was that I wasn't involved in it.
I didn't mean that...
an unfair labor practice on Hyung Sung's side didn't exist.
Five years ago, a meticulous and malicious...
destruction of the labor union was enacted...
and that...
directly contributed to the death of Kwon Hyuk Soo.
Sir, do you understand...
what you are saying and what results...
it may bring?
I do,
and I am fully prepared.
Are you looking for that old man?
I don't see him today.
This is the Certificate of Disposition...
from the Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
"No charges".
"Disposition of non-indictment".
What does this mean?
It means he can not be punished, due to a lack of evidence...
to prove that Han Jae Hyun is guilty...
or because he did not constitute a crime.
Then...
what happens now?
Legally,
there's nothing we can do now.
He is a nasty and meticulous man.
Goodness, Hyuk Soo.
My poor boy. What can we do?
I can't live like this.
I just can't live like this, Mr. Lee.
I don't think I can live like this either.
I understand that...
you own a lot.
The whole country knows that.
I also know how you obtained it,
so I won't ever be taking anything you offer.
I heard you think dearly of your son,
but I guess that was wrong.
It's because I think dearly of him.
And please stop tailing me.
I will report you...
for illegal tailing and surveillance.
I haven't shown even the slightest amount...
of what I own and what my powers are...
because I pitied...
your sick dad...
and what happened to your mom and sister.
I'm sorry but I have no interest at all.
I don't want anything from you...
carrot nor stick.
It's all illegality and blackmail to me.
(Murderous Company, I report the brutality of Hyung Sung!)
I'll show you...
what Han Jae Hyun did.
It's been 25 years since we promised this.
I guess so.
I don't think it tastes the same.
It was really good back then.
It must be because you were really hungry back then.
No.
It's because of the change.
Because you've changed.
It's a relief the arrest warrant was dismissed,
but I'm not sure.
I don't know what the truth is...
or what is right.
And I know the old man who protests alone...
in front of the company.
I helped him out when he was having a hard time.
Did that...
really happen to his son because of you?
It's a long story,
but the conclusion is "no".
You may not believe me because of all I've done,
but I don't intend on lying to you.
This is like a thorn in my side,
but if you can wait a while,
I will tell you the long story.
Although I won't be able to at the moment.
(Jae Hyun)
Jae Hyun.
I think I'll have to hear it.
The long story.
Yoon Hyung Gu's daughter came to see me this afternoon.
She's a tough one.
Unlike her father,
she has a kind of temper or spite.
She got me full of thoughts, wondering what I should do...
with this ignorant fool.
- Sir... - I told you to sit down, already.
I came to see you...
because of something I found while looking into Yoon Hyung Gu.
What is it?
It goes all the way back to my father.
I got a call when I was in the army.
That my father had taken his own life.
After being tormented by false accusations that...
he had betrayed his colleagues,
taking the lead in the destruction of the labor union,
and acting as the informant on the company's side.
Unlike the bastards in the union...
who call for a strike whenever possible,
there was a man who tried to hear the company's side as well.
He was that man, and he was a perfect fit...
for our plan.
He was good with people, so things worked out well,
and the existing labor union dissolved.
We agreed on a restructuring with the new labor union, but...
So what are you trying to say?
He sued the company...
for unfair labor practice.
And we stopped that, didn't we?
Yes, the prosecution worked things out...
and laid the dissolution of the labor union...
and the layoffs to his charge.
Because of that, the executives of the dissolved union labor...
and the employees who had been laid off...
all ended up suing him.
So all the charges on the company were dismissed,
and he was the one charged for illegal destruction...
of the labor union.
He committed suicide sometime after,
and we just confirmed that...
he was Han Jae Hyun's father.
It was the most lonely funeral.
(When My Love Blooms)
If someone was to take the blame for what happened to my father,
it has to be me.
Yoon Ji Su's son used violence against Jun Seo.
What are you trying to say?
I don't know how to fight nicely.
I will win and rip you apart to pieces.
Let's end this.
I don't want to repeat the most painful mistake...
in my life.
Since I need to be happy.