You must have given it a deep thought. You look sunken.
I've been thinking about it since that day.
About why you were doing this.
You were the one who had an affair...
before Young Min could even walk.
You agreed to give up custody at court...
without giving it a second thought.
Why would you suddenly want it?
Why were you so focused on destroying the man...
instead of bringing back your son?
How can the custody of your child and Han Jae Hyun...
even be comparable?
And did you find the answer?
My dad once told me about the opportunity cost...
25 years ago.
If you choose one side,
you must give up the other.
You need to choose what you want to do the most...
or avoid what you're most afraid of.
You need to choose either side.
So?
I've decided...
to avoid what I'm most afraid of.
What I'm most afraid of,
back then and even now,
is him falling because of me.
It doesn't matter if my choice is right or wrong.
I will go back to you.
(When My Love Blooms)
(Some topics were exaggerated for dramatic effect.)
I'm not dragging you into a fiery pit.
I don't appreciate the sad face.
It'll get better.
You have changed, but so have I.
And I'm not as stupid as to make the same mistake twice.
What should we do with the wedding?
Whatever you want.
I'll give you time. Sort out whatever you must.
Especially...
any old relationships.
You answer everything so clearly that...
we're speeding ahead with the investigation.
Let's eat, then you can review your statement.
What would you like? Seolleongtang or ox blood soup?
I'll have ox blood soup.
(Hyung Sung Distribution VP Han at Prosecutors' Office)
You shouldn't have gone to Ji Su.
Her ex-husband sued for custody...
of their son.
Is it because of what happened at school?
No. It's because of you.
He suspects an affair.
(Prosecutors' Office)
It's leek soup.
I love leek so much, I always eat like this.
It's crunchy and fresh, and not bitter at all.
Leeks are the best at cutting through grease.
I started eating even more leek since I got this job.
Mr. Han.
When will you play your next hand?
What do you mean?
Don't underestimate us prosecutors.
Listen.
One fine and breezy day,
a stack of papers on Hyung Sung Group...
ended up in our office.
It was easy to read and understand,
and so very well organized.
Just when I was trying to make sense of it,
only a few days after I got the papers,
the papers and news started to report on what I was reading.
One would even think we orchestrated it with the media.
The announcement.
Is that what happened?
So that is how, naturally,
we ended up interviewing you today.
And you, Mr. Han,
came alone, without even a lawyer that other rich successors...
have so many of.
And without missing a beat or a word,
you admitted to every single charge.
The questions I prepared were of no use at all.
If every investigation were like this,
a prosecutor would be such a great job.
Since it came to this,
there's no way I can't suspect something.
Us prosecutors...
aren't a bus or subway that sticks to the same route.
Even more so,
we aren't like a taxi that's at your beck and call.
How about you tell me...
what's coming next?
Eat your leek soup before it gets cold...
and continue the questioning.
Did you admit the charges?
Did you window-dress the accounts?
- Give us a comment! - Say something!
Do you admit the charges?
Say something!
Any comments?
- How did it go? - Pretty well.
Pretty well for whom?
What does that mean?
Is it going well for you or for my dad?
Which is better for you?
I want it to work out for you both.
So that you don't have to fight.
There won't be any problems for either of us for now.
Are there any other problems?
Anything not involved with work.
I wish you'd be consistent.
Okay. Beating around the bush isn't my style...
and I can't stand it.
Yoon Ji Su.
How is she doing?
All I know is that she's trying to fight a custody battle.
- Is that all? - For now.
Hey. What happened to your foot?
I walked too much.
Why?
I hate someone.
Who is it this time?
Me.
My gosh. You have such a temper.
You're a nasty one.
Your feet are tiny, like a princess'.
Why do you abuse them? Be nice to them.
Be nice to yourself...
if you want others to value you.
Grandma.
Be my mom.
Why should I be your mom?
Just because...
Just because I miss my mom so much.
I wish I had a mom...
who would beat me on the back like crazy.
Is something wrong?
It hurts because of the medicine.
Bear it.
It'll heal very soon.
There's no wound that doesn't heal.
You're really smart.
Now you know?
You shouldn't cry then laugh.
Hello?
Is this Ms. Yoon Ji Su?
Who's this?
Hey, Ji Su.
Do you not even remember my voice?
Dong Jin?
Wow, Ji Su, you haven't changed at all.
You're still in the top three prettiest women in our year.
You too.
I know. I don't look my age at all.
I get younger every year.
I might end up a baby.
Anyway, I'm pretty skilled as well.
How about I take your case?
The custody case.
I'm a divorce expert,
so I can defend you with my eyes closed.
"He's the one person I don't want to lose to."
That's the motto of everyone else in my office.
You got lucky.
With me, your divorce becomes a winning lottery ticket.
- Dong Jin. - It's fine.
You don't have to thank me.
I won't go to court.
You won't?
Oh. Is it because of money?
It's true I'm the most expensive divorce lawyer in Korea,
but you get me free of charge.
How could I make you pay me?
Thanks for the offer,
but the lawsuit was dropped.
I see.
He dropped the lawsuit?
Why?
I don't know.
You should've asked for details.
Isn't it good if the lawsuit was dropped?
It's weirder to ask for the reason.
- Jun Woo. - Yes?
I need you to follow someone.
I'll pretend you're on holiday and hire a temporary secretary.
Move discreetly.
Yes, sir. But who am I to follow?
Lawyer Lee Se Hun.
Ji Su's ex-husband.
- What? - When he's away from home,
what he does, who he meets, and where he goes.
Don't miss out on a single thing.
I understand.
Welcome.
How are you?
Don't greet me like we're strangers.
Say, "I'm home."
I apologize.
Wash your hands.
He's too much like a girl.
Is it because he lived with his mom?
We're getting back together.
What? You're doing what?
Getting back together.
Did she manipulate you again?
I said just get the kid.
It's final and that's that.
If you let Young Min know you disapprove,
I won't see you ever again.
Thank you.
How about this place?
I like it.
You like this place and the other one? Both?
A boy should have opinions.
- Sorry. Keep practicing. - Okay.
Dad says this is where we'll live together.
(Ji Su)
Hye Jung.
What?
What do you do when you have time to kill...
but have too many thoughts to sit and do nothing?
I go home and sleep.
A lesson got canceled, so I can't go home.
Have a coffee.
Then I can't sleep and I already can't sleep.
Then drink alcohol.
I'm not out of my mind.
Think carefully. You might be.
Hey. What about singing?
Ringing?
Boxing?
Like when they ring the bell?
Do you live in a cave?
Singing alone in a coin karaoke both.
Don't you know?
Tonight, I can't bear to
Speak to you in person
Forgive me for putting in writing
How I feel about you
For a long time
I was frighteningly into you
But now I might regret
How I was like
But, my darling
Even if you forget everything else
I wish you will
Remember this much
Just how much
I am
In love with you
Just how much I love you
Are you okay?
You're getting back together?
You're so stupid.
Clean it up before you get hurt.
What's the real reason?
Is it Jae Hyun again?
No, it's because of Young Min.
You got divorced because of him.
You know too much about me.
I need you gone.
You don't know...
anything about me.
I don't?
Hey, I even know what type of woman...
Does it hurt when I press down?
Did a shard get stuck inside?
Let me see.
Hold this.
I don't see anything. Why does it hurt?
It's because of you?
What nonsense.
It hurts because of you.
Because I like you.
It's because...
I like you.
I'm not against the idea because...
I'm afraid I won't get a shot.
If that's how I felt, I wouldn't have...
just watched you for years.
The glass is out. Keep your hand up.
I saw in a movie that...
the blood stops if your hand is higher than your heart.
I lost another friend.
If I say I'll remain a friend,
will you do as I say?
You're my only friend too,
so I didn't confess for fear of losing you.
That meant we wouldn't break up, so it kind of worked for me.
But I want to stop now.
Watching you...
walk straight ahead.
You're walking into a fiery pit.
I can't let you.
I'll be firm and mean and will interfere in your life.
Young Woo.
We can't meet anymore.
I can't come anymore once I get back with my ex.
We have to say goodbye sooner than that.
But some cream on that, but not a band-aid.
It's not good to cut off air circulation.
Use a vacuum cleaner, then a mop.
I have to get going.
Thanks a lot, Young Woo.
And I'm sorry.
(Prosecutors' Office)
(Karl Marx's Ideologies)
So,
this is what we found in your boarding house's common room.
And you still say you aren't communists?
These books are on philosophy and history.
They're also used as textbooks in lectures.
"Let's unite laborers to create a socialist society."
You use such blatant language and say it's about education?
Even our constitution guarantees freedom of conscience and ideas.
How can we guarantee ideas that are...
about overthrowing our regime?
Ji Su...
was kind and affectionate since she was young.
She was never firm and was easily swayed.
That's why she always gave in, willingly took a loss,
and shared what she has.
All she got in return was betrayal, manipulation,
and loss of her belongings.
I was more worried for her because of what she was like.
I was afraid she'd take the wrong path.
If you don't give up on her,
you'll rot in prison for a good few years.
You'll never graduate...
and won't be able to find employment.
You'll use...
your authority for personal gain?
You could say that.
I won't let this happen.
This is oppression and abuse for personal revenge.
I'll let the world know.
Your parents are here.
Ji Su and your parents...
are willing to go through this for you.
What are you doing?
Do you think what you do is so grand and huge that...
this kind of sacrifice is obligatory?
Jae Hyun.
Are you okay?
(Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office)
Ji Su and your parents...
are willing to go through this for you.
What are you doing?
Do you think what you do is so grand and huge that...
this kind of sacrifice is obligatory?
You're out at last.
Ma'am, Jae Hyun didn't get a prison sentence.
- He doesn't need to eat tofu. - Even so.
Are you okay? You're healthy?
You don't have to go to prison, right?
And you can graduate?
- Yes. - Good.
Jae Hyun and I broke up.
Why must I go abroad?
I'm sorry,
but I don't trust you.
"Out of sight, out of mind."
I trust that more.
Right now, not seeing him will make you think you'll die,
but I guarantee that you'll be over him in a month.
Plus, you're majoring in classical music.
Study in earnest in a bigger pond,
where the music came from.
Since when did you care so much for me?
Don't spend money on a daughter you're disappointed with...
and let me stay here.
I don't want to go even if Chopin comes back to life.
All you did so far was disappoint me.
It's time you do as you're told.
I might really die.
Too bad, then.
Why come here when I want you to study?
I don't want to go to lectures.
Why? You used to live on campus.
I can't stand the protesters.
Why? What do they say?
It's because they don't talk to me. They just whisper in secret.
What do they say in secret?
That I betrayed them over a girl.
That's not true.
I heard you broke up with that girl.
Are you okay?
I'm not going to school, so I can be okay.
If I go,
I'll be reminded of her all the time.
Ji Su.
When you arrive at the airport in Frankfurt,
you'll see a Korean man who will help you with your homestay.
Ji Su, I heard he's really handsome.
Good for you.
What's the point of having a handsome house owner?
- Not the house owner. - Ji Young.
What are you talking about?
What?
- It's nothing. - Right.
You'd better tell me.
He's the youngest son of Sangguk Production's chairman.
We heard that the school he's going to isn't far from yours.
Is this the Joseon Dynasty?
Do you want me to have an arranged marriage?
My gosh, you don't have to marry him.
You can just go on a few dates with him.
There you are!
There you are.
Yoon Ji Su.
I wasn't sure if I should tell you or not.
But I thought you should at least see her off.
I heard it from Eun Dae.
Ji Su is leaving Korea today.
To Germany to study.
But what's in Gangchon?
A senior student I know runs a guesthouse.
I can just stay at your place.
If I were your parents,
my house would be the first on the list.
I think you can stay there for a few days.
I need more than a few days.
You won't go back home?
No.
What will you do?
I want to marry you.
We should write one too.
Write what?
"Jae Hyun and Ji Su were here."
Let's not do something like that.
I heard there are scribbles in Korean...
all over Heidelberg Palace in Germany.
Don't even bring up Germany.
I think he's going to move.
He's house-hunting.
- House-hunting? - Yes.
He's looking at houses on the outskirts of the city.
And he's been taking his son when he goes to see the houses.
Young Min?
Yes. It looks like...
they are going to live together.
It hurts because of you.
Because I like you.
It's because...
I like you.
I'll give you time.
Sort out whatever you must.
Especially...
any old relationships.
Dad says this is where we'll live together.
Nothing is easy.
It's all right.
It's okay.
I think you're hurt.
I fell.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to check something.
I heard that your ex-husband petitioned to get the custody back.
That's why you must have sent Dong Jin to me.
I heard the lawsuit was dropped.
Did he give up?
No.
We decided to get back together.
Now, why would you make such a decision?
To protect.
To protect what?
Young Min?
Do you think that will truly protect your son?
He needs his father at his age.
As he's a boy, there's only so much I can do for him.
I'll get going.
Take care, Jae Hyun.
There are more people watching you...
than the guy who's tailing you.
As if.
I can't even cook ramyeon right.
I'm not okay at all.
Nothing is okay.
Everything is a mess.
I fell.
She should enjoy her life like normal people.
I'm sure you're busy with other work these days.
I am sorry to inconvenience you again.
- Please have a drink. - Okay.
It's not an inconvenience at all.
I only told the prosecutor in charge to follow the rules.
That's all.
The situation hasn't changed from what you told us before, right?
Right.
According to the Corruption Prevention Act...
and the Whistleblower Protection Act,
as for accounts under borrowed names, fraudulent accounting,
professional negligence, and embezzlement,
whistleblowers who reported aforementioned activities...
will not be protected under our law.
Our law is surely in our favor.
That's right. If our country protects traitors,
it will be hard to run businesses.
Since we can't make deals with the sentencing in Korea,
like you see in the movies,
it's impossible to work with prosecutors with an agenda.
A leading country must follow the law and the rules.
That sounds great, Mr. Kim.
- Give him one more drink. - Yes, sir.
By the way, sir,
are you sure you want to do that to your son-in-law?
People say that you ought to scold your children...
to raise them properly.
That goes for the dogs you raise.
I was just curious about the progress.
We're getting back together.
Did your ex-wife agree to that?
Of course.
I have a bad feeling about it.
What do you mean?
I think something is going wrong.
It will go my way.
Do you trust her 100 percent?
I don't trust her 100 percent,
but I know exactly how she is.
Since she knows what she will lose,
she won't change her mind.
Is it because of Jae Hyun?
I joined hands with you as I was desperate.
But your love scares me a bit.
A woman is willing to sacrifice her life for a man she loves.
How could you think about living with her?
I thought at least you of all people...
would understand my decision.
Was I wrong?
Mr. Lee Se Hun met with Ms. Jang.
- Seo Kyung? - Yes.
And I noticed the shape of our dashcam seemed a bit different.
So I took it out and checked it out.
- Where are we going today? - The branch in Bundang.
To Gyeonggi Province? We're driving there, right?
We're taking the subway.
Are you going to buy snacks with the leftover company money?
I can't buy snacks because I have leftover company money.
What happened to your shoe?
How would I know that?
I told you I didn't want to get on the subway!
- Where did you lose it? - I don't know.
I'm going to call Mr. Kim.
(Entrance to the Subway)
Where did you find it?
Where did you lose it?
The shoe came off when I was climbing up the steps.
I found it on the subway platform.
What happened to your face?
What about it?
You look ugly.
What? Ugly?
Everyone, fill up your glass.
This is a drinking relay. I'll start.
Let's go clockwise.
I'll pass.
- Drink it for her. - What?
Let's skip Seo Kyung. You'll start Jae Hyun.
That won't be a drinking relay then.
It looks like Seo Kyung can't drink. You just drink yours.
You talked about the legitimacy of a drinking relay.
You sounded like a stickler for rules.
Can you be out here during your working hours?
You said an after-work get-together was an extension of work.
What's wrong? Why are you out here?
I lost something.
You lost something? Why did you lose?
Money?
Someone.
I lost something too.
My mother.
(From Ji Su to Jae Hyun again)
To protect.
("The End of That Summer", Poems by Lee Seong Bok)
(Lee Se Hun)
You haven't forgotten about tomorrow, right?
I know.
And you know what you need to prepare?
Yes.
(Donation List)
(Donor Name, Yoon Ji Su)
(Jae Hyun)
Do you have a moment?
I'll head over.
No.
I'm away at the moment.
This train will soon arrive...
at Gangchon Station.
(Jae Hyun and Ji Su, Our love will last a million years.)
You must be tired. Why don't you go to bed?
I'm not that tired.
Then should we go out and exercise?
So this is what they mean when they say, "It's raining stars."
Aren't you worried?
I am worried.
About what Dad will do now.
Why is he acting like this?
He's a chief prosecutor now,
but his goal is to get into politics.
So he needs the money.
Marrying me into a wealthy family has been his long-time dream.
And he said you were precious to him.
What? Who?
You.
To whom?
To me.
Why?
Because I feel bad.
Why would you feel bad?
Because I love you.
What did you just say?
I didn't hear you.
Forget it.
Come on, I really didn't hear you.
Say it one more time.
One last time, okay?
Listen carefully.
Ji Su.
There you are, again.
I'm glad you came.
(Registration of Marriage)
(Wife, Yoon Ji Su, Signature)
There's something I want to confirm.
Can we meet up tomorrow?
Jae Hyun.
I want for us...
to finally end it now.
It has been so many years,
but I still feel bad and miss it.
I think it's because we never properly said goodbye.
So we need a proper farewell.
A complete goodbye.
I can't do that, Ji Su.
I want to protect it.
It's not because I feel bad...
or because I miss it,
nor is it because of some hope.
It's not "I wanted to protect it."
I want to protect it.
Because of that one desire.
Just like you did.
The last train to Yongsan will soon arrive.
Please take a step back.
(Jae Hyun and Ji Su, Our love will last a million years.)
(For a million years... Our love shall bloom.)
I see you've been holding me captive without my noticing.
You should've been more careful if you were going to act like that.
You know how the world is today.
You will have to stop what you are planning.
I have no intentions of doing so.
Go ahead and reveal the video.
Are you sure about that?
They haven't even finished your investigation yet.
It doesn't matter.
I will also be winning through this.
Take the child from the mother...
who had been having an affair.
And I will be taking Ji Su...
when she loses her child.
(When My Love Blooms)
I've decided to interfere in Ji Su's life.
At the moment, I'm afraid.
That Ji Su might disappear.
Goodbye, Jae Hyun.
I found out what you had lost.
Were you aware that Jae Hyun has a woman?
Something might happen to you while I'm away.
I'm not being pushed. I'm standing up to it.
Whether it's fate or people.