I saw that Leon was still there.
I guess someone kept taking care of it.
I wonder how that happened.
Actually, that's not Leon.
Right?
No wonder.
I planted it not long ago.
On purpose.
Right here.
I forgot.
What this place was.
It's the asyli,
so no one can see us or find us,
so just for a while.
I was afraid of being held back by the past,
so I kept walking forward without looking back,
but I realized that I was always at this place.
Maybe...
I had been walking here all this time.
Now, my legs hurt,
and I just want to stay today.
Because if we're here,
we will be okay.
(Episode 9)
I have to go now.
Okay. Sleep well, Ji Su.
Get home safely.
Do you want some ramyeon?
Do you not eat ramyeon now?
Not much.
So people in your neighborhood really don't eat this.
You must've lost half your joy in life.
Is that so?
- You won't eat that? - What?
No.
Eating ramyeon and drinking coffee in a convenience store.
It's just like a date the youth go on.
If we speak like the youth do,
does that make us a couple?
We might...
get stoned.
I'm not afraid of being stoned,
but if we get stoned, it will hurt others too.
I'll get stoned for us both.
It's not like you're Iron Man.
You can't take it all.
I can. Because I have you.
You are my Iron Man suit.
If I'm your suit, doesn't that mean I'm the one who gets stoned?
Is that what it means?
He's lucid 20 percent of the time.
He's a kind, mild-mannered gentleman 50 percent of the time.
The rest of the time, he's a sick old man...
who is too tired to talk.
It must be so hard on you.
It was my dad who first taught me to play the piano.
"Child on the Island".
Your father played the piano too?
Slowly, with one hand.
I never understood him in my life,
but these days I do.
He was like a tiger for over 50 years,
and now he's a kitten.
He must be so flustered when he's lucid.
So...
I get it when he throws things and yells at me.
Just because I get it...
doesn't mean I just take it.
I get angry too.
Listening to old songs on the radio is her only hobby.
Your mother was a beauty.
Last time, her radio was broken,
so I sang a song for her myself.
- Did you? - Yes.
What did you sing?
"Because I Love You".
Did you sing well?
Not really.
I just sang, ignoring the beat and notes.
Sing it for me too.
I can't sing.
Liar.
I know how well you can sing.
That was back then. I forgot how.
Did you really?
Yes.
Was my head heavy?
It was light.
That's not a compliment.
Go on inside.
I'll really go now.
Who is it?
Mr. Kang the secretary.
What's going on?
Up there.
Over here.
- Is this the one? - That's it.
This is the newest and best door lock.
Fingerprint access, tampering alarm,
waterproof, dust-proof, earthquake-proof.
Even a mob of thieves can't break in.
(Vice-president Han Jae Hyun)
Hi, Ji Su.
The people here won't listen to me.
You tell them to leave.
They won't leave until the police drag them away.
- Jae Hyun. - They're doing it for me.
Not you.
I want to sleep in peace.
You must eat well if you're to stay up all night.
Do you disapprove?
Pardon?
It's not for work or family matters.
I keep making you do things that people ridicule.
That?
It must be hard physically and psychologically too.
I bet I'm the only person in all of Korea...
who knows the life you lived.
It's not Ms. Yoon, your wife, or the chairman.
I know more than anyone about the life you led so far.
I'm on your side. Without question or condition.
You've grown up.
I always was tall,
but you're just taller.
You even talk back at me now?
I apologize.
Thanks.
(Convalescent Ward)
(Celebrate with your family)
It's "Child on the Island".
My daughter played the piano well.
What did you say, Dad?
My daughter played the piano well, ma'am.
Hello.
Yes. Hello.
What's that?
It wouldn't fit in your home,
and I knew you'd refuse it.
So I donated it here.
I said it would be good for the patients,
and the director accepted it.
I squeezed out what little creativity I had.
Does it look okay?
It's not okay. It must've cost a fortune.
I asked them to let anyone play it.
That's what I said,
but I hope you play.
Give it a go.
Your father's memory might return.
So, will you be detained or not?
I wouldn't know.
Are you speaking in rhymes?
Is that a challenge?
Not only are you on the verge of being detained
You were sued for something you did five years ago
How are you so relaxed?
Man, yes.
What on earth are you doing?
- My gosh. - You wouldn't know.
Then what? Should I pray?
To avoid being detained?
You would be really crazy if you were in your right mind.
I'm in a great mood these days.
You're crazy.
Gosh.
Hey.
Look at you. You are crazy.
- Hey. - What?
What time do you get off work?
Do you want to have a drink?
I can get off right now.
Is this room soundproof?
Soundproof? Why would you ask?
Can I spend the night here?
Hang on.
At night, in a soundproof...
You fool. You and Ji Su?
Gosh, you have an imaginative mind.
Too bad it's in the gutter.
Hey, what are you saying?
Tell me honestly and I'll let you stay!
What? How dare you?
(911 Ambulance)
Can you spare me some time in the evening?
Ji Su.
I'll go back to you.
I won't stop,
and I won't look back.
These past few days,
until today,
I felt as if I was in a movie.
Out of all we did,
this was my best scene.
The longer I walk with you,
the heavier my footsteps become.
Everything you taught me,
I kept in my heart.
So I wouldn't feel ashamed...
if I ever met you again.
I'll take a path...
where I can stand proudly in front of anyone.
I won't deceive anyone anymore.
I have things to sort out,
so it might take some time,
but I will go back to you.
(Chief Prosecutor Kim Hak Cheol)
Everyone's so busy, first thing in the morning.
- Let's begin. - Okay.
How far is Jae Hyun taking this?
According to Chief Prosecutor Kim,
the prosecutor got a search warrant according to...
the Real-name Transaction Law, Capital Market Law,
and International Tax Collection Law.
Other than the dividends sent to the borrowed-name accounts...
I believe your slush fund too...
How does that fool know about that too?
He gathered information when he was in Strategy and Planning.
That's why I wanted to...
If only it hadn't been for Seo Kyung...
It was definitely him who alerted the press about...
the borrowed-name accounts.
I told him to do time,
and he's preparing to pay tax.
He's planning to take those shares.
I apologize, sir.
The best offense is the best defense.
You only win a fight when your opponent is down and beaten.
You don't win if they take a stand.
Find a ring to fight him in.
Not where he wants to meet us,
but where we can summon him to.
There is something...
he is spending a lot of time on.
You only watch "Love Letter" or this movie.
I watched it.
"Days of Being Wild" is not fun at all.
I plan to get rid of this room.
Should I turn it into...
a dressing room or a wine bar?
We ended up like this because you spend...
too much time here reminiscing.
Even before I met Ji Su again,
our marriage was over.
I was inattentive,
and you dated another man.
When my fight with Father is done,
one of us will pay the price.
Whether it's me or Father,
it'll be hard on you.
It's all in the past.
Must it end this way?
Being abused and discarded...
is the natural order for the likes of me.
You're not responsible at all for this fight.
But still, you will get hurt.
What is the best I can do for you?
I'm still wondering.
I want only one thing.
I'm sorry but...
I can't divorce you.
I can't help but weep.
That woman should weep too.
If I can't have my love,
she can't either.
I may seem like a monster,
but my love was love too.
Are you Ms. Yoon Ji Su?
What do you want?
Could you spare me some time?
My chairman wishes to see you.
Your chairman?
You look alike.
What do you mean?
Chief Prosecutor Yoon Hyung Gu's...
only living child.
His weakness.
The world is a small place,
Ms. Yoon Ji Su.
Did your father never mention me?
Until that incident, we were very close.
Did you know your father wanted to be a politician?
That requires money,
and businessmen require connections with prosecutors.
We sometimes met for a drink...
and to play golf.
He was so proud that...
his daughter went to Seoul National University.
Was that you?
You can't have asked to see me to talk about the past.
I'm smiling as I speak, so you might get me wrong.
I don't always smile.
If it hadn't been for that accident, he'd have gotten into politics...
and become an assemblyman and prime minister.
Why is the daughter of such a noble man...
seeing my son-in-law?
Do you need money?
Then say so. I knew your father...
and can give you a certain amount.
I warned my son-in-law many times.
When it comes to my daughter,
I find it impossible to control my temper.
This is a warning of sorts,
so it would be best for you to act wisely.
(Murderous Company)
(I report the brutality of Hyung Sung!)
How long was he there for?
Pardon? Who do you mean?
Lee Se Hun's client.
That man?
It was shortly before you were imprisoned.
It has been a bit over four years.
He's the person who threw the raw eggs at you.
(I report the brutality of Hyung Sung!)
Sir.
I looked into the prosecutor.
Did you know that was his father?
Who?
Kwon Hyuk Soo.
I see. That Kwon Hyuk Soo.
You can't just barge in here without making an appointment.
When you negotiated last year with the union,
you promised to raise 20 percent of the basic salary...
and 50 percent of our bonus...
and to give permanent positions to 50 percent of contract workers.
The terms were all settled,
but none of that had come true over the past year.
And we didn't even get to start negotiating for this year's demands.
I requested to see you multiple times,
but you didn't get back to me at all.
Not giving you an answer was the position we took. But...
I'm sure there was a precedent to execute those terms.
That if the economy gets bad,
the negotiation won't be valid?
The company suffered a blow because the company invested...
in the Australian steel business without analyzing the demands.
Is that our fault?
When you guys decided on that, you didn't discuss it with us.
The management has the sole right...
to decide on the investments the company makes.
It's not to be negotiated with the labor union.
Are you telling us that you call all the shots,
but we'll pay for your consequences?
Because of that investment, the entire company is struggling.
For now, until the shipbuilding industry and economy get better,
we must just hang in there and bear it through.
We're the last ones to enjoy the fruit,
but we're the first ones to suffer from the fall.
Is that the motto of Hyung Sung Group?
Think whatever you want.
It's so easy for you people to say to hang in there.
But to us, it's a matter of survival.
As it is a matter of survival, you must decide yourself...
before someone else does it for you.
Back then, Han Jae Hyun was the director...
of Strategy and Planning Department.
Based on what I have gathered,
right after Hyuk Soo met with Han Jae Hyun,
he declared the union failed to negotiate...
and decided to go on a strike.
But that strike didn't last a day.
Right.
From what I can conclude from this, I believe...
Hyuk Soo had been taken advantage of by the company.
What?
The strike didn't proceed as planned...
because Hyuk Soo got a new set of terms from the company.
That the company would give them the raise as promised...
and other demands would be met.
He persuaded the union members with the offer...
and ended the strike.
And they dropped all the charges against the management.
But afterward, the company had a change of heart.
The employees who led the strike were terminated.
And even the employees who were involved were separated...
and sent to other subsidiaries.
And when that happened, Hyuk Soo was the only one who stayed.
And he even got promoted to the unit leader.
But it's obvious how the people who left and stayed...
treated him.
Hyuk Soo.
My poor baby.
We must make him pay...
for this tragedy...
as he had the biggest part in this.
Young Min, is everything okay?
Yes.
But your grades have been dropping.
I'm sorry.
If you are, study harder.
Okay.
By the way,
are you interested in studying abroad?
Abroad?
This company runs a lot of good programs.
They select students with good grades and send them abroad.
And this time, you were selected.
But my grades have been going down.
It has nothing to do with your...
You used to get good grades before. Right?
Wouldn't that cost a lot of money?
If you're willing to go...
It won't cost a thing.
That company...
will pay for your education and living expenses.
Yes, Young Min.
I got selected for a scholarship program to study abroad.
Study abroad?
It's a scholarship program from Hyung Sung Group.
Hyung Sung Group sponsors scholarship students.
It will be favorable when he applies for jobs at Hyung Sung Group.
But don't they usually give that out to college students?
Right.
That's why I was very surprised that Young Min was selected.
That just means that Young Min is that much distinguished.
I see.
I'll tell you more about it when you come down this weekend.
Okay.
- Right? - My gosh.
- You look much better. - Bye.
- You should tell us how. - My goodness.
- Is that him? - I heard about them.
- Are you serious? - Is that true?
- Really? - I heard they're having an affair.
- My gosh, I had no idea. - They are having an affair.
- They shouldn't do that. - My gosh.
- I can't believe her. - How could she?
- I know, right? - Unbelievable.
- How could they do this at school? - This is awful.
She must be ashamed.
Young Min.
I have a bad feeling about it.
About what?
The scholarship program.
Why?
There are no free lunches in life...
except for lunches from me.
But once you start eating meals outside,
you'd have to pay for the food.
So it doesn't matter whether they are mere feelings or things,
if they are too much,
it makes you wonder how you are going to...
return the favor.
I'm just worried that you might get a stomachache...
when you have to worry about how you'll pay for the meals.
It's disappointing, right?
A bit.
But I knew it wouldn't work anyway.
Why not?
You can't come with me.
Why would I go with you?
People study abroad by themselves.
Because I'll always be glued to you.
- Dad. - Yes?
Let's go home now.
Okay.
Aren't you cold?
It's really cold for me.
When I go out to the street for the strike,
I try to layer up as much as I can,
but it's still very cold.
My son didn't commit suicide.
The company...
and Vice-president Han Jae Hyun made him end his own life.
According to Mr. Kwon,
the father of the late deputy speaker...
from Hyung Sung Steel's labor union who died five years ago,
Vice-president Han Jae Hyun...
who was the director of the Strategy and Planning Department...
(Murderous Company! I report the brutality of Hyung Sung!)
Are you trying to confirm it?
I'll show you...
what Han Jae Hyun did.
If that's true, he will face an appropriate punishment.
I don't plan to cover it up and side with him.
I wonder if you'll say that after when this is all over.
Are you targeting him because of me?
Han Jae Hyun was in the middle of that case.
And he had the biggest deciding power regarding the union matters.
He called the shots.
To be honest, I did start this because of you.
But once I got started, I began to develop an interest in Han Jae Hyun.
I found more stories along with this one.
And the main genre of the stories is crime.
Did you expect that the arrest warrant would be dismissed?
Are you the actual owner of the accounts under borrowed names?
What about the accusation regarding the slush fund?
- Give us a comment. - How do you feel right now?
Why? Why on earth do you want to drink at a place like this?
Why? Are you really broke?
I came here a few days ago, and it was nice.
Drinks here are much better, but cheaper.
All right. Then,
you should order eels or chicken gizzards at least.
What is this? Look at this empty table.
You know that I go for the food, not the drinks.
Sure thing. I'll turn this table into a buffet.
That's right!
- Ma'am. - Turn this into a buffet.
It makes me wonder if you guys ended up like this...
because of the era you were in.
What if...
you didn't have to study hard?
What if you didn't have to protest like the 80s?
Music, movies, and books. You name it.
Our era was the golden era.
Right.
I keep trying to figure it out,
but I still think it was a great era. You know?
But...
it was cruel as awesome as it had been.
It took away a lot of good people.
And it turned a good man into a bad one too.
Hello?
This is Kim Mi Hwa. Do you remember me?
Yes. Hello, Mi Hwa. Have you been well?
Of course.
What about you?
I've been well too. But what is this about?
I heard from Sun Hee.
Can you play the keyboard for us too?
The keyboard?
There's a separate labor union in the supermarket, not the company.
And we also have a culture festival.
Of course, I should go. I have your back.
Okay.
Then, I'll see you tomorrow. Okay.
- Jae Hyun. Wake up. - What?
What?
You're here.
Wait. How much have you been drinking?
Dong Jin kept feeding me drinks. Dong Jin gave me those drinks.
You should go home. Why did you come here?
Going home was tough.
It bothers me that an old man who always protests...
in the same spot stopped coming.
And it also bothers me that his son died...
because he had been wrong.
And I'm worried about my mother too.
I'm also worried about her stupid son.
I'm worried about Seo Kyung.
And Jun Seo too.
I'm worried about you...
and Young Min.
My gosh, I decided to go back to you.
But I keep seeing obstacles on my way to you.
It's because I live in a tough world.
The path coming to me is bumpy and rocky.
So coming to me...
will be very hard.
Why are your eyelashes still beautiful?
(Taxi Services in Seoul)
I don't think he can wake up.
I need Mr. Kang's number.
He's not a man, but a package.
I'm not inviting him in to seduce him.
This is beyond my control.
I'll lock the door and go to sleep.
Next time, I'll let you freeze to death on the street.
I recommend refraining from consuming alcohol.
My gosh, this is awful.
(Karam International Middle School)
Are you sure something is going on...
between Jun Seo's father and Young Min's mom?
- Isn't that obvious? - Right?
I could tell there was definitely something going on that day.
That day?
Listen. I saw them when they came to school last weekend.
I could feel the intense gaze between each other.
They did that even at school?
My gosh, they've got some nerves!
- Yes? - It's me, Jun Woo.
- My gosh. - Gosh, it hits the spot.
I couldn't say hi properly earlier.
You look great.
- Really? - Yes.
Are you dating a guy? You're glowing so radiantly.
Is it botox?
What are you talking about? She was always pretty.
By the way, you looked incredibly pretty...
playing the keyboard back there.
- That's right. - Yes, since you're pretty...
and have delicate fingers.
Gosh, I used to play the keyboard too,
but I kept pressing two keys, so I quit.
Go on a diet.
- Exactly. - You're hilarious.
- Why is the light off? - Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Mi Hwa
- This is good. - It is.
- You chose well. - Exactly.
The strawberries are great.
- Yes. - Really? Let me try one.
This is so delicious.
Thank goodness my birthday and the first visit was on the same day.
What are you doing?
You're taking everything?
- Where are you going? - Who else but her boyfriend?
You can't do that on your birthday. We need to eat together.
We can eat now.
Your dad already left for work.
Then what do we do?
Dad said to wait until dinnertime.
So we didn't even buy a cake yet.
I have plans tonight.
Just come back in time.
It's your birthday. How can we eat without you?
You're never home these days too.
All right. I'll try to be early.
What kind of cake do you want?
Any kind.
We're going to the department store to fix the clock today.
Should we get the strawberry cake there?
Whatever you want.
Get back early. Your dad will get mad again.
Yes, ma'am.
That brat. Look at her leaving without a proper goodbye.
I barely remember your face now!
- I know. - The cake is good.
- It's delicious. - It's good.
- Good choice. - Ji Su.
Why aren't you having any cake?
Oh, well...
What is it? Don't you like it?
I'm full.
You don't look too good.
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
Should I wrap some up for you?
We need to share the birthday cake.
Have some to go.
I realized something while looking around your place...
without your permission.
How you spent the past years...
and why you left me.
I would've done the same if I were you.
So don't blame yourself for anything...
and please be happy, Ji Su.
Aren't we going to have any eggs?
Why are you here?
I'm going to school.
Why are you taking a train?
This may seem like a lie, but Jun Woo took a leave.
Then you can drive yourself.
This may seem even more like a lie,
but my car is getting its regular checkup.
How did you know I was taking this train?
I was there waiting all morning.
What for?
I just wanted to.
You live alone, eat alone,
and even take the train alone.
It was just on my mind.
I'm not alone. I have my dad and Young Min.
(Karam International Middle School)
(Daham Hospital)
- What's wrong? - What's going on?
- Call the conductor. - What's that sound?
- Why is the light off? - What's going on?
- Goodness. - I can't be late.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we will be stopping momentarily due to a problem with the generator.
The train will start again as soon as we finish maintenance.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
It's okay.
It's raining. I need to go find my daughter.
My daughter will be cold out in the rain.
Ji Young!
Honey!
Ji Su.
Excuse me.
Your mother is a great cook.
Doesn't it look like I made it?
No, it doesn't.
You know everything.
You're so much darker now.
Is it difficult here?
I'm used to running around at school, so it's fine.
By the way, are you sure...
it's okay to be here on your birthday?
We have breaking news.
Another unprecedented accident has happened.
This afternoon, a popular department store in Seoul collapsed.
Fire trucks and ambulances are currently on-site,
with rescue operations underway.
We're going to the department store to fix the clock today.
Should we get the strawberry cake there?
The death rate is expected to be substantially high.
We will now contact a reporter on-site...
to look into details.
Ji Su!
Hold on a moment.
We're not sure yet, so...
Dad told me to come to his office right away.
He won't say anything else,
but he said to come.
But still... It's going to be fine. It will be all right.
I should still hurry up and go.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
Please let me go out for a moment.
Go back inside.
Please, sir. Let me go out.
It will be considered desertion if you go out.
Then I will do so, sir.
Just this... Let go.
Let go of me!
Ji Su!
Let go of me...
Ladies and gentlemen,
our train will be stopping momentarily...
in order to maintain distance.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
What do I do...
No.
I need to go.
Please open this door!
This is all my fault.
I...
I was too late.
I told them I would be early.
What will happen to Mom?
Please open this door.
Please open this!
I need to go!
Please open this door!
Ji Su.
Ji Su?
I don't remember.
I remember everything...
that happened that day,
but I can't recall...
the last moment I saw Mom and Ji Young,
no matter how hard I try.
Ji Su...
(When My Love Blooms)
I don't think I've been able to take a single step away from that day.
Mom, please look over here!
A deep wound also leaves a deep longing.
How can you make that decision so easily?
Nothing was ever easy.
I had to put in my everything.
How could you know that just now?
This is all your mom's fault!
I'm sorry, Young Min.
I think we need some time to heal.
Yes, I think you may be right.