(Jae Hyun and Ji Su, Our love will last a million years.)
(For a million years... Our love shall bloom.)
Jae Hyun.
I want for us to finally end it now.
It has been so many years,
but I still feel bad and miss it.
I think it's because we never properly said goodbye.
So we need a proper farewell.
A complete goodbye.
I can't do that, Ji Su.
I want to protect it.
It's not because I feel bad...
or because I miss it,
nor is it because of some hope.
It's not "I wanted to protect it."
I want to protect it.
Because of that one desire.
Just like you did.
Just 20 years out of a million?
We just took one step forward.
How can we part now?
Why you made the choice you did,
I found out.
It was because of me,
so I will correct it.
I see you've been holding me captive without my noticing.
You should've been more careful if you were going to act like that.
You know how the world is today.
You will have to stop what you are planning.
I have no intention of doing so.
Go ahead and...
reveal the video.
Are you sure about that?
They haven't even finished your investigation yet.
(Lee Se Hun)
It doesn't matter.
I will also be winning through this.
Take the child from the mother...
who had been having an affair.
And I will be taking Ji Su...
when she loses her child.
A long time ago,
Jae Hyun said he lost something.
With very sad eyes.
It's you, isn't it?
You won't deny it, so I'm right.
I want to know something.
I think you two were very much in love.
Why did you break up?
You're taking turns to make me look bad.
You both say you'll...
sacrifice yourself for the other as if you agreed on it.
If you loved each other so much,
why did you break up?
I said what I came to say. I will leave now.
I left him.
Can I ask why?
My life fell down in a single moment,
and my fury and despair took over.
I was afraid I'd hurt him too.
I don't understand,
but if it was that hard, couldn't you have shared the pain?
Sharing the pain...
wouldn't have halved it.
We'd have both become monsters.
Take me to your bar.
Are you sure about this?
You can't drink.
You remember that?
You used to be my idol.
I liked you. You seemed cool.
I wanted to be like you.
I protested because you did.
Whether it changed the world or not.
But what you're doing now...
seems greedy and foolish.
You're just being selfish.
I've decided to interfere in Ji Su's life.
What'll you do?
I don't accept him...
or you either.
It has to be you?
I don't care if it's not me.
As long as Ji Su's happy.
That's what...
both you and I want,
and it seems to be so hard.
What you said...
to Lee Se Hun earlier.
Were you serious?
I was, Young Woo.
If that were to happen,
I'll claim Ji Su.
(Family Relation Certificate)
You haven't forgotten about tomorrow, right?
You know what to bring.
Why you made the choice you did,
I found out.
It was because of me,
so I will correct it.
(Jae Hyun)
Where are you? I'll come.
Don't do it, Ji Su.
If you do something silly again,
I'll do something silly as well.
If you go back to him,
I will have the video released.
You will lose...
everything you have.
I will.
I might even get stoned in the street.
But Ji Su. Look back.
Why did we break up?
Can you really cook?
(May 1995)
I cooked since I was in middle school.
Mom and Dad both worked.
You grew up early.
Kids who are alone grow up fast.
I feel kind of sorry for you,
but it's also nice.
How shall we raise our kids?
- Are you okay? - Excuse me.
Are you Han Jae Hyun?
You ignored your draft notice,
and are wanted under Military Service Law.
As of 11:05am of May 20, 1995,
you're under immediate arrest.
Don't hold him so tight. You're hurting him!
Go home and don't worry.
It's my fault.
I think it was my dad.
You said you applied to enlist later on.
Get my things from the house with the persimmon tree.
They're expensive, so don't run away with them.
It's just a while.
See you a while later.
(Military Police)
(From "Gray Snowman" by Choi Yoon)
(May 12, Hiding with Ji Su in the house with a persimmon tree)
One starry night
I hear your voice
I wish to become white pollen
And land on your flower
As I look up at the night sky
I feel your breath
I wish to take a small boat
And sail on your lake
If you are to leave my side
I will follow you to the end
I will follow to the end, my love
(Marriage Registration)
(Yoon Ji Su)
Where are you?
I'm sorry for changing my mind.
I can't go back to you.
I'm not being manipulated.
I want to take a stand whether it's against fate or people.
Did you register your marriage?
(Lee Se Hun)
Your husband came to see me.
Did he know anything?
He knew about the video...
and that I was trying to reconcile with Ji Su.
- And? - If we release the video,
he said he'll claim Ji Su.
I think he got to Ji Su as well.
She said she won't come back to me.
I found out what you had lost.
If you were to get it back, I was going to congratulate you.
But I can't.
Why won't you say anything...
when you know I handed over the video?
Because I'm in the wrong.
So what, Seo Kyung?
You deliberately said it was something you'd lost.
I was lost,
not abandoned.
Mom. Mom.
(Jang Seo Kyung)
If you're abandoned once,
you blame the one who left you.
If you're abandoned twice,
you blame yourself.
So...
don't abandon me.
It hurts my pride.
The food's ready. Come in and eat.
Did my wife put them there?
She told me to throw them out.
I'll take care of them.
(2nd Album of Zoo)
Can you find me a cassette player?
The retro culture from the 90s is hip these days.
So I'll easily find one online.
Then, can you find me one?
Sure.
I guess you're also visiting the Online Tapgol Park.
Where's that?
I see. Well,
it's not a real place. It's an online website.
It's where you walk down memory lane...
while watching music shows from the 90s.
Hey, it sounds like you're calling me old.
No. Not at all.
I know the slangs young people use these days.
Totally hating it.
Why are you laughing?
(Kim Hyun Sik)
I don't think you went through with it.
But I was curious about your decision.
(But I was curious about your decision.)
I decided to not get back together with him.
(I decided to not get back together with him.)
I'm glad to hear that.
(I'm glad to hear that.)
I think it's better that you and I don't meet.
(I think it's better that you and I don't meet.)
I want to protect you.
It's coming from the bottom of my heart. And it's my goal.
(It's coming from the bottom of my heart. And it's my goal.)
Whether you see me or not, I'll do my best.
(Whether you see me or not, I'll do my best.)
And I'll do my best...
to get far away from you.
(And I'll do my best to get far away from you.)
(Karam International Middle School)
Young Min.
My gosh. You look like Leon.
Who's Leon?
He's a cool guy.
The school gave one to everyone.
I want to grow it at home.
Not at home. Why don't you grow it somewhere more spacious?
The roots won't go deeply in a flowerpot.
Sounds good.
Young Min, it would've been better for you if you lived at a big house.
Like the house you saw with your dad.
Are we really going to live with him?
Young Min.
Can you forgive me just this once?
I did something bad.
Without discussing it with you first,
I told you that we were going to live with him.
And then, I told him that I couldn't do that.
Then, does it mean we won't live with him?
I'll forgive you.
Are you okay?
Not living with him is slightly better for me.
Why?
You don't like him.
That's why you broke up.
You agreed to live with him,
but you realized you couldn't do it.
You're only a middle schooler.
But you're too rational.
No, I'm sensitive to feelings.
Living with him scares me and is uncomfortable.
My baby is growing up too quickly.
Is it because he's the only child?
(The original soundtracks of the movie, "Leon")
I guess I cried too much after watching the movie.
I can't see.
Take off your sunglasses.
My gosh. These are too black.
Did you really cry?
You bet.
My brother, Leon, broke my heart.
He's such an unlucky guy.
Mathilda's last line was heartbreaking too.
What did she say?
This is what she said when she was replanting the plant at a park.
"We will be okay here, Leon."
We will be okay here, Leon.
Ji Su, you can speak pretty good English.
It's her listening skill.
Whatever. Since we're talking about the movie,
why don't we drink something that looked like the milk...
Leon was drinking? How about a bowl of rice wine?
You said you'd leave after watching the movie.
Who do you think I am? Why do you keep telling me to leave?
My gosh, do you think you're funny? That was not funny at all.
By the way, there's something I want.
Hey, let's go drink rice wine. Don't go shopping.
What is it?
Leon.
What?
Just because you're holding a plant, it doesn't make you Mathilda.
A girl who can pull that off comes once in a million years.
Ji Su is much prettier.
You guys are ridiculous.
Do you think I'll be jealous...
Of course. I'm totally jealous.
Why are we planting it here?
Because...
this is a special place.
What's special about it?
Well, there's the Lord.
And there's Our Lady. There are a lot of priests...
and believers too.
It won't be lonely at least.
Water it.
(June 1995)
I finally planted Leon in a big garden.
I didn't have to think about where. I planted it there.
"We will be okay here, Leon."
We will be okay here.
(Sender: Yoon Ji Su)
(Recipient: Recruit Han Jae Hyun)
My gosh. I think that might be the one. Or not.
Why am I disappointed?
Goodnight, Ji Su.
Bye, Jae Hyun.
Jang Seo Kyung.
I'm glad you're here.
Actually, I've been wanting to have a drink with you.
Why are you moping around here again?
This is all your fault.
- Why? What did I do? - Because I take after you,
I chose someone like my mom to fall in love with.
My mom never smiled in front of you her whole life.
But at the amusement park, she smiled only once.
It was such a beautiful smile.
Just like my mom,
Jae Hyun is as cold as ice.
But he said that he was willing to give up everything for that woman.
That woman?
I'm sure he smiled for her.
Every single day.
I bet it was a beautiful smile.
What about Seo Kyung?
She drank a lot last night.
She doesn't want to have breakfast.
Can we talk?
I'm done talking.
I've done something.
And I can't just sit back as if nothing happened.
The video will never leak.
Then, you won't have to be responsible for her.
And nothing will change.
Leave me alone. I feel nauseous.
- You work at a distribution center? - Yes.
Isn't it hard?
Yes, it is.
I used to be a cashier, but now, I have to lift heavy things.
Is it some kind of revenge?
Probably.
I have a permanent position, so I'm in the labor union.
- So I like that. - That's a relief.
What about you?
You're doing well, right?
I'm doing really well.
Are you still busy?
If we're not busy, it means trouble.
That's true.
By the way, I wanted to ask you for a favor.
I'm not sure if you'll say yes.
In our labor union, I'm in charge of the culture team.
So we're doing a culture festival.
No one can play the keyboard.
And I thought about you right away.
Can I still play even if I'm not in the union?
Of course. We invite a lot of people from outside.
- I'll do it. - But it won't pay much.
- You don't have to pay me. - No, you should get paid!
I wanted to donate my talent.
Do you want some more food?
(Vice-president Han Jae Hyun)
The investigators from the prosecution...
are in the lobby for their second raid.
They have another warrant.
They brought a subpoena for you.
Things look really intense.
Is something going wrong?
If they want me, I must go diligently and cooperate.
You seem so calm. That's making me more anxious.
What if you get imprisoned again?
Stop making a fuss. Just make sure to follow our plan.
The real game is beginning now.
(Culture Festival of Hyung Sung Group Labor Union)
What's that sound?
There's the festival by the labor union.
They're trying to provoke the chairman.
My gosh.
- Let us live a life of a rock - Let us live a life of a rock
- Even if there is a nasty storm - Even if there is a nasty storm
- No temptation can waver us - No temptation can waver us
- Let us live a life of a rock - Let us live a life of a rock
- Only the reeds with weak stems - Only the reeds with weak stems
- Will be swayed by the wind - Will be swayed by the wind
Why are they doing that again?
Can't you call the police and arrest all of them?
It looks like they got the permit from the district office.
By the way, there's Ms. Yoon Ji Su.
Who?
You told me to look into the woman Vice-president Han has been seeing.
What is she doing over there?
I'll find out.
Which one is she?
She's the one playing the keyboard.
I can see that she's unusual from a distance.
(Culture Festival of Hyung Sung Group Labor Union)
- If you need me, call me - If you need me, call me
- I'll run to you whenever - I'll run to you whenever
- I can go during the day and night - I can go during the day and night
20th floor.
Canceled. 30th floor.
Sir, I'm heading to the 30th floor, not the 20th floor.
I'm heading to the 30th floor. And you're coming with me.
I saw you taking photos of the event the union was having.
Yes. The chairman wanted to see photos.
Can you show me the photos too?
I must figure out the employees who are in the union.
Then, I'll send them to your email.
I must see them now.
Please?
(Move 1 image to the Trash?)
(Trash, Empty)
(Deleting)
(Three-way Supermarket)
Ji Su.
You don't have to go.
I came here for an official matter today.
I'm telling you this as an executive of the company.
I don't want you to participate in an event like today's.
I'm not the company's employee.
Even if I was,
you don't have the right to tell me that because you're an executive.
Exactly. You're not an employee. Why were you there?
I was doing a favor for my old coworkers.
I liked it.
I always felt sorry because I felt like I ran away like a coward.
It made me feel like I wanted the world change without any effort.
This was only a small change, but I should still contribute.
Besides, it's something I'm the best at.
Unlike those haters online who fight on their computer keyboard,
I want to fight the world by playing the keyboard.
You said it's hard for you to make ends meet.
How can you fight the world too?
That's why this is the least I can do.
So it's embarrassing.
You're still there.
Because people are still there.
I guess the people were still there,
but I was the one turning a blind eye.
Jun Seo, are you having fun at school?
Well... Not really.
You're not?
It's just annoying.
Why? What's wrong?
Your school has the best facilities...
and the best staff. What's the problem?
Don't you know?
Some punk threw a chair at me.
How could you hide...
such a serious incident from me?
I'm sorry, sir.
And when he's the victim too.
I wanted to publicize it back then...
and punish him,
but Jun Seo's parents came...
and told me to go easy on him.
Seo Kyung did?
Ms. Jang was firm about it,
but Mr. Han insisted that we don't hold the committee.
(Murderous Company)
(I report the brutality of Hyung Sung!)
(The shameless family of Chairman Jang should apologize!)
("Love Letter")
Hello?
Hello, this is Hyun Woo's mom.
Will you be attending the school's open house tomorrow?
I do want to go,
but I actually don't feel comfortable going.
I guess my husband met up with her because he's soft-hearted.
I guess he went easy on her when she cried...
because they went to the same school.
Gosh, how could that happen?
It's embarrassing,
but I'm telling you because it was making me frustrated.
It's a good thing you told me.
It's not like I have any authority,
but I do have control over the mothers.
This is the worst case I've ever heard.
Even my face feels flushed.
Anyway, I don't feel comfortable seeing Young Min's mother,
so I don't think I can go.
What are you talking about?
Why would you have to avoid her?
She's the one who is guilty.
I'll take care of it.
I can never let things like this pass.
If word gets out, it will ruin the school's image too.
You're getting another investigation?
Are you going to end up in jail again?
What are you, an honorary ambassador for jail?
I was expecting this to come from the beginning.
That I might go to jail again.
I wasn't afraid of it at all back then.
Well, the first time is always the hardest.
But I am afraid now.
Why now?
That Ji Su might disappear.
That something might happen to her while I'm away.
I'm sure...
something like that can't happen twice.
Why is your relationship so sad?
You two used to be so awfully pretty together...
that it even made me wonder.
(Open House Day)
Hyun Woo! Good luck!
Goodness, you're here!
I'm glad you came.
- Come on in. - You look great.
You're so pretty.
Ms. Yoon.
Yes?
Do you have a moment?
- Why? - I want to discuss something.
All the other mothers will be there.
- Really? - This is so good.
Come on in, Ms. Yoon.
We already finished our lunch.
Go ahead and order something.
I'm good.
All right, then.
We don't have much time, anyway. Let's speed this up.
I know that you're going through a lot,
but you crossed the line.
Please get to the point.
All right. The point.
How could you hit on another student's parent?
- Unbelievable. - How could she?
I heard that's how you stopped the School Violence Committee.
I know you were desperate, but how could you take that road?
If word gets out,
the school image will turn vulgar sooner or later.
A mother should at least have...
some dignity, shouldn't she?
Can you even bring yourself to look at Young Min after acting like that?
He might already know.
Kids know everything these days.
I heard you even lied about your husband being...
a famous lawyer in Gangnam.
And you even attend protests after being fired from some supermarket.
How could you not even apologize...
after lying to us like that?
Go ahead and say something.
Don't just sit there like the cat got your tongue.
I guess you failed to dig up this part.
That I have a past record.
A previous conviction of foul play.
It was a place just like this.
It brings back memories.
Are you threatening me?
How dare you speak so disgustingly?
I understand that you want to leech off of...
Jang Seo Kyung by acting like her slave,
but you chose the wrong person to pick on.
"Slave"?
Why, you...
Don't bite me. I'll bite back.
You got all your stories wrong,
and I'll risk going to jail again...
if you spread rumors to the kids too.
- Goodness, ma'am! - Why, that...
It doesn't look like she was picked on.
- Let's talk again later. - Yes, sir.
You had a quiet way here today, didn't you?
You called me so suddenly,
so the lobby was empty.
So far.
We do try to keep confidentiality every time we call you,
but word gets out quickly here.
I guess there are a lot of ears.
Sir...
Things got complicated.
I don't think we will be able to protect you...
as a public interest informant.
There are a lot of flaws in the law...
regarding whistleblowing in our country.
We may have a big net,
but the mesh is just as big,
so it's not easy catching a big fish.
This is not what you said last time.
I guess this isn't your choice?
I guess at the moment,
the fish is still stronger than the net.
I guess I will have to go into the water...
to catch the big fish.
Are you saying there's more than the borrowed-name stakes?
It's not just the stakes and tax...
that are the problem for that.
As we discussed before, we are looking into it,
but we're dealing with a very widely hidden area,
and it's just as deep.
I will help you out.
Sir.
I'm not the kind of person who sees only what I want to see.
I see as I see.
Once I see it, I play by the rules.
If we dig any deeper,
things will get difficult for you too.
What can I do?
I knew I would have to risk it from the beginning.
You are...
one determined man.
I have a lot to clear up,
so let's get started.
Thank you.
So when you say "borrowed-name stakes"...
- That is correct. - All right.
How are you involved with the case?
- Please give us a word! - How did it go, sir?
- How involved were you? - Give us a word, sir!
We are ashamed of you!
(Eliminate the corrupt owner)
(Dishonest Supermarket, Corrupt Group)
(Arrest Han Jae Hyun for Economic Democracy)
- Please give us a word! - How did it go, sir?
- How involved were you? - Give us a word, sir!
What was the investigation on?
- Give us a word, sir! - What were your words?
What will happen next?
Give us a word, sir!
We are ashamed of you!
The family of the late employee, Kwon Hyuk Soo,
who took his own life during the general strike...
of Hyung Sung Steel five years ago,
filed a complaint against the vice-president...
of Hyung Sung Supermarket, Han Jae Hyun.
We want to reveal that...
the death of Kwon Hyuk Soo was not an accident...
due to personal reasons, but a tragic sacrifice...
against the company's unfair labor practice.
Five years ago, Han Jae Hyun...
enforced an inhumane restructuring...
within the company for business rationalization,
and he is the key suspect.
Sir...
The lawyer who filed the complaint today is Lee Se Hun.
I guess this is the best way for each other.
- What day is it today? - Wednesday, sir.
(March 1995)
Get them!
Hey, you!
The body of Christ.
Amen.
Take it and say, "Amen".
May the Lord be with you.
Follow her.
The body of Christ.
Amen.
The asyli had been trampled on.
"The asyli"?
It means asylum in Latin.
Even criminals and fugitives can't be arrested when they are in it.
But they did today.
Then I will be your asyli.
I will hide you away whenever you come to me.
So that no one can take you away.
We will be okay here.
If we're here,
we will be okay.
Gosh.
You're using that line often.
(Monthly Wednesday Mass)
The body of Christ.
I saw that Leon was still there.
I guess someone kept taking care of it.
I wonder how that happened.
Actually, that's not Leon.
Right?
No wonder.
I planted it not long ago. On purpose.
Right here.
I forgot.
What this place was.
It's the asyli,
so no one can see us or find us,
so just for a while.
I was afraid of being held back by the past,
so I kept walking forward without looking back,
but I realized that I was always at this place.
Maybe...
I had been walking here all this time.
Now, my legs hurt,
and I just want to stay today.
Because if we're here,
we will be okay.
(I had been spending my life waiting for you,)
(and my heart had been...)
(the sound of your footsteps.)
("The Footsteps", by Paul Valery)
(When My Love Blooms)
I'm not sure. What the truth is...
or what's right.
I'll confirm it for you.
What Han Jae Hyun did.
It's a matter of survival, so you should decide for yourself.
It must be because you've changed.
You're very similar.
Haven't you heard about me from your father?
You said you were curious, right?
About why I left.