Episode 3
What are those flowers?
Plume blossoms, my Lord.
Spring... is upon us.
Lord?
My Lord! My Lord!
What are you waiting for!
Call for the doctor!
My Lord! My Lord!
Queen Jo
Queen Mother Hyoyu
How many people witnessed
our Majesty collapse, today?
Everyone has been silenced,
Queen Mother.
If anyone finds out,
I will have every single
one of your heads.
Yes, Queen Mother.
Doctor your diagnosis?
How is our King's condition?
A tumor on his back
combined with a cold chest.
Our King will not even be able to stand.
Haok Jwa-Keun Kim
Prime Minister
Such a shame.
Send him our highest quality
wild ginsengs.
Yes, Father.
I will deliver the ginsengs to the Princess
to present to the King.
Good.
Father...
it hurts see you like this...
Did the Lord Byung-Woon Haoak
send you to spy on the King?
No, Ma'am
How dare I do such a thing.
You must always watch your mouth.
Yes, Queen Mother.
Your princess status was discovered
by the 'Jangdong Kim-Moon' Family
but a person of the Kingdom.
Never forget that
but you are of royalty.
Yes, Ma'am.
Give me rice soup, rice soup!
Wait a second...
aren't you?
My savior! My hero!
Yesterday, I saved you
from the Kim-Moon thugs!
Great to meet you!
My name is Pal-Yong, Yong Pal-Yong.
Backwards it's Yong-Pal-Yong.
Forwards it's Yong-Pal-Yong.
Yong-Pal-Yong-Pal-Yong-Pal-Yong.
Pal-Yong-Pal-Yong-Pal-Yong-Pal.
Easy right? Here.
A man of few words, like a hero.
We can get to know
each other slowly.
Here, have some sweet rice tea.
I did not order this.
It's on me, drink.
So handsome,
like my younger brother.
What are you doing?
Are you discriminating!
How many others are here!
Just piss off, will you?
Stop loitering around our tavern!
For 10 years you couldn't pass
the state exam!
Just give up and go back
to your hometown!
You idiot!
You're going to regret
treating me like this!
When I pass the state exams,
I will never return,
even if you beg me to!
Please, have some tea.
Give me rice soup, rice soup!
In a hurry?
A little...
Darn you!
A real big hurry?
Um... it's...
My apologies! I'm sorry!
Oh, God, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
My nose!
A secret to Fame and Fortune
There are no paths there...
Yes, Master... No paths at all...
I don't know...
how I should live anymore.
What destiny holds for those scoundrels
that made you like this,
what path you must take
your father's unjust murder...
Focus on all of these things.
This cliff has ended this path
create your own.
That woman, your soul mate,
was also
destined to lose her lover.
But now that you live
everything has changed.
Why don't you create
your own destiny!
Creating a new path where a path ends.
Chun-Jung, remember my words!
Do not ever avenge me!
Lower your head and
live in secrecy.
You must keep your life!
Father!
Once he arrives,
a fair investigation will reveal the truth.
We have no evidence.
You have a witness.
I saw everything unfold haven't I?
Thank you. Bong-Ryun
Explain yourself.
Why was there gun powder
on the cargo vessel?
I do not know
what he is talking about.
I witnessed Gyung Choi and his men
move gun powder onto the ship.
Are you always enraged?
Maybe your father was trying to
suppress all of your rage.
That isn't it.
It's just...
Why would Bong-Ryun betray me?
This question is stuck in my head.
It was to prevent you
from an untimely death.
If you cannot forget her
and seek after her
she will kill you
and complete her destiny.
You must let go.
Yes, master.
I will wait patiently,
and never forget...
I will avenge my father's death.
Where the path ends,
I will create my own destiny!
As if to brand a cow or pig!
Jajahyung
Branding a criminal’s face or arm
How dare they scar
your noble body!
It's alright.
It does not hurt anymore.
Let go! Stop!
Going through such pain
to save Lord Chun-Jung,
do you think he knows?
It does not matter.
As long as he is alive.
Oh, right!
Miss, these were posted on
all ports throughout the country.
But no one has yet to reach out
about your mother.
Could it be my memory fading?
Sometimes it's hard to remember
her face.
No, Ma'am! I asked the servant,
Mr. Jang, and he said
She looks just like this!
My Lord!
What brings you here?
I just really miss my daughter!
Is she happy? Is she healthy?
Please let me just see her!
Don't worry.
His Majesty has prepared
an orderly residents for you.
You will be escorted there.
Please, sir!
She cannot even sleep properly
without me.
She is still a child
who should be with her mother.
She is not your daughter,
she is a princess.
Everyone here is treating her
as royalty.
Mother! Mother!
The princess has already
forgotten you,
and sleeps well with silk blankets.
Is that true?
Take her.
Yes, sir.
My Lord!
My Lord, is that true?
Mother!
Bong-Ryun!
Mother...
Mother... Mother...
How is the King?
When will he pass?
It is up to the heavens.
Today, tomorrow? I do not know.
Trying to protect him?
Since he is still your father?
I acknowledge your hard work.
If you do well once more,
you will be greatly rewarded.
Once more?
Do you think you can find
the next Young Lord of Ganghwa?
the next Lord of Ganghwa...
Are you looking for someone
with the potential to be King?
The next King you say...
I will find him...
I will do whatever it takes.
Move! Move aside!
You'll get hurt!
Let me through!
Hey!
What? What!
In a hurry again?
As if running
from the East Sea to the West?
I am four months
overdue at the tavern!
I know my way
around this neighborhood,
I'm working all odd jobs
to make some money.
Why don't you just steal from
this neighborhood?
Come on now...
Listen, that really was
a one time deal
I'm not that kind of a person
Let's just move on with it, huh?
I'm sorry! I’m sorry!
Forgive me! Let me live!
If you know this area so well,
why don't you run
a few errands for me?
Huh?
The Red Monk!
He is the most popular fortune teller
in Han Yang!
Red Monk?
He always wears a red cape.
His readings are
said to be very accurate!
Why? Your life is
in need of some good fortune?
Maybe... But just curious.
About?
How big my potential is.
Nothing much.
There is a virgin ghost
among your ancestors
You're going to die alone!
I'm already getting old,
but forever?
That is what your palm says,
but give me your birth date.
Yeah, so... a few days
before I was born,
there was a fire
in the grain deposits,
which would make my birth date...
the sixteenth!
the sixteenth...
that is all I know.
How can I read properly
if you don't know your birth date?
Listen! Just sleep with
this in your pillow.
Then men will line up for you!
Oh my!
How much is this?
A measly 100 coins
a... hundred?
Please give me a better deal
Do you want to die alone?
Please, just a little bit...
By any chance,
was that fire by the river?
Who are you?
How'd you know?
I mean, how do you know this, sir?
According to history,
During King Sunjo's reign in March,
Jobo
Official newspaper
You are born the year of the snake,
second week of May.
Your readings are hot
but this year is cold with water...
Hasn't a man related to
the seas approached you recently?
Water...
Water you say...
water, water...
Oh! Oh my! Oh!
The water boy! Mr. Sim!
He has been coming on to me!
Who are you!
He is your soul mate,
try to make things work with him.
Do not waste your money
with such a fraud!
Yes. Thank you, master!
How dare you call me a fraud!
- You!
- Yes?
Hey!
How can a beauty like me
be destined to die alone?
You want to palm read this?
Thanks for this though...
That cost 100... coins...
This guy is a complete crook.
A snake at best!
Trying to cheat good people.
What? Huh?
You are a masterful fortune teller!
Please, excuse me, master.
She can't just...
It appears I have ruined
your business.
In exchange, let me read your future.
What? Get him!
I see your ears have blackened.
You have experienced
blistering winter winds.
Your thumbs and hands
are of a boat man.
The scars around your throat...
Remnants of a chain I assume.
A warship's slave.
Correct?
How, how did he...!
Hey! Get out!
Although you act like a scum
you are very smart and crafty
I assume you're born
in the year of the monkey?
Good at manipulating others,
so May? Right?
Only my mother knows
my real birth date...
Do you know my mother...?
How would I know your mother.
Oh! my Master!
I was born 1884, days of the black monkey,
time of the white rat!
Nothing has been working out
for me lately!
How will this year be for...
You, becareful of the seas.
Especially this month,
stay away from water.
Recently, I was caught
under heavy rain,
for days, I lay sick!
The doctors told me
I should have died, but I was lucky!
You are lucky thus far but,
you must be more careful,
your life depends on it.
My life?
Master! Help me!
I am but a poor lowly man!
I lost my father
at a young age and...
never met the right woman...
I've spent my life all by myself...
Brother, he's gone...
He left? He left?
Everyone left?
Yup, everyone.
Master! Master!
That was amazing, master!
Master?
I am no such thing
Thanks to you man,
I mean thanks to you master,
I remembered I, Pal-Yong,
did not come to Han Yang
to work these petty jobs
and live day by day.
I should aim for better things
and bet big!
Bet big? Where?
Oh, God, It's my time!
I have the best luck today!
Nice, nice! Let us play!
Investigate Lord Heungseon-gun's
recent activities.
The King has fallen ill,
royal families
will begin to seek power.
Figure out
who he has been meeting,
what he's been doing, watch him carefully.
This is our Baeohgae's
famous spectacle!
That kid,
he's a brother of the tavern lady!
Wow, the states are high!
Have a look.
Now, show your hands please
High five!
High eight.
So intense!
Noble sir, what is your hand?
I have...
double nines!
I win again...
You move impatiently, my Lord.
1, 2, 7 and...
double tens!
Double tens?
Not possible, I had one of the tens!
My Lord, your eye sight
is darkening so quickly!
You filthy cheater!
Come here you brat!
You thief!
You cheating thief!
You're quite large...
Arrest these gamblers!
Where do you think you're going!
Please forgive me!
I was just watching!
Let's go!
I was just looking...
Follow me.
Hold on...
Wait!
Lieutenant!
What brings you here?
I had some business.
He cannot remember me.
What a remarkable face.
His eyes glow in the dark.
A high prominent nose.
This man...
Has the features of a tiger!
We're safe,
no one’s following us!
Well...
For saving my life.
I'm alright.
Take it, it's fine!
Why are you staring at me
so hard.
My apologies.
You have rare glowing eyes.
Glowing eyes?
I have eyes that glow
like a tiger's?
Are you some sort of
fortune teller?
You must be very talented!
Let's see...
So back at the gambling house,
you noticed my eyes
blinking and glowing?
No sir.
A true tiger would hide his eyes
at such a pitiful place.
You were constantly watching me
back there huh?
I am Ha-Eung Lee.
I am...
Mu-Myung Choi
Mu-Myung you say...
Can't be your real name...
you must have had quite a life?
If fate has it,
let us meet again!
I will leave now.
Goodbye.
Extra precautions, for this writing
will be hung at a Seowon.
Seowon(Library)
I appreciate you coming
at such an hour.
I've spent a long time
in Ganghwa Island and
I don't have many relatives,
and none whom
I am comfortable with.
My gratitude, Your Majesty.
Please summon me anytime.
How is my writing?
My King,
you mustn't write this.
There are many Seowons across the nation,
which ever receives
a writing from the King himself,
will have power over the others.
Did you know this?
I have ears to listen,
of course I understand the effects.
But, Jwa-Keun Kim has requested,
how could I turn him down?
I have ears to listen,
but have lost the mouth
to say no.
I shall rewrite this.
Tomorrow the Minister of Finance,
Byung-Woon Kim
Nahab (Jwa-Keun Kim’s concubine)
We pray to
the dragon king of the seas,
take our humble offerings
and give us
wealth, fame, and respect!
Provide the unfortunate with luck,
lengthen our lives,
heal the sick,
guide the dead to the heavens.
Lead our Jangdong Kim-Moon
Family to eternity!
Bring us great fortune and wealth!
Look at all that white rice!
They're feeding all that to the fish?
All that precious rice!
Our ives are worth less than
those fish.
That Kim-Moon Family
has gone mad with riches!
The people are starving to death!
How do they have so much?
Please stop brother!
You don't see the pile of money?
Come on, hurry.
Did you not listen to
the strange master earlier?
He warned you about water.
Do you know how much we lost
because of that daylight demon?
Think of all those people
I paid to stand outside!
You paid them?
What about us?
Hurry up,
we don't have time.
- Brother.
- What!
You don't know how to swim!
If we don't steal it,
someone might steal it before us!
I said hurry up!
You're driving me crazy brother!
You don't have to hit me...
You aren't coming?
Leave!
Leave me then you idiots!
Fine, we're really leaving!
Let's go for a bowl of soup.
Yeah, sounds good.
Really? You're really leaving?
Do you have any loyalty!
Becareful of water,
becareful of water...
Becareful of water...
It's freezing!
What is that!
Someone went in.
He's going for the money?
What a waste.
What are you waiting for!
Can't you see him!
Someone do something!
Handle this!
Becareful of water...
Come here!
He ruined the ritual
for the dragon king.
Give him a harsh penalty!
Yes, Ma'am!
I don't care if he dies.
Beat him!
Yes, sir!
Watch carefully!
Anyone who messes
with the 'Jangdong Kim-Moon' Family
Stop!
The money and rice
you have squandered
Yet the 'Jangdong Kim-Moon' Family
rather feed fish?
And try to stomp and
kill our people like insects?
Do you not fear the heavens!
Do you not fear our people!
He's right!
He’s right!
Alright then.
We shall let him live,
please calm down!
- Let's go
- Yes, sir!
Daylight demon...
Becareful of water...
Come on, I got you.
Thank goodness!
Amazing!
Thank you.
Here.
Thank you
Do you think you can find
the next Young Lord of Ganghwa?
None of them
are King worthy material
You little child thief!
I am not a thief!
Someone threw it away!
Big excuses!
Let it be.
Let the child have some food
left over from the feast.
Take it.
I have my reasons
for my actions...
But still, I will not forget
your grace.
It's must be that child.
The child with fiery eyes...
True king's potential
is within that girl!
Ja-Young Min
Future Empress Myeongseong
Here you are!
Please come with me.
To where?
You will find out,
please follow me.
This way.
The hero who saved
the citizen by the river!
Baeohgae's new rising Master!
Master Choi, this way!
This way, please, we're almost there.
This is the man!
He predicted my future to perfection!
Grettings.
Applause!
How much for his readings?
His readings...
three coins per, two for you,
one for me, yes or no?
Huh? What!
Insufficient? Then I want free boarding
at the tavern, indefinitely
I can conceive a deal with
the tavern lady.
It wouldn't be so bad
for her either.
Of course!
Yes or no?
Indefinitely...
free... housing?
Three coins per person!
Make a line!
What are you waiting for?
Come in, please!
Please pay back what you owe.
My father worked hard for
that money before he passed.
I paid for his funeral fees,
I paid for his body to be prepared
and his grave to be dug, no?
I do appreciate that
but preparing the body cost
eight coins,
and six coins
for the grave diggers,
I remember correctly, right?
Hmm?
I'm not sure.
Call forth the workers
and let us confirm.
They will agree with me.
My father has more than
one hundred coins to be paid back.
How dare a child talk back
to an adult like this!
Our family has lost it's pillar,
I do not ask for
your pitty or sorrows,
But I expect you to behave
like a man not a lowly thief.
Why you...!
Jayoung, why don't you
help me in the kitchen.
Help the family servants,
with your efforts I promise
to pay your hundred coins back.
Our family is poor of
materialistic things,
but it seems your family
is poor of heart and brains.
Have I ever seen such a brat!
I will be back
for my father's money.
But, I will not listen to your lies
and excuses disguised as empathy.
So please stop talking.
Come and throw some salt at her!
Miss!
The little child thief,
I looked into her.
Who is she?
She is a servant working
at the Wallsong-ru Concubine house.
No one knows her name or address.
Is that so?
I will leave a message
at Wallsong-ru,
to bring the child here upon sight.
No, Do not send anyone
to Wallsong-ru.
If Byung-Woon Kim finds out about her,
he will look into all of our affairs.
Bring me a Concubine's disguise.
Miss, you cannot!
Today I shall play a Concubine.
Miss...
This place is amazing!
Truly genius!
Are you not impressed!
Come, next! Next!
Come in, please!
This way, this way!
Good!!
We have love, wealth,
honor, caution readings!
Chun-Jung Choi has not been seen
at the Choi's residence.
We have searched Ganghwa carefully
but he has not been seen.
So? You have failed?
Why don't we service
a shaman or fortune teller?
Fortune teller?
There have been many famous
fortune tellers lately.
Baeohgae has a new Master Choi.
Alright.
If I seek amusement
I will find one.
Go find Chun-Jung Choi!
Do you understand!
Yes, sir!
What brings such a noble
elder down here...
You honor me, my Lord.
I have heard so much about you,
I could not resist.
I waited such a long time
to see you.
What do you see?
Do I become rich?
Do I have peaceful days
before I die?
His face is definitely of a tiger,
but why is his future so bleak?
Just like when we met,
you have a rude habit of
staring at my face.
Are you infatuated with my face?
Yes, sir,
you have a wonderful face.
As I have said previously,
you have the face of a tiger.
But your future is merely of
a pleasure seeking nobody.
A nobody?
Are you mocking me?
No, I just find it odd.
Your future has anger towards
the higher ups, and no fear.
You are not afraid to
speak your mind.
In the past couple days,
I am sure you spoke too much
and got yourself into trouble.
Your future is spent writing
apology letters to the nobles.
Are you telling
my future or mocking me!
You bastard!
There is nothing to be
angry about,
because I am not telling
your future.
I thought other wise, but now I know.
Are you playing me?
What are you doing here?
Why do you come meet a fortune teller
and give false information?
What do you have to gain?
Maybe, this could be the beginning
of a trusting relationship.
Bunguyusin
Faith should reign over
the relation between friendship
Or maybe not...
Why don't I act like you this time?
Let me tell you your fortune!
Someone will come looking for you.
He will prepare
a feast just for you.
However!
During the feast
you must choose your words wisely.
Very masterful.
He is very accurate!
Come in.
That man is Heungseon-gun, the King's relative right?
Move aside,
I must throw some salt.
Why?
Because I've heard things.
Two fortune tellers
have told his future.
One died right after the reading,
and the other disappeared,
yet to be found.
Heungseon-gun, that man...
He's been living recklessly
for some time now.
Ever since Ganghwa Island,
5 years ago,
he came back broken.
He brings bad energy!
Come, hurry! Next! Next!
Come in, come in.
Are you alright?
Mother...
Try standing up.
Who are you?
I am Ban-Dal's daughter Bong-Ryun.
Your mother has fallen sick, I am here
to perform a healing ritual.
My sickness will plague you too.
I do not fall to sickness.
you will be fine as well.
I know it because I can see.
Take care, Young Lord.
What brings you here.
I am here to give you
a small gift, Princess
You like birds right?
I chose this one myself.
Take it back.
I hate animals caged up.
You are not allowed to
enter here freely.
If you come in again without permission,
you will be punished.
Why do you smell of
such perfume?
Have you used a Concubine's perfume
to seduce men?
Even if this world collapses,
and you are the only man alive,
please do not worry,
I will never seduce you.
I am the only person who knows
your past and is willing to accept you
You loser.
Do you think I will let you go
with with another?
Let go!
I said let go!
My princess!
Let go of her!
I will leave the bird.
Miss, are you alright?
Hurry!
Let's go!
Do you realize who we are meeting!
Wallsong-ru (Concubine tavern)
Master Choi!
The Queen Mother's nephew,
Lord Cho wishes to see you.
Please come in.
Is this what
Heungseon-gun spoke of?
What are you doing?
You see a ghost or something?
What are you waiting for,
come in.
We're coming.
When will we ever come to
a place like this!
Let's go.
Miss, please buy
one of these pendants.
No, thank you.
Please be kind and buy one.
Pease be kind and buy one.
My Lord!
Miss, please buy
one of these pendants.
No, thank you.
Please be kind and buy one.
Pease be kind and buy one.
My Lord!
Lord Chun-Jung!
My Lord...