I said take the shot.
Previously
Please stop!
Young Lord Chun-Jung is different.
It's as if he shines.
You do remember what I told you?!
you cannot let others know
that you can see people's futures.
But it is also a curse...
if people find out about your gift.
You can never reveal
your abilities to others!
You are the one who perishes!
So, you are the one with
the real gift, not your mother?
Bong-Ryun!
Mother!
Could you possibly
still remember me?
I've waited 5 years, upon the hill
with the ribbon tied to the tree.
Bong-Ryun!
How dare you put
your hands on her!
The fireflies came to greet
you as well.
It really must be you,
my Bong-Ryun.
What are you doing?
Write the royal order.
Our family's future depends on
your mission in Ganghwa.
And we must get rid of Kyung Choi.
Jangdong Kim-Moon' Family
your marriage with the princess.
Arrest Kyung Choi for hiding explosives
in the ship headed to Hanyang!
Father!
Once he arrives, a fair investigation
will reveal the truth.
As princess, can you vouch for
what he is saying?
I witnessed Kyung Choi and his men
move gun powder onto the ship.
Bong-Ryun!
Lower your head and
live in secrecy.
You must keep your life!
Father!
Promise me!
Promise that you will
not kill him!
If you ever betray our family
or try to run from us,
your mother and Chun-Jung
will be slaughtered!
I will wait patiently,
and never forget...
I will avenge my father's death.
Go find Chun-Jung Choi!
Do you think you can find
the next Young Lord of Ganghwa?
Are you looking for someone
with the potential to be King?
The King has fallen ill,
royal families
will begin to seek power.
I have the best luck today!
Please forgive me!
What a remarkable face.
What are you doing here?
Why do you come meet a fortune teller
and give false information?
Heungseon-gun, that man...
He's been living recklessly
for some time now.
True king's potential is
within that girl!
She is a servant working
at the Wallsong-ru Concubine house.
No one knows her name or address.
Why would Bong-Ryun betray me?
This question is stuck in my head.
If you cannot forget her
and seek after her
she will kill you
and complete her destiny.
Episode 4
My Lord!
My Lord Chun-Jung.
Please stay!
My Lord!
Let go of me!
Why? You grabbed me.
It really is you, Lord Chun-Jung
If I wasn't Chun-Jung Choi,
you would be beaten or hurt.
If I was Chun-Jung Choi,
you would die.
What do you choose?
My Lord...
You should at least check
that I am still human
and not a rabid animal.
before you grabbed me.
I don't want to know why
you betrayed me.
Finding the truth
will not bring my father back
So just...
Go live your life
Thank you,
for being alive...
If you do not forget her
and go looking for her
She will kill you
and complete her destiny!
He's no ordinary Master!
I agree sir.
I was wondering
why the city was empty,
everyone's down here.
Please move aside!
Move! Move along!
What is everyone doing?
- Can't you tell?
- What is all this?
You guys refugees rom Qing dynasty?
Your lives are useless readings
won't change that.
Aren't you the Red Monk?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to interrupt
our business?
Hasn't our master saved your life?
That is true, thanks...
Hey!
You stinky little brat! Back off!
Whatever,
go easy on him.
Yes, boss!
I'll 'Go easy on him!'
Easy huh?
What are you doing?
Piss off!
You idiots!
Literally go easy, relax!
Hey!
Why! You!
Idiot!
Don't ever touch my brother again!
You crooked monk!
Sister!
Boss, you alright?
What? What's wrong?
You are the first woman
to treat me like this.
What?
Suddenly in love?
You like her?
You do like her!
He likes her!
Look at him blush!
Your cheeks are brighter
than a bride's!
Silence! Shut up!
I'll let it slide this time.
Let's go...
I said easy! Easy!
He said go easy!
Stay, get your other side beat too!
Where are you going?
Out the back.
You just got back.
I have some unfinished business...
Come on now...
You kept me in that room
since I woke up,
I've been fortune telling all day!
This is a prison!
You're right, it is a prison.
Day and night,
money generating prison!
If I can stay with you
I could be locked up here forever
You... crazy...
Don't be like that!
My Master look over there!
Look at that long line!
Over there too!
How desperate must they be,
to wait here for more than
10 hours since the morning!
5 Sijin
Roughly 10 hours
Just up to them.
OK!
Listen up, I'm sorry to inform you all
we are done for today!
We've waited all day!
Please, up to us?
Will I pass the state exams this time?
How many years have you tried?
This would be my 10th...
But it's because I've been very unlucky.
Unlucky you say...
So unlucky you gets to live off of
your little sister working
at the prostitute house,
pouring drinks, selling her smile?
While you study?
How did you know where I work?
Your clothes are old,
your face is full of worries
yet your hair smells of perfume.
Last night you were busy pouring drinks,
and this morning you just changed
your clothes? Right?
Yes, Master.
Our mother is sick too.
Hey, fortune teller,
I've seriously worked hard.
I've done everything I can.
And yet you still fail?
Listen, I've spoken to other fortune tellers
They said I was unlucky to
constantly fail but...
I feel like my luck is changing...
So now...
You think I'll pass?
If you really studied hard...
Maybe your birth date
and time are wrong.
And as for your exam...
I will not say.
Huh?
I will refund your money.
Here's some more,
for your 10 hour long wait.
This is worth 5 times more than
my payment.
My apologies.
You can't be serious.
- Older brother!
- What?
Stop talking.
Those siblings from earlier.
Why'd you just send them?
His destiny is like a candle flickering
in the winter wind.
Within fortune telling,
he is an unsolvable problem.
Weak both in the mind and body.
A candle in the winter...
A candle in the wind
Easily blown out?
He has good parents
but he think's he is of greatness.
Unaware of his limitations
like a candle on the damp ground.
He is lazy and thrill seeking.
But the odd thing is...
For the past 10 years,
something has protected his flame,
Luck?
He had good luck?
He said he had bad luck
and flunked the exams.
That's why it is odd.
Is that why you didn't read his future?
Out of all the bad people,
do you know who
Nope.
The weakest and most untalented.
Afraid to be outed,
carries a knife around.
When threatened,
swings his knife around.
So a fight that could end with fists,
becomes a cold murder scene.
That's the kind of future awaiting him.
Acting out extremely to hide
his weakness.
Avoiding him is best.
Anyways, does this guy pass the exam?
Does he fail?
What's it to you?
I didn't accept his money.
Come on, just tell me.
You already know, just tell me huh?
Jangdong Kim-Moon Jwa-Keun Kim’s residence
I opened my eyes this morning
to this beautiful weather.
Which is why
Nahab (Jwa-Keun Kim’s concubine)
I sent out messages
for all you noble women
It's my honor
that every single misses showed up.
Who are we to ever deny you Ma'am.
Yes, Ma'am.
Of course, we came.
My lady, Princess Wha-Ryun is here.
What?
Princess?
The princess is here?
I don't recall sending a message
to the princess...
What brings you here?
Am I not allowed to be here?
That is not what I mean...
I heard all the noble women
were gathering.
So I came to greet everyone.
A kind gesture, your highness
Absolutely beautiful!
Yes, yes...
I hear your mother passed away early,
no one to have taught you
womanly manners.
Maybe we can teach you.
How does a former prostitute mock
our princess's origins
It is ironic that she thinks
she's above others.
Move aside.
Please sit.
Although I do not know
my womanly manners,
I would still enjoy
talking with all of you.
By any chance,
Have you heard
about the ugly prostitute's love story?
Excuse me?
Once lived an ugly prostitute who secretly
loved a handsome noble man.
She successfully called
the noble man out
to meet her by the water well.
My Lord? My Lord!
My Lord!
Let go of me!
She was rejected harshly.
How she pleaded and begged.
Her nickname became
'Pants grabber'
Her colleagues and clients all
began calling her
'Pants grabber', ugly 'Pants grabber'.
What a sad and tragic tale.
Who on earth is this ugly prostitute?
- Who?
- Who is it?
She is...
- Who is she?
- Who?
She is...
Oh no, my dress!
Is there anyone outside?
I just bought this yesterday!
How did you know!
No one knows about my past,
No can knows anymore!
Lord Haok used to tell us that
the princess had abilities to
look into people's hearts...
Is this true?
As you said, my mother
never taught me womanly manners.
but she taught me other skills.
The nobleman you loved
is now a prosecutor.
He has no idea you are
'Pants grabber' either.
You wrote a letter to him,
with loving heart.
What will happen
if the Lord Haok finds out?
Every time I see
something devious from you,
will I have to tell the Lord?
Finally showing your true colors.
What do you want?
Riches? Men?
My life?
What could I do with your life?
All I need is a room.
A room in the Wallsong-ru prostitute house.
What?
Miss! Miss!
I only provided you with one fact,
Na-Hab recently sent drinks
to the prosecutor's office
How did you get the Wallsong-ru room
I saw Na-Hab's face
within one of the employees
Pardon?
You're amazing!
But what are you trying to do
Look for the girl.
That girl...
Will become my weapon.
My my, when will it stop snowing?
Where are you going?
My Master, I am going to get you health
prolonging medicine before the winter comes!
Why? So you can work me
day and night?
Working hard makes you rich too!
Hello?
Have you come for medicine?
Yes.
What are you staring at?
Let's go in.
Owner! Let's see...
- Please come in.
- Give me the best in value not price!
Thank you for stopping by!
Yeah, sure.
Give this to your mother.
This is expensive herbal soup
your going to give it to her?
She has great respect and posture.
She is a well taught daughter of a noble.
With skinny wrists,
too weak to properly cut the herbs,
she is of a poor starving family,
Use this to help feed your family.
Do not refuse out of pride.
Noble?
Master!
Are you mad?
Why are you over the top charitable?
Do you think I was being charitable?
That child back there
is destined for greatness.
She looked normal to me.
What? She's got
the face of an empress?
Who knows if
she will become an empress
We shall have to see.
My goodness,
even if you're a Master,
you just wasted that herbal soup
and money
Such a waste.
My wrists are skinny too.
Look!
Changdeokgung Injeongjeon
My illness is worsening,
and I am worried about
who will take over.
I plan on passing
the crown to a relative
Cheoljong
25th King of the Joseon Dynasty
Haok Jwa-Keun Kim (Prime Minister)
I will like to know
your thoughts on the matter.
My King you are still young.
An abdication? Not just sire!
Byung-Woon Kim (Minster of Finance)
That is enough.
I have made up my mind!
Go and find a relative of
good morals and wisdom.
Help the kingdom and find
my successor!
My King,
How could you speak of abdication?
Queen Jo
Queen Mother Hyoyu
Everyone knew this was coming.
If we do not quickly find a successor,
I will be a sinner to
this country and the throne.
Alright.
Your Majesty
I would like to introduce you to someone.
Gyeongwon-gun, Ha-Jeon Lee.
Gyeongwon-gun Ha-Jeon Lee
Ha-Jeon Lee,
an honor to meet you my King.
Now, you do not have to worry about
a successor.
Ha-Jeon here is a fine young man...
Who will proudly
lead the country as the new king?
- Stop.
- Everyone Stop.
It's been a long time, my Lord.
It sure has.
You did not show up to
the princess' gathering.
My second child had fallen ill and...
I had to pawn off my coat
leaving me with nothing to wear.
If I could borrow some money
for my child's medicine...
A king's relative borrowing money
from a Lord...
- Servant Jang.
- Yes, my Lord.
Let's go.
Stop!
Halt.
Let him go.
Are you not Lord Kim?
This vulgar servant works
for you my Lord?
I will pay for his sins,
to end your troubles.
Before anything,
he must beg for forgiveness.
Please forgive me, my Lord!
This is the Lee Family's Joseon Dynasty.
Do not ever forget that!
Yes, Lord.
Apologies my Lord.
We were about to leave.
Come on, we're leaving!
Show your respects.
He is Chi-Seong Yeon, my guardian warrior
Although he's the son of a concubine
His face might be fair
but he is a fierce warrior.
He sure had strength.
Leave us.
If I think back,
the servant begging brings me joy.
What about you?
You shouldn't be that way.
You should never provoke them,
they are like beasts.
It'll be alright. Please do not worry.
Recently the Queen Mother
has requested
for a renowned and respected
I am disappointed.
Even the Queen Mother believes
in these readings.
That isn't it.
When it comes to politics,
the people want to believe
in legends and dreams.
Let's see...
Someone does come to mind...
Queen Mother,
the person you have been looking for.
Are you Mu-Myung Choi?
Yes, my Queen Mother.
Our business here today
shall never be spoken of.
Yes, My Queen Mother.
Stop!
You dare laugh at me?
A King's bloodline?
Jae-Geung Lee
Heungin-gun
If you ever make me angry again
I will kill you
My Lord.
I'm getting drunk.
Jae-Won Lee
Heungnyeong-gun
Saju (Four Pillars)
Fortunetelling by one’s birth date and time.
These are birth dates of
the King's bloodline.
What are they looking for?
What do you think?
One is of immense greatness,
and the other loves alcohol and women.
May I ask
who these birth dates belong to?
Do not question!
She is the Queen Mother!
I have already warned you,
What happened today shall
never be spoken of.
You may leave now.
Yes, Queen Mother.
Wallsong-ru (Concubine tavern)
Let's see... Let's see...
Here it is!
You must be careful of men!
The man you see right now...
is worthless right?
Oh! She's amazing! Truly!
Throw him out and find
a new man.
- If I do will I find happiness?
- sure, sure.
Leave in peace. Now, next!
Let's see... Let's see...
The foreign fortune telling
is very popular!
Really?
Excuse me...
Sorry...
May I ask you a question...
Pardon?
I have come to your urgent request.
You have read
Lord Heungseon-gun's destiny?
Who are you?
Ministry of Justice
Responsible for prisoning criminals
and guarding them
Payment for helping the government.
Government?
What has Heungseon-gun said?
What was his destiny?
Tell me everything you know.
I am a lowly fortune teller,
but I read people's lives.
I will not share
their privacy with others.
Excuse me.
You dare deny
the government's request?
If the government wishes to learn
about Heungseon-gun,
tell your superiors
to come find me themselves.
If they put in the effort
maybe I'll tell you.
I work with the lady shaman.
if you tell me your story,
I will make sure to tell the shaman.
It's fine.
I do not need my future read.
Everything will be alright.
What do you mean?
A man promised my brother
that he would make sure
Pass the state exam?
Who has said that to you?
Our mother has fallen ill
trying to take care of us.
We had to sell her house as well.
My brother felt horrible and responsible,
because he was just unlucky
for the past 10 years.
No matter how hard he tried
he couldn't catch a break.
So they sent me off
to some Lord's place
in exchange for some money...
And paid off a high official.
A man of the Jandong Kim-Moon' Family.
You must get your money back
from that family at once!
Would they simply give it back?
I will help you.
Get the money back and run away!
- Run away?
- That is...
I'm fine right now!
I've always wanted to learn
about herbal medicine.
When my brother passes his exams
and becomes an official,
he promised to pay me back.
Then I can be free and live my life.
I will live happily.
Do not forget your dreams.
No matter what happens...
You might find yourself stranded
and lonely on
a dangerous cliff one day...
I've lost someone
in a similar situation.
I hope someone will be
there for you.
I will pray for you.
What of the task
my father has requested?
Finding the next Lord of Ganghwa
you mean?
I have not seen anyone.
No one among the relatives.
I'm sure that is.
It must be difficult to find a child
with such potential.
I have had a strange dream recently,
and would like to discuss it with you.
What is it?
I saw the Choi Family's Chun-Jung.
Chun-Jung despised me
from the darkness.
But suddenly the darkness disappeared.
Are you... chasing after him?
It's been 3 years
since I've heard his name.
Alright then, I believe you.
But... you cannot forget our agreement.
Betraying Kyung Choi
for our Kim-Moon Family
in exchange for Chun-Jung Choi's life?
Do not worry,
we haven't killed him.
If he is still alive
you should be worried princess.
I bet he will come after you.
If I was Chun-Jung Choi
you would die.
So just go live your life!
Where's mine?
Eat later.
Mine!
Master, have some breakfast!
Sit here and have some breakfast.
Please, take a seat.
Here...
Try the soup! My goodness!
Master, as you have requested.
I have looked into the man who failed
his exams for 10 years.
He is an arrogant scum student,
living off of his parents.
There is a street
where many students live.
He resides with traveling students.
Has his own private room.
His mother and younger sister
send him money,
With that money he gets drunk
and wakes up late.
He lies that he is tired from studies
but in reality
he spends all his time gambling
and drinking with other students.
All these students become close friends
and spend everyday living like that.
I passed!
I passed! I passed!
When he first failed he was alright!
Idiots!
It was his first time,
surely he would pass on the next...
I passed! I passed!
I finally passed!
Failing twice became three times,
then four...
All his drinking buddies
slowly disappeared.
He ended up selling his family home
and had no where to stay.
Even if he wanted to be a farmer
like his father,
they had already sold
all their land to support him.
His pride couldn't bare...
working for someone else's farm.
That's how his 10 years went!
Where are you going brother?
Mother is ill!
Brother!
That's why he blamed luck.
'It's not my fault,
I've been unlucky.'
it's my unlucky destiny.'
The only way to handle
the pain of his choices.
This time though,
he bribed the Kim-Moon Family.
Surely he'd pass right?
Just tell us.
We're partners, friends!
Tell me!
- Anyone inside?
- Yes, who is it?
He doesn't even have manners.
Eating breakfast?
Fake fortune teller.
Been a while huh?
Just leave, please.
No!
No matter how hard I try not to be,
I'm furious.
You don't even know all the hardships
I've been through
A measly fortune teller
looks down on me?
I'll come see
your face once I pass, huh?
Your destiny has you hanging yourself.
You really want me to tell you?
Now? All of a sudden?
It's for your poor sister and
another woman who cares for her.
Go on.
You...
Your destiny has you hanging yourself.
You really want me to tell you?
Now? All of a sudden?
It's for your poor sister and
another woman who cares for her.
Go on.
You...
fail...
Your bribes are useless.
And you are doomed to fail.
What?
Go back to the Kim-Moon Family
and ask for your money.
It's the only way to save
your mother and sister.
You fake fortune teller...
When I pass
I'm going to come back and kill you!
You hear?
What are you looking at?
I'll see you then.
Goodness, what a scumbag.
The superiors are planning a celebration
for your promotion
I am not sure if I am worthy to attend.
Why would you think that.
I thank you and the prosecutors
for my success.
You are a dear colleague.
Thank you, officer.
Let me pour you a drink.
What's wrong my Lord?
Nothing.
He's come looking for Chun-Jung Choi.
Chun-Jung must be nearby!
Get someone! Help!
He's crazy!
You scumbag get out!
Damn you!
Back from your acceptance ceremony?
Bangbangre
A list of people who have passed
the state exam
You failed?
Yeah!
You wrote a charm and cursed me!
I know you did!
Why would I?
You blame misfortune now me?
Shut up! It's your fault
you did something to me! Fix it!
There's no point.
You will suffer misfortune
for the next 20 years.
What?
Master! Why are you provoking
a mad man!
- Try stopping him!
- How could I?
Misfortune until I'm 55 years old?
Take it back!
Sure, I take it back.
Happy?
Whatever I say or don't say
It's purely your destiny.
No!
I said it isn't!
Listen, the past 10 years,
you were very fortunate.
You happily squandered your life away.
Leaving your mother and sister,
to carry your weight.
You used up all of your good days.
Lies! This cannot be!
There's no way!
For the next 20 years...
You will suffer the consequences of
your choices.
Even the most unfortunate succeed.
If they try their best.
But a scum like you...
The destiny you trusted?
Will turn it's back.
Come out! Get out!
Sister! Sister!
We're letting him leave?
He's going to make another mess!
Let's see... Let's see...
It's completely empty today.
Where did Miss go?
Leaving me here alone.
Miss! Where'd you go?
The Lady Song-Hwa left this for you.
Your hands were very cold.
Boil these roots and drink them.
They will help.
It came with these.
There will be a horrific accident.
We must get her out of there
before it happens.
Pardon?
Never mind.
What's going on...?
What's wrong?
Dan-Ah, stay here.
I'll be right back.
Do not worry.
Miss! Miss!
Come on...
Absolutely ruined!
This was expensive!
What is wrong?
Some maniac brother took Song-Hwa
as if he wanted to kill her.
He was crazy!
Where's Song-Hwa's house?
Song-Hwa...
Sulfur!
Petroleum Sulfur / Crude oil
Often used as the raw material for matches
Song-Hwa,
Miss Song-Hwa wake up!
Miss Song-Hwa!
We must leave!
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Hey!
Who are you? Die!
This was it...
I was the one to die today...
Die!
My Lord...
The bruises around your neck
will hurt.
Where are we?
My humble residence.
Where's Song-Hwa?
Song-Hwa and her mother are safe
thanks to you.
Her older brother Song-Jin
visited me today.
I anticipated that he would lash out.
He came to you? Why?
Because I accurately read him
his destiny.
Are you disappointed?
Because I'm a fortune teller?
I am honored my grace.
The princess conversing with
a lowly fortune teller like myself.
This way.
What?
Why?
Help me stand up.
Your legs were not injured.
I'm certain you can walk on your own.
This way.
What?
Why?
Help me stand up.
Your legs were not injured.
I'm certain you can walk on your own.
Are you disappointed?
Yes! Incredibly disappointed!
We were friends, then newly weds.
You were the commanding family
of Ganghwa,
and I was a herb picking
daughter of a shaman.
Back then you never treated me
like a peasant.
You expect that...
I would be different?
Where were you?
I was...
I was with the princess!
You expect me to believe this?
Should I tell him his son treats
his father's loved ones
with absolutely no respect?
Why are you doing this?
I'm investing.
Where is this Master Choi staying?
what can we do against
the Kim-Moon Family?
We cannot oppose them for orphans.
Who is capable of protecting our weak?
I will tell the King
about the nursery children.
What about Heungseon-gun?
The man called
Master Choi will not talk.
What do you ask in return?
I was instructed to bring...
To whom does this destiny belong to?
This…
This is...
Lord Dojeonggung
He does not know to fear the world.
His son is
what we are curious about.
When I flip my glass...
Kill him.
Nobody can deny the world
when it calls upon you.
Mark my words.
That is called...
destiny.