Episode 2
You came back...
Bong-Ryun
Do you, still remember me?
How could I forget you?
I've waited 5 years,
upon the hill with
the ribbon tied to the tree.
Is that so...
How have you been?
Why did you suddenly leave?
I will tell you in due time.
You...
aren't glad to see me?
Bong-Ryun, Bong-Ryun!
I said,
aren't you glad to see me?
My Princess!
How dare you
put your hands on her!
I should cut your throat!
Princess?
What do you mean by...
Step back!
Dan-Ah, stop!
He is the son of
the Lord of Ganghwa.
Step back and
show your respect!
She is our Princess.
In due time,
I will tell you everything...
Please excuse me.
This marriage is too extravagant
for my son.
Kyung Choi (Ganghwa Governor)
Please, reconsider.
If you're loyal to the crown,
how can you deny the King's orders?
Delay the cargo vessel's departure
and constitute an engagement.
The cargo vessel will be
on schedule.
It will not be delayed.
Okay, as you wish.
A million coins?
How are you so wealthy?
It is our family's fortune
that Kyung Choi seized
and hid in the ship.
All this money
you have plundered
and embezzled cost this country
it's economic crisis!
This is quite a feat...
Byung-Hak Kim
The King and Kyung Choi
are already in alliance.
If the cargo vessel reaches
the King,
Haoak Jwa-Keun Kim (Prime Minister)
he will annihilate our family.
Our family's future depends on
your mission in Ganghwa.
Do you understand?
Yes, father,
I will delay the ship's departure.
Then, I will extract
all the riches back.
Why don't you just assassinate
Kyung Choi?
If anything happens to him,
the ship will lock down
and set sail right away.
It will not stop
at any port and go straight
to the royal guards in Hanyang.
Thus, our family won't be
able to interfere.
Instead, we should let him live
and coerse him.
Kyung Choi has a son yet
to be married?
Yes, father.
Take the princess with you.
Even Kyung Choi cannot deny
a Royal wedding proposal,
he will have to delay
the departure.
His son is decent and useful.
We could make him our follower.
Yes, father.
He is Hanyang's best fortuneteller.
Gwansanggam
A royal office dedicated to studying
geography, astronomy, math…
He came to see
this land's Feng Shui,
and decided to pay respects to you,
the local governor.
Why don't you tell
these young men their fortune?
Shall I, sir?
You have a good face.
What is your birth date and time?
You mean me?
He has been failing
his test for years.
Will he find
any success this year?
I was born on the year of the Monkey,
on the 18th day of the 6th moon.
Like a stone buried in dry desert.
You should not expect greatness,
just tag along a worthy friend
and hope for the best.
Is that so?
A worthy friend?
He must mean you Chun-Jung!
Young Lord, how about yours?
I'm okay, thank you.
Born in 1984, on the 28th of May
And the time?
I do not know.
I was dispatched to Gyeongsang
as a temporary governor
and missed his birth.
Hm... without the time of birth,
I cannot read accurately.
He's a dragon.
A black dragon soaring up
from a vast plain.
Your name will be known
across the nation!
With both wisdom and strength,
you are worthy of
becoming a great general.
Huh? Governor Choi's son is
such a noteworthy champion?
That is enough!
Also! Your soul mate is
very near by!
His what? soul mate?
She is no ordinary human.
She is of royalty
and greatness.
Host!
Where is the bathroom?
Jungbang (Bathroom)
How can i stand idle as you pour
poison into this young man's ear?
I shall help him wash his ears.
Are you saying
my words are poison?
What is this insolence!
Apologies my Lord!
There's always some crazy person
trying ruin the day!
It's been a while, Kyung!
Let him go,
he is my old friend.
My friend it's been 10 years,
what an entrance!
He is my oldest friend.
The people know him as
the Monk of nature.
Monk of nature?
This monk predicted the coming of
Emperor Xiangfeng
when he was just a child.
He is a great monk.
Is that actually him?
Could I please join your table?
Sure.
Chun-Jung,
let me cure your ears,
listen carefully.
You are in fact the black dragon.
Dragons have great power
but lack finesse
and soar high but
fall just as hard.
Soon you will experience
great loss and defeat.
Also, you will prove unworthy of
your soul mate's greatness and soon,
will lose her too.
But!
There is one right thing
that man said.
Soon, you will have to choose
between two paths.
Are you disguising insults
about my life as a cure?
Please take my cup.
It is my appreciation.
You don't believe his words,
nor mine.
Destiny and my future,
can be told
from multiple narratives.
Fortune telling is like putting
a ring on an ear
and calling it an earring.
you've just taught and
proved it's uselessness.
And anyone who pardons wisdom
on me, even a beggar,
is my teacher.
In your words, I am the beggar?
Why'd you leave so early?
Things were getting interesting.
Father looked furious.
He was demanding me
to leave with his eyes.
Right... After the monk spoke
he looked distressed.
Young Lord!
A message from the princess.
Pr... Princess? Wait...
Open it sir.
Let us meet... Alone...
Bong-Ryun...
I mean...
Princess, what may I do for you?
We have something to see,
let us go.
Go where?
The night is upon us.
Follow me.
If I told you why I snooped
around the port at night
and snuck into the boat...
If I told you my reasons
and ask for service,
will you help me?
Help?
Are you in trouble?
Are you asking me to
believe this?
Please listen to me.
A horrific accident
will happen here,
and I cannot do anything
about it.
The only person I can trust...
is you Young Lord.
Princess, you have
always been different.
I will never take
your word as false.
If so, will you help me?
I will always come to
your rescue.
But you already knew that no?
I have one question though.
What do they earn
from committing such heinous acts?
Truthfully...
I am not certain of their motives,
it could be money, power,
or someone's death...
but I am not sure.
One thing for certain is
they will do anything to succeed.
Rather it be sacrificing hundreds
and burning this whole place down,
they will do anything to get
what they want.
Sacrificing hundreds you say...
I will begin searching
and observing Bong-Ryun,
I mean Princess.
Let go of me you bastards!
I said let go!
Young Lord why?
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't expect greatness and
tag along a worthy friend?
These were your words for me?
Huh?
All I do is deliver
what is written.
Now read my true future.
Let me try again...
Try again,
and try harder this time.
Please excuse me first.
Well... your powers my princess.
If you can see someone's death,
can you also see good things?
Like someone's greatness...
or who might love and
care for them?
Greatness...
I have seen it once
within one person.
Ja-Young Min (Future Empress Myeongseong)
I do not know who she is.
She was merely a child passing by.
What about, someone to care,
and love for?
That...
Those things even
ordinary people can see!
He brightens up
at the sight of you.
Brightens?
My Bong-Ryun
will be married soon!
What do you mean married!
The fireflies came to
greet you as well.
It really must be you,
my Bong-Ryun.
My Bong-Ryun?
I must... leave now.
Cold and darkness...
What?
Suksaljigi (A cold murderous breeze)
Explain yourself.
You are like a scary forsaken sword
discarded upon a cliff.
You do not
cherish life thus...
you are fine with murder...
Please be careful.
Murder you say...
You are correct this time.
Young Lord!
I left a letter in your room.
It writes that you are
leaving to Jeolla-do.
Jangdong Kim-Moon' Family
is requesting
your marriage with the princess.
The princess and I?
All of this is
about the cargo vessel.
Nothing much change.
I have requested for you
to stay with the Monk,
go train for a few years.
Once the ship sets sail,
horrible events will consume us.
Respectfully, no sir.
I shall not leave!
What?
What did you just say?
Young Lord!
Even after winning the state exam
at 17, I stayed by your side.
Yet you tell me to do nothing?
Hide from the world,
and lose the love of my life?
Why must I live like this?
Everything is for your sake.
I will not leave.
I have made a promise to
the princess.
And I plan on keeping it.
You have met with her separately?
This is my martial arts technique
Seven Dragons.
You still don't wish to
come with me?
I've lived my whole life
as my father commanded.
I won't have it anymore.
It is quite ironic because,
your father has suffered
just like you.
He couldn't accept your fate of dying
at a young age!
Your soul mate will betray you,
and you will die young.
But if you quit everything
and come with me
you and your father will live.
Your words are inconsistent.
How can someone betray me
and be my soul mate?
Leaving with
you can change my destiny?
Then there is nothing
to be afraid of.
I can just change my future.
Sure.
Go fight against your destiny.
That is in fact, your destiny.
What are you doing?
Write the royal order.
Cheoljong
25th King of the Joseon Dynasty
Governor of Ganghwa, Kyung Choi,
accept your Royal command.
The Royal Family approves
and congratulates
the wedding of Kyung Choi's son
Chun-Jung Choi
and his Majesty's daughter
Hwa-Ryun.
Kyung Choi must proceed with
the upmost respect,
not make any complications,
and report back accordingly.
Governor of Ganghwa, Kyung Choi,
accept the royal command!
Congratulations!
You are now the King's son in law.
Sir.
The wedding must proceed
without any complications,
why don't you delay
the cargo ship's departure?
Do you understand?
Pardon me but,
my father is the leader of this area,
Gwanjin
Main Border Port
he knows what's best.
What?
I will delay...
the ship's departure.
Yes, exactly!
Congratulations Princess!
Thank you
Is that all?
You will be a dear wife now!
Are you not excited?
Mother would have been happy.
Look over here Dan-Ah.
6 years have passed since I left,
but it is exactly the same.
Miss, we should leave now.
The court ladies have gathered
to congratulate you.
Okay.
Could I truly rid myself of them?
Miss!
Attention!
Group 1 border the port,
Group 2 guard
the main road entrance!
Yes, sir!
Although the departure
has been delayed,
we must protect the ship
at all costs.
This is a strict order from the governor,
maintain high alert!
Yes, sir!
What do you mean
you can't intrude the ship!
My apologies.
The perimeters have been reinforced.
You're saying you
cannot retrieve the cargo?
No, sir!
I will bring it back,
no matter what!
How?
You idiot...
You leave me no choice.
I shall kill the dog
that bites the feeding hand.
Move the hidden gun powder
to the port.
Enter the ship during
the chaotic aftermath of the explosion.
Yes sir!
A message from the princess!
My Lord.
Room 2-1
How dare you share
the gwana's key to a stranger...
You have committed
a major crime!
Sorry, my Lord!
I thought he was a soldier
from the gwana...
You brat!
You call that an excuse?
He paid me a small fortune
so I borrowed the key
from the officer's station.
Jilchung
Resting place for officials
I got it back quickly, I swear!
I have found
what you were looking for.
Come to the port.
My Lord!
My Lord you cannot.
I am fully aware you secretly
met Chun-Jung Choi.
Seducing him
for my family is good,
but if you become a threat
to my family...
You will suffer
another great punishment!
My Lord this is... gun powder!
Retreat!
This is gun powder!
This is a piece of oil paper,
unrecognizable sigil
because of the tear
Get him!
Surround him!
Who sent you!
Congratulations on
the young Lord's marriage my Lord.
I am more pleased
about this ship's departure.
It must arrive at Hanyang
without failure!
Yes, sir!
My Lord, you look too happy!
So Handsome!
Bong-Ryun...
the King's daughter... a princess?
Bow!
My Lord Governor! My Lord!
The ship...
the cargo vessel has exploded!
Gather all the troops guarding
the wedding!
- Off to the port!
- Yes, Lord!
Young Lord!
You must finish your wedding!
My God, what do we do?
What now!
It's a fire! A fire!
This was my dream...
He is the one responsible!
What is all of this...
My goodness...
They're all dying!
Oh, my! Oh, my!
How much is this worth my Lord!
My son has done a great job.
Now what will you do with
Ganghwa's governor Kyung Choi?
Higher ups promoted me to Commanding
Governor to handle this situation!
Arrest Kyung Choi for hiding explosives
in the ship headed to Hanyang!
He will suffer for conspiring
against the crown!
Yes, sir!
Conspire?
What do you mean?
Chun-Jung...
Father!
- Arrest him!
- Yes, sir!
My Lord! My Lord!
Father!
My Lord!
What?
Do you have something to say?
Gun powder?
You found this in your ports
and say it is of our family?
The culprit killed himself.
But, we have heard that
he was a soldier under your command!
Do you have any proof of
your claims?
It seems more likely
it was your father's gun powder...
You and your father's dark plan
to conspire against the crown.
Don't you agree?
This was your plan all along right?
You lead me to the gun powder
in the storage area on purpose!
Am I right?
Escort prisoner Chun-Jung Choi
to his cell and make sure he behaves.
Yes, sir!
My father's sword worth more than
1,000 golds from the Qing Dynasty.
A fine sword...
but I have so many of them.
This is nothing special,
take it and leave.
The higher ups have sent a judge to
investigate the ship's explosion.
The judge is said to be close
with the King and Kyung Choi.
If you stand idle,
you will be found guilty.
As long as Kyung Choi lives,
he will find a way to tie you
to the crimes committed.
And?
I shall dirty my own hands to
put your mind at ease.
When you buy livestock,
do you purchase from
a peddler unbeknownst to you?
Reaching out to you,
my life is already in your hands.
If you find me to be useless,
I shall cut my throat here.
Amusing!
Let's see how useful
my new livestock proves to be!
My Lord!
We shall see...
Come here, hurry!
The Minister of finance sends gifts
for all your hard work!
So heavy, here!
Go have some drinks!
Good night!
Long days working, huh!
My God, this is great!
What are you doing?
Lord Minister of Finance sends
his gifts for our hard work...
What, how is this possible?
Where did they go?
Where is prisoner Chun-Jung Choi?
Shouldn't he be right here?
That is...
he was here just a moment ago...
You let him loose?
No, sir!
I didn't. I swear!
Why are you standing around?
Find the people responsible
and Chun-Jung Choi!
Yes, sir!
- The prisoner has escaped!
- Find him!
Bong-Ryun...
Are you hurt?
I will watch the perimeters.
I have something to tell you.
A judge,
sharing your father's theories,
has been appointed and
is on his way.
Once he arrives, a fair investigation
will reveal the truth.
How? We have no evidence.
You have a witness.
Who?
I am the witness.
I saw everything unfold haven't I?
Byung-Woon Kim will
come after you.
I don't care.
For once,
I am glad to be a princess.
Thank you. Bong-Ryun
I won't ever,
forget your kindness.
Lord Heungseon-gun, Ha-Eung Lee
Chamhaekgwan
Greetings, I did not realize you
would be our appointed judge.
Just following the King's orders.
He has asked to proceed
with integrity.
Yes, of course!
Please.
If Jangdong Kim-Moon Family sends
Byung-Woon Kim,
it is to retrieve their ill gotten money
from the cargo ship.
Will you be safe?
My Lord, I will not disappoint.
If anything happens to me,
please take over...
I swear with my life
to protect the King
and bring them to justice.
Princess, why have you requested
to see me?
That is...
Please speak freely.
The truth is...
Who are you?
I am simply here to provide
the judge with the truth.
Do not make me cut you down.
As you please.
I am son of the Governor Kyung Choi,
Chun-Jung Choi.
Please, excuse my manners.
Put down your weapons.
Explain yourself.
Why was there gun powder
on the cargo vessel?
At first we discovered
hidden gun powder in the port.
Byung-Woon Kim's men attempted
to ignite it
but I was able to stop them.
But we did not realize Lord Kim had
also hidden gun powder in the ship.
I have an eye witness,
the princess who has helped me so far.
Is this true?
As princess, can you vouch for
what he is saying?
No.
I do not know
what he is talking about.
I witnessed Kyung Choi and his men
move gun powder onto the ship.
What are you waiting for?
Seize the criminal!
Yes, sir!
Bong-Ryun...
Bong-Ryun!
Grab him!
You have embezzled our people
and profited more than
200 times over!
Through the people's blood and sweat
you bought your way to noble status
Now tell me,
are you Ganghwa's rich noble man
or a conniving thief!
Please forgive me!
I have committed a heinous act!
I have committed a heinous act.
Your whole family is nothing
but silk wearing thieves!
Search Jinsa Chae's house and
recover all that has been stolen!
Yes, sir!
Please let me live.
Please let me live!
Our Lord is innocent!
If we let them take him
to Hanyang, they will cut his throat!
We have to rescue our Lord!
Rescue him!
Move! Back off!
Father!
Let us go!
Father, are you alright?
My son? Are you alright?
Did they hurt you?
It is dangerous here,
follow me!
No my son!
If we leave, we become
the criminals they claim we are!
Chun-Jung, remember my words!
Do not avenge me!
Lower your head and
live in secrecy.
You must keep your life!
Father!
I just wanted to keep you safe.
Father! Father!
In-Gyu!
Father!
Chun-Jung... you mustn't!
Father... hold on...
Chun-Jung!
My Son...
Forgive me...
Father! Father!
Father!
He is the Minister of Finance!
Bow down!
Do you recognize this head piece?
What does this mean?
What have you done
to my mother!
Where is my mother!
If you are worried,
you should watch your mouth.
Am I to be scared of
such a threat?
Why don't you test me.
Save Chun-Jung Choi and
see your mother's corpse.
How dare you...
my mother's...
How dare you!
Promise me!
Promise that you will
not kill him!
Spare your mother,
spare Chun-Jung...
If you wish for such,
why don't you get down
and beg me?
Please, sir. I will as I am told,
spare Chun-Jung's life.
Fine.
But once we return to Hanyang,
you must prove
your gratitude to me.
How was your fight
against destiny?
What are you doing?
Let go!
What is all this!
I have spared Chun-Jung
as you requested.
In return you must prove
you are our family's property.
No... Stop!
Let go! Let go! Stop!
If you ever betray our family
or try to run from us,
your mother and Chun-Jung
will be slaughtered!
Baeogae Street, Hanyang
If you profit in our neighborhood
you must pay tax to us!
Profit?
I merely sold smokes and some rice wine,
what do you mean profit!
Ouch, my nose!
What are you idiots doing?
Are you Jangdong Kim-Moon'
underlings?
What is it to you, dirty beggar?
Huh?