Episode 1
1862 (King Cheoljong's 13 year reign)
Ja-Young Min
Future Empress Myeongseong
Min Ja-Young.
This child seems...
foolish and pitiful to you?
That means,
there is someone behind him
who dares to fool even
the most dreadful Regent Heungseon.
Who is it?
Can you see him
through your clairvoyance?
This person has such a power
that even a great Shaman like me
has never seen.
Certainly, she will find
my Lord's hidden enemy.
Soon, he will show up,
the man your majesty fears,
to this very place.
Capture Choi Chun-Jung!
I will greatly reward
whomever is successful!
Ha-Eung Lee
Prince Heungseon
Yes, my Lord!
Who might you be?
I have some business...
with the lady inside.
Let me see her face.
How dare you ask of
such a thing?
Arrest him!
Enough!
But my lady!
If you see my face,
it'll cost you your life...
Are you still willing?
You should not, my lady.
Move aside.
My lady!
You are...
the woman…
I have been looking for.
I will help you recollect me.
From now on I will never...
Lose you nor
let you leave me again.
What have you done to Bong-Ryun?
I cannot answer.
Let her go.
I'm sorry.
You still like to watch
the birds flying,
just like back then.
Back then?
Do you...
know me?
It's more than I just know you.
Everything you see here,
is the result of trying to redeem you.
You are...
the love of my life.
Your Love?
You do not remember me
because of memory blocking poison.
Mihonsan
A psychoactive drug that causes dizziness
It is the cause of your pain, too.
We must cure it.
Or else you will lose
your sight.
You…
How will I know if you are
trying to cure me
from this poison
or to harm me with another?
3 days...
please give me 3 days,
and I will have you remember me.
And if I can't still remember you?
I'll let you go.
To wherever you desire.
Now, will you listen to
what I have to say?
Ganghwa Island
Look, it's young Lord Chun-Jung!
The first place in the state exam
at 17 years old!
He's just like a Prince
from a story book!
Chun-Jung Choi
Bong-Ryun Lee
In-Gyu Chae
Father, your son Choi Chun-Jung,
I return with the first place
in the state exam.
What an excessive title and
honor considering your inadequacy.
Kyung Choi
Put the King's grace to
your heart and behave humbly.
Yes, Father.
Hew... a day like this could do
better with warm words.
Our master is
always tougher on his son.
Young Lord, congratulations!
Congratulations! My applause!
Here now, get up!
Ban-Dal (Shaman)
Here!
Have some soup as well.
It goes down better.
Yes.
You have some good news?
Actually, I saw
young Lord Chun-Jung today.
That's why you've been
smiling all day!
I have not!
I just thought of something funny.
You are still too young to desire
a handsome guy too much!
It's not like that.
Mom, young Lord Chun-Jung
is different.
It's as if he shines... somehow.
I can't really read him like
I do with others, but...
He just shines.
Amazing, huh?
You do remember what I told you?!
you cannot let others know
that you can see people's futures.
But it is also a curse
if people find out about your gift.
You can never reveal
your abilities to others!
Yes, I will never.
Don't worry mother.
You!
You're the daughter of
Shaman Ban-Dal?
I saw you when your mother was
performing rituals for my family
Yes, young Lord of the Chae Clan.
My memory was correct,
you are quite pretty.
Follow me.
Excuse me?
I will be spending my afternoon
shooting some arrows,
but no girl servant is available.
You will have to attend
to my needs today.
Sorry my Lord, but I am tasked with
delivering medicine to the doctor's.
Please find someone else.
What are you doing!
What's in there?
Pick it up.
This will be to your graceful benefit.
Follow me.
I have no intention of
entertaining young Lords!
Does this bitch wish to die?
She still has not
learned her lesson, yet.
Take another shot.
My Lord...
What if I make a mistake?
I said take another shot!
Yes, sir!
Please stop!
What do you think you're doing?
Stop at once!
Wow... the first-place winner
has arrived.
My dearest friend has visited.
Go on, take the shot.
I said stop!
Relax my friend.
We're just jesting.
Did you not hear my order?
I said take the shot.
Sir!
Release the child
and take her home.
Yes, my Lord!
Trying to kill someone?
Are you okay?
Hurry! Get her down!
- Brother.
- Hey, Chun-Jung!
- Top of the exam?
- Congratulations!
Well done.
Let us go.
Let us go for drinks.
Wow. A wild ginseng!
A whole patch of wild ginseng!
Thank you, mountain spirit!
Brother Chun-Jung.
Shouldn't there be a prize for
whomever catches the nine tailed fox?
Sure!
Whoever catches it, I will treat
him like a big brother for a month!
Yey!
Hey, I'll catch it first!
Let me go!
Over there!
Let's go!
Take me too!
Oh, shit... that leads to
the field of Wild ginseng!
What if they step all over them?
Why is Lord Chun-Jung
with them anyways!
It's not here.
Where is it?
I heard it here...
The nine-tailed fox!
Run, run away!
- Take me with you!
- It's the nine tailed fox!
Chun-Jung!
In-Gyu!
Give me your hand!
Lift me up!
Just fall...
Fall and perish!
Just disappear!
In-Gyu!
I'll go get the help.
You should hold on meanwhile.
In-Gyu?
In-Gyu!
Come on!
Use your strength!
So, what you're saying is,
you're the nine tailed fox that
pushed me down the mountain?
That is not true.
It is you and the young Lords
who almost ruined my ginseng field
and I'm the one who pulled you up
from the cliff and saved your life.
Well...
You sure speak well
for such a small girl.
By the way, how did you
manipulate the fireflies?
I don't know.
I was just born with it.
You are a mystery.
Very peculiar
since the first time I saw you.
Excuse me?
You've seen me before?
The day I was returning
from my exam,
were you not watching me
under your dirt basket?
You were shining then too,
as if fireflies were all around you.
Thank you.
Just tell me what you want,
I shall repay my debt.
Thanks to your acting out
a great hunter that night,
many young masters got injured!
Stop acting irrationally!
Never to stand out, and always
press down your wild temper!
My apologies, sir.
You are grounded for 3 days.
Copy all the books I left in the study!
This is your punishment!
A lowly brat like you
does not even bow?
You wish to be punished again?
Just fall.
What?
Just fall, fall and perish.
Those were your words.
I saw everything.
Just fall.
In-Gyu? In-Gyu!
What the hell are you talking about?
Fortunately, Lord Chun-Jung is safe.
Should I let him know?
That you didn't try to get help?
Listen,
if you ever bully the weak again,
I will tell him everything!
Even all your darkest
thoughts hiding deep in you!
How dare you!
Loser...
I am here to see Choi Chun-Jung
at your residence.
Here to see my Master?
You crazy! Come here!
Ouch!
Let her in, please.
She is my guest.
You...
Why did you ask for such a wish?
Because you just can't see anything.
Pardon?
I was just curious,
since you're so different.
I am not any different.
I am just like
all the others around me.
Reading all these and writing out
copies you say this is average?
17 years old, first place in the state exam?
This isn't ordinary.
Young Lord,
you are definitely different.
No, I am not really
any different than others!
I even...
Yes, play the drums!
Excuse me?
Without my Father's knowledge,
I play the drums and sing…
This is the secret,
music is my true passion!
Perhaps this is destiny?
What?
This is not a secret for me, but...
I dance, too.
Huh?
Turn around.
I said turn around.
If you see that hair ribbon tied up
here, it's a sign that I'm coming.
You can see it from far away,
so you better come as well.
If I have time, I guess I can.
[iQIYI Ver] CSTV E01 'Wind and Cloud and Rain'
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Bong-Ryun!
Mother!
Let go of me!
Let, go! Mother!
Mother!
Byung-Woon Kim (Minister of Finance)
Is this the Shaman who cursed
our town governor and all our Lords?
Yes, sir.
These are the amulets for cursing.
A Shaman's curse...
Start interrogation.
You witch!
Why have you buried these amulets
right in front of our government office?
They are not for cursing, sir!
They are the good luck charms
I made
when I prayed and summoned
Lord Chae's ancestors.
We have a witness to
your conniving crimes!
Who is it?
He would be the one entrapping me!
Silence!
Beat the hell out of her!
Yes, sir!
Sir!
Sir! My Lord!
She wrote that amulet
for the Lord Chae's father
as my mother knew
he would pass away!
How is this a crime?
Who the hell is she?
Take her away!
Wait.
Sir?
So?
Your mother has such psychic powers
enough to predict someone's death?
Yes, my Lord.
Okay then. Predict correctly
and I will grant you your life.
Sir?
Put a knife to her throat.
Yes, sir!
Make your prediction, you Shaman.
Will I kill you or let you live?
Bong-Ryun...
No, never...
Do not utter a word!
You can't even tell me
your own death a second away.
What a useless Shaman.
Let me tell you your own future.
You are the one who perishes!
My mother's life
is not destined to end today.
However... your life I am afraid
will end around midnight today.
9 PM to 11 PM
You, you insolent bitch!
- Stop!
- Yes, yes sir.
So, you are the one with
the real gift, not your mother?
How interesting!
Let us see if I die tonight.
Until then...
I will keep you both alive.
Did you not say that I die tonight?
Midnight is upon us
and I am still breathing?
Oh, I am too scared to
keep on drinking...
When will I die?
If I let you live,
You must keep your promise of
releasing my mother!
You, insolent bitch!
Oh, no.
The last bell has just rung now.
Your mother will die
because of your bluff.
Bitch!
You can never reveal
your abilities to others!
Enemies! Get them!
Get them!
How dare you who are you!
Lord, are you alright?
As I promised, it is midnight, now.
How is this possible?
There was a death written all over
your face and the governor's face.
But after I have arrived,
it has disappeared from your face
meaning that you have avoided
death at my hands.
What a miraculous child!
Now please let my mother go!
I have discovered a real treasure!
Imprison this child.
We have much use of her!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
You must keep your word!
Let go of me!
Help, Bong-Ryun!
Bong-Ryun!
Bong-Ryun, My daughter!
Mother... Mother!
Mother...
Bong-Ryun!
Mother!
Princess?
This lowborn daughter of a Shaman
Jwa-Keun Kim (Prime minister)
is a princess, you say?
when I was younger,
I shared the bed with her in Gang-Hwa
Cheoljong (25th King of the Joseon Dynasty)
If so, she would have
brought her child to you already.
Byung-Woon Kim (Minister of Finance)
Why would she raise
a child on her own until now?
I did not know the young Lord
back then
Ban-Dal (Shaman)
had become a King.
How could I have imagined?
After losing my daughter to a master,
I returned back to my village
to seek help from her father.
That is when I found out you
had become King.
At the time,
I was just a meager poor noble,
but still my status prohibited me
from marrying a Shaman.
As she left the village
after giving birth to my child,
I never heard back from her again.
I am sorry
I did not seek you out
My King!
Please help me
get my daughter back!
Taking her back?
We can compensate you for giving
birth and raising the King's daughter.
Queen Hyoyu, Mrs. Jo
But now she belongs
to the Royal Family.
She cannot be the daughter of
a low birth like you anymore!
Pardon me?
I know you have risked
your life coming here but...
What could you possibly offer
your daughter as a mother?
As Kim family at Jangdong
will take great care of the princess,
put your mind at ease.
Please my King...
'Jangdong Kim-Moon' Family Residence
Move on, my Lord.
If you put that man
in a minister position,
Dangsanggwan
Under management of Ranking 3 officers and above
he will make a negative report to
the King to betray you.
I thought so myself...
Is this not enough?
Let me go, please.
My mother...
where is my mother?
Princess as your gift is incredible,
our Jangdong Kim family
will thrive from it
until your very last breath!
You bastard!
You made the promise!
Let go of me!
Mother... mother!
Mother!
5 Years later
Chun-Jung Choi
Kyung Choi (Ganghwa Governor)
In-Gyu Chae
Over there!
Chun-Jung!
Aren't you the minister of finance?
As a rabid dog ran towards us,
I assumed they were bandits
and ordered an attack.
However…
You almost got me.
We were tracking wild boar
surfacing near our town,
and I am afraid
we were too careless.
Anyway, what brings you here
to Gang-Hwa?
Nothing worth mentioning.
Just strolling with the ocean breeze.
Pardon me, Sir.
I am Choi Chun-Jung.
Ganghwa Gwanjin
Main Border Port of Ganghwa Island
Raise it higher!
Up until the top!
Why do your peasants walk the road
when the local governor is passing?
They deserve the spanking
for disrespect!
I ordered them not to my Lord.
What?
These people are trying
to make a living here.
It would be the big waste of time
if everyone had to stop and bow
for every highborn passing?
Choi Gyung, since you have
become a governor here 5 years ago,
this place has changed greatly.
It is all thanks to
the hard work of the people.
Ganghwa Gwana
Ganghwa Island city hall
Is this all?
Oh, no way my master.
We have another carriage
full of pressing matters.
Must I tend it all?
Aren't we used to your Father
working you to death by now?
I don't understand our Lord Governor!
He only listens to that ridiculous monk's
premonitions to keep you here,
a great young man who won
the first place in the state exam.
That enlightened monk happened to
foresee the date of my mother's death.
He is a great Shaman and my father's
best friend, so watch your mouth.
Yes, sir...
By the way, have you heard?
The minister of Finance
arrived with a princess today.
and they say she is gorgeous!
When men get a glimpse of her
they all fall head over heels!
Do you still yearn for Bong-Ryun?
It has already been 5 years since?
Haven't you searched everywhere
for her already?
She probably has forgotten
all about you
and is married happily to
somebody already by now...
If so, I will feel kind of bad...
I present Wha-Ryun princess.
Bong-Ryun Lee
It is an honor to meet
your presence, Princess.
I have heard much about you.
Your people look
all lively and eager!
Yes, my Lady.
Our people are very busy with
preparing for the cargo vessels.
Jounsun
Cargo vessels ferrying collected tax from states
Is that so?
Cargo vessels...
When is the fleet's departure?
In two days, my Lord.
Two days you say...
Not much time to carry out
this mission.
A mission?
The King has requested
your son and Princess's marriage.
Talking about her marriage in front of her
must make her too self-conscious...
Why don't we find
some other place to speak?
Have you looked into it?
Yes, Ma'am.
Your mother Ban-Dal...
is not here anymore.
Yes, I see...
It has been 5 years
since I left here...
Do you know where she went?
Nobody knows ma'am...
my apologies.
What is this?
Children working
at the Gwan-Jin ferry found this.
It is gun powder, my Lord
Gun powder? At the ferry?
I suspect smugglers are dealing here.
This is a piece of oil paper
wrapping the pouch,
but hard to tell the exact shape
because of the tear.
Have you moved
the gun powder safely?
Yes, Lord.
Our family's future depends on
your success of the job at Gang-Hwa.
Are you up for the task?
Yes, Father.
I will delay the fleet's departure
and as for Choi Gyung...
We must get rid of him
in the end?
This dream again...
ever since I came here…
Are you not the minister of finance!
You came back.
What the hell are you doing now?
You know you can lose your head
for intruding the cargo vessel?
Your martial arts is terrible
but you are more slippery
than an eel!
Why are doing this?
You do not know why?
Because you look too suspicious?
Happy now?
Could you possibly
still remember me?
You came back.
Bong-Ryun!
Wind and Cloud and Rain